[
    {
        "question": " 2年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.021136613160236
    },
    {
        "question": " 2558日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8455306819859354
    },
    {
        "question": " 374日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.952625736210056
    },
    {
        "question": " 3203日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.663884111196579
    },
    {
        "question": " 1101日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.978345787840614
    },
    {
        "question": " 87億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.996816467867503
    },
    {
        "question": " 2526時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.022209872090499
    },
    {
        "question": " 69.8時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.6219846800150632
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.97万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.02899050785109
    },
    {
        "question": " 2281兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.63752115428058
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.98億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.139329435601949
    },
    {
        "question": " 109分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.25871616266260444
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.84万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.363017571468582
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.65分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.99585607996239
    },
    {
        "question": " 7597万秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.3818150498537609
    },
    {
        "question": " 8689億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.00248046691613
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.28億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.166727999574368
    },
    {
        "question": " 609秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0065733261826404
    },
    {
        "question": " 156京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.695222178078427
    },
    {
        "question": " 19.4兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.35076537497878
    },
    {
        "question": " 34.2億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.978044655197003
    },
    {
        "question": " 2524万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6239155583441196
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.38億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.141423447843939
    },
    {
        "question": " 1674兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.724886982091044
    },
    {
        "question": " 168京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.288624701390631
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.74兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.3852350005743514
    },
    {
        "question": " 1281兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.329318247428419
    },
    {
        "question": " 1038兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.016236125855919
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.07兆usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.028629320765788
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.12万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 7.048594377084934
    },
    {
        "question": " 687京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3384313028015313
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.28京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.579024504076255
    },
    {
        "question": " 67.8垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.274992263794703
    },
    {
        "question": " 647兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.032618921309268
    },
    {
        "question": " 2105億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3232431960146647
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.8兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.072569891589283
    },
    {
        "question": " 5712億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.756779864617673
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.84万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.828241882555081
    },
    {
        "question": " 66.5年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.765146287914334
    },
    {
        "question": " 22.7億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.794179756496295
    },
    {
        "question": " 1413万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.530427262236795
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.45万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.320197692613972
    },
    {
        "question": " 771日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.823811398333326
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.7億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.252606070880703
    },
    {
        "question": " 418時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.241440749031928
    },
    {
        "question": " 143万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.933503343363465
    },
    {
        "question": " 4178時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.177298255590485
    },
    {
        "question": " 561時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.30498279048689
    },
    {
        "question": " 382万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8614810269757744
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.87億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.299448647878194
    },
    {
        "question": " 2483分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6168604066232006
    },
    {
        "question": " 36.8分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.3443430710017044
    },
    {
        "question": " 627億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.298222686428688
    },
    {
        "question": " 5556万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8082405645953754
    },
    {
        "question": " 27.3兆秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.880493981904483
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.2万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.845236529878341
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.08万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.610243216164782
    },
    {
        "question": " 67.4秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.8284109607758126
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.64京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.714824705926226
    },
    {
        "question": " 206億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.377965451504307
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.42億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8280040987905977
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.09兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.541361381156912
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.2兆msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.963853799334373
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.01msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 3.9548820886061242
    },
    {
        "question": " 73.7兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.3687132411789962
    },
    {
        "question": " 1241億usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.15725091953290193
    },
    {
        "question": " 2366京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.817767984003295
    },
    {
        "question": " 365兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.784586420750691
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.2兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.079745636987475
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.06億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.024466875314129
    },
    {
        "question": " 8097usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.9083481673783
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.87京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.18877281908033394
    },
    {
        "question": " 746京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.936307058290771
    },
    {
        "question": " 81.1垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.352667347997107
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.98兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.821891718316977
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.2京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.049297080118809
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.71兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.756518810530605
    },
    {
        "question": " 41.9万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 2.621790992671066
    },
    {
        "question": " 2886年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.0225417089580535
    },
    {
        "question": " 72.8億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.299886689041998
    },
    {
        "question": " 846万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.307376221676293
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.02万日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.540579684883403
    },
    {
        "question": " 42.9日は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.568959892087923
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.68億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.28358874669151
    },
    {
        "question": " 180億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.874718017353459
    },
    {
        "question": " 339時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.308527604177837
    },
    {
        "question": " 462時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.221096277681482
    },
    {
        "question": " 43.4億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.916900100875065
    },
    {
        "question": " 1260万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.9421329332101585
    },
    {
        "question": " 30.3億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.703303443231113
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.8万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.949635920639505
    },
    {
        "question": " 308億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.990287856830791
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.1億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.108674819315875
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.41兆秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.176569805612587
    },
    {
        "question": " 1218秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.307523212163646
    },
    {
        "question": " 4836秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.6845167155713785
    },
    {
        "question": " 505億msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.2042099538036568
    },
    {
        "question": " 9325万msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.033163092774919356
    },
    {
        "question": " 2477万msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8375955294104975
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.16億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.9343429854321954
    },
    {
        "question": " 75.4万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8776531387844817
    },
    {
        "question": " 107万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.0303974925877
    },
    {
        "question": " 5826msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.765393311192037
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.36垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.873465243538217
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.22垓usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.408974234918311
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.6兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.858503103240574
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.7兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.389002334381593
    },
    {
        "question": " 7648万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8835469643544
    },
    {
        "question": " 153億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.184218253879816
    },
    {
        "question": " 112万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.048251476271036
    },
    {
        "question": " 23.2垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.8658647274499085
    },
    {
        "question": " 5578京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.809993447110569
    },
    {
        "question": " 113兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4974190555152966
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.59垓nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.883801310292307
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.3京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.212231252294814
    },
    {
        "question": " 2597兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.414480153178046
    },
    {
        "question": " 53.2億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.726150301947173
    },
    {
        "question": " 2582万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.974254050990313
    },
    {
        "question": " 4172万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.058076571552452
    },
    {
        "question": " 1210日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.46316215479499
    },
    {
        "question": " 7日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.00319895640491
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.31万日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.570518671243336
    },
    {
        "question": " 20.1万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3609914506856358
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.41億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.544811836146936
    },
    {
        "question": " 1656万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.99711725843632
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.83万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.008218626775216
    },
    {
        "question": " 548時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.295109440391492
    },
    {
        "question": " 1092万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3177296747967826
    },
    {
        "question": " 618万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.632910327216381
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.6万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.0412080658457894
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.6兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.706218040440769
    },
    {
        "question": " 528万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7861909690782851
    },
    {
        "question": " 285億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.898579468274089
    },
    {
        "question": " 62.5億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.017658832444845
    },
    {
        "question": " 127万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.10243548109634
    },
    {
        "question": " 107秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.030057459693149
    },
    {
        "question": " 463兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.167193972727283
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.75京msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.952750956032038
    },
    {
        "question": " 4591億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.1056080238201424
    },
    {
        "question": " 312万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7159509919265958
    },
    {
        "question": " 274億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.438151968452157
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.57万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.87919065363635
    },
    {
        "question": " 4739msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.67568200961827
    },
    {
        "question": " 5960兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2764713387772284
    },
    {
        "question": " 2878億usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.522554281187162
    },
    {
        "question": " 156京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.63761891966482
    },
    {
        "question": " 5248億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.9418247738884373
    },
    {
        "question": " 578兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.76223893600583
    },
    {
        "question": " 153億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.184096437129607
    },
    {
        "question": " 103万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.01301976378874
    },
    {
        "question": " 367垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.06643038033457
    },
    {
        "question": " 1055京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.086910986271322
    },
    {
        "question": " 30.2兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9239255547755754
    },
    {
        "question": " 1172億nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.29059693211800686
    },
    {
        "question": " 8968億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.952681990260546
    },
    {
        "question": " 1353兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.131398660071604
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.61万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 1.8199090555505548
    },
    {
        "question": " 1107年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.986754645160634
    },
    {
        "question": " 488年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.409195204437761
    },
    {
        "question": " 3859万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.024150422909503
    },
    {
        "question": " 227日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.7356237627868074
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.61万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.822472514581872
    },
    {
        "question": " 28.3日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.388597929029559
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.68日は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.502070169769878
    },
    {
        "question": " 6786万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.889095117251772
    },
    {
        "question": " 1286万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.729039367469869
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.26万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.185470197126328
    },
    {
        "question": " 6503万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.0924352614769504
    },
    {
        "question": " 20.5億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.1530179945662455
    },
    {
        "question": " 11億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.2644509804026764
    },
    {
        "question": " 28万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.224771912176472
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.4分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.964801570876931
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.19億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8408814969229861
    },
    {
        "question": " 795兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.963652803379606
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.4億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.535762954313681
    },
    {
        "question": " 98.1億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.213489561393242
    },
    {
        "question": " 853億msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.43212386780175804
    },
    {
        "question": " 47.2兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.737262318240984
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.51京msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.843064838741459
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.74兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.050737565111042
    },
    {
        "question": " 2287msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.3591963329459147
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.6msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 7.244834147284237
    },
    {
        "question": " 38.9兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.0915065414380456
    },
    {
        "question": " 8696兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.0028190434239095
    },
    {
        "question": " 273兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.880307515975363
    },
    {
        "question": " 122億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3091534455790894
    },
    {
        "question": " 137万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.13551220452112878
    },
    {
        "question": " 2108usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 0.32382637627465294
    },
    {
        "question": " 20.4垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.811308686602125
    },
    {
        "question": " 1643京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.2792168237668236
    },
    {
        "question": " 7562京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.32233716421802
    },
    {
        "question": " 3910兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.81405647730406
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.7兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.4318501656281897
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.86億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 2.2706770462070858
    },
    {
        "question": " 1644万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.215788117058486
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.5年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.912289976105345
    },
    {
        "question": " 1336万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.563445506193037
    },
    {
        "question": " 22日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.500599452535845
    },
    {
        "question": " 101日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.938711541132179
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.16万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0193627783303627
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.8万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.8457498283010283
    },
    {
        "question": " 393万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.372641929612541
    },
    {
        "question": " 180時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.810962328584894
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.17兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.9931840732335555
    },
    {
        "question": " 969億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.828032456292564
    },
    {
        "question": " 329万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.738574582254845
    },
    {
        "question": " 2260分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.1321928206877985
    },
    {
        "question": " 3480分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.319739730734998
    },
    {
        "question": " 144億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.659661304817157
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.59兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.725732352730362
    },
    {
        "question": " 7684秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.32930551967902844
    },
    {
        "question": " 4832億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.905958904888701
    },
    {
        "question": " 300秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.476730217932756
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.29秒は何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.632331102995602
    },
    {
        "question": " 1851億msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7686506359690581
    },
    {
        "question": " 19.7億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3590173862129862
    },
    {
        "question": " 33.9億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9738381475175766
    },
    {
        "question": " 37.4億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.794276165481998
    },
    {
        "question": " 32.5億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.512100519006971
    },
    {
        "question": " 85.9京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.435021567075269
    },
    {
        "question": " 218兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.400994737241345
    },
    {
        "question": " 184兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.70962390305687
    },
    {
        "question": " 4兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.824082923298596
    },
    {
        "question": " 1194兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.076875392439783
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.94万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.595815303358391
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.91usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 3.7715585550682507
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.5垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.523365291458614
    },
    {
        "question": " 44.3京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.7095092536099106
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.45京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.092070341154996
    },
    {
        "question": " 5625億nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9719585517039697
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.48京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.170494501996049
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.41兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.148967858017898
    },
    {
        "question": " 364億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.561252115967704
    },
    {
        "question": " 36万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.118589363826072
    },
    {
        "question": " 2389年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.320695664138449
    },
    {
        "question": " 193年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.006916182555075
    },
    {
        "question": " 235万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.808030034817671
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.8万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.451910911336092
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.54日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.123677196213999
    },
    {
        "question": " 42.8万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6884823875041266
    },
    {
        "question": " 112時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6672105561023589
    },
    {
        "question": " 284万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.232096523841042
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.8時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.320055350809019
    },
    {
        "question": " 1288億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.389405650440891
    },
    {
        "question": " 69億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.680325269321367
    },
    {
        "question": " 1332分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3462198592022379
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.4万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.965455037163638
    },
    {
        "question": " 1717分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.012820783593659
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.2億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.464930732433951
    },
    {
        "question": " 161兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.271059003932146
    },
    {
        "question": " 121万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5278426363944853
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.14億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.551911595297813
    },
    {
        "question": " 895万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.951721253367122
    },
    {
        "question": " 943億msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.4754873350029387
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.1億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.10462101411389146
    },
    {
        "question": " 192億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.7272563360459277
    },
    {
        "question": " 156億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.414074245224182
    },
    {
        "question": " 2473万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.393293703358152
    },
    {
        "question": " 36msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.556003260052713
    },
    {
        "question": " 60.1msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 7.779102954025722
    },
    {
        "question": " 877兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4443207543939995
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.52垓usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.245172904315268
    },
    {
        "question": " 20.3京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.751790601936865
    },
    {
        "question": " 2356億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.5941127969369004
    },
    {
        "question": " 491億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.691369682281704
    },
    {
        "question": " 934万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.9702892151319027
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.01万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 7.954536089142875
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.96垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.098769598353655
    },
    {
        "question": " 811京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.972369248223899
    },
    {
        "question": " 478兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.123478138291354
    },
    {
        "question": " 63.5兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.024956940121876
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.02京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.007909454138468
    },
    {
        "question": " 5812万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.7643147342065124
    },
    {
        "question": " 170億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.23018510647092
    },
    {
        "question": " 2040年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.872039605194274
    },
    {
        "question": " 94.2万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.916700671686728
    },
    {
        "question": " 279年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.16642907544484
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.17兆日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.506912122002904
    },
    {
        "question": " 107日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.187151624208877
    },
    {
        "question": " 3274億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.5725271045520515
    },
    {
        "question": " 90.2万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.574952931710493
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.28時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.279266787539115
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.11時間は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.880891971791097
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.09兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.316268855826906
    },
    {
        "question": " 47.6億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.519664714567661
    },
    {
        "question": " 368万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.787418072909623
    },
    {
        "question": " 3114分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.271463710154967
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.4分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.936704699014598
    },
    {
        "question": " 155億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6907458396427844
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.08億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.5516018336424446
    },
    {
        "question": " 39.2億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.036595821413161
    },
    {
        "question": " 464億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.888705393262187
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.51万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.179091205276013
    },
    {
        "question": " 4951兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.195921073031063
    },
    {
        "question": " 31.5億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5614967910232824
    },
    {
        "question": " 1233億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.534602060358396
    },
    {
        "question": " 66.1億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.042373122757265
    },
    {
        "question": " 2579msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.41144435442801
    },
    {
        "question": " 461msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 5.6632419331259864
    },
    {
        "question": " 234京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.870201724660762
    },
    {
        "question": " 104京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.082046852130799
    },
    {
        "question": " 63京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.243090618580768
    },
    {
        "question": " 1134兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.2766418060900655
    },
    {
        "question": " 35.3兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.547467056668492
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.93億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.466854547483717
    },
    {
        "question": " 372usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 5.570970760096179
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.38垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.6413886831113773
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.5垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.123207044336732
    },
    {
        "question": " 5109京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.152023487869133
    },
    {
        "question": " 1740京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.46237927875677
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.18兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.714697760851223
    },
    {
        "question": " 352万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 0.546145051970538
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.23万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 1.0897939221804764
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.73年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.237319067051975
    },
    {
        "question": " 28.9年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.180993660037926
    },
    {
        "question": " 71.2年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.35140418524137
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.73億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.874216377810066
    },
    {
        "question": " 117万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.4476034649026825
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.37万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.533387912829948
    },
    {
        "question": " 18.8億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.3311537824529385
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.42億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.35343262793976
    },
    {
        "question": " 21万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.1008364513349775
    },
    {
        "question": " 8662時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.493938534421374
    },
    {
        "question": " 377時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.13210822839135
    },
    {
        "question": " 2887兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.73975444724069
    },
    {
        "question": " 69.5万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.683545227171881
    },
    {
        "question": " 332億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.742351238538378
    },
    {
        "question": " 422万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.403672862261253
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.53万分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.434690273159347
    },
    {
        "question": " 364億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.0624260791431235
    },
    {
        "question": " 221億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.408025979130623
    },
    {
        "question": " 390万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.0343792020663205
    },
    {
        "question": " 3746秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7953740345225888
    },
    {
        "question": " 320万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.505596853484871
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.7秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.069994761077427
    },
    {
        "question": " 721京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.35938026784766
    },
    {
        "question": " 3506兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.608275458583767
    },
    {
        "question": " 783兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.337382924175865
    },
    {
        "question": " 184兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.487797336838943
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.85万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4547987702940512
    },
    {
        "question": " 18.3msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 7.262273729756553
    },
    {
        "question": " 24.2京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.8850516187553206
    },
    {
        "question": " 4746兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.739826306408155
    },
    {
        "question": " 64.9兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.255981636137274
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.22京usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.729538725253093
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.18兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.338198293898595
    },
    {
        "question": " 2953万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.470261864433404
    },
    {
        "question": " 29.9万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 8.475524967101599
    },
    {
        "question": " 1496垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.676099827375401
    },
    {
        "question": " 1005垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.065816025350594
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.3垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.681093390219862
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.09京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.834078213976857
    },
    {
        "question": " 110兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.041123944491455
    },
    {
        "question": " 73.4兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.865487575905993
    },
    {
        "question": " 7999nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 0.9030091570917465
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.06年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.3450087818608196
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.76年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.772396173495595
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.49億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.61034702703714
    },
    {
        "question": " 315日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.656354026480589
    },
    {
        "question": " 8896日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.885681279782498
    },
    {
        "question": " 3013万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.536523986502935
    },
    {
        "question": " 738万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.487786208479775
    },
    {
        "question": " 185時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.044406612345418
    },
    {
        "question": " 244億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.66709741869299
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.07万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.15781993275884
    },
    {
        "question": " 798万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.123775201964693
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.72万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.014458334368367
    },
    {
        "question": " 206兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.814619044912996
    },
    {
        "question": " 44.2万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7092777642810832
    },
    {
        "question": " 93.7億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.415481955641281
    },
    {
        "question": " 5476万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.960281211565869
    },
    {
        "question": " 24.8万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.394694163453568
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.1秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.959276818221397
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.25兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4177620657714662
    },
    {
        "question": " 181億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3201426026049896
    },
    {
        "question": " 1911兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.725063152055634
    },
    {
        "question": " 219億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.563071455158476
    },
    {
        "question": " 30.3万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.482011889335155
    },
    {
        "question": " 123msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 5.088793617032589
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.71垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.488233533759692
    },
    {
        "question": " 1212兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.147138391107344
    },
    {
        "question": " 51億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.1513848185857214
    },
    {
        "question": " 69.1億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.0614533980474317
    },
    {
        "question": " 950万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9776132089681022
    },
    {
        "question": " 28.3万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 2.451388054817243
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.55usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 3.815962936998192
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.15垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.5619387969653973
    },
    {
        "question": " 1386垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.205384958451575
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.3京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.495351953627994
    },
    {
        "question": " 343兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.7568102516649415
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.4億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.12865721857098555
    },
    {
        "question": " 201万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 0.3030639175684213
    },
    {
        "question": " 2252nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 0.3525016361499722
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.37万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.089314382059837
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.61万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.359059012178566
    },
    {
        "question": " 51.1億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.146006807273291
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.06億日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.989039755240627
    },
    {
        "question": " 26.3日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.578861082876198
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.3兆時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.171621494976193
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.93億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.214042301838376
    },
    {
        "question": " 371時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.125286860580036
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.1時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.706630629108094
    },
    {
        "question": " 686兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.115776044390497
    },
    {
        "question": " 227億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.198080620892691
    },
    {
        "question": " 1415億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.372603288360672
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.8分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.0289765224941743
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.51分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.178686776774892
    },
    {
        "question": " 5563兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.246504809182293
    },
    {
        "question": " 894万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.014599441167866
    },
    {
        "question": " 35.4兆秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.992257306054743
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.01億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.699708141149139
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.8兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.333481138028375
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.15億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.3964457564758084
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.51兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.097450320600158
    },
    {
        "question": " 70.8億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.071975894425415
    },
    {
        "question": " 70.5万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8483889615103806
    },
    {
        "question": " 137msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 8.137940436728318
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.57垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.380304411599256
    },
    {
        "question": " 3029億usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5447626219126356
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.75京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.332859689238948
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.28兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.58030550135034
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.56億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.980684311153804
    },
    {
        "question": " 61.9億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.79198850038456
    },
    {
        "question": " 776usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 5.889663336564697
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.1垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.650589021954314
    },
    {
        "question": " 73京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.926810855299161
    },
    {
        "question": " 8094京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.351852867956526
    },
    {
        "question": " 9746億nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2106850318474338
    },
    {
        "question": " 116億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.062634745421338
    },
    {
        "question": " 822万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 0.9149162434083336
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.15万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 1.0611245591663987
    },
    {
        "question": " 53.2万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.288357171006993
    },
    {
        "question": " 239年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.09923862127271
    },
    {
        "question": " 220年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.840635341282148
    },
    {
        "question": " 4450億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.086017609056704
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.8日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8274271407357157
    },
    {
        "question": " 21.2万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.384342714450264
    },
    {
        "question": " 1859時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8890110361310541
    },
    {
        "question": " 2372時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.153284540987063
    },
    {
        "question": " 43時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.190156115668964
    },
    {
        "question": " 201億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.581537746903161
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.16万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1770190763127286
    },
    {
        "question": " 43.7億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.862404851976185
    },
    {
        "question": " 286分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.233969839651539
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.4兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.627093856813772
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.52兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.46472195050158
    },
    {
        "question": " 615万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.23254651144415
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.82億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.987130406017595
    },
    {
        "question": " 193万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.285049455175447
    },
    {
        "question": " 20.4秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.309138794737723
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.97京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.974295157884372
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.86億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.33319348047936903
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.7兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.546935918773108
    },
    {
        "question": " 337億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.749060872596422
    },
    {
        "question": " 77.2万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8877334674292756
    },
    {
        "question": " 339万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.530576316184527
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.73msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.988050943466697
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.88京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.961155495313834
    },
    {
        "question": " 5682億usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8179657094465909
    },
    {
        "question": " 60.3億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.22415342631763147
    },
    {
        "question": " 147億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3877816394616644
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.8億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.199452791755081
    },
    {
        "question": " 1231億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.09040313662188
    },
    {
        "question": " 826万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.916903572475281
    },
    {
        "question": " 64.4京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.309923678172954
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.6京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.267494827476156
    },
    {
        "question": " 91.3京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.40412063953897
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.82垓nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.672021598367484
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.74京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.240577588348616
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.92億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 2.840063585674205
    },
    {
        "question": " 219万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 3.3401264221636726
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.86年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.1492206792619584
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.02万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.952761085427571
    },
    {
        "question": " 1568億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.633160687212682
    },
    {
        "question": " 28.6万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.8369786108669075
    },
    {
        "question": " 2773日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.601237774308359
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.4億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.246245524751422
    },
    {
        "question": " 164万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.833890264315405
    },
    {
        "question": " 1796万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.032460803160356
    },
    {
        "question": " 2960億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.750577789984135
    },
    {
        "question": " 5720分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5990107720653692
    },
    {
        "question": " 19.5億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.5112942405739345
    },
    {
        "question": " 585万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.545326724971053
    },
    {
        "question": " 3764億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.076825460722847
    },
    {
        "question": " 942億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.0373239249776836
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.62兆秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.37925615641066
    },
    {
        "question": " 983億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.21429986558222
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.13秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.0534375629375408
    },
    {
        "question": " 22.9秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.360697755275489
    },
    {
        "question": " 38.7京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.089146027407213
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.76兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.893508927758542
    },
    {
        "question": " 1364兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.578494603378171
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.85億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.4893814116105935
    },
    {
        "question": " 44.2億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.6453202039580725
    },
    {
        "question": " 4660msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.668414305667223
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.21msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.506792193874976
    },
    {
        "question": " 2228垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.849126368719142
    },
    {
        "question": " 157京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.258574442191753
    },
    {
        "question": " 86.4兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.380219521937314
    },
    {
        "question": " 101兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.226309401777039
    },
    {
        "question": " 4804億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.681613082080705
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.8億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.2563921466794366
    },
    {
        "question": " 173usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 5.2373648084756566
    },
    {
        "question": " 155京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6923506594877014
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.12垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.557159995168452
    },
    {
        "question": " 374京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.016931242345562
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.24兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8492163278609142
    },
    {
        "question": " 91.2京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.95998533872602
    },
    {
        "question": " 1740億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.240664534173321
    },
    {
        "question": " 578万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 3.761738470944894
    },
    {
        "question": " 109年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.599871835206822
    },
    {
        "question": " 20.6年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.257148057224913
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.05年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.742933977336968
    },
    {
        "question": " 36.6年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.062846745138874
    },
    {
        "question": " 2319日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8030119694822235
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.17億日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.881428224735112
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.69万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.144610486843177
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.8日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.13466248336943
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.82万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.31653691225249525
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.24万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.4152291799255172
    },
    {
        "question": " 175時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.022414694944024
    },
    {
        "question": " 19.2万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.838735660844604
    },
    {
        "question": " 6284万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.0775997441792637
    },
    {
        "question": " 1027万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.853242934436363
    },
    {
        "question": " 994万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.2191298078998205
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.43万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.934854208270879
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.98万分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.2522839747032
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.99京秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.403842886688468
    },
    {
        "question": " 6910億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.902995244058843
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.6億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.57809910947409
    },
    {
        "question": " 27.5億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.661111968007795
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.6万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.414910990473213
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.01垓msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.503769144523432
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.1兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.295440808217676
    },
    {
        "question": " 148兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.6142060654822
    },
    {
        "question": " 143億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.378699182656794
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.68億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.670287864263192
    },
    {
        "question": " 1977msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.296105632302713
    },
    {
        "question": " 229垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.86015670006464
    },
    {
        "question": " 276兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.5037728806034174
    },
    {
        "question": " 1220億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5299784482118683
    },
    {
        "question": " 58.8京usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.990957951649134
    },
    {
        "question": " 2353兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.371678826609651
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.49万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.1732735617108248
    },
    {
        "question": " 116usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 5.063256494011047
    },
    {
        "question": " 281京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9495425527965593
    },
    {
        "question": " 1254兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1617847690762784
    },
    {
        "question": " 275京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.882977881942057
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.76京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.211459285309061
    },
    {
        "question": " 37.2兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.570319919242777
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.93兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.2857154453538975
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.08億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 5.4886105717756895
    },
    {
        "question": " 23.7万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.936668047817664
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.7年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.137954231296062
    },
    {
        "question": " 472年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.394444480937736
    },
    {
        "question": " 1860万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.707190293273245
    },
    {
        "question": " 705日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.228159265101241
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.31万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.5227818996330456
    },
    {
        "question": " 65.3日は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.751333297342699
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.71億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.49091320056233
    },
    {
        "question": " 9287万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.587694323942577
    },
    {
        "question": " 933万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.748041467836272
    },
    {
        "question": " 5666時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.30954898510717
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.74時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.993809621339675
    },
    {
        "question": " 271万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7122187044821016
    },
    {
        "question": " 43.7億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.4821268701055335
    },
    {
        "question": " 8630万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.1578388408058835
    },
    {
        "question": " 246分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.169230938334478
    },
    {
        "question": " 144分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.935324835767439
    },
    {
        "question": " 5280億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.223846665578947
    },
    {
        "question": " 171億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.295556058255755
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.38兆秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.582514781658183
    },
    {
        "question": " 141万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.369776177819757
    },
    {
        "question": " 68.4秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.83482311351954
    },
    {
        "question": " 40京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.103714108797432
    },
    {
        "question": " 1758兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.308412220885819
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.35京msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.815182793339574
    },
    {
        "question": " 125兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.319900459264144
    },
    {
        "question": " 130億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.114472146794629
    },
    {
        "question": " 89.5msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 7.952060682840994
    },
    {
        "question": " 308京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.989888753133707
    },
    {
        "question": " 99.1京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.059450586460883
    },
    {
        "question": " 825億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3599611602361972
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.93兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.506879691420298
    },
    {
        "question": " 3553万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.550536592111349
    },
    {
        "question": " 35.8万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 2.553750540760068
    },
    {
        "question": " 23.4京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8702702652055305
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.67垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.948327584670896
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.92垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.9088934702882625
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.65兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8895021941341517
    },
    {
        "question": " 22.7兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.356368265826044
    },
    {
        "question": " 74.1億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.869785142385971
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.15億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 5.062527291496744
    },
    {
        "question": " 6682年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.3872312172884165
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.24年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.8152025135108705
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.75年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.175865854633583
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.3万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.528347848835588
    },
    {
        "question": " 314万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.876693691356178
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.66日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.3784549592397974
    },
    {
        "question": " 1054日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.959536518262492
    },
    {
        "question": " 1967万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.3512760057735247
    },
    {
        "question": " 27.9億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.06519799000346
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.5万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.747685798268659
    },
    {
        "question": " 2598時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.970877467419081
    },
    {
        "question": " 161億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.487337385573125
    },
    {
        "question": " 360万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.398526590319956
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.7万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.452165512343134
    },
    {
        "question": " 4134分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.39447704160051
    },
    {
        "question": " 3183分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.280920513945105
    },
    {
        "question": " 957兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.482178417669248
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.41兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.212788614805762
    },
    {
        "question": " 207億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.759927233829317
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.62万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.780929773640489
    },
    {
        "question": " 601万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.778970163241794
    },
    {
        "question": " 5332京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.228121371667228
    },
    {
        "question": " 621億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8568236610246
    },
    {
        "question": " 2046兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.754698101659725
    },
    {
        "question": " 264万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6437023660098138
    },
    {
        "question": " 1992億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.299288697505837
    },
    {
        "question": " 18.2msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.259870108415588
    },
    {
        "question": " 493msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 8.692719695225948
    },
    {
        "question": " 82.1兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.4155172830145537
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.22京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.150166869249372
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.72兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.2014301917641386
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.69兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.8933372673213675
    },
    {
        "question": " 1646万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2163279129361926
    },
    {
        "question": " 19.9万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 2.299004253656748
    },
    {
        "question": " 143usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 5.15676061762545
    },
    {
        "question": " 2303垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.86357790941308
    },
    {
        "question": " 2221垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.410075295624239
    },
    {
        "question": " 302兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9235923637000596
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.84垓nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.48656069463698
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.9億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.07599354655250967
    },
    {
        "question": " 3036億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.482367551517656
    },
    {
        "question": " 1145nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 0.05868027359095418
    },
    {
        "question": " 9998年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.562233204722373
    },
    {
        "question": " 129年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.610062569707102
    },
    {
        "question": " 14万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5834803636194916
    },
    {
        "question": " 134万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.5075692156566305
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.31日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.077778350512825
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.91万日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.707926122059202
    },
    {
        "question": " 219万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.398394948319109
    },
    {
        "question": " 963時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6035180878178668
    },
    {
        "question": " 48.7万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.465670780430108
    },
    {
        "question": " 1588時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.757021353113434
    },
    {
        "question": " 235兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.650870362764273
    },
    {
        "question": " 1178万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.912928687669165
    },
    {
        "question": " 1414億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.372329372905924
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.45分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3165056236430304
    },
    {
        "question": " 25.7分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.188736289867393
    },
    {
        "question": " 882兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.446744662918431
    },
    {
        "question": " 136万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1960869642282401
    },
    {
        "question": " 6693万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.269332060893634
    },
    {
        "question": " 60.9秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.006521500662127755
    },
    {
        "question": " 38.3秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.583714858447144
    },
    {
        "question": " 583億msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.2667690478163709
    },
    {
        "question": " 312億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5582387009708096
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.5億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.842411637247242
    },
    {
        "question": " 8009億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.12541237753137
    },
    {
        "question": " 11億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.0408681004389475
    },
    {
        "question": " 2410msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.381934352384882
    },
    {
        "question": " 831垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.420718418751617
    },
    {
        "question": " 4762京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.741245247554566
    },
    {
        "question": " 424兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.070983716368836
    },
    {
        "question": " 115兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.280939758837629
    },
    {
        "question": " 186億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.269265496432615
    },
    {
        "question": " 25.5億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.407022232374167
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.62e+05垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.250913481186597
    },
    {
        "question": " 2780兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5074693631661729
    },
    {
        "question": " 45.7兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1034082013577384
    },
    {
        "question": " 65.4兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.0377065077802614
    },
    {
        "question": " 373京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.571282300967601
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.3兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.013026022227285
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.69万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 1.5674244624174027
    },
    {
        "question": " 1105年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.605609431561267
    },
    {
        "question": " 1009万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.441781783848869
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.56日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9314723071337037
    },
    {
        "question": " 29日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.620970542213031
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.7日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.0403718636695425
    },
    {
        "question": " 43億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.690843997415621
    },
    {
        "question": " 104万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.637233828721371
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.74時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.994691679733731
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.1億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.986537385277217
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.48兆分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.01309627577446
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.44万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6094617385761265
    },
    {
        "question": " 3789万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.356706920947666
    },
    {
        "question": " 8289億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.419694468393245
    },
    {
        "question": " 321万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5704652530126562
    },
    {
        "question": " 4176秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.06443350241256418
    },
    {
        "question": " 87.5万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.163818749604792
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.12万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.048768858895944
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.2京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.508780238413859
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.35億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7918889655534356
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.62億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.193630685840444
    },
    {
        "question": " 485兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.907805864307093
    },
    {
        "question": " 79.3万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.89900074028675
    },
    {
        "question": " 69.5msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.842030623446653
    },
    {
        "question": " 773京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.389225518386992
    },
    {
        "question": " 18京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.319861777693079
    },
    {
        "question": " 38京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.023860465660098
    },
    {
        "question": " 2305億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.584553711844184
    },
    {
        "question": " 1362万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.134291328632191
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.97万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.6964794524910742
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.218e+04垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.465851385634725
    },
    {
        "question": " 976兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0527755356924873
    },
    {
        "question": " 2759京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.884509363440371
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.21兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3044850603294411
    },
    {
        "question": " 303億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.482138747438887
    },
    {
        "question": " 64.5兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.809533508956495
    },
    {
        "question": " 4052nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 0.6076633913141682
    },
    {
        "question": " 9633年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.926285395071092
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.19年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.572804270160591
    },
    {
        "question": " 4548万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.095556689542844
    },
    {
        "question": " 4269日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.010501232823601
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.73万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.594872893668356
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.68日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.607079402420191
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.3日は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.093268833480362
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.92億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.749130848867459
    },
    {
        "question": " 460時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2830071036248503
    },
    {
        "question": " 1301時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.89250791316925
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.97万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.25248153087942
    },
    {
        "question": " 66.9万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.10495880428988635
    },
    {
        "question": " 690億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.680613800239547
    },
    {
        "question": " 6000万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.0000305551417075
    },
    {
        "question": " 73.7分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.645469528722076
    },
    {
        "question": " 2428億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.8864451133566535
    },
    {
        "question": " 130億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.178860783208886
    },
    {
        "question": " 531万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.168459004735263
    },
    {
        "question": " 537秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9521825111189974
    },
    {
        "question": " 101秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.004642878338242
    },
    {
        "question": " 66.6秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.823355253728507
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.89秒は何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.897125540046158
    },
    {
        "question": " 1024京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.511634393288608
    },
    {
        "question": " 184億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3286351405817127
    },
    {
        "question": " 2110兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.768040462963127
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.2万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.23029620402478246
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.4億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.144929133345759
    },
    {
        "question": " 302万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.479471176641818
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.2京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.6223057126988345
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.01京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.366580698192416
    },
    {
        "question": " 61.3京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.231272279717196
    },
    {
        "question": " 81.7億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1342119012612804
    },
    {
        "question": " 162万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.20979854095906303
    },
    {
        "question": " 1231usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 0.09038419873359849
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.61usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 3.7488261475167795
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.7京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6054003550940501
    },
    {
        "question": " 209垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.383750934989596
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.2垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.492356697669198
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.46京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.386699158380555
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.4兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.1459667007485512
    },
    {
        "question": " 337億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.527454764800948
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.04億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 5.847402005735986
    },
    {
        "question": " 9435年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.695396382480967
    },
    {
        "question": " 1399日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5834559630828684
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.6億日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.93674763894323
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.28兆時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.689433503015406
    },
    {
        "question": " 25.3億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.023753388683165
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.37万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.9153256041986495
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.74万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.129748276458022
    },
    {
        "question": " 4309万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9136855484979498
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.9兆分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.87892927908496
    },
    {
        "question": " 5403万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.954460801561421
    },
    {
        "question": " 21.7万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.114147224409008
    },
    {
        "question": " 9201分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.741974481075713
    },
    {
        "question": " 18.2京秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.760362309087991
    },
    {
        "question": " 297億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.536247263585049
    },
    {
        "question": " 1億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.444488574376239
    },
    {
        "question": " 6021万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.001499860189837
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.9秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.076506318613183
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.5兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1540003673550254
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.9京msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.139116970715488
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.3億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8061768857319793
    },
    {
        "question": " 124兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.31693420658316
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.42億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.734272387217526
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.13万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.328599597841446
    },
    {
        "question": " 1561兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6947244576776277
    },
    {
        "question": " 9406京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.036885355050659
    },
    {
        "question": " 118億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5150989775731141
    },
    {
        "question": " 5145兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.933201996891124
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.77兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.760884571869318
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.72兆usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.887716404722864
    },
    {
        "question": " 332万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.521648265709693
    },
    {
        "question": " 90.5垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.457973561369183
    },
    {
        "question": " 7359京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.9303408771321084
    },
    {
        "question": " 87垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.383140012409623
    },
    {
        "question": " 6001京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.000107926583906
    },
    {
        "question": " 126億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.099003972564374
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.33億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 2.367961524484495
    },
    {
        "question": " 89.5億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.951842446555723
    },
    {
        "question": " 32.2年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.0701343165344985
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.55万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.348971958628027
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.57兆日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.634537186437084
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.94日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.849201526472789
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.36億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.430053113110787
    },
    {
        "question": " 45.4時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.2767786041144271
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.73万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.605904599026932
    },
    {
        "question": " 157時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.7523623703808004
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.21兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.90317176586778
    },
    {
        "question": " 2831億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.293556618253831
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.65億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.645312870745705
    },
    {
        "question": " 9544万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.757858456538935
    },
    {
        "question": " 158分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.97718551565487
    },
    {
        "question": " 8466億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.428895972960887
    },
    {
        "question": " 520兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.779684389958868
    },
    {
        "question": " 38.2万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.0253636131819164
    },
    {
        "question": " 409秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8334534982727526
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.36秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.133384085021568
    },
    {
        "question": " 193秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.285391827704757
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.47兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6676090153873813
    },
    {
        "question": " 511億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7715567651965864
    },
    {
        "question": " 911兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.403331833363954
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.01兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.700110166182101
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.7万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.0288407835543296
    },
    {
        "question": " 692msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 8.840236507026603
    },
    {
        "question": " 31.6兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.0005458215386888732
    },
    {
        "question": " 271兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.496372427791573
    },
    {
        "question": " 2351兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.814874740157362
    },
    {
        "question": " 18兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.476125171383462
    },
    {
        "question": " 2132兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.328843475101912
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.44万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.1588898030913553
    },
    {
        "question": " 444京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.149032279472002
    },
    {
        "question": " 778垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.954261431217173
    },
    {
        "question": " 187京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.714870155638118
    },
    {
        "question": " 2987億nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6971457752225518
    },
    {
        "question": " 141億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.148293505218575
    },
    {
        "question": " 83.1億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.91938923286944
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.33兆nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.636197104620793
    },
    {
        "question": " 219万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.902799892973405
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.7万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.0055836229290147
    },
    {
        "question": " 32.9日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.675847920764059
    },
    {
        "question": " 1260万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.157704172968595
    },
    {
        "question": " 684万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.455152904653512
    },
    {
        "question": " 1678万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.00289616222944
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.9万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.757991473355416
    },
    {
        "question": " 1566億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.474177706033945
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.57億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.036426418532339
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.56万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4137865068057662
    },
    {
        "question": " 2303万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.140479644525016
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.5分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.968583128382564
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.26億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0144338413476817
    },
    {
        "question": " 843万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9893529085520134
    },
    {
        "question": " 28.7万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9011408763189541
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.53万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.406847801987735
    },
    {
        "question": " 556秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.745014518918556
    },
    {
        "question": " 171京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.733271017588679
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.69兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.292103362850723
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.04億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.459024549734469
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.1万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.22609997736983134
    },
    {
        "question": " 1753億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.243696643813658
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.5万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.131768080229612
    },
    {
        "question": " 54.4垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.236496875269356
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.6垓usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.61994629685839
    },
    {
        "question": " 871京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.383565988826145
    },
    {
        "question": " 171兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.455792546986231
    },
    {
        "question": " 1847兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.266485302096712
    },
    {
        "question": " 19.4万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 2.288511443300123
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.93usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 3.284915311041532
    },
    {
        "question": " 199京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7995523064230123
    },
    {
        "question": " 4455垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.712357107401713
    },
    {
        "question": " 6154兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.232865690926391
    },
    {
        "question": " 37.2京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.792574581876082
    },
    {
        "question": " 368兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.566345751648506
    },
    {
        "question": " 23.5兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.371048090489768
    },
    {
        "question": " 6762nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 0.8300842535054065
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.3万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.614015171929353
    },
    {
        "question": " 110万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.985839879972312
    },
    {
        "question": " 183年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.760759498780047
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.1億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.616628767598795
    },
    {
        "question": " 201万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.683323738168875
    },
    {
        "question": " 468日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.828767479275216
    },
    {
        "question": " 496日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.631845832926861
    },
    {
        "question": " 4397万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.700653869501381
    },
    {
        "question": " 25.7時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.030390586070891956
    },
    {
        "question": " 44.1万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.422519833993089
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.37時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.693831187585851
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.4兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.371296824689204
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.99万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4420972187759662
    },
    {
        "question": " 31.1億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.713961705766041
    },
    {
        "question": " 2288分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.137697804921185
    },
    {
        "question": " 722分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.636804149764877
    },
    {
        "question": " 23.6京秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.87330099961125
    },
    {
        "question": " 128億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.171534409153304
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.31億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.562502633906948
    },
    {
        "question": " 207億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.537484154251555
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.76万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.83006071835342
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.84秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.264150240460059
    },
    {
        "question": " 446億msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.15096917642069219
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.22兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.857589311053322
    },
    {
        "question": " 149億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.61649890738727
    },
    {
        "question": " 164億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.437346402853432
    },
    {
        "question": " 5091msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7067996174926627
    },
    {
        "question": " 66.8万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.825017160437827
    },
    {
        "question": " 387兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0893487978119787
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.15垓usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.12487664624417
    },
    {
        "question": " 972億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4312449058724752
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.6兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.38547574652946
    },
    {
        "question": " 4697億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.671802473071934
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.54兆usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.404652424905152
    },
    {
        "question": " 66.2usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 4.820937977727993
    },
    {
        "question": " 204京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8117406107475964
    },
    {
        "question": " 5705京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.8197487228644675
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.64垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.86604969797951
    },
    {
        "question": " 4469億nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8720354022942889
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.04兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.702357458646853
    },
    {
        "question": " 249万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 0.3963459013776649
    },
    {
        "question": " 3391nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 0.5302681985518365
    },
    {
        "question": " 2018年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.867230058740854
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.73年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.327020447953306
    },
    {
        "question": " 38億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.017363696765031
    },
    {
        "question": " 9940万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.377601312417848
    },
    {
        "question": " 40日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.5385481234177
    },
    {
        "question": " 22.3日は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.284780321336493
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.04兆時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.075871178683872
    },
    {
        "question": " 33.6億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.145820983983604
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.5万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.797513134765364
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.4時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.796926431000575
    },
    {
        "question": " 256万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6883436333671444
    },
    {
        "question": " 233億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.209841669952935
    },
    {
        "question": " 414分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8389181931847312
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.7万分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.008377806008651
    },
    {
        "question": " 35.5分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.328186930818768
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.4兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.646676496131778
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.78億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.8948441130329527
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.93万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2842710742387664
    },
    {
        "question": " 996秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2199823167096135
    },
    {
        "question": " 205秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.310965059752014
    },
    {
        "question": " 754秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.87748714299595
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.36秒は何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.372473168453338
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.72京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.736393046642775
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.39京msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.705694483677098
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.7兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.875026738452011
    },
    {
        "question": " 151億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.400533066907295
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.24万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3497469901011205
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.17msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 3.962431800521232
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.91msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.463489355515554
    },
    {
        "question": " 703垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.348051180268083
    },
    {
        "question": " 5468京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.801366015500536
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.38兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5837616646337858
    },
    {
        "question": " 212億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5474930591252054
    },
    {
        "question": " 39.3兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.594461730430559
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.7万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 2.06696990740328
    },
    {
        "question": " 58.2垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.266366719192951
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.28京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.169722264371712
    },
    {
        "question": " 945兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4189607894824574
    },
    {
        "question": " 2068兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.537349559098289
    },
    {
        "question": " 808億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9076054265972164
    },
    {
        "question": " 5161億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.71275342006917
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.18億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 5.502083531860236
    },
    {
        "question": " 640万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.368396949571354
    },
    {
        "question": " 67.6万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.772657058342492
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.9億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.511799956705185
    },
    {
        "question": " 2922万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.845876241706229
    },
    {
        "question": " 2387日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.314390361446916
    },
    {
        "question": " 25.9日は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.34929390951776
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.13億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.0177860277624795
    },
    {
        "question": " 2143万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.950796306877403
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.16時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.397250587734635
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.04億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.18473839528847
    },
    {
        "question": " 3974万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.440837362155755
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.5万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.412310771314723
    },
    {
        "question": " 138分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.918057045240336
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.98分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.2517386891475715
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.83億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.18556977651879
    },
    {
        "question": " 86.2兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.999027131573293
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.31兆秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.243892768697025
    },
    {
        "question": " 152万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.404538345192178
    },
    {
        "question": " 6002秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.778262259605807
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.39秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.379270092551852
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.33京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.4711133999025074
    },
    {
        "question": " 929兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.031706337814413
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.64兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.380072873054058
    },
    {
        "question": " 197兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.51665357615573
    },
    {
        "question": " 4582億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.661081083083916
    },
    {
        "question": " 93.6兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.47265603112781607
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.45京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.2249564725819475
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.09兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4797268444586096
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.79億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1132680756226943
    },
    {
        "question": " 789万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8972870709840153
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.24万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.5105807430290086
    },
    {
        "question": " 48.1万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 8.6819812942453
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.202e+04垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.293758417256866
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.7京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.2322231859347337
    },
    {
        "question": " 800兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3470421665144228
    },
    {
        "question": " 331兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.7411599076241107
    },
    {
        "question": " 196兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.293311677398407
    },
    {
        "question": " 106兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.025663740645353
    },
    {
        "question": " 365億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.562600751205393
    },
    {
        "question": " 104万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.95834707469041
    },
    {
        "question": " 97.2万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.4252339200905713
    },
    {
        "question": " 5764日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.140913492342335
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.16万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.07012459260877
    },
    {
        "question": " 43万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6906875062688376
    },
    {
        "question": " 1760億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.865377244722325
    },
    {
        "question": " 427時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.408500300545746
    },
    {
        "question": " 25.9時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.969435244576145
    },
    {
        "question": " 44.9時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.208141951413069
    },
    {
        "question": " 94.1億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.252906635384438
    },
    {
        "question": " 99.6万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.839945988039015
    },
    {
        "question": " 410億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.834964923437504
    },
    {
        "question": " 1203万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.858357284208761
    },
    {
        "question": " 445分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.426962969488409
    },
    {
        "question": " 8416億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.426292220985868
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.92億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.013657998970402
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.53万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2587311441105586
    },
    {
        "question": " 225万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.573504896031489
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.52秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.182143563459622
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.5秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.175180768724741
    },
    {
        "question": " 75.6兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.379569116917558
    },
    {
        "question": " 20.7兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.379053208384282
    },
    {
        "question": " 259兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.856829851230866
    },
    {
        "question": " 238億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.598283405188061
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.91兆msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.46457326483097
    },
    {
        "question": " 8932msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.950971474269563
    },
    {
        "question": " 509msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 8.706900455814079
    },
    {
        "question": " 99.9京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.5008413170363255
    },
    {
        "question": " 16京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.268205610071972
    },
    {
        "question": " 490京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.134088873890104
    },
    {
        "question": " 25.6億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6292867089463514
    },
    {
        "question": " 1205万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0810366061678511
    },
    {
        "question": " 208万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.3187223549041036
    },
    {
        "question": " 2737usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.437229875057858
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.34e+06垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.628365062188003
    },
    {
        "question": " 261兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.47959134037784623
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.84京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.7087899169936933
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.96垓nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.692801474524895
    },
    {
        "question": " 2160兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.33454233086497
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.68兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.885615463534221
    },
    {
        "question": " 662万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 3.821122497081454
    },
    {
        "question": " 671年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.769381082602117
    },
    {
        "question": " 59.6年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.27385642723163
    },
    {
        "question": " 114億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.494036377593128
    },
    {
        "question": " 54.9万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.1198713060183785
    },
    {
        "question": " 19.7万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3526743212417358
    },
    {
        "question": " 849時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.548607400483366
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.32兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.248552155461436
    },
    {
        "question": " 4243分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.4692969752474463
    },
    {
        "question": " 124億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.315791333867377
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.76兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.261358956712108
    },
    {
        "question": " 193兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.348279823034568
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.55万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2596260344975785
    },
    {
        "question": " 633億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.02301711592277
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.01万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.603661081211113
    },
    {
        "question": " 453兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.15769654545313
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.14億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.024355829547211
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.9兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.722571755164282
    },
    {
        "question": " 250億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.620585845635585
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.8万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.107340061923433
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.22万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.62573086139171
    },
    {
        "question": " 1883兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7759721858199018
    },
    {
        "question": " 875億usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.005353056928444344
    },
    {
        "question": " 501億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1433635384319552
    },
    {
        "question": " 572兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.979337513075523
    },
    {
        "question": " 116万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.06462067993449505
    },
    {
        "question": " 135万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.1295037454990204
    },
    {
        "question": " 4129京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.1170844297407365
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.92京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3472086190836405
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.88垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.21287524849362
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.53垓nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.769086490756642
    },
    {
        "question": " 3707兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.569039569546683
    },
    {
        "question": " 2323兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.366015976167596
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.38兆nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.141404511863676
    },
    {
        "question": " 235億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.808825537679532
    },
    {
        "question": " 21.1万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.7036477878886815
    },
    {
        "question": " 458万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.819201571086237
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.98日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.232512562328086
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.5日は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.334077343830684
    },
    {
        "question": " 83.5億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.979253911553611
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.1万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.7354723566216164
    },
    {
        "question": " 1332時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.680880963363931
    },
    {
        "question": " 466兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.947353660976892
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.4万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8988293128601441
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.23万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.310420603825838
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.04分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3848094618915425
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.43分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.164199797136364
    },
    {
        "question": " 37.4億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.074307038836427
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.25兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.69203595468978
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.75億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.273139319210118
    },
    {
        "question": " 536万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.951170456353019
    },
    {
        "question": " 809秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.90802867953869
    },
    {
        "question": " 7944京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.401259934411101
    },
    {
        "question": " 613億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8509440666831445
    },
    {
        "question": " 175兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.686459314683369
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.09億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.260552000177217
    },
    {
        "question": " 567億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.753677823727716
    },
    {
        "question": " 14万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.146382245202524
    },
    {
        "question": " 211垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.824468212207922
    },
    {
        "question": " 94.9京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.04054217448565
    },
    {
        "question": " 154億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6309498558047566
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.47億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.38877053724706956
    },
    {
        "question": " 196億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.292963321417881
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.7億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.431844502940661
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.7usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 4.247327019930723
    },
    {
        "question": " 414垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.118605034608777
    },
    {
        "question": " 1392垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.207018055252908
    },
    {
        "question": " 42.7垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.074244902619604
    },
    {
        "question": " 265兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.6452354539342258
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.2兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.007487597723562
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.39兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.377582345330214
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.35兆nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.525190976284746
    },
    {
        "question": " 1037年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.958285925855522
    },
    {
        "question": " 3693億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.005076190497478
    },
    {
        "question": " 1024日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.39059168188615
    },
    {
        "question": " 12日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.238046939871976
    },
    {
        "question": " 81兆時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.966157272696496
    },
    {
        "question": " 3384万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.149178634252266
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.24万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.8721146396456305
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.3万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.712162343445577
    },
    {
        "question": " 3074万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7670702086130208
    },
    {
        "question": " 191億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.122690760678612
    },
    {
        "question": " 7812万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.114591050568333
    },
    {
        "question": " 23万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.140152289489867
    },
    {
        "question": " 582兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.265952893358685
    },
    {
        "question": " 14万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.20887149890808754
    },
    {
        "question": " 4040秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.050093550238717865
    },
    {
        "question": " 424万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.849635408223727
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.29兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.0180237581261307
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.29億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.17576148929668078
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.1兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.765225424929569
    },
    {
        "question": " 5626億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.972061642697134
    },
    {
        "question": " 2032万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.307890940670661
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.2msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.208217676088097
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.1京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.585023679226851
    },
    {
        "question": " 92.1京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.0279752828360165
    },
    {
        "question": " 378兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.021366374780331
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.83億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0564243580553245
    },
    {
        "question": " 171億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.231760336579499
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.13億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.327940400210231
    },
    {
        "question": " 1455京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.664003626836986
    },
    {
        "question": " 131京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.181256536289144
    },
    {
        "question": " 162京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.651925322375821
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.15垓nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.283453746714441
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.29京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.723104457694396
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.5億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.2161762861971974
    },
    {
        "question": " 7499億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.874991937316757
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.65万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.504242797389809
    },
    {
        "question": " 3895年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.311155031483162
    },
    {
        "question": " 134年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.626601527587585
    },
    {
        "question": " 48.7万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.125628179034795
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.49万日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.109106020968088
    },
    {
        "question": " 2608億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.473780608119362
    },
    {
        "question": " 1826億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.88126247856556
    },
    {
        "question": " 63.7万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.5821738911047385
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.4万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.936827582767902
    },
    {
        "question": " 27.7兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.722561364515498
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.16兆分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.460565258759544
    },
    {
        "question": " 359分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.777054725455919
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.68万分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.205624758348685
    },
    {
        "question": " 22.7億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8577627442659406
    },
    {
        "question": " 395兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.66000473878918
    },
    {
        "question": " 43.8億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.085007800228253
    },
    {
        "question": " 94.9秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.19898989366568087
    },
    {
        "question": " 42.8万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.631685424038192
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.2秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.236188830588459
    },
    {
        "question": " 51.3京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.211685230174871
    },
    {
        "question": " 67.3億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8916854926904303
    },
    {
        "question": " 4300億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.077118220487575
    },
    {
        "question": " 4598万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8844522456697708
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.8億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.251473132315596
    },
    {
        "question": " 5805msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.7638135263923
    },
    {
        "question": " 843兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4270068429925487
    },
    {
        "question": " 9139億usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0243807162990226
    },
    {
        "question": " 23.5兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.8144538435531175
    },
    {
        "question": " 4231兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.848247080963225
    },
    {
        "question": " 42億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.623203572183468
    },
    {
        "question": " 19.8万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 2.297351944575874
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.34usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 3.6378613525854187
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.02垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.5081317817277924
    },
    {
        "question": " 43.1垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.697933483291235
    },
    {
        "question": " 1322兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5650218434310004
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.93垓nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.506892969912869
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.27京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.5142014516312905
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.05億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 2.484544522204797
    },
    {
        "question": " 219億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.341220687178351
    },
    {
        "question": " 44.3万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.208605786994271
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.77万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.518856042774797
    },
    {
        "question": " 41.2年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.114076532477283
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.2億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.559741668734289
    },
    {
        "question": " 1700万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.610620301497525
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.95日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.7551381873318226
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.9日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.215747173884491
    },
    {
        "question": " 693億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.898439512073504
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.07万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.936756217255895
    },
    {
        "question": " 1589時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.979380000448001
    },
    {
        "question": " 6010時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.335148013422352
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.01億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2844556464581025
    },
    {
        "question": " 433万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.4777592477035393
    },
    {
        "question": " 182分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.48160391364088895
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.6分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9431071025437894
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.3兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.655541267709401
    },
    {
        "question": " 27.5万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5024879335606636
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.71兆秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.877403595440693
    },
    {
        "question": " 218万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.5610303488891315
    },
    {
        "question": " 801秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.903533851050042
    },
    {
        "question": " 6553億msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3176130549678466
    },
    {
        "question": " 109兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.100441172303556
    },
    {
        "question": " 313億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.9390517405633387
    },
    {
        "question": " 69万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.060505163534825
    },
    {
        "question": " 3100万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.4913489524982575
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.49msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 3.1717993187813223
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.53msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.815032413104488
    },
    {
        "question": " 4449兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.149411073742382
    },
    {
        "question": " 25.2兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.465564194609875
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.2京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.494269550387724
    },
    {
        "question": " 4825億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.905373197101291
    },
    {
        "question": " 46.8億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.6704405607837054
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.02兆usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.779423400476027
    },
    {
        "question": " 254万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.405640615885092
    },
    {
        "question": " 39.3京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0960476380329998
    },
    {
        "question": " 616京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.853176821031289
    },
    {
        "question": " 4042兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.0503305580675235
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.08垓nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.25528453059031
    },
    {
        "question": " 92.8京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.96774668521611
    },
    {
        "question": " 1784兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.251358738877235
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.32兆nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.800413266746327
    },
    {
        "question": " 107年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.75029987684985
    },
    {
        "question": " 4725日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1120941734032874
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.95万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.222034500993613
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.75日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.401499960512674
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.43日は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.322005132602918
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.5万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2745274797361517
    },
    {
        "question": " 241時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0021370610682745
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.3時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.963515155464145
    },
    {
        "question": " 2932時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.0235112291106025
    },
    {
        "question": " 63.8兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.084434649983738
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.71億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.82883875102644
    },
    {
        "question": " 1292億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.333117486892755
    },
    {
        "question": " 52.2分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.4956676798572417
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.71京秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.174022706676709
    },
    {
        "question": " 789兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.960548809220356
    },
    {
        "question": " 1191億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.519721904636452
    },
    {
        "question": " 70.6億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.070450124547932
    },
    {
        "question": " 56.7京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.2544234631233895
    },
    {
        "question": " 38.9京msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.653750928344955
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.63兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.65707259633009
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.4万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.2798052086989278
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.63億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.66554253406372
    },
    {
        "question": " 274msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 5.437081881211592
    },
    {
        "question": " 665兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3240576398944326
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.39兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4425876074493016
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.1京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.649358785007588
    },
    {
        "question": " 886兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.169046076264831
    },
    {
        "question": " 6491億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.812296493525433
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.17万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.0669727759416603
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.59垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.7028090680424084
    },
    {
        "question": " 140兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.2093755089151339
    },
    {
        "question": " 5214兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.160905413806032
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.24垓nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.849494338714972
    },
    {
        "question": " 178兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.251609022858106
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.8兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.447796752498021
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.05億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 5.78172027035114
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.9年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.781343527424271
    },
    {
        "question": " 160年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.701920866312575
    },
    {
        "question": " 86.2万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.373099866602849
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.55万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.312159711255314
    },
    {
        "question": " 219万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.499463008185337
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.78億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.308098342277855
    },
    {
        "question": " 179億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.871499861424935
    },
    {
        "question": " 611万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.564220893817726
    },
    {
        "question": " 2082時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.874695087946261
    },
    {
        "question": " 2957兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.750227463822345
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.19億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.557133679647517
    },
    {
        "question": " 341億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.754595857666715
    },
    {
        "question": " 29.5万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.2479262590649185
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.5分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.909459231430643
    },
    {
        "question": " 62.4兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.296678917674219
    },
    {
        "question": " 4405億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.707447723628831
    },
    {
        "question": " 163億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.6571785966152595
    },
    {
        "question": " 22.3億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.569981851447376
    },
    {
        "question": " 533万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.726650600729446
    },
    {
        "question": " 32.7秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.514788198088493
    },
    {
        "question": " 28.1京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.9501083026225965
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.14兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.394518061834911
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.91億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7252832462608214
    },
    {
        "question": " 42.1兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.845842040535679
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.03万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.012119803620538
    },
    {
        "question": " 800msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 8.903251671345467
    },
    {
        "question": " 4107京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.114680466671594
    },
    {
        "question": " 2836京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.516188412179615
    },
    {
        "question": " 862京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.379398848731915
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.62億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6393245672993908
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.57億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.745682351307346
    },
    {
        "question": " 425億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.628380526958988
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.11usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 3.0470474806173287
    },
    {
        "question": " 74.9垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.37587491473605
    },
    {
        "question": " 50.2垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.7639649942759945
    },
    {
        "question": " 73.1京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.307767600945448
    },
    {
        "question": " 82.1京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.136041954976523
    },
    {
        "question": " 184億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.265214430896432
    },
    {
        "question": " 52.1兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.7170370110103015
    },
    {
        "question": " 322億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.507906549671678
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.13年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.049937631754166
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.44億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.309528341644346
    },
    {
        "question": " 480万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.061720242393841
    },
    {
        "question": " 6727日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.986188688930688
    },
    {
        "question": " 6144万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.845971762619679
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.43億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.773829877033938
    },
    {
        "question": " 468時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.44806287453729
    },
    {
        "question": " 285万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7335052382227092
    },
    {
        "question": " 3984億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.441970791168215
    },
    {
        "question": " 75.6万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.100353091984148
    },
    {
        "question": " 7669分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.66287155594849
    },
    {
        "question": " 34億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.0321965048396406
    },
    {
        "question": " 596万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8389191147805428
    },
    {
        "question": " 135万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.575277108070101
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.65万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4388292429159417
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.76兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3309853663609035
    },
    {
        "question": " 639億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8692551550707557
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.42京msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.9779360704492
    },
    {
        "question": " 407億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.831542690121441
    },
    {
        "question": " 2784万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.444634183577767
    },
    {
        "question": " 542msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 5.7342701157974
    },
    {
        "question": " 37.6京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.076706162663701
    },
    {
        "question": " 3520億usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6100086749118261
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.2京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.492576338778005
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.34京usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.192304953247767
    },
    {
        "question": " 3090万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.48998253777479
    },
    {
        "question": " 245万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.3885213842529827
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.75e+04垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.177867135517584
    },
    {
        "question": " 3780京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.6410116215859984
    },
    {
        "question": " 31.7京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.944264273507075
    },
    {
        "question": " 620京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.014045313088786
    },
    {
        "question": " 836億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9220563300694449
    },
    {
        "question": " 211万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 0.32389395297924284
    },
    {
        "question": " 108億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.034466894792479
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.28万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.2848985731266716
    },
    {
        "question": " 82.4年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.63669640368728
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.78億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.268973215848205
    },
    {
        "question": " 1200万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.459254170542263
    },
    {
        "question": " 59.9日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.9354210874761755
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.07日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.545578159907292
    },
    {
        "question": " 208億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.376373366355131
    },
    {
        "question": " 1816時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8788441890313257
    },
    {
        "question": " 413万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.394589132865155
    },
    {
        "question": " 141万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.706539708610833
    },
    {
        "question": " 417兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.899290042928898
    },
    {
        "question": " 125万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9369550579842354
    },
    {
        "question": " 19.6万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.514351383125147
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.1億分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.819414282529568
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.68万分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.447953716224852
    },
    {
        "question": " 5396万秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.2332844644586629
    },
    {
        "question": " 70.3兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.910356441587954
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.54万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6299059244227467
    },
    {
        "question": " 1392億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.365510559583996
    },
    {
        "question": " 1648秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.216871705305872
    },
    {
        "question": " 122秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.086198297470945
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.95京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.790732118227263
    },
    {
        "question": " 21.2億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3903214781278561
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.62兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.654141601507325
    },
    {
        "question": " 768万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1069417519387565
    },
    {
        "question": " 1064万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.026996106463997
    },
    {
        "question": " 64万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.805858732410313
    },
    {
        "question": " 1850兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7682817395471273
    },
    {
        "question": " 7387億usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.931939569569471
    },
    {
        "question": " 7030兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.290682486364978
    },
    {
        "question": " 237兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.5966365394784985
    },
    {
        "question": " 451兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.654294932384678
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.36億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.372231293934728
    },
    {
        "question": " 750垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.376177670412986
    },
    {
        "question": " 18.7垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.334607511978847
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.37京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.311374141649208
    },
    {
        "question": " 123兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.3101068236590416
    },
    {
        "question": " 724兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.859699496242748
    },
    {
        "question": " 6459億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.810141690970202
    },
    {
        "question": " 569万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 3.7550840273234174
    },
    {
        "question": " 138年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.702157185367559
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.8兆日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.693223219945095
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.8日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.827975656354639
    },
    {
        "question": " 25日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.556988558888363
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.16日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.27169591817911
    },
    {
        "question": " 11兆時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.09716708454894
    },
    {
        "question": " 21.2万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.945811167983646
    },
    {
        "question": " 2356時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.15032228079208
    },
    {
        "question": " 439時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.199118756225836
    },
    {
        "question": " 8989万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2330667651340033
    },
    {
        "question": " 80億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.744798157744972
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.26万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3238001052648807
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.63万分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.33835766835672
    },
    {
        "question": " 653兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.316102274556183
    },
    {
        "question": " 354万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6124968335042256
    },
    {
        "question": " 29.3億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.910592135301006
    },
    {
        "question": " 3210億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.728345848552745
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.5秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.242810562700764
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.8兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7516900135915776
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.08京msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.021797674762773
    },
    {
        "question": " 3049万msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9279081013965207
    },
    {
        "question": " 3558万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.773058981931573
    },
    {
        "question": " 3245万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.511179480234793
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.9msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.075860472061644
    },
    {
        "question": " 2275京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.858115475683363
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.19京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.027009586304047
    },
    {
        "question": " 1095兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.4831658627183675
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.26兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.323696162397722
    },
    {
        "question": " 9903億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.995759113501715
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.56億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.194177287952551
    },
    {
        "question": " 29.4垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.969405142775759
    },
    {
        "question": " 448兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7150798401182101
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.6垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.544189357426694
    },
    {
        "question": " 46.4京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.888344523725007
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.14兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.910427837022896
    },
    {
        "question": " 42.5億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.6279882602155133
    },
    {
        "question": " 59.2万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 2.7725283832655356
    },
    {
        "question": " 29.2年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.185429559900655
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.81億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.694538934570957
    },
    {
        "question": " 437日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.020808150860016
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.1日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.205560890109186
    },
    {
        "question": " 36.3兆時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.61691441296842
    },
    {
        "question": " 137億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.757129903691068
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.6万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.941173651401149
    },
    {
        "question": " 2964時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.0281616234010515
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.5兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.441126798273752
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.32兆分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.56760151688487
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.3億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.407553694832628
    },
    {
        "question": " 82.9分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.6969146553753585
    },
    {
        "question": " 1297億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.614261381902477
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.59億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.477203329086146
    },
    {
        "question": " 809万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.3515853195234078
    },
    {
        "question": " 19.3万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.5084602694492126
    },
    {
        "question": " 274秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.438250196423734
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.06兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8160553988149797
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.35京msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.193302070256328
    },
    {
        "question": " 2582億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.855669848432884
    },
    {
        "question": " 143億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.37622393538708
    },
    {
        "question": " 7813万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.892844920679616
    },
    {
        "question": " 2079msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.317835434634214
    },
    {
        "question": " 6677兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.325793580429496
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.44垓usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.22049243580129
    },
    {
        "question": " 4331億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.0803074734635163
    },
    {
        "question": " 77.2億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1092908976413494
    },
    {
        "question": " 4830兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.683904214929816
    },
    {
        "question": " 589万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.7699645433160978
    },
    {
        "question": " 480京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1825373305866327
    },
    {
        "question": " 592垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.835795448694926
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.03京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.348210787275464
    },
    {
        "question": " 5523億nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9639917891658001
    },
    {
        "question": " 30.5兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.484348560651349
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.2億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.20906028619392
    },
    {
        "question": " 4911nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 0.6911406695400901
    },
    {
        "question": " 61.1万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.34836435720568
    },
    {
        "question": " 5639日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1888768818075068
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.7日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8111783589675934
    },
    {
        "question": " 60.6日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.940492300217648
    },
    {
        "question": " 112日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.98627799505851
    },
    {
        "question": " 505億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.760532046846453
    },
    {
        "question": " 324億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.130364439154716
    },
    {
        "question": " 30.9万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.267960308427881
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.11時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.265005320162889
    },
    {
        "question": " 24.2億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.6637529437678564
    },
    {
        "question": " 82.6万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7588412107721485
    },
    {
        "question": " 248億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.616962456552528
    },
    {
        "question": " 9498万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.755781059266752
    },
    {
        "question": " 6927分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.618694125231306
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.96分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.62085850440521
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.6億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6951165664894985
    },
    {
        "question": " 1442万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2223839610332696
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.25兆秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.072293857576213
    },
    {
        "question": " 36.4億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.783091455673512
    },
    {
        "question": " 973秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.988066880848088
    },
    {
        "question": " 1033京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.515179377017887
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.7億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2864123058044796
    },
    {
        "question": " 8377兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.366770088449032
    },
    {
        "question": " 268兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.649618219052202
    },
    {
        "question": " 533億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.727024003264795
    },
    {
        "question": " 741msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 5.8700082752799245
    },
    {
        "question": " 2垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.802144167907453
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.9兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2065685370827905
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.73兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.879979679640703
    },
    {
        "question": " 7794兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.11359189939287
    },
    {
        "question": " 1669万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.222555152098892
    },
    {
        "question": " 268億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.428267993825565
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.32万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 7.92022680744801
    },
    {
        "question": " 627垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.298298966161812
    },
    {
        "question": " 836京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.985556074830189
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.58京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.8560073381568194
    },
    {
        "question": " 600億nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.000295413537039213
    },
    {
        "question": " 2497兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.397349390716938
    },
    {
        "question": " 424兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.627233352307995
    },
    {
        "question": " 1691nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 0.22810839392294446
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.11万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.267346044387379
    },
    {
        "question": " 65.5年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.536683637567355
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.03億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.7444904152508816
    },
    {
        "question": " 2360日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.753054585237067
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.91日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.622901410209707
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.13億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.1090996803780575
    },
    {
        "question": " 187万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.891322284487129
    },
    {
        "question": " 82.2万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.471059958721122
    },
    {
        "question": " 673万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1074898236785047
    },
    {
        "question": " 50.1億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.541137178874928
    },
    {
        "question": " 57.5億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.9816321275635085
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.24万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.872532559075985
    },
    {
        "question": " 3266億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.015271627178725
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.57兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.044370749026553
    },
    {
        "question": " 861億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.378949260979448
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.17億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.289250680536034
    },
    {
        "question": " 1032京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.514667362799885
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.48億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.605570857982306
    },
    {
        "question": " 2125兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.770998324396778
    },
    {
        "question": " 505億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.924916539991639
    },
    {
        "question": " 7902万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.897756290776783
    },
    {
        "question": " 56.1msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.748834246443698
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.1msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 7.082448285182035
    },
    {
        "question": " 427兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.131488665223015
    },
    {
        "question": " 353兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.611758975740289
    },
    {
        "question": " 44.4兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.091281017410321
    },
    {
        "question": " 613億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.0090347766273773
    },
    {
        "question": " 3786万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5782050681518345
    },
    {
        "question": " 12万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 2.077620319025013
    },
    {
        "question": " 141京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6500753636608056
    },
    {
        "question": " 816京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.975085797830474
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.76京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.884046863372872
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.19京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.296638259806803
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.1兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.0053927919643675
    },
    {
        "question": " 7501億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.875124394624008
    },
    {
        "question": " 98.4億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.992896678984348
    },
    {
        "question": " 364年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.123062389560119
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.53万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8402238824698713
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.38万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.756176895290891
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.96万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.630116048853823
    },
    {
        "question": " 385日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.522184356307867
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.9億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.167986870425906
    },
    {
        "question": " 417時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2402870667460064
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.6時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8415785760019374
    },
    {
        "question": " 514時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.266997933299203
    },
    {
        "question": " 176億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.525370578192597
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.27兆分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.808829522406421
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.76万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.111755855048605
    },
    {
        "question": " 1719分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.013327023590179
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.09兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.822165074576735
    },
    {
        "question": " 612億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.850239820430011
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.9万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4807804420581971
    },
    {
        "question": " 284億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.675871557922525
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.9万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.689869167427064
    },
    {
        "question": " 62.2兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.295129920851263
    },
    {
        "question": " 64.7兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.874634751689268
    },
    {
        "question": " 385兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.029417133141298
    },
    {
        "question": " 188万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4956408024662249
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.25兆msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.860423693442431
    },
    {
        "question": " 93万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.96831775799667
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.9msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 7.173035342724589
    },
    {
        "question": " 55.3兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.24427854079689726
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.61京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.812082606968646
    },
    {
        "question": " 351兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.988651218136788
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.12兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.836664343054588
    },
    {
        "question": " 334億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.523501735275466
    },
    {
        "question": " 48.4万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 2.684962079035267
    },
    {
        "question": " 32.5usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 4.5125441511868525
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.461e+04垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.040447476139098
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.4京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.932487986749729
    },
    {
        "question": " 48.2京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.126854964470924
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.78京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.47126866400604
    },
    {
        "question": " 448億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6516657041824834
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.38兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.529487541202803
    },
    {
        "question": " 206万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 3.3129741209671817
    },
    {
        "question": " 112年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.6129310998012425
    },
    {
        "question": " 42.6万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.571964228602681
    },
    {
        "question": " 240億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.817388714027494
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.45日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3556122746016683
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.03万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.005213500096831
    },
    {
        "question": " 79.9日は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.839316166488363
    },
    {
        "question": " 24.6兆時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.4484853698396
    },
    {
        "question": " 57.7億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.380619016761292
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.66万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.446213451236464
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.49万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.208916988871142
    },
    {
        "question": " 84.1時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.481219916307793
    },
    {
        "question": " 197万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5731847875032958
    },
    {
        "question": " 4407分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.4857484587447447
    },
    {
        "question": " 3162億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.721833406549443
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.87万分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.546849383294047
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.95兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.401330424944579
    },
    {
        "question": " 6670万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.887655639811404
    },
    {
        "question": " 3199億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.948696846177194
    },
    {
        "question": " 231億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.58454002181427
    },
    {
        "question": " 60.2万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.779737098397879
    },
    {
        "question": " 1036秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.015479712052622
    },
    {
        "question": " 589兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.27144290683497
    },
    {
        "question": " 16京msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.266512382809234
    },
    {
        "question": " 347兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.9839759375258
    },
    {
        "question": " 51.9兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.936937481850116
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.8万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9910431122319616
    },
    {
        "question": " 130兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6144128972095431
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.18兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4025791548480493
    },
    {
        "question": " 262京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.862717492155623
    },
    {
        "question": " 74兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.0910584941010555
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.89兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.5901191848901775
    },
    {
        "question": " 144万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.1574744527090726
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.37万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 7.373973919650744
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.946e+06垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.790446961850632
    },
    {
        "question": " 5466兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8011527198592214
    },
    {
        "question": " 221京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.787109327211314
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.03兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2361338404466193
    },
    {
        "question": " 141京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.150403030602583
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.8兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.763114849725946
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.93兆nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.284661187606972
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.1万年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.761864183252897
    },
    {
        "question": " 79.6年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.399736113952043
    },
    {
        "question": " 307万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.924839627101966
    },
    {
        "question": " 8097日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.2885307960437045
    },
    {
        "question": " 2787日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.603451200558476
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.84日は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.390453657914835
    },
    {
        "question": " 5831万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.82326589843628
    },
    {
        "question": " 75.7時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.4989215003552183
    },
    {
        "question": " 74.8万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.6517766578450495
    },
    {
        "question": " 41.3時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.171768378502356
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.54億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.02286350926091
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.01万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6202850899581012
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.68万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.447355414152874
    },
    {
        "question": " 16分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9822855339487884
    },
    {
        "question": " 1374分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.916273156408373
    },
    {
        "question": " 188億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7743245811060326
    },
    {
        "question": " 65.3兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.878143965352884
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.58兆秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.64241024180222
    },
    {
        "question": " 123万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.312695337513559
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.8万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.4470079369105235
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.86京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.958084263819482
    },
    {
        "question": " 132億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.183345449251013
    },
    {
        "question": " 54億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.1760050844550958
    },
    {
        "question": " 479兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.902617464871003
    },
    {
        "question": " 781万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.892434187372449
    },
    {
        "question": " 577msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 5.761395257183511
    },
    {
        "question": " 7856京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.396416639097268
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.4兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.796264585980949
    },
    {
        "question": " 49.5京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.138411442886076
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.39兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.027662516978562
    },
    {
        "question": " 1664兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.221025335647685
    },
    {
        "question": " 838億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.9233068430255615
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.82usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 3.259380134251215
    },
    {
        "question": " 841垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.425859137438551
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.02京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.0725281909100457
    },
    {
        "question": " 41.2京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.059122056175651
    },
    {
        "question": " 243兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.606599672783364
    },
    {
        "question": " 52.2兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.71796100569425
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.52億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 2.4015750006654124
    },
    {
        "question": " 3648nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 0.562060435745817
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.5年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.6216826581022565
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.76万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.620278608471654
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.59年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.9214688830782265
    },
    {
        "question": " 61.7億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.228149799523624
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.37万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.908385561105724
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.75万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.14728966280958
    },
    {
        "question": " 4645日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.603520497014067
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.36億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.697055804574023
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.2万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.7071795775843306
    },
    {
        "question": " 22.9時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.1387331321580025
    },
    {
        "question": " 861時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.491459791485326
    },
    {
        "question": " 154時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.74396467398636
    },
    {
        "question": " 1392億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.4230359967862025
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.77兆分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.603072214566899
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.15億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.076399466133254
    },
    {
        "question": " 48.7万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.465966293724392
    },
    {
        "question": " 4895分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.467885542396665
    },
    {
        "question": " 26.7兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.928411079724354
    },
    {
        "question": " 1447万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2239607444238016
    },
    {
        "question": " 24.1兆秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.825574019867565
    },
    {
        "question": " 93.6万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.193222183488812
    },
    {
        "question": " 544兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.236891617335678
    },
    {
        "question": " 574兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.822708629401574
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.83京msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.706050737344396
    },
    {
        "question": " 7500億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.096909002260778
    },
    {
        "question": " 89億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.949248349404531
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.28万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.358121258877261
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.34京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6284184730872417
    },
    {
        "question": " 53京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.787968871150643
    },
    {
        "question": " 114京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.49954304252784
    },
    {
        "question": " 2023億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.5279057485421452
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.56億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7448134337366525
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.01兆usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.005125463645275
    },
    {
        "question": " 171usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 5.23320697552958
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.36京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.3044115911973888
    },
    {
        "question": " 5965京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.839122028633666
    },
    {
        "question": " 83.7兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3664203601099378
    },
    {
        "question": " 2183京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.560997712610293
    },
    {
        "question": " 2276億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3572020761687575
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.47兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.540521316499742
    },
    {
        "question": " 82.9万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 2.918565004592628
    },
    {
        "question": " 897年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.895512609274583
    },
    {
        "question": " 4118年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.335350665716375
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.91兆日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.902267504810624
    },
    {
        "question": " 20日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.68141626446581
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.33日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.5732792508010265
    },
    {
        "question": " 54.1兆時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.790675433301608
    },
    {
        "question": " 2009億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.922673646258286
    },
    {
        "question": " 93時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.7465915892661106
    },
    {
        "question": " 189万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.832116545433802
    },
    {
        "question": " 226兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.634000068882456
    },
    {
        "question": " 509億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.548424749282616
    },
    {
        "question": " 8949万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.173642134129849
    },
    {
        "question": " 110分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.819341000658716
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.77分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.219876674933623
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.2億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5810598950019497
    },
    {
        "question": " 461億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.727545561566558
    },
    {
        "question": " 470万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.1154531030371215
    },
    {
        "question": " 523億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.94033746159926
    },
    {
        "question": " 200万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.300182213156244
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.34京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.025308205195129
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.27京msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.41963510043046
    },
    {
        "question": " 105億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.465164970224266
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.89兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.216971160672294
    },
    {
        "question": " 8399億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.924207499063442
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.9垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.673125104421562
    },
    {
        "question": " 18.4兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3272410236513053
    },
    {
        "question": " 1344兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.57197659793948
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.84億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9886041920392719
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.02兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.480452409238703
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.66億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.884022769180434
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.044e+05垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.520090920007284
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.15京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5616103300395796
    },
    {
        "question": " 323京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.952903505279884
    },
    {
        "question": " 3419京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.755725271259141
    },
    {
        "question": " 174兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.241152619318151
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.74億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 2.572425143186
    },
    {
        "question": " 8138nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 0.9105224154580582
    },
    {
        "question": " 564万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.313654896953944
    },
    {
        "question": " 3075年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.430357669311359
    },
    {
        "question": " 3563億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.989462692575142
    },
    {
        "question": " 87万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.31971792719845
    },
    {
        "question": " 968日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.144122071938014
    },
    {
        "question": " 1378日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.075680866106294
    },
    {
        "question": " 96.1億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.040000337807664
    },
    {
        "question": " 466時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2882335043741588
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.33時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3004105131827526
    },
    {
        "question": " 93.2時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.525927291394162
    },
    {
        "question": " 89.2時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.506568521638494
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.41億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.0862067820643766
    },
    {
        "question": " 100億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.843281849194057
    },
    {
        "question": " 1222万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.308775348921857
    },
    {
        "question": " 329万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.294954370339497
    },
    {
        "question": " 8892兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.45019709880026
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.63億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.2760446029839594
    },
    {
        "question": " 7207秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.30148342043058385
    },
    {
        "question": " 350秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7664662497987262
    },
    {
        "question": " 9281秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.96759468954542
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.46兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3116441373335617
    },
    {
        "question": " 135億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1947106282840956
    },
    {
        "question": " 522兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.160996693618642
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.08億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.2551744214371414
    },
    {
        "question": " 28.7億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.457762403310189
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.74msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.240266195028536
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.42垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.426626024322368
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.84京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.747989353061515
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.21京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.950010643861924
    },
    {
        "question": " 49.3兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.91469657448545
    },
    {
        "question": " 134兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.127791464073793
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.47億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.166391962518881
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.42万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 7.973866849353966
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.038e+04垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.517372724368142
    },
    {
        "question": " 1251京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.160759165895233
    },
    {
        "question": " 1583兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6431524233920687
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.64兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4355789457580526
    },
    {
        "question": " 86.4億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9365766949835519
    },
    {
        "question": " 26.2億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.4181659973284537
    },
    {
        "question": " 6688億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.825280035530506
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.84年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.328430575494914
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.47年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.81566236148306
    },
    {
        "question": " 1046億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.457228479146877
    },
    {
        "question": " 53.8日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.1113022166152082
    },
    {
        "question": " 2476日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.330252437883887
    },
    {
        "question": " 49.5日は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.63151455864691
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.71億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.491128804088297
    },
    {
        "question": " 416億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.239124285826374
    },
    {
        "question": " 649時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.590298918025274
    },
    {
        "question": " 38.3時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.1391040765269045
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.16兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.345426427659582
    },
    {
        "question": " 31.8億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.344115377769903
    },
    {
        "question": " 1513万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.401668761966356
    },
    {
        "question": " 48.6分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.465119926639594
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.73分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.666141046572523
    },
    {
        "question": " 22.6兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.854504399800689
    },
    {
        "question": " 7034億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.910727241754069
    },
    {
        "question": " 80.5万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3492647396661903
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.44億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.3811174271478786
    },
    {
        "question": " 64.8秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.8114726099355725
    },
    {
        "question": " 3470兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.041556354823287
    },
    {
        "question": " 6452億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.873178259490162
    },
    {
        "question": " 733万msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.3088113498062961
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.45兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.759565621552226
    },
    {
        "question": " 5189億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.71505822837616
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.6msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.065231748759368
    },
    {
        "question": " 66.6msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 7.823505725091912
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.13垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.828625048122479
    },
    {
        "question": " 4188億usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6855375455161128
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.57京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.640597412441938
    },
    {
        "question": " 266億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6469994629790747
    },
    {
        "question": " 8486万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9286952315636774
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.42億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.644935686910152
    },
    {
        "question": " 667万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.823977271781635
    },
    {
        "question": " 1437垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.658572608843346
    },
    {
        "question": " 109京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.101409795541375
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.34垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.36498006766233
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.96垓nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.917059967507068
    },
    {
        "question": " 685億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8356305625587077
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.1兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.785033501572011
    },
    {
        "question": " 134万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 3.127927246247716
    },
    {
        "question": " 431年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.196705594252996
    },
    {
        "question": " 36.1万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.500356915361166
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.98年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.418189183385342
    },
    {
        "question": " 32.9億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.955024998764133
    },
    {
        "question": " 1094万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.419322163767115
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.47万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.550537902489694
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.51兆時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.237598358531068
    },
    {
        "question": " 620万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.411856341936239
    },
    {
        "question": " 164時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.9940452264312665
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.81時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.449141172968534
    },
    {
        "question": " 150時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.733623690808503
    },
    {
        "question": " 6458億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.089471558497159
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.53億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.656496343803969
    },
    {
        "question": " 101億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.224780866684108
    },
    {
        "question": " 817分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.690161187300128
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.59分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.980311829077043
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.36京秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.874415140084084
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.43億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.4493335610833875
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.7兆秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.665536895343582
    },
    {
        "question": " 116億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.287787567902011
    },
    {
        "question": " 3463兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.04066509719253
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.19億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9769530475185162
    },
    {
        "question": " 371億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.013415438334675
    },
    {
        "question": " 1185万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.295731121521769
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.42億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.645290119635103
    },
    {
        "question": " 7550msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.87793533047639
    },
    {
        "question": " 69.1京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.340395738948772
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.01京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.842318094021433
    },
    {
        "question": " 19.5京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.734186883630777
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.1京usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.227460535464813
    },
    {
        "question": " 24.3兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.385474742749679
    },
    {
        "question": " 1762億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.245911888961963
    },
    {
        "question": " 4849usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.685677731407626
    },
    {
        "question": " 130垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.614610459627018
    },
    {
        "question": " 1810垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.321139081137181
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.71京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.6778910989068025
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.14京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.075384093532497
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.58兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.746681843282201
    },
    {
        "question": " 5136億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.710593330064155
    },
    {
        "question": " 1620nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 0.20957269384835553
    },
    {
        "question": " 21.3年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.8897628645856264
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.36年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.582230407554241
    },
    {
        "question": " 1349億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.567646186091324
    },
    {
        "question": " 5754万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.140138666178572
    },
    {
        "question": " 36.2日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.7166986032306015
    },
    {
        "question": " 109億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.095168554594964
    },
    {
        "question": " 2126億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.947335268530377
    },
    {
        "question": " 23.1時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.141506188247617
    },
    {
        "question": " 220時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.898589344672912
    },
    {
        "question": " 2383億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.65647633457171
    },
    {
        "question": " 6528万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.656429150271604
    },
    {
        "question": " 67.1分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.04886649631170692
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.5分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.87477944901077
    },
    {
        "question": " 5669兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.254681137950868
    },
    {
        "question": " 130万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1771615854126305
    },
    {
        "question": " 13億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.556195858777477
    },
    {
        "question": " 507秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9272776681364947
    },
    {
        "question": " 199万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.299810101296837
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.78京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.392239101894109
    },
    {
        "question": " 3310兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.583325512199533
    },
    {
        "question": " 789兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.340634128340836
    },
    {
        "question": " 93.5兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.192531489865631
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.8兆msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.681303341925652
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.87msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 3.2729912743518597
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.9msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.949492620397395
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.23京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.59283467682888
    },
    {
        "question": " 2394兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.442549744393439
    },
    {
        "question": " 605兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.225176033469485
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.2京usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.458568424853379
    },
    {
        "question": " 4600億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.662772919614691
    },
    {
        "question": " 3135usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 0.49622895280524215
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.744e+05垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.074569297224517
    },
    {
        "question": " 23.4京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.4319639718269137
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.85京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.897846984186594
    },
    {
        "question": " 95.4兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.2013277585265385
    },
    {
        "question": " 593兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.77334063529185
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.83億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 2.834503802452477
    },
    {
        "question": " 40.2億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.604198311693347
    },
    {
        "question": " 455万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.22072327751918
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.43年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.813755386497249
    },
    {
        "question": " 2825年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.171725064964654
    },
    {
        "question": " 2277日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7950454715670674
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.27日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.010353049419744
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.52日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.136936009645565
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.7日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.005144991837464
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.82万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5081374339733413
    },
    {
        "question": " 137万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.756003759457137
    },
    {
        "question": " 37.4時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.350646289741195
    },
    {
        "question": " 1408時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.704901625804066
    },
    {
        "question": " 22.5兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.6319239215306665
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.1億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.990118012653949
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.9万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.364956379491307
    },
    {
        "question": " 493万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.471174712925277
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.99分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.555441971149426
    },
    {
        "question": " 1118億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.5495384783931847
    },
    {
        "question": " 442万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.708845760919454
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.45兆秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.419220004275834
    },
    {
        "question": " 1904秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5014771703144059
    },
    {
        "question": " 6892秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.838317563581342
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.65秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.667266101596665
    },
    {
        "question": " 2010兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.8043336201952975
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.5京msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.60720795976976
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.4億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5378010858020614
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.47兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.762547253050883
    },
    {
        "question": " 1079万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.032862344120145
    },
    {
        "question": " 50.3msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.701136806116208
    },
    {
        "question": " 1659兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7210004386948186
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.46兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2278903277912012
    },
    {
        "question": " 360兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.000491297128353
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.1億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4007794009018526
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.9億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.0741185807577063
    },
    {
        "question": " 1076億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.031983615729146
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.374e+04垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.42413091770999
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.16垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.562631077087312
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.43垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.829110504366814
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.1京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.263256631671087
    },
    {
        "question": " 2476億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.39372195284967
    },
    {
        "question": " 1218億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.085701156658343
    },
    {
        "question": " 64.5億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.809576676669444
    },
    {
        "question": " 1179万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.633820597899929
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.82万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.202116237141356
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.7億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.468961165524779
    },
    {
        "question": " 286万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.837300125051536
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.07万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.767795548677304
    },
    {
        "question": " 50.4日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.638620907753555
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.61日は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.141995645713381
    },
    {
        "question": " 6897万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.8961668654483574
    },
    {
        "question": " 183時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8821186362903743
    },
    {
        "question": " 1343万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.906248977968557
    },
    {
        "question": " 325時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.068807056739577
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.16時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.622604294010274
    },
    {
        "question": " 1881万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5536476540507849
    },
    {
        "question": " 1701億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.072475595851976
    },
    {
        "question": " 1635億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.435319535268837
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.96分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.071180676089035
    },
    {
        "question": " 41.8分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.399084223438498
    },
    {
        "question": " 22.8億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8583898540738997
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.46兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.7128909321005965
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.05万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2258068897621799
    },
    {
        "question": " 51.9億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.937412146553489
    },
    {
        "question": " 1002秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.00107338575234
    },
    {
        "question": " 5892億msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2714657361852044
    },
    {
        "question": " 31.4兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.559880780998991
    },
    {
        "question": " 79.4兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.343368178511325
    },
    {
        "question": " 677万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.052572556155302
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.8億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.2548946118719915
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.54万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.187698165207449
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.18垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.5719849967091495
    },
    {
        "question": " 3871京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.651307360893343
    },
    {
        "question": " 404兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.049743812722407
    },
    {
        "question": " 435億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8601965288021756
    },
    {
        "question": " 29.3兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.4672184446381475
    },
    {
        "question": " 932億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.969351551084495
    },
    {
        "question": " 125usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 5.0964176101473395
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.509e+04垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.900736056011671
    },
    {
        "question": " 7702京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.950084992260335
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.5京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.573590767662664
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.3兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4595552544499046
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.1京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.207464236754692
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.59兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.413657111678255
    },
    {
        "question": " 64.1万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 2.806572229192752
    },
    {
        "question": " 80.7万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.849167491108293
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.4億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.969067674782673
    },
    {
        "question": " 3419日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.914069083607027
    },
    {
        "question": " 3万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.635273512811972
    },
    {
        "question": " 27.5日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.375208291770625
    },
    {
        "question": " 97.2億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.045197788827865
    },
    {
        "question": " 33.6時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.14581221087467178
    },
    {
        "question": " 123万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.867836930182543
    },
    {
        "question": " 43.2時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.19146421096597
    },
    {
        "question": " 3872兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.867250371781473
    },
    {
        "question": " 7941億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.741528015829648
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.62億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.157359682990312
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.1分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7832849753822666
    },
    {
        "question": " 9236億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.466699620562775
    },
    {
        "question": " 388億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.652748345118358
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.12万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.153252386253213
    },
    {
        "question": " 48.1万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.9036878560245114
    },
    {
        "question": " 24.9万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.395413724718871
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.1京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.650476692237145
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.33京msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.431524267040775
    },
    {
        "question": " 51.1兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.152216415889583
    },
    {
        "question": " 29.7億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.695114872618906
    },
    {
        "question": " 532万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.7257409127652066
    },
    {
        "question": " 5741msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.7590121142023705
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.72msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.8876533121927155
    },
    {
        "question": " 90.3垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.45669074435079
    },
    {
        "question": " 1911京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.344849339007174
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.81京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.024185602229494
    },
    {
        "question": " 287兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.679908576735526
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.16兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.712454318519865
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.6兆usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.414859193544832
    },
    {
        "question": " 325万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.511695461979745
    },
    {
        "question": " 2966京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9733601018954503
    },
    {
        "question": " 4805兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.745237393288116
    },
    {
        "question": " 126京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.5448902005178855
    },
    {
        "question": " 65.6兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.0385534156896945
    },
    {
        "question": " 38.7兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.587843428236513
    },
    {
        "question": " 1162万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.0652920489674633
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.17万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 1.620540152369111
    },
    {
        "question": " 88.6年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.509718457019939
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.46年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.3334369528918355
    },
    {
        "question": " 65.7年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.538044886203405
    },
    {
        "question": " 21.3年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.82689757600741
    },
    {
        "question": " 1286日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5468421316530059
    },
    {
        "question": " 128日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.488573186095535
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.3日は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.173293936658496
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.57兆時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.609577524095904
    },
    {
        "question": " 29.9時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.0953461096215491
    },
    {
        "question": " 40.2時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.3820823724149287
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.28時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.663618977368888
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.1兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.281765728145261
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.96億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.6172157064435435
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.7万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.326026762760146
    },
    {
        "question": " 186億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7701270189640037
    },
    {
        "question": " 43.9億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.706101125060318
    },
    {
        "question": " 64.5億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.253401094990228
    },
    {
        "question": " 3773万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.798571656898714
    },
    {
        "question": " 4826秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.683626352061647
    },
    {
        "question": " 420秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.623227502292963
    },
    {
        "question": " 254兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.9068778438440734
    },
    {
        "question": " 21.7京msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.400090829284121
    },
    {
        "question": " 173億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.680677624162212
    },
    {
        "question": " 172億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.457357397522278
    },
    {
        "question": " 53.5万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7279789310440083
    },
    {
        "question": " 331万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.520350234621631
    },
    {
        "question": " 2673京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.928141110317357
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.16京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.126586658847393
    },
    {
        "question": " 49.6億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.13915566703852744
    },
    {
        "question": " 4664億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.8906474104522837
    },
    {
        "question": " 1047万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0201325032855546
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.5億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.1897333842765345
    },
    {
        "question": " 825万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.916554859679295
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.11垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.209518622497399
    },
    {
        "question": " 2263垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.418156865472616
    },
    {
        "question": " 16兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6472483137537044
    },
    {
        "question": " 5514京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.96332884971911
    },
    {
        "question": " 3758億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5749797606126767
    },
    {
        "question": " 476億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.677933851983647
    },
    {
        "question": " 34.7億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.539774413124814
    },
    {
        "question": " 241年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.9434632351151535
    },
    {
        "question": " 49.6年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.638099593987958
    },
    {
        "question": " 2290万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.797551416064991
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.07日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4115874748545143
    },
    {
        "question": " 454日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.5931937924863036
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.42日は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.670483121039343
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.44兆時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.216892650063794
    },
    {
        "question": " 736万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.486869278974221
    },
    {
        "question": " 5939時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.551898025623304
    },
    {
        "question": " 101万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.559889177177086
    },
    {
        "question": " 539時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.287864048307533
    },
    {
        "question": " 63.5億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.081965633584819
    },
    {
        "question": " 39.5億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.438625013458077
    },
    {
        "question": " 46.1万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.8856296018976977
    },
    {
        "question": " 363億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.0613344950103527
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.16億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.9749507407384987
    },
    {
        "question": " 68.3万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2781434358158883
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.84億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.806005614797019
    },
    {
        "question": " 337京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.02839737435898
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.74京msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.739697610642681
    },
    {
        "question": " 621兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.236473596362268
    },
    {
        "question": " 2192万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5627262413424945
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.3万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9188277581127156
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.01msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 3.9035679091191855
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.23垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.010314913423958
    },
    {
        "question": " 5垓usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.762504494955031
    },
    {
        "question": " 153兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.628051924196502
    },
    {
        "question": " 13兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.336607098490922
    },
    {
        "question": " 5350億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.728359475325266
    },
    {
        "question": " 4183億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.62153262031782
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.71usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 3.5696263385498384
    },
    {
        "question": " 5931京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.2742950215177915
    },
    {
        "question": " 836京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.985689109619546
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.7兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.3831706855970085
    },
    {
        "question": " 680億nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.054252436645095825
    },
    {
        "question": " 527京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.721515245914237
    },
    {
        "question": " 111億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.0467792152264686
    },
    {
        "question": " 330億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.5189929555816635
    },
    {
        "question": " 119年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.639560143275203
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.12年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.214202728244
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.2億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.558875576235685
    },
    {
        "question": " 193万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.666735056220406
    },
    {
        "question": " 360日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.714961604158303
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.78兆時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.308676596558605
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.68万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.50534905906831
    },
    {
        "question": " 1672時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.001413562895639
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.8万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.003553468845665
    },
    {
        "question": " 5197億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.995070478715062
    },
    {
        "question": " 483億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.5257293019815386
    },
    {
        "question": " 853万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.152724225229813
    },
    {
        "question": " 308分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.266741489321613
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.8億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6099355311839247
    },
    {
        "question": " 231億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.427804598045495
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.61兆秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.649752028271006
    },
    {
        "question": " 7045万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.069742027980642
    },
    {
        "question": " 143万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.156226666329221
    },
    {
        "question": " 43.7京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.142053422560495
    },
    {
        "question": " 80億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9665440498670117
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.14京msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.498956980935544
    },
    {
        "question": " 544億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.957060486438001
    },
    {
        "question": " 1328億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.123320661506874
    },
    {
        "question": " 8281msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.918084929264876
    },
    {
        "question": " 502兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2016249529259804
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.9兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3429127395161222
    },
    {
        "question": " 52.7京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.165111219549793
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.45京usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.610415423625925
    },
    {
        "question": " 194万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.2878539337857089
    },
    {
        "question": " 41.3万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 2.6154551160039685
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.15万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 7.498566982838756
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.19京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.004455825196165719
    },
    {
        "question": " 6893垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.901935098538138
    },
    {
        "question": " 1641兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6589101984995036
    },
    {
        "question": " 193兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.5079882476180346
    },
    {
        "question": " 1258億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.099623076776721
    },
    {
        "question": " 1261兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.100792195020585
    },
    {
        "question": " 67.8億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.830981490992427
    },
    {
        "question": " 172万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.798536406407692
    },
    {
        "question": " 18.5万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.209214365249043
    },
    {
        "question": " 40.5年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.32821070548492
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.44億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.825903356862474
    },
    {
        "question": " 7801日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.272358487426675
    },
    {
        "question": " 131万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.276821181232082
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.03億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.069247835225206
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.33万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.255954650112799
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.38億時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.919523071130246
    },
    {
        "question": " 4兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.881160207078406
    },
    {
        "question": " 23.7万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2165855950013134
    },
    {
        "question": " 196億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.51505923341675
    },
    {
        "question": " 45.6分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.4372857153648084
    },
    {
        "question": " 46.2億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1656056960591687
    },
    {
        "question": " 83.8万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9866715926703351
    },
    {
        "question": " 3039万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.926382649134811
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.12万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2692299513695313
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.56京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.160392714149763
    },
    {
        "question": " 56.9億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8184459408618359
    },
    {
        "question": " 37.9兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.022107747269072
    },
    {
        "question": " 72.9兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.08467581657405
    },
    {
        "question": " 67億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.825936538809893
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.26msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 3.100941632302675
    },
    {
        "question": " 56.1msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 7.748695278890362
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.24垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.851719508776685
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.04兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5457952670179576
    },
    {
        "question": " 930京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.412223398362833
    },
    {
        "question": " 56.7京usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.975236165321157
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.19兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.075435794594627
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.66億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.753175836834678
    },
    {
        "question": " 139usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 5.144206378533417
    },
    {
        "question": " 81.6垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.413110543016789
    },
    {
        "question": " 889兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0124845814754235
    },
    {
        "question": " 298垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.917740860862514
    },
    {
        "question": " 201京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.5261132674896745
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.4億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.21608178505054143
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.41兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.644826456261038
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.09兆nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.958548661457378
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.61万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.443826298586703
    },
    {
        "question": " 75.7万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.821357708136473
    },
    {
        "question": " 350億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.981617318085041
    },
    {
        "question": " 825万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.29645453223593
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.8万日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.38351364727129
    },
    {
        "question": " 92.6万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.0239903602060694
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.1万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.6649928692748013
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.1万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.27009459522527
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.94時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.151367995465148
    },
    {
        "question": " 315万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7781185836866389
    },
    {
        "question": " 50.3億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.5432385405465965
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.96億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.820082130127441
    },
    {
        "question": " 485兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.187367313896363
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.1兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.9145351395875405
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.82万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1266358247058572
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.33億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.344277196722084
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.44万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.157584415485535
    },
    {
        "question": " 1331兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.625418864546727
    },
    {
        "question": " 188兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.3376360061126435
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.28京msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.551016768423551
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.6億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.467967842513666
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.04億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.847453751039575
    },
    {
        "question": " 232msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 5.36481503588541
    },
    {
        "question": " 41兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.1138259970511224
    },
    {
        "question": " 148兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.233130642748666
    },
    {
        "question": " 492億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.135617022789961
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.14京usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.719204674015335
    },
    {
        "question": " 374億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.572492318811654
    },
    {
        "question": " 2464万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.3916662596739195
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.1万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 8.081668369275178
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.47垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.8943186866598136
    },
    {
        "question": " 301京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.541844706674429
    },
    {
        "question": " 1668京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.665777277075789
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.85兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9076447585457645
    },
    {
        "question": " 23億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.36250669541764147
    },
    {
        "question": " 5767兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.760966478864454
    },
    {
        "question": " 585万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 3.7673625577969805
    },
    {
        "question": " 205万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.873888138685652
    },
    {
        "question": " 175年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.1850854582356956
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.1億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.760545539715325
    },
    {
        "question": " 2674万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.807391121327798
    },
    {
        "question": " 521万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.875308881974902
    },
    {
        "question": " 21.7日は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.272951291170688
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.17億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.124126066107122
    },
    {
        "question": " 26.1万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.035797778486476
    },
    {
        "question": " 20.3時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.085756052530224
    },
    {
        "question": " 7877時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.452644144374948
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.5時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.685038978658005
    },
    {
        "question": " 1377万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4181966722250283
    },
    {
        "question": " 9432万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.8162586867100154
    },
    {
        "question": " 405万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.8289470904723695
    },
    {
        "question": " 461万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.442018413463972
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.46万分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.650794503062595
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.75分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.352016036551186
    },
    {
        "question": " 5505兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.241971248067916
    },
    {
        "question": " 965億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.047938374877382
    },
    {
        "question": " 4172秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.06401088888055573
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.4億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.367416006445735
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.97万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.696110852730214
    },
    {
        "question": " 154秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.18878448520862
    },
    {
        "question": " 1015億msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5075472881776932
    },
    {
        "question": " 1兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.06518159793586
    },
    {
        "question": " 2002兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.745219459616331
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.8億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.391521306283057
    },
    {
        "question": " 48.9億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.689553519655523
    },
    {
        "question": " 114msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 5.056691382987579
    },
    {
        "question": " 197兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7946597108179432
    },
    {
        "question": " 262京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.48245991073926
    },
    {
        "question": " 212京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.770543179059016
    },
    {
        "question": " 2562兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.630440003015
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.83兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.263594248803017
    },
    {
        "question": " 1495億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.174705262134845
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.2万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 7.71629170015785
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.46垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.891498534482032
    },
    {
        "question": " 518兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7774117404383984
    },
    {
        "question": " 1461兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.608392600318811
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.19兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.185358177645905
    },
    {
        "question": " 67億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8257815997249196
    },
    {
        "question": " 48.4兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.684929630742131
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.28万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 1.7979979548990377
    },
    {
        "question": " 23.3万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.930543332232043
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.76年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.187141923649099
    },
    {
        "question": " 67.3年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.548805489540249
    },
    {
        "question": " 35.2億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.984527883622237
    },
    {
        "question": " 10万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.380294714687223
    },
    {
        "question": " 164万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.372841904609135
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.92兆時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.053924479363014
    },
    {
        "question": " 133億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.744885159778175
    },
    {
        "question": " 7861時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.6736341715615435
    },
    {
        "question": " 902時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.511593216675301
    },
    {
        "question": " 343兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.81522674038069
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.19兆分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.55700795179509
    },
    {
        "question": " 3801億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.801786436845529
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.96万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.7305968053506335
    },
    {
        "question": " 26.7京秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.927082956313368
    },
    {
        "question": " 48.5兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.749045294061784
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.66兆秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.869304982477779
    },
    {
        "question": " 795万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.121952821554921
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.98秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.69720410169489
    },
    {
        "question": " 2886億msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9615463814462399
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.38京msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.986825401597855
    },
    {
        "question": " 148兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.6140901790817175
    },
    {
        "question": " 464兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.888356630534298
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.3億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.211333463325356
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.4万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.869265862433776
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.07京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8163491952268527
    },
    {
        "question": " 53.6京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.7930487366770205
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.7兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.47113382163718
    },
    {
        "question": " 241億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.603899594427853
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.66兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.752539820920739
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.56億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.551814700555488
    },
    {
        "question": " 1821usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.260330097482559
    },
    {
        "question": " 614京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2891851080884495
    },
    {
        "question": " 2464京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.455073617380748
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.7兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6659840064602918
    },
    {
        "question": " 31.3京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.71707611846011
    },
    {
        "question": " 576兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.760198095425173
    },
    {
        "question": " 1038万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.0161869082596164
    },
    {
        "question": " 5022万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.70088446109059
    },
    {
        "question": " 6327年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.363533139932722
    },
    {
        "question": " 22.1万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.782801252324363
    },
    {
        "question": " 21.9日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7210276712660084
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.55日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.564384487862747
    },
    {
        "question": " 490億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.7476495186635095
    },
    {
        "question": " 50.8時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.32553562604700326
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.9万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.727608206483421
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.53時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.104561368156798
    },
    {
        "question": " 368億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.845417460903306
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.46兆分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.38111878305175
    },
    {
        "question": " 24.9万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.6186978108134307
    },
    {
        "question": " 7450分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.650287880126344
    },
    {
        "question": " 1240分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.871705620410957
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.87京秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.495448760993368
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.5兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.124628634331772
    },
    {
        "question": " 40.5万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.050911922157291
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.99万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.066325074202989
    },
    {
        "question": " 121秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.08180503032219
    },
    {
        "question": " 206京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.814676677370373
    },
    {
        "question": " 78.1兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.9563737649049555
    },
    {
        "question": " 40.1兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.046982881924509
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.53兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.098708110900759
    },
    {
        "question": " 69.9億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.844696084723301
    },
    {
        "question": " 334万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.523341414411247
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.23垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.360175014780566
    },
    {
        "question": " 7843億usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9579647846025541
    },
    {
        "question": " 43.6兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.082714707135232
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.18京usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.723705249993795
    },
    {
        "question": " 1584万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1998863832594264
    },
    {
        "question": " 30.6万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 2.485720966775258
    },
    {
        "question": " 30.3usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 4.481170056539097
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.16e+05垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.835736435237553
    },
    {
        "question": " 174垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.304516575266723
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.69垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.873451119924885
    },
    {
        "question": " 407兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.8313457432824647
    },
    {
        "question": " 17兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.229556708724534
    },
    {
        "question": " 40.4兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.606806040127379
    },
    {
        "question": " 431億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.634862849978871
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.06年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.2560673633779045
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.22万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1549959962704754
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.63日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7998930735321472
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.3日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.343397319265851
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.34日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.459775815226113
    },
    {
        "question": " 28.1兆時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.50685853786623
    },
    {
        "question": " 893時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5706201074395254
    },
    {
        "question": " 57.7時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.317654695756657
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.98時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.3333337044779086
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.25時間は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.653160283448889
    },
    {
        "question": " 5073億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.984630763461373
    },
    {
        "question": " 943億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.816258704884163
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.46万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6135074379743073
    },
    {
        "question": " 1154分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.8402691242676745
    },
    {
        "question": " 34.8分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.3195485631644335
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.36億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6346261280502252
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.32億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.1839370161528766
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.45万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9810789280376242
    },
    {
        "question": " 1509秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4005123432833255
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.46万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.9760439481723635
    },
    {
        "question": " 88.6秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.947389740949933
    },
    {
        "question": " 49.2京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.19286953780078
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.68兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.6290925372122125
    },
    {
        "question": " 34.8兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.984701685526834
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.68兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.447566846894013
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.28兆msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.358710887144102
    },
    {
        "question": " 117万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.067452442637002
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.06msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.848900239975056
    },
    {
        "question": " 152京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.682864267437675
    },
    {
        "question": " 1593兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.2657664032164675
    },
    {
        "question": " 22.4兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.7935242057533882
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.49京usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.874460292979299
    },
    {
        "question": " 1512億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.179427210790314
    },
    {
        "question": " 8133億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.910267659453698
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.56万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 7.659326775872969
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.51京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.24221489352351022
    },
    {
        "question": " 665京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.886580618615071
    },
    {
        "question": " 2944兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.912580209346763
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.86京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.215777084807055
    },
    {
        "question": " 300兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.477594061714951
    },
    {
        "question": " 1174万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.0696297974810853
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.92兆nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.772147783146178
    },
    {
        "question": " 636万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.365808606754598
    },
    {
        "question": " 233年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.866131826525235
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.09億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.4733922901458785
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.71億日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.813881770057165
    },
    {
        "question": " 24.3日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.543727959630876
    },
    {
        "question": " 404億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.664134733948947
    },
    {
        "question": " 394時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2153218556429513
    },
    {
        "question": " 27.1時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.2113163178729085
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.94兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.230776585488147
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.22兆分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.929233691621087
    },
    {
        "question": " 229分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5815904288732543
    },
    {
        "question": " 74.8分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.6519838222910748
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.15万分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.396595938961395
    },
    {
        "question": " 40.1億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1039868321461643
    },
    {
        "question": " 43.6万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7031731607159419
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.33億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.170397904420541
    },
    {
        "question": " 1804万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.478092862274901
    },
    {
        "question": " 100万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.001463540937124
    },
    {
        "question": " 3949京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.097669116014035
    },
    {
        "question": " 11兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.104490028650379
    },
    {
        "question": " 1495兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.61829578291434
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.63億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.6415718886349735
    },
    {
        "question": " 1278msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.10639432510387681
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.83万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.765308256118391
    },
    {
        "question": " 8579兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4346389689595895
    },
    {
        "question": " 134兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.1914482715537607
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.08京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.932927009766699
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.48億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.15014454984103
    },
    {
        "question": " 313億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.49541768952381
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.65万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.8225924601711174
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.19usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 3.7914782438222905
    },
    {
        "question": " 453垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.157151571800722
    },
    {
        "question": " 6778京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.894581996062219
    },
    {
        "question": " 5211京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.160642481993599
    },
    {
        "question": " 54.2京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.95565960428581
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.21兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.624732009044939
    },
    {
        "question": " 886兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.947389803927347
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.9万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 2.2269228840254787
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.4万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.72082475034402
    },
    {
        "question": " 36.1万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.499736885679722
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.27兆日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.54227227254631
    },
    {
        "question": " 568日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.1345444450454245
    },
    {
        "question": " 3332億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.580241443618241
    },
    {
        "question": " 50.4万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.322310683260526
    },
    {
        "question": " 323時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.286709877812327
    },
    {
        "question": " 7023時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.4027949777512
    },
    {
        "question": " 102時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.564184844027691
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.9兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.557130713526135
    },
    {
        "question": " 152万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.0242351575325954
    },
    {
        "question": " 274億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.66002443922724
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.48万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.948794441736821
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.22分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.863139264758766
    },
    {
        "question": " 20.9億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8213807755508538
    },
    {
        "question": " 4978万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.760533305492298
    },
    {
        "question": " 654万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.2589933703951877
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.84万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6747121557684816
    },
    {
        "question": " 552万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.742304241198093
    },
    {
        "question": " 7223京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.359917284802657
    },
    {
        "question": " 589兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.83365444090244
    },
    {
        "question": " 46.9兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.114424588061369
    },
    {
        "question": " 375兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.795556319414402
    },
    {
        "question": " 21.2億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.326612080087615
    },
    {
        "question": " 3935msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.594997560328339
    },
    {
        "question": " 4746msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.676350199656682
    },
    {
        "question": " 9551京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.481228884306141
    },
    {
        "question": " 69.5京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.905545194700612
    },
    {
        "question": " 773億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3317641092495947
    },
    {
        "question": " 1390兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.364728253349291
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.63兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.882664738201472
    },
    {
        "question": " 887万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.9478753804345903
    },
    {
        "question": " 202usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 5.305617087939138
    },
    {
        "question": " 1218垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.586736163539536
    },
    {
        "question": " 748兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9372138778069061
    },
    {
        "question": " 6132兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.2313015968580086
    },
    {
        "question": " 924京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.187342518774564
    },
    {
        "question": " 2956億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4706400104092783
    },
    {
        "question": " 1165億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.066254089908069
    },
    {
        "question": " 56.8億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.754096511275317
    },
    {
        "question": " 2044年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.87268880656035
    },
    {
        "question": " 19.4年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.229825475439775
    },
    {
        "question": " 46.8年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.169126735729748
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.63万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2589596435091597
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.79日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.1023324479938825
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.75万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.4970806897394664
    },
    {
        "question": " 130万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.733970447348577
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.43万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.4246773632421235
    },
    {
        "question": " 2484万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.674524116835745
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.34万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7626192230716875
    },
    {
        "question": " 1121万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.271520025007784
    },
    {
        "question": " 7191万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.6349563142706
    },
    {
        "question": " 654億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.316660559930539
    },
    {
        "question": " 263兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.484272331602691
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.86兆秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.900701079318846
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.1万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.266043107920563
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.09万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.036422417872377
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.52秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.742178561206845
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.6兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7043134326078369
    },
    {
        "question": " 406億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6719006693559
    },
    {
        "question": " 4449億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.091988243739935
    },
    {
        "question": " 84兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.145885106058078
    },
    {
        "question": " 5269msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7217218245358703
    },
    {
        "question": " 64.3msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.8081919112297715
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.8京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.3932124296844246
    },
    {
        "question": " 5336億usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7907153468373218
    },
    {
        "question": " 197億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7385732824065583
    },
    {
        "question": " 3181兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.724441261588973
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.49億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.17282123064954
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.21兆usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.344165297549576
    },
    {
        "question": " 6454京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.3110311804968573
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.79京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8955164815174186
    },
    {
        "question": " 6815京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.277163278294499
    },
    {
        "question": " 308京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.710053356941638
    },
    {
        "question": " 326兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.51331371871524
    },
    {
        "question": " 74.5兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.87202971677133
    },
    {
        "question": " 1331万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.124156643279591
    },
    {
        "question": " 28.5万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.01728422981622
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.36年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.745784154104188
    },
    {
        "question": " 685億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.27350139716469
    },
    {
        "question": " 24.9日は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.332492494956853
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.69兆時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.624424299540923
    },
    {
        "question": " 281億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.06902504331843
    },
    {
        "question": " 132時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.8977909087009643
    },
    {
        "question": " 263時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.976074299405301
    },
    {
        "question": " 129兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.388963975897063
    },
    {
        "question": " 5400万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.574033178038338
    },
    {
        "question": " 143万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.3777503395280535
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.52分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.708417445778646
    },
    {
        "question": " 24.9京秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.897903254708373
    },
    {
        "question": " 24.6億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.454267746585004
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.64億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.659640878927646
    },
    {
        "question": " 197億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.516309565057695
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.12万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.852175305552823
    },
    {
        "question": " 33京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.0203320245864385
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.7京msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.092873619466733
    },
    {
        "question": " 1486万msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6157375593015724
    },
    {
        "question": " 300億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.698359962397475
    },
    {
        "question": " 1434msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.15644766968640145
    },
    {
        "question": " 559msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 5.747797914760935
    },
    {
        "question": " 808京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.408557858603435
    },
    {
        "question": " 301兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.5415677735995943
    },
    {
        "question": " 4349兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.082132549311334
    },
    {
        "question": " 1734兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.4609196882459425
    },
    {
        "question": " 408万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6104931950503933
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.78兆usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.250807797809697
    },
    {
        "question": " 21.1万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 8.324907920111247
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.8垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.081446214616392
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.21京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.687648136296615
    },
    {
        "question": " 1528兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6279534073580137
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.23垓nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.312694417288967
    },
    {
        "question": " 165億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2186364880846756
    },
    {
        "question": " 39.9兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.600528246231347
    },
    {
        "question": " 2943万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.468764573343579
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.28万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.4801479908702735
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.78万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6885562544564903
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.69万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.607407815748616
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.52万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.339940930679596
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.92万日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.2188783235015
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.3日は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.052073538152264
    },
    {
        "question": " 9601時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.03981661985851481
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.88億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.208314652760884
    },
    {
        "question": " 20.3時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.863456851745278
    },
    {
        "question": " 50.4億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.9820034412340775
    },
    {
        "question": " 3734万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.413772846843347
    },
    {
        "question": " 4445億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.869723762012688
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.1万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.824613991279015
    },
    {
        "question": " 7648分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.661713746115506
    },
    {
        "question": " 5830億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.266873076362787
    },
    {
        "question": " 2545億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.469212403042138
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.61万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6512793296715436
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.65万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.158932365265865
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.76秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.677301830043228
    },
    {
        "question": " 677秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.830900126646828
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.55秒は何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.189056296147477
    },
    {
        "question": " 968京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.487024918948492
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.56京msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.614687984715394
    },
    {
        "question": " 683兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.278098008426081
    },
    {
        "question": " 7769万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.11220835336532
    },
    {
        "question": " 165万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.217721080918041
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.77msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 3.2468747587385183
    },
    {
        "question": " 248msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 8.394533225061856
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.1京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.5039205674026497
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.1兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9720784417539672
    },
    {
        "question": " 1087億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.480013133042447
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.61億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1034315188839217
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.46億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6490408158031475
    },
    {
        "question": " 173万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.2385293241134585
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.63万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 7.420451488886997
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.955e+06垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.97179077922847
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.3京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.11491986376754
    },
    {
        "question": " 3133京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.939713497920722
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.29京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.580806181062616
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.4兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.380013771025978
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.05兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.484948952402539
    },
    {
        "question": " 1272万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.104392010662455
    },
    {
        "question": " 2122万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.889126447258858
    },
    {
        "question": " 3924億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.031392794909452
    },
    {
        "question": " 174日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.619710754441522
    },
    {
        "question": " 69.4万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.999815589253402
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.74万日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.612508920995918
    },
    {
        "question": " 616億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.846759004698977
    },
    {
        "question": " 735時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4859916383183736
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.46時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.169934790281043
    },
    {
        "question": " 159万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.4794093450823711
    },
    {
        "question": " 19.6万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1328827399505257
    },
    {
        "question": " 3589分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.776768419113396
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.09万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.815684309927427
    },
    {
        "question": " 5032万秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.20290884587996105
    },
    {
        "question": " 52.1万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7800655449834148
    },
    {
        "question": " 169万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6722100352654623
    },
    {
        "question": " 143億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.37800198458405
    },
    {
        "question": " 447万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.65048182464741
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.78京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.391962400731223
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.71億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.633394884724443
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.6兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.506490011326841
    },
    {
        "question": " 721億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.07976011467051
    },
    {
        "question": " 74.6億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.87263332397119
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.67万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.884669046682995
    },
    {
        "question": " 1895兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7788807289350672
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.02京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.843038149280602
    },
    {
        "question": " 66京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.263465242946873
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.8億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4722597637385937
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.16兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.0660926221493945
    },
    {
        "question": " 106億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.02474676778815
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.52usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 3.5471552297876174
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.03e+06垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.514118449098687
    },
    {
        "question": " 84垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.987717936471338
    },
    {
        "question": " 7716兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.3310904266401664
    },
    {
        "question": " 517兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.9350933507849097
    },
    {
        "question": " 1527兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.183831802585048
    },
    {
        "question": " 128万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 0.10733445042218293
    },
    {
        "question": " 6169nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 0.7902354462889782
    },
    {
        "question": " 27.2年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.934071337887667
    },
    {
        "question": " 142億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.591497411408686
    },
    {
        "question": " 117万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.448400791321666
    },
    {
        "question": " 16万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.36151051590256
    },
    {
        "question": " 24.7万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4505225068188965
    },
    {
        "question": " 94.7億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.596117538737007
    },
    {
        "question": " 143万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.933683219687828
    },
    {
        "question": " 557時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.302444440286039
    },
    {
        "question": " 80.4兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.184779912947
    },
    {
        "question": " 1358万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.9744830744170487
    },
    {
        "question": " 3946分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.817978844910385
    },
    {
        "question": " 38.4分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.3621434247498625
    },
    {
        "question": " 38.3億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.0848145948813124
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.56億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.722534540740422
    },
    {
        "question": " 9800秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.4349274705334605
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.12万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7163379319197944
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.82兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9508480001963158
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.9億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.102375176802437
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.01億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.447429729313351
    },
    {
        "question": " 103万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2344860168640803
    },
    {
        "question": " 6201億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.792473282499124
    },
    {
        "question": " 8847msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.946776828694281
    },
    {
        "question": " 701msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 8.845534263681028
    },
    {
        "question": " 1908京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.7817986930774445
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.47京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.455337709098872
    },
    {
        "question": " 2372億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8188137431952567
    },
    {
        "question": " 765兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.105289015324346
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.23兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.62628930537921
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.54兆usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.187175723828096
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.41万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 7.644120467967628
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.02e+06垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.50990438045191
    },
    {
        "question": " 4366兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.703595768481574
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.8京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.516525464083092
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.95垓nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.692245726739216
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.5京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.022150895908473
    },
    {
        "question": " 9556兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.980257697906353
    },
    {
        "question": " 2483nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 0.3949191746856384
    },
    {
        "question": " 8686万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.376488604952412
    },
    {
        "question": " 451日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.034291491249439
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.21万日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.280722757631237
    },
    {
        "question": " 30兆時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.53433053168189
    },
    {
        "question": " 9265万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.586654967012743
    },
    {
        "question": " 293兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.745614607482743
    },
    {
        "question": " 461億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.505471949797667
    },
    {
        "question": " 928分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.189594025629357
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.9分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.815343896557175
    },
    {
        "question": " 8271万秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.4187253280702097
    },
    {
        "question": " 226万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4185283295964113
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.45万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1800210004057177
    },
    {
        "question": " 93.6億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.193263566073194
    },
    {
        "question": " 39.6京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.0986931335086725
    },
    {
        "question": " 77.6億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9535257912605641
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.8億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8902744473217359
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.56億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.038440148772585
    },
    {
        "question": " 8289万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.918504719543569
    },
    {
        "question": " 432兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1371255559624682
    },
    {
        "question": " 3546兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.613283748648996
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.23京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.791959081236017
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.3億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2739127802108985
    },
    {
        "question": " 6635兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.821869349629091
    },
    {
        "question": " 1489usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 0.17296440168390936
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.81万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 7.892782189139743
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.45垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.66317881708789
    },
    {
        "question": " 377垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.6397987478329
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.17垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.944092989826299
    },
    {
        "question": " 44.4京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.869312980374116
    },
    {
        "question": " 9771億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.989938712500755
    },
    {
        "question": " 94.1兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.973380912019168
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.34万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 1.9214035027821252
    },
    {
        "question": " 827年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.479584909801202
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.6万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.042767356527541
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.03年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.422055229722773
    },
    {
        "question": " 4066億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.046870375914246
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.3万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.535815049814041
    },
    {
        "question": " 221万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.503371494286624
    },
    {
        "question": " 82.8日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.8544711294669805
    },
    {
        "question": " 6416億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.864760953132814
    },
    {
        "question": " 1312万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.737716111368374
    },
    {
        "question": " 38.6時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.142958561954365
    },
    {
        "question": " 1442万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4382774595896897
    },
    {
        "question": " 32.2億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.349127326153685
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.01億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.824986005134228
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.32万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.143025947548329
    },
    {
        "question": " 50.4分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.480748928171574
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.11分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.486687870623152
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.64京秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.437548461435782
    },
    {
        "question": " 789兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.960402888341536
    },
    {
        "question": " 720億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.301057760701319
    },
    {
        "question": " 814億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.132417092655597
    },
    {
        "question": " 2120兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.827587589035904
    },
    {
        "question": " 119兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.13834809835268
    },
    {
        "question": " 164億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.658971909106702
    },
    {
        "question": " 169万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4485765634166714
    },
    {
        "question": " 7322万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.864614884014414
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.88msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 3.4600705968447834
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.06垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.527773709867933
    },
    {
        "question": " 29.6兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5342412712771645
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.61京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.426578685648488
    },
    {
        "question": " 41.5兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.839685194548672
    },
    {
        "question": " 435兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.63807350342
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.94兆usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.467981190667924
    },
    {
        "question": " 265usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 5.423438590546094
    },
    {
        "question": " 1415垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.6520616100216055
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.9京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.2072030517056938
    },
    {
        "question": " 2970京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.916384162001785
    },
    {
        "question": " 3957億nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8191983827179161
    },
    {
        "question": " 4007兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.602832077938111
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.91兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.280258187040497
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.45兆nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.388877883683264
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.95億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.727343455771799
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.6万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.480410290277037
    },
    {
        "question": " 2480万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.4519562683323213
    },
    {
        "question": " 22.2億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.965306291653765
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.26兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.075986610670864
    },
    {
        "question": " 6149億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.630459257435758
    },
    {
        "question": " 456分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8805367952494603
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.7万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.914090255115646
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.86兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.770894036604092
    },
    {
        "question": " 99.8万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0627243054901403
    },
    {
        "question": " 33.5億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.969342783762794
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.01億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.227396672966922
    },
    {
        "question": " 198秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.295983323348561
    },
    {
        "question": " 1360秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.133423833332843
    },
    {
        "question": " 9114兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.460924184061505
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.5兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.162075112274309
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.61億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3786648222089326
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.42億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.955900495238337
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.22万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0853307122671396
    },
    {
        "question": " 314京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.998717752155185
    },
    {
        "question": " 487京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.750743968197881
    },
    {
        "question": " 6762兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.273758521972575
    },
    {
        "question": " 39.7京usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.82094870113341
    },
    {
        "question": " 602億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.779560283358418
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.9億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.277845257464321
    },
    {
        "question": " 6200usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.792402042065879
    },
    {
        "question": " 127垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.6044523677967595
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.85京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.518935649341123
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.09垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.763834232309339
    },
    {
        "question": " 1538億nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.4087420742764747
    },
    {
        "question": " 2062億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3141881450900748
    },
    {
        "question": " 112兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.04893808656243
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.74億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 5.67571274954184
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.8年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.5534041648943027
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.32万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.668638100130536
    },
    {
        "question": " 767万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.322586473244774
    },
    {
        "question": " 177万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.627207134389805
    },
    {
        "question": " 41.3日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.552450651241104
    },
    {
        "question": " 5892億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.827722551290134
    },
    {
        "question": " 417万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.239834787853783
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.15時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.489915190097365
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.42時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.363544475828867
    },
    {
        "question": " 106時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.58349188938868
    },
    {
        "question": " 246万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.669967613650515
    },
    {
        "question": " 318万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.3445225200536477
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.2万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.4308291939336923
    },
    {
        "question": " 2億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8018980101785889
    },
    {
        "question": " 202万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.367875064446833
    },
    {
        "question": " 3159万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.9433003509672093
    },
    {
        "question": " 33.6万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.748551932074593
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.19万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.076963614483088
    },
    {
        "question": " 206京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.815974752807406
    },
    {
        "question": " 7437億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.934874920675556
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.8億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5506760938963167
    },
    {
        "question": " 286兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.678631943436107
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.21万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0820962283981395
    },
    {
        "question": " 87.5万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.94208789128826
    },
    {
        "question": " 2539垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.905790265091143
    },
    {
        "question": " 212兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.3892211364176275
    },
    {
        "question": " 109京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.48014440667718
    },
    {
        "question": " 4947兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.916193714318847
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.77兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.890183890272835
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.38兆usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.7304739302919
    },
    {
        "question": " 2123usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.327024022540995
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.246e+04垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.012537624747338
    },
    {
        "question": " 1167京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.130504292039789
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.72兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.20114657085352872
    },
    {
        "question": " 2327億nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.588736814558144
    },
    {
        "question": " 269京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.430300960032596
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.53兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.8151813989323795
    },
    {
        "question": " 43.5万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 2.638885843212706
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.3万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.799863511247253
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.39万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.673958665209033
    },
    {
        "question": " 816年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.632462044054567
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.53年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.154925213476517
    },
    {
        "question": " 27.9万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8831480078128746
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.05万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.692709143676547
    },
    {
        "question": " 47.5万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.834865227913806
    },
    {
        "question": " 32.5億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.57000136901763
    },
    {
        "question": " 623時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4145297354075648
    },
    {
        "question": " 1487万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.950490792740244
    },
    {
        "question": " 31.5億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.7779068205277913
    },
    {
        "question": " 2187分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.18156538731779137
    },
    {
        "question": " 163分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.4348877339739088
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.96分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.474044062635785
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.31兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.619774893897647
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.05億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.547129266551469
    },
    {
        "question": " 25.1兆秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.843031598889992
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.6万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.4146225851102363
    },
    {
        "question": " 1698秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.229954943501646
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.3秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.113451304217644
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.38秒は何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.139956167353217
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.7兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3272357349785566
    },
    {
        "question": " 49京msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.753862108962629
    },
    {
        "question": " 2554億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.850923035218219
    },
    {
        "question": " 587万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9905932236250168
    },
    {
        "question": " 2056msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.3131206930876884
    },
    {
        "question": " 21.7万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.337141866907743
    },
    {
        "question": " 3258京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.014149576199048
    },
    {
        "question": " 3071京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.550841836698682
    },
    {
        "question": " 37.2京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.013960626196898
    },
    {
        "question": " 1946兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.511057000866408
    },
    {
        "question": " 8269億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.917469263954173
    },
    {
        "question": " 6919億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.840057921202087
    },
    {
        "question": " 1650usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.217493000182573
    },
    {
        "question": " 1209垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.583543697409237
    },
    {
        "question": " 28.7垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.520669173069603
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.45垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.981415979984341
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.38兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9524995052654737
    },
    {
        "question": " 2955億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4705867203541096
    },
    {
        "question": " 157兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.196761943109797
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.54兆nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.549489223366262
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.1年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.6057540589463075
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.2年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.177034768703334
    },
    {
        "question": " 3852年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.306341911832583
    },
    {
        "question": " 2353万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.809268494471008
    },
    {
        "question": " 61.7日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.1705840189381074
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.98万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.35306532157579507
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.3億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.6743956789806855
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.74時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6666428342522264
    },
    {
        "question": " 4412兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.923993670234148
    },
    {
        "question": " 62万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6341161759915313
    },
    {
        "question": " 480万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.903223428559876
    },
    {
        "question": " 6487万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.590212269091426
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.65億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1682351249217882
    },
    {
        "question": " 758万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9429802125535711
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.61兆秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.650796322887427
    },
    {
        "question": " 6078秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.0056271478170262
    },
    {
        "question": " 3188秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.503515523132245
    },
    {
        "question": " 5509億msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2423048394646352
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.57兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.723645719443958
    },
    {
        "question": " 39.3億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.038279608112233
    },
    {
        "question": " 28.4兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.674744234698155
    },
    {
        "question": " 2363万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.373497005849124
    },
    {
        "question": " 422msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 5.6249820628071046
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.1垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.544166711531921
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.58垓usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.61719972250586
    },
    {
        "question": " 4367兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.083905273088222
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.36億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7478088547965445
    },
    {
        "question": " 2474兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.393473560477277
    },
    {
        "question": " 16万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 2.203643060050562
    },
    {
        "question": " 25.8usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 4.411004260070505
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.057e+05垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.525313090279313
    },
    {
        "question": " 1069京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.092315788353816
    },
    {
        "question": " 6346兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.2461693235778255
    },
    {
        "question": " 2751京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.661367498736048
    },
    {
        "question": " 5960兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.775246711749078
    },
    {
        "question": " 443億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.646631913739866
    },
    {
        "question": " 18.1万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 2.2582271415877098
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.19年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6381694760209538
    },
    {
        "question": " 64.5年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.308287674711757
    },
    {
        "question": " 745億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.30989996715413
    },
    {
        "question": " 2609日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.7967469280921335
    },
    {
        "question": " 8783万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.001145352448772
    },
    {
        "question": " 1612億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.82717203795104
    },
    {
        "question": " 877万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.720920721057428
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.18万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.894330645784409
    },
    {
        "question": " 1348時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.68598971458603
    },
    {
        "question": " 8488億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.2081608456430395
    },
    {
        "question": " 3628万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.401335965065339
    },
    {
        "question": " 223分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5698927914813023
    },
    {
        "question": " 12万分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.85554469589411
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.7京秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.731066303395169
    },
    {
        "question": " 3870億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.651256138288657
    },
    {
        "question": " 1527億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.627513088766208
    },
    {
        "question": " 413万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.837361237783597
    },
    {
        "question": " 451万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.654528520559518
    },
    {
        "question": " 715兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.355717588171277
    },
    {
        "question": " 37.1億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6326341801642097
    },
    {
        "question": " 26.9兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.873119969565638
    },
    {
        "question": " 4906億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.91260494309619
    },
    {
        "question": " 6591msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8189202271564466
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.05msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 3.021490866707497
    },
    {
        "question": " 1642垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.716598652749234
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.74垓usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.501251869937093
    },
    {
        "question": " 1013京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.449104388737341
    },
    {
        "question": " 2067億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.537111268193663
    },
    {
        "question": " 2071兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.31621148961651
    },
    {
        "question": " 89.5万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 2.9517710383497486
    },
    {
        "question": " 684万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.834804366585466
    },
    {
        "question": " 20.5垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.813753616209659
    },
    {
        "question": " 3665京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.627592573447835
    },
    {
        "question": " 298垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.917902004369992
    },
    {
        "question": " 3007億nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7000152266185011
    },
    {
        "question": " 18.5億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.26605775998491454
    },
    {
        "question": " 124兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.09210182531452
    },
    {
        "question": " 86.6万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 2.9377063277284297
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.95万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.853325353548519
    },
    {
        "question": " 359年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.4980394955875
    },
    {
        "question": " 21.8年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.060000281666151
    },
    {
        "question": " 39.6年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.096469530175899
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.08万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2215264855709704
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.15万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.439952575135498
    },
    {
        "question": " 643万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.96660419375292
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.66万日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.361644002117304
    },
    {
        "question": " 544万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7930180442885497
    },
    {
        "question": " 5176時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.333775730855444
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.39万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.308236904108457
    },
    {
        "question": " 77.1時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.443079428894118
    },
    {
        "question": " 1221億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.366114603740168
    },
    {
        "question": " 5066億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.546290133885623
    },
    {
        "question": " 107万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.249536652474232
    },
    {
        "question": " 3529万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.325786097028972
    },
    {
        "question": " 472分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.451964169509107
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.55兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.051158356040014
    },
    {
        "question": " 37.1万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.632930892075998
    },
    {
        "question": " 1342万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.5713243905427783
    },
    {
        "question": " 130億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.335848760687536
    },
    {
        "question": " 638秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.804844076141173
    },
    {
        "question": " 5753秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.759909217233536
    },
    {
        "question": " 577億msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.26265434408452193
    },
    {
        "question": " 10億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0655756396389693
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.65兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.380913324095339
    },
    {
        "question": " 3123万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7164281666426993
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.5万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.021180928971553
    },
    {
        "question": " 3051垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.985581654574124
    },
    {
        "question": " 265兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.486396586156788
    },
    {
        "question": " 91兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.402858679162371
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.03億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9232862203060743
    },
    {
        "question": " 623兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.794510113924991
    },
    {
        "question": " 3069usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 0.4869359522439176
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.66usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 3.2194045615180156
    },
    {
        "question": " 28.1垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.949429789219424
    },
    {
        "question": " 320垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.569063249595763
    },
    {
        "question": " 25.2京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.845811873979606
    },
    {
        "question": " 2129兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.550044207978477
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.33兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.920535739337417
    },
    {
        "question": " 399万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 0.6006096358838509
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.7万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 2.1049917715149116
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.96万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.463260702597684
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.08年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.6484588051663565
    },
    {
        "question": " 113年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.77388896986017
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.22万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7832341685202058
    },
    {
        "question": " 1019日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.388556804034671
    },
    {
        "question": " 309億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.547577045308336
    },
    {
        "question": " 2387億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.997687445566147
    },
    {
        "question": " 1626時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.989313579745623
    },
    {
        "question": " 503時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.257613775090922
    },
    {
        "question": " 70.1万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.12505057112756512
    },
    {
        "question": " 1245万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.93670645784699
    },
    {
        "question": " 238分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5991275669828677
    },
    {
        "question": " 3739分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.350928354649974
    },
    {
        "question": " 6818分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.611830306281314
    },
    {
        "question": " 67.7兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.3319271830262185
    },
    {
        "question": " 1221億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.150161219779617
    },
    {
        "question": " 1715億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.677929431400928
    },
    {
        "question": " 3427億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.756773745113454
    },
    {
        "question": " 682秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.833911832109747
    },
    {
        "question": " 142京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.654792475342638
    },
    {
        "question": " 33.2億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5849864285684667
    },
    {
        "question": " 47.5兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.120063303778441
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.35億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.5935672189571233
    },
    {
        "question": " 810億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.908365754654357
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.89msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 3.2766101668816825
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.4msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 7.215034988863092
    },
    {
        "question": " 2549京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.907534000290359
    },
    {
        "question": " 21.4京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.392945321867711
    },
    {
        "question": " 394京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.039132394807586
    },
    {
        "question": " 316兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.7212699004402
    },
    {
        "question": " 127万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.10250112328839767
    },
    {
        "question": " 53.5万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 2.728207398531628
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.01usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 3.005371467509809
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.559e+05垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.052568423333447
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.85京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3312398096982676
    },
    {
        "question": " 22.1京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.788412344275567
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.4京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.601454532252099
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.07兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.9067301577428513
    },
    {
        "question": " 1093万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.0387023585961563
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.28万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 1.3575120140095687
    },
    {
        "question": " 3603年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.1190149893324755
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.78万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.886021778427907
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.63兆日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.648853985783363
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.8日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.451328946948186
    },
    {
        "question": " 20.9日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.2569475699843045
    },
    {
        "question": " 134億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.184334601231194
    },
    {
        "question": " 637万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.4238773061280945
    },
    {
        "question": " 40.1万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.381615800898853
    },
    {
        "question": " 6978万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.123089366378581
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.46兆分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.380323585611087
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.49万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.961429121561032
    },
    {
        "question": " 421万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.401932129691327
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.05億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9859322625106803
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.66億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.887127897832283
    },
    {
        "question": " 49.4万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1376980364547107
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.93万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.0625578142800656
    },
    {
        "question": " 423万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.626698174481662
    },
    {
        "question": " 27.6秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.440912765109782
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.9京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.779281937098783
    },
    {
        "question": " 6942億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.904990634385629
    },
    {
        "question": " 267億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.8700533902130285
    },
    {
        "question": " 120兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.299303074052487
    },
    {
        "question": " 197億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.29447023183729
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.31msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 3.364402721353782
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.55垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.6914104500915474
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.85京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.33046413490559
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.41京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.594274222712562
    },
    {
        "question": " 8565兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.154565898446082
    },
    {
        "question": " 2647億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.422830109815808
    },
    {
        "question": " 8592万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.934106831972605
    },
    {
        "question": " 66.2万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 8.820723890631797
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.029e+04垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.982496936122526
    },
    {
        "question": " 1062兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0898071861891045
    },
    {
        "question": " 38.5垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.029135215368703
    },
    {
        "question": " 352兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.7678847961305264
    },
    {
        "question": " 2302兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.362072411435852
    },
    {
        "question": " 773兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.887964828989293
    },
    {
        "question": " 1780nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 0.2503795930099195
    },
    {
        "question": " 66.6年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.765808041834408
    },
    {
        "question": " 71.2年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.572944368273058
    },
    {
        "question": " 104年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.51652288964137
    },
    {
        "question": " 310億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.929189324227615
    },
    {
        "question": " 999日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.379740797372786
    },
    {
        "question": " 45.6日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.817691885455454
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.37兆時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.193726177655915
    },
    {
        "question": " 577時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3810409191028772
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.06万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.482626416931651
    },
    {
        "question": " 543兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.014523649865303
    },
    {
        "question": " 21.9億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.183022114052496
    },
    {
        "question": " 9834分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2145640328548657
    },
    {
        "question": " 1667万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.000034436297545
    },
    {
        "question": " 839分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.701877029149065
    },
    {
        "question": " 130分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.893111118775268
    },
    {
        "question": " 8413兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.426163689364163
    },
    {
        "question": " 516億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.776196672176236
    },
    {
        "question": " 44.8万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.0948548749558507
    },
    {
        "question": " 26.8億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.649373578113234
    },
    {
        "question": " 160万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.203054922270198
    },
    {
        "question": " 158京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.699011355496335
    },
    {
        "question": " 67.8京msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.894541416251407
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.73兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.681784431601187
    },
    {
        "question": " 1082万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2561726250076974
    },
    {
        "question": " 3515億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.545942239162411
    },
    {
        "question": " 588兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.270331562181577
    },
    {
        "question": " 309兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.553822405084727
    },
    {
        "question": " 1184京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.516929547679045
    },
    {
        "question": " 347兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.762115403480823
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.5兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.129993496583811
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.91万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.4637498073699406
    },
    {
        "question": " 31.3万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 8.495048786949809
    },
    {
        "question": " 25.9垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.91489299275136
    },
    {
        "question": " 1707垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.295734002942154
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.07京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.47413809721139
    },
    {
        "question": " 143兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.376844825746963
    },
    {
        "question": " 1277兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.106335238716175
    },
    {
        "question": " 780兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.891820170550762
    },
    {
        "question": " 148万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 3.1697747621473416
    },
    {
        "question": " 160年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.766612962958493
    },
    {
        "question": " 4281年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.5740961507459525
    },
    {
        "question": " 9400年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.693797632906566
    },
    {
        "question": " 1596万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.640758953495192
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.12億日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.70594040349037
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.6万日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.599024659804225
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.05億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.079979540718245
    },
    {
        "question": " 101万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.6233612402349085
    },
    {
        "question": " 4178時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.399168240726385
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.62時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.973930178290113
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.84兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.732268681353792
    },
    {
        "question": " 8910億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.791529602571742
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.15億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.719645194661535
    },
    {
        "question": " 76.3万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.660727046838939
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.6万分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.525996790049797
    },
    {
        "question": " 27.8分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.222418501332571
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.74京秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.93960958362403
    },
    {
        "question": " 447兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.713656056729604
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.4億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.087261038799733
    },
    {
        "question": " 285秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6764231102931617
    },
    {
        "question": " 5115秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.708880927892489
    },
    {
        "question": " 6529億msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3160352284141719
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.37京msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.437426839988746
    },
    {
        "question": " 1257万msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5429585013880789
    },
    {
        "question": " 9036万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.177810227742067
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.4億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.532066098639419
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.3msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 7.211201673722336
    },
    {
        "question": " 6700兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3272910234062927
    },
    {
        "question": " 55.6兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.808770679333824
    },
    {
        "question": " 87.7億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.38653254157341
    },
    {
        "question": " 1426億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.3759900284656474
    },
    {
        "question": " 64.3兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.808524429664824
    },
    {
        "question": " 88.9万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 2.948717345574824
    },
    {
        "question": " 96.6usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 4.98477544293047
    },
    {
        "question": " 3546垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.05096675149422
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.19垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.138023247078933
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.3兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.30702358111548644
    },
    {
        "question": " 446兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.8716380746089585
    },
    {
        "question": " 29.5億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.4699690389107103
    },
    {
        "question": " 192兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.283925974338821
    },
    {
        "question": " 5277億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.722423860721655
    },
    {
        "question": " 282年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.012653240635213
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.17万年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.78834980466732
    },
    {
        "question": " 63.7万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.241937761785892
    },
    {
        "question": " 83.4万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9786705866932763
    },
    {
        "question": " 33.6時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.1463629900170227
    },
    {
        "question": " 5911時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.327976373291742
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.33時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.192654564043504
    },
    {
        "question": " 3222兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.787434010195744
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.57兆分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.587470603243249
    },
    {
        "question": " 1304億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.337110427044145
    },
    {
        "question": " 1944分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.066758664833275
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.96分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.070817895835026
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.37億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4239400612544106
    },
    {
        "question": " 45万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7169094611426929
    },
    {
        "question": " 1280億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.55091713736995
    },
    {
        "question": " 46.2万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.886588093202874
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.83万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.261732247906365
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.74京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.329825959840307
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.01京msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.366752363555964
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.36億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5756920648912487
    },
    {
        "question": " 30万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6984745824930871
    },
    {
        "question": " 124億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.093013978704745
    },
    {
        "question": " 744msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 5.871306042079141
    },
    {
        "question": " 2374京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.876742245750193
    },
    {
        "question": " 1323京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.184960476436416
    },
    {
        "question": " 1047兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.463581713383555
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.51兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.621498440674965
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.01兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.002342507412974
    },
    {
        "question": " 16万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 2.2047975907579764
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.9usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 4.142896879793188
    },
    {
        "question": " 68.7京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3382095900780644
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.75垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.503067001353369
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.53京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.6287644980946387
    },
    {
        "question": " 733京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.086677263279924
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.48京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.738415144186408
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.7億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.166739650713838
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.16万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 1.0648387980969498
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.76万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8781130097599352
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.16日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8792942874996532
    },
    {
        "question": " 282億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.507810136698845
    },
    {
        "question": " 4993万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.318150042439246
    },
    {
        "question": " 36.6時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.3414260972313237
    },
    {
        "question": " 626億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.075908211081663
    },
    {
        "question": " 9760万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.8311216722533645
    },
    {
        "question": " 369分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.788556014402646
    },
    {
        "question": " 2278万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.135613259000662
    },
    {
        "question": " 23.9兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.878989962157553
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.4億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.120572602175015
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.8兆秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.612647615941452
    },
    {
        "question": " 299万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.697783501830316
    },
    {
        "question": " 317秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.501555865570902
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.18秒は何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.620692651051524
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.67京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.723712701149916
    },
    {
        "question": " 56.3京msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.8137884660919
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.84兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.436735232034552
    },
    {
        "question": " 31.9万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7262526062052688
    },
    {
        "question": " 477億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.678369374611148
    },
    {
        "question": " 23.9msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 7.377507124443018
    },
    {
        "question": " 20.3垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.809104165206295
    },
    {
        "question": " 3642億usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6248848492920334
    },
    {
        "question": " 4778億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.122977429905264
    },
    {
        "question": " 33.4億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.746097800237073
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.8兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.199796838559566
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.46億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.3910194699700575
    },
    {
        "question": " 12万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 8.079453113216198
    },
    {
        "question": " 163京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7144057263647727
    },
    {
        "question": " 207垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.379304597035524
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.89兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.3927041178627677
    },
    {
        "question": " 4888京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.910938974545369
    },
    {
        "question": " 68.8兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.837719521183112
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.67兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.426538837415706
    },
    {
        "question": " 2809nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 0.44858428768820957
    },
    {
        "question": " 8858億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.38501394562054
    },
    {
        "question": " 487日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.845883967786714
    },
    {
        "question": " 1790万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.3103315838812755
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.16億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.332632513686125
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.82万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.360371693342598
    },
    {
        "question": " 1320時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.676899251585664
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.94兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.972683721678114
    },
    {
        "question": " 1767万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.08884624488403
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.37億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.597260213520757
    },
    {
        "question": " 245万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.166838531080835
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.3万分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.93250376069885
    },
    {
        "question": " 38.5兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.08671806204695
    },
    {
        "question": " 12万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.1410606047385088
    },
    {
        "question": " 2158万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.7776673129658933
    },
    {
        "question": " 162秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.4310642436385914
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.01万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.478066916670878
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.1兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9926477396001363
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.4兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.795667284056825
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.28億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.959716259573775
    },
    {
        "question": " 323億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.731659346476698
    },
    {
        "question": " 155億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.191716664467598
    },
    {
        "question": " 1703垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.732445206426792
    },
    {
        "question": " 31.7京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.563946838496618
    },
    {
        "question": " 820億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3572731371791014
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.61兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.4276987700290285
    },
    {
        "question": " 249兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.395366082110687
    },
    {
        "question": " 90.4億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.95607604306659
    },
    {
        "question": " 59.8京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2776377598216981
    },
    {
        "question": " 6748垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.89267074345615
    },
    {
        "question": " 29.3京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.9112493504699675
    },
    {
        "question": " 87.6京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.164213817377231
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.56京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.408049084898657
    },
    {
        "question": " 1415兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.150735314741688
    },
    {
        "question": " 3166億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.500579151077636
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.62年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7707598942404665
    },
    {
        "question": " 366年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.505913996267281
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.3年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.51220355222698
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.2億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.647830986857445
    },
    {
        "question": " 486日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.066622375817692
    },
    {
        "question": " 121万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.242771747945211
    },
    {
        "question": " 74万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9265630302189896
    },
    {
        "question": " 196万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.911350386633778
    },
    {
        "question": " 52.9時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.501978684467205
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.6兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.0275753209928045
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.9億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.0698864882744
    },
    {
        "question": " 2281億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.58006278703165
    },
    {
        "question": " 25.9分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.1908859144426427
    },
    {
        "question": " 37.1億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.070673032654564
    },
    {
        "question": " 3433万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.599157089222798
    },
    {
        "question": " 1903億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.72323407284972
    },
    {
        "question": " 27億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.653735879392211
    },
    {
        "question": " 367兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.0659256944872455
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.7京msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.294882876627346
    },
    {
        "question": " 1398兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.58911158367891
    },
    {
        "question": " 1795万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.475937248732818
    },
    {
        "question": " 862億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.935315248449123
    },
    {
        "question": " 827垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.418796808912829
    },
    {
        "question": " 6499京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.876334179558542
    },
    {
        "question": " 701京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.289142278516756
    },
    {
        "question": " 182億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.480897621846262
    },
    {
        "question": " 376万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5756510680904225
    },
    {
        "question": " 5560usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 0.7450698379620024
    },
    {
        "question": " 40.6usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 4.608587639949339
    },
    {
        "question": " 184垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.767003577662085
    },
    {
        "question": " 1739京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.30371618279212
    },
    {
        "question": " 24.7兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.837134544396787
    },
    {
        "question": " 2191京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.562462289448144
    },
    {
        "question": " 2京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.301341163756704
    },
    {
        "question": " 162万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 0.2106966041075431
    },
    {
        "question": " 1283万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.108065965331409
    },
    {
        "question": " 303年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.201731841591059
    },
    {
        "question": " 255億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.844586341515509
    },
    {
        "question": " 232万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.74630655162486
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.4日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.250487293563051
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.29日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.659616762304076
    },
    {
        "question": " 34.1億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.590024159473774
    },
    {
        "question": " 23.4億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.988274187795571
    },
    {
        "question": " 1760万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.023713470936531
    },
    {
        "question": " 477億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.958153804479435
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.3万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8947282164821544
    },
    {
        "question": " 2000億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.52279565707585
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.39億分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.91960075570811
    },
    {
        "question": " 246分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.169849155232756
    },
    {
        "question": " 287億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9586160121911065
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.25兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.160313335138751
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.89兆秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.1330190233301
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.41万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7548867933070023
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.5万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.216759631160325
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.59垓msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.702363764372665
    },
    {
        "question": " 594兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.8369490547468885
    },
    {
        "question": " 790万msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.3411564412081991
    },
    {
        "question": " 130兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.336738423874062
    },
    {
        "question": " 4710万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.672996595479619
    },
    {
        "question": " 568万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.754305057766132
    },
    {
        "question": " 27.7京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.9432308884412692
    },
    {
        "question": " 30.8兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.552548628780278
    },
    {
        "question": " 2448兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.832573622600395
    },
    {
        "question": " 32.3兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.7312279928271925
    },
    {
        "question": " 420億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.623454846277277
    },
    {
        "question": " 55.1万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 2.7412766553543877
    },
    {
        "question": " 2816usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.449573692449588
    },
    {
        "question": " 6932京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.3420410631486885
    },
    {
        "question": " 622垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.857221158985995
    },
    {
        "question": " 116兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5064228308482486
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.43垓nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.377267288371602
    },
    {
        "question": " 1535兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.186174894368362
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.1兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.177949542522773
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.41万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 1.8695471566368516
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.13万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.349507116993789
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.3万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.09743994868928
    },
    {
        "question": " 82.8万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.3557853885217237
    },
    {
        "question": " 414日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.997285814228589
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.28万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.789770054457548
    },
    {
        "question": " 624日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.731691614398021
    },
    {
        "question": " 22.5億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.408866998993088
    },
    {
        "question": " 1828時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8816782162193824
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.44万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.513917510990672
    },
    {
        "question": " 177万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.80392276282545
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.7時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.38234249505431
    },
    {
        "question": " 3724万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8503425444139532
    },
    {
        "question": " 8341億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.762845922725203
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.24億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.081621904879181
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.57分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9752679069444101
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.32京秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.622878248928878
    },
    {
        "question": " 7453万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9358220471832164
    },
    {
        "question": " 99億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.439234146505219
    },
    {
        "question": " 76.2万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.103691312414266
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.4京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.648018780985911
    },
    {
        "question": " 218兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.401889332772189
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.64京msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.865968199166948
    },
    {
        "question": " 9253万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.1881357530598042
    },
    {
        "question": " 1191msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.07574101530749333
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.6万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.203837117588319
    },
    {
        "question": " 2965兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9732892901949872
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.62垓usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.482148411242125
    },
    {
        "question": " 371億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0130186352681925
    },
    {
        "question": " 967兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.207253505085008
    },
    {
        "question": " 212億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.32560664556548
    },
    {
        "question": " 6831usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 0.8345153557197516
    },
    {
        "question": " 645usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 5.809600936338062
    },
    {
        "question": " 145京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6622568627321277
    },
    {
        "question": " 372京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.634352696866337
    },
    {
        "question": " 106京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.470334582609029
    },
    {
        "question": " 1050兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.243223147260564
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.7億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.028386104597213357
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.9兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.142789957290714
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.7万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 2.1354806671933346
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.23年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9103380466455264
    },
    {
        "question": " 8363年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.643030149004288
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.19億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.779029136393223
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.04万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.398876983612563
    },
    {
        "question": " 36.9万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.724932184105299
    },
    {
        "question": " 2306日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.299346668160407
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.61億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.264011035194166
    },
    {
        "question": " 182万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.880302213830739
    },
    {
        "question": " 220時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.119813875732836
    },
    {
        "question": " 6196時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.34843471937919
    },
    {
        "question": " 1200億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.3586783391103445
    },
    {
        "question": " 329万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.358409295759106
    },
    {
        "question": " 1394万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.366233400755226
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.7万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.973744704378248
    },
    {
        "question": " 4584分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.43938858242243
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.3億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.738900687775129
    },
    {
        "question": " 595兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.838249452843637
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.49万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3726827180572743
    },
    {
        "question": " 69万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.060634740878374
    },
    {
        "question": " 136秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.133870434688204
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.2兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.588500713359351
    },
    {
        "question": " 175兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.3053672151436135
    },
    {
        "question": " 1377万msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5824905183757745
    },
    {
        "question": " 133億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.344524035135526
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.11万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6134012625710081
    },
    {
        "question": " 6398兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3072142700356233
    },
    {
        "question": " 3534億usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6117476696793722
    },
    {
        "question": " 24.1兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.825001930070877
    },
    {
        "question": " 260兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.637195576376499
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.8兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.1397630262795495
    },
    {
        "question": " 1690万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.227967507532559
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.04万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 7.482306234910451
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.4京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6287406835242759
    },
    {
        "question": " 795垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.96377573532159
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.34垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.569576636395259
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.43京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.376571272090731
    },
    {
        "question": " 512兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.709446538879518
    },
    {
        "question": " 168兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.224935567265636
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.57兆nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.817547046928475
    },
    {
        "question": " 2126年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.889910947810656
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.36年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.077519424113811
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.8年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.753394301945138
    },
    {
        "question": " 144万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.5975088094535046
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.38日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5211138177891659
    },
    {
        "question": " 166万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.276319171265265
    },
    {
        "question": " 46.7時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.28904945228373724
    },
    {
        "question": " 215万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.111003228077296
    },
    {
        "question": " 285時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.010769140504978
    },
    {
        "question": " 8702万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2189473196951983
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.3兆分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.20253676835015
    },
    {
        "question": " 1739万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.462088321696733
    },
    {
        "question": " 6165分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.5680616281798425
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.02億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.347399107220708
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.71億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.6331978347349683
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.03億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.223754208255617
    },
    {
        "question": " 43.8万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.862987244540186
    },
    {
        "question": " 580秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.7635422044547004
    },
    {
        "question": " 28秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.446421134839555
    },
    {
        "question": " 372京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.071889533875797
    },
    {
        "question": " 6134兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.851257873076255
    },
    {
        "question": " 1947兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.733026190933126
    },
    {
        "question": " 71.5億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.076403338970856
    },
    {
        "question": " 2337億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.368580437119538
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.41msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.8699719611597505
    },
    {
        "question": " 6153兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2902694513305044
    },
    {
        "question": " 9561兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.044004862684176
    },
    {
        "question": " 350京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.988166940732015
    },
    {
        "question": " 42.2兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.847426005403689
    },
    {
        "question": " 18.2億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.2606895058545304
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.4兆usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.806515241072212
    },
    {
        "question": " 19.5京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.791891025078828
    },
    {
        "question": " 1089垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.100410299856973
    },
    {
        "question": " 7381兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.3118433615980933
    },
    {
        "question": " 2961兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.69336027269573
    },
    {
        "question": " 534兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.727856690644345
    },
    {
        "question": " 594億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.774073221935228
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.4兆nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.380250926733071
    },
    {
        "question": " 314年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.058656973508727
    },
    {
        "question": " 159年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.144711881101737
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.77万年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.968756411511988
    },
    {
        "question": " 1129億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.490220850734225
    },
    {
        "question": " 8448万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.30696691498073
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.8兆時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.636868829939152
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.03億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.524369832806394
    },
    {
        "question": " 161兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.486357568150796
    },
    {
        "question": " 191億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.12233632986531
    },
    {
        "question": " 2403分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6025986598248465
    },
    {
        "question": " 728万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.640169080506084
    },
    {
        "question": " 70.3分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.625232554764624
    },
    {
        "question": " 4786億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.181180540759671
    },
    {
        "question": " 3126億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.558527391778217
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.59兆秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.190816048880984
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.67万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.444143690471552
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.27秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.1036427455833584
    },
    {
        "question": " 1549秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.190168786510748
    },
    {
        "question": " 6486京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.313138476809144
    },
    {
        "question": " 351億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.609205746365962
    },
    {
        "question": " 20.1兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.747786287647034
    },
    {
        "question": " 102億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.229271968119411
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.57億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.196666589415292
    },
    {
        "question": " 1791msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.252994233507114
    },
    {
        "question": " 8165京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.41316067849788
    },
    {
        "question": " 152兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.2446784138802256
    },
    {
        "question": " 1254兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.541986991300679
    },
    {
        "question": " 787億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.1176977765190594
    },
    {
        "question": " 7096億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.851000428895424
    },
    {
        "question": " 23.5億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.3710365444242525
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.13万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 7.328235831426118
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.841e+04垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.085671765165252
    },
    {
        "question": " 21.9京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.4040847910809138
    },
    {
        "question": " 91.4京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.404651759347139
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.05京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.244618608875129
    },
    {
        "question": " 108京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.032897187921103
    },
    {
        "question": " 3802万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.579971022461859
    },
    {
        "question": " 1396nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 0.14480124249305892
    },
    {
        "question": " 967万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.54764068681851
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.82年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.202958042192905
    },
    {
        "question": " 92.8億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.40505770121564
    },
    {
        "question": " 51.3日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.0904231808275426
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.01万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.637293448122337
    },
    {
        "question": " 43.2日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.572433334286378
    },
    {
        "question": " 1632億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.270316808834191
    },
    {
        "question": " 13億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.7326233029625335
    },
    {
        "question": " 44.8億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.9310893663025737
    },
    {
        "question": " 328万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.3579079959563805
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.11万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.266689156417454
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.3万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.868394563949937
    },
    {
        "question": " 2762分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.219325659618931
    },
    {
        "question": " 109分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.816521314156137
    },
    {
        "question": " 3146億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.998998547561061
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.63兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.622907183504562
    },
    {
        "question": " 338万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.973010725897236
    },
    {
        "question": " 493億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.914312524829285
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.33万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.522744326967987
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.36京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.873681079008635
    },
    {
        "question": " 326億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.577194752022071
    },
    {
        "question": " 35.4兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.992162671539672
    },
    {
        "question": " 50.7万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9265660470822035
    },
    {
        "question": " 33.3億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.522775831484367
    },
    {
        "question": " 39msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 7.5915460718698355
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.67垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.325300088992211
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.67垓usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.489703274022782
    },
    {
        "question": " 41.8京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.064649179143279
    },
    {
        "question": " 3764兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.797554715689077
    },
    {
        "question": " 59.7兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.776003820806896
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.97万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.5985308099872808
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.87e+05垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.959070647783264
    },
    {
        "question": " 587垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.832468747648889
    },
    {
        "question": " 74.3垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.314933654681965
    },
    {
        "question": " 6479京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.033346442528584
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.44京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.157876065376946
    },
    {
        "question": " 2444万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.388076611592547
    },
    {
        "question": " 63.3万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 2.8015722505673812
    },
    {
        "question": " 725年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.422803522926868
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.71兆日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.870426598714221
    },
    {
        "question": " 24.6万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.771644044399368
    },
    {
        "question": " 28兆時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.504409926856926
    },
    {
        "question": " 376時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1954881819585084
    },
    {
        "question": " 179万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.03113345872201
    },
    {
        "question": " 33.7時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.084148025589414
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.49時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.208992333535392
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.1兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.285244273566269
    },
    {
        "question": " 1583億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.040994322920552
    },
    {
        "question": " 2129万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.550041889553986
    },
    {
        "question": " 8671万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.716211054645054
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.2分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.788157521508212
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.47億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6689823521159266
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.49億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.7160023233114527
    },
    {
        "question": " 224億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.793164964936053
    },
    {
        "question": " 576万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.982507045810312
    },
    {
        "question": " 5483秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.739014872114391
    },
    {
        "question": " 4918億msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1929428351703442
    },
    {
        "question": " 74.2兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.93382235713289
    },
    {
        "question": " 1948万msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7332223362010126
    },
    {
        "question": " 6671億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.046066964903204
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.12万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.325446383070108
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.28msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 3.1082531380143763
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.75垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.940816924100793
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.58京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.943147592651554
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.4京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.603517562329568
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.15億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9338828991918691
    },
    {
        "question": " 4344兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.63785901794267
    },
    {
        "question": " 36.5億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.562124652537595
    },
    {
        "question": " 1367usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.135757682650791
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.04e+04垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.8108136414935725
    },
    {
        "question": " 1091兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1013513129176855
    },
    {
        "question": " 454京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.100432251238379
    },
    {
        "question": " 1191兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.297823093491956
    },
    {
        "question": " 2870億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.457930829509154
    },
    {
        "question": " 125億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.095341174995153
    },
    {
        "question": " 7333nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 0.8652914738907114
    },
    {
        "question": " 1306年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.678123349714043
    },
    {
        "question": " 218年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.2809699823987595
    },
    {
        "question": " 20.2億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.743420398798525
    },
    {
        "question": " 6234日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.17499620511477
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.6日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.351782790428123
    },
    {
        "question": " 3194億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.561848833447713
    },
    {
        "question": " 421時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2436677056196777
    },
    {
        "question": " 1014時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.56228785681273
    },
    {
        "question": " 26.5時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.980087373392577
    },
    {
        "question": " 1669兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.50185818319192
    },
    {
        "question": " 900億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.796067847110458
    },
    {
        "question": " 533分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9489680823455571
    },
    {
        "question": " 748万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.65227642054473
    },
    {
        "question": " 385億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.086211079763417
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.8万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.28898713450081326
    },
    {
        "question": " 48.2万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1267614764034315
    },
    {
        "question": " 20.8億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.538901685751412
    },
    {
        "question": " 127兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.603587279745062
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.63兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.884740118095112
    },
    {
        "question": " 52.1億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.1605837037839324
    },
    {
        "question": " 121億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.304282541949758
    },
    {
        "question": " 3628万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.559621410628059
    },
    {
        "question": " 294万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.468288459914175
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.58msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.412144271144806
    },
    {
        "question": " 731垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.36513612086089
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.76京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.309753050119626
    },
    {
        "question": " 2697京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.874544920906152
    },
    {
        "question": " 455兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.8797046483918685
    },
    {
        "question": " 575万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7599256022020806
    },
    {
        "question": " 28.2億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.449585484502829
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.94usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 3.5955296007083803
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.17京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.0025807884762452105
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.19垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.403940523997989
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.26兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.24007185529496766
    },
    {
        "question": " 227京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.578097780433387
    },
    {
        "question": " 22.6億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.35491067943806964
    },
    {
        "question": " 7327兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.864936051232691
    },
    {
        "question": " 444億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.647851401845262
    },
    {
        "question": " 746年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.434769758374369
    },
    {
        "question": " 6387年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.747827704503759
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.3億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.591990880772519
    },
    {
        "question": " 32.5日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8921290617201025
    },
    {
        "question": " 222日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.504012348349828
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.57日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.59596029800753
    },
    {
        "question": " 56.4兆時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.808903171068517
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.51億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.799805275319351
    },
    {
        "question": " 68.9万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.616090461215564
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.9万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.593145242068697
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.74億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8520769639456356
    },
    {
        "question": " 2262万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.196070787729809
    },
    {
        "question": " 74.2分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.0920655222873712
    },
    {
        "question": " 1495分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.952730574549538
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.12分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.737995689860078
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.15分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.83897377477577
    },
    {
        "question": " 165兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.717383698513633
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.79万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.007553752206471698
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.54億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.8477411340251635
    },
    {
        "question": " 352秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7684424647723376
    },
    {
        "question": " 200万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.301274180308427
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.14秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.055494242291934
    },
    {
        "question": " 7065兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.350308216868997
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.49兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.237196983639099
    },
    {
        "question": " 9519億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.422275701233388
    },
    {
        "question": " 219兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.561889568249443
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.7億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.1045584193633795
    },
    {
        "question": " 771万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.887155663964634
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.86垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.770820152434547
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.58垓usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.262609654887445
    },
    {
        "question": " 150億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6209365275512635
    },
    {
        "question": " 54.8億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.960307462156965
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.4億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.1865128480683858
    },
    {
        "question": " 6863万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.836520693746048
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.4usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 3.531225020866761
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.53e+04垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.480295520088276
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.02京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.069973608175925
    },
    {
        "question": " 2724京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.87885445322996
    },
    {
        "question": " 207京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.537972578843853
    },
    {
        "question": " 359京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.554678754696015
    },
    {
        "question": " 1669兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.222450528106778
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.84兆nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.68479689751769
    },
    {
        "question": " 73.8万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.3058094586623477
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.25万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.475927616720434
    },
    {
        "question": " 47万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.830753473150091
    },
    {
        "question": " 861日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.871551680277559
    },
    {
        "question": " 24.8万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.45256610763852
    },
    {
        "question": " 7611万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.501256525346012
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.71時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.765587335972292
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.6万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.657263180824748
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.25時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.651633476530829
    },
    {
        "question": " 414万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.896254838210645
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.4万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.0013533121895675
    },
    {
        "question": " 19.4万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.508617609999529
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.35万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.699641159334125
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.2分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.8649489129258034
    },
    {
        "question": " 70兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.346001864188161
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.52兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.805058643506434
    },
    {
        "question": " 136億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.576757198128852
    },
    {
        "question": " 551億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.96293023076841
    },
    {
        "question": " 28.1万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.449063233572566
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.01秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.903516252978576
    },
    {
        "question": " 107京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.52928107449922
    },
    {
        "question": " 199億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3628255634915707
    },
    {
        "question": " 1017万msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.4509183920429416
    },
    {
        "question": " 37.6兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.797077726002303
    },
    {
        "question": " 168億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.224632857405407
    },
    {
        "question": " 2350msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.371080012782238
    },
    {
        "question": " 322垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.00968737566697
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.81兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.008242686760445
    },
    {
        "question": " 2935京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.911290885250743
    },
    {
        "question": " 442億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.867695289659684
    },
    {
        "question": " 19.7億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.293671596074587
    },
    {
        "question": " 29.6億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.471449877665986
    },
    {
        "question": " 50.6usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 4.703915689041997
    },
    {
        "question": " 4399京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.144570818995808
    },
    {
        "question": " 6617京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.884186254961087
    },
    {
        "question": " 3582京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.99786705319725
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.17京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.8422394749777204
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.73兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.4365425740240116
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.66億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 2.218844830251081
    },
    {
        "question": " 19.2億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.282374675461644
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.6億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.57003044904841
    },
    {
        "question": " 191万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.660269792476022
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.6日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.821095617618251
    },
    {
        "question": " 385億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.643389303105289
    },
    {
        "question": " 52.7万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.341716079786885
    },
    {
        "question": " 534時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.505706235168077
    },
    {
        "question": " 159万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.756642071578254
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.51時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.370092375435466
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.38億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.0838963907036243
    },
    {
        "question": " 29.1億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.30514432043272
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.23億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.7305281376865445
    },
    {
        "question": " 7879億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.397672225516985
    },
    {
        "question": " 5479万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8022003725853226
    },
    {
        "question": " 146万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6093609633662505
    },
    {
        "question": " 382万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.804308490324415
    },
    {
        "question": " 52.3京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.219965679483229
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.61兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.72746282349222
    },
    {
        "question": " 1134兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.498168812969155
    },
    {
        "question": " 140兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.366800203553451
    },
    {
        "question": " 44.3万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6459721841339787
    },
    {
        "question": " 551万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.741487390159607
    },
    {
        "question": " 71.1兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.3527661244003133
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.3京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.07719861900558
    },
    {
        "question": " 2355兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.8156788494596885
    },
    {
        "question": " 50.2京usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.922149706849988
    },
    {
        "question": " 2121兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.326540492309734
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.54兆usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.815688108094564
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.39usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 3.6422803578878593
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.03垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.8092072300382442
    },
    {
        "question": " 7196垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.920568311290666
    },
    {
        "question": " 2210兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7880062063255395
    },
    {
        "question": " 7636京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.104697388485473
    },
    {
        "question": " 56.3京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.750543887255676
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.61兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.207834671735948
    },
    {
        "question": " 429億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.632138238060616
    },
    {
        "question": " 19.1万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.844125564946055
    },
    {
        "question": " 59.1万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.714364263419705
    },
    {
        "question": " 4465日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0874991766159037
    },
    {
        "question": " 950万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.357884142628329
    },
    {
        "question": " 4034日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.764049586985673
    },
    {
        "question": " 8106万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.966326106036103
    },
    {
        "question": " 1198万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.698303921127346
    },
    {
        "question": " 1430時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.9333553904985274
    },
    {
        "question": " 213時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.884215644228354
    },
    {
        "question": " 618万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0703030257283097
    },
    {
        "question": " 144億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.999718068452934
    },
    {
        "question": " 349万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.764387196823093
    },
    {
        "question": " 18.5万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.044865872058567
    },
    {
        "question": " 1502兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.677792226374313
    },
    {
        "question": " 205億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.375768109431959
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.2万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0671425566814574
    },
    {
        "question": " 3902億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.81310612118112
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.79秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.578521684076755
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.81秒は何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.580915954595028
    },
    {
        "question": " 75.9兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.3815356766464832
    },
    {
        "question": " 3580億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.6173402909433072
    },
    {
        "question": " 4416万msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.088717259858999
    },
    {
        "question": " 2631億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.642048430316404
    },
    {
        "question": " 30億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.477296139195202
    },
    {
        "question": " 102兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5106224499244827
    },
    {
        "question": " 7611京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.944934043433545
    },
    {
        "question": " 9172億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4061527697214533
    },
    {
        "question": " 50.7億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9266030727916983
    },
    {
        "question": " 18.4億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.265639996738389
    },
    {
        "question": " 3569億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.552502951764264
    },
    {
        "question": " 54.4垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.2365291877845275
    },
    {
        "question": " 107兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.0916186202504432
    },
    {
        "question": " 14京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.5883419660301
    },
    {
        "question": " 58.1京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.985987742394001
    },
    {
        "question": " 303兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.48103355891167
    },
    {
        "question": " 33.8億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.529135633181167
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.3億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.238965421969395
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.68年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.788153622592533
    },
    {
        "question": " 29万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.899579345463985
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.02日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.686381925635625
    },
    {
        "question": " 90.3万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.113960047197029
    },
    {
        "question": " 666億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.880941706863478
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.3億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.671925914883264
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.1時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.5973429458785944
    },
    {
        "question": " 533億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.0058069972039
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.34億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.762841835052032
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.34億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.949753278137312
    },
    {
        "question": " 40.2万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.382135925835311
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.94京秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.274725886660233
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.18億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.8544137654197144
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.6万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.637486810566895
    },
    {
        "question": " 1574秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4189804103776393
    },
    {
        "question": " 437万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.640954151960011
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.12垓msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.994886334719057
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.1京msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.914874738934053
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.83兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.706000602269214
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.16億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.7216299266444497
    },
    {
        "question": " 379億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.578633584250106
    },
    {
        "question": " 757msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 8.879185819130534
    },
    {
        "question": " 108京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.535639414781375
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.32兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4289210895524829
    },
    {
        "question": " 241兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.825101453719116
    },
    {
        "question": " 65.5兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.038097048577466
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.78億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8310533894365975
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.24兆usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.719309375840284
    },
    {
        "question": " 271usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 5.432723049564042
    },
    {
        "question": " 88.3京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4473242650769502
    },
    {
        "question": " 20.6京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.3768234859156223
    },
    {
        "question": " 18.2垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.702875681881482
    },
    {
        "question": " 2197億nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5636300254399862
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.8億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.2509023825366752
    },
    {
        "question": " 7125万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.8527941745982968
    },
    {
        "question": " 1011nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 0.004657776873471242
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.27年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.299104556937367
    },
    {
        "question": " 88.6年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.668317182140276
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.47億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.606192243255154
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.5億日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.924529095501919
    },
    {
        "question": " 21.1日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.481786146126263
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.57万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9365765126421555
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.1億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.660610963311925
    },
    {
        "question": " 337万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.306369576354717
    },
    {
        "question": " 72.1万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.4142675427162
    },
    {
        "question": " 114時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.614815629516357
    },
    {
        "question": " 204兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.588722411994757
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.26兆分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.471492361146822
    },
    {
        "question": " 84.8万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.150259103094376
    },
    {
        "question": " 86.7億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4394375989805974
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.7兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.130585772154268
    },
    {
        "question": " 36.7億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.008421581495421
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.72億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.979322399568008
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.61兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3826841172692212
    },
    {
        "question": " 1895億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.3410902990452174
    },
    {
        "question": " 1202兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.523747017392129
    },
    {
        "question": " 121億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.305100909734014
    },
    {
        "question": " 872億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.940575564149508
    },
    {
        "question": " 541万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.733010777904878
    },
    {
        "question": " 165msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 8.218592662808197
    },
    {
        "question": " 254垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.906659861031565
    },
    {
        "question": " 192兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.347858829743906
    },
    {
        "question": " 4137兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.060337503431157
    },
    {
        "question": " 3085兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.711159116699763
    },
    {
        "question": " 5億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6988617459371977
    },
    {
        "question": " 67.3億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.8282858259593215
    },
    {
        "question": " 7289usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.862692899497963
    },
    {
        "question": " 2476京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8950194761578696
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.45垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.7120378892415005
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.78垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.021701797768609
    },
    {
        "question": " 1734兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.4608647310006155
    },
    {
        "question": " 556兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.745063910994489
    },
    {
        "question": " 645億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.809578439311637
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.63億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 5.213347473506244
    },
    {
        "question": " 282万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.013020789815599
    },
    {
        "question": " 24.5億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.826938403076302
    },
    {
        "question": " 154日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.5689632722169664
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.53日は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.12216417515289
    },
    {
        "question": " 1312億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.175547620875075
    },
    {
        "question": " 2504万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.018357192006433
    },
    {
        "question": " 854時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.709536322791479
    },
    {
        "question": " 499時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.254596482300108
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.03時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.038018264101256
    },
    {
        "question": " 110億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.31939147821046
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.3億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.705145163252493
    },
    {
        "question": " 6625万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.043051482358239
    },
    {
        "question": " 44.5万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.426212981683942
    },
    {
        "question": " 66.3分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.599500524152802
    },
    {
        "question": " 1988兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.7996911306310786
    },
    {
        "question": " 345億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.60158857527499
    },
    {
        "question": " 19.5億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.73409076418792
    },
    {
        "question": " 6526万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.036498101851681
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.18万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.620752599120205
    },
    {
        "question": " 5717秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.757185358034487
    },
    {
        "question": " 1523兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.6839913075546855
    },
    {
        "question": " 45.3兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.719366500659781
    },
    {
        "question": " 19.8億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7403918164513517
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.87兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.680054995679005
    },
    {
        "question": " 36.6万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.563021392280913
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.7万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.222770683506145
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.47京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.4774487842385815
    },
    {
        "question": " 2481京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.458104204377587
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.41京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.177116234079771
    },
    {
        "question": " 7155万usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.07645137188574513
    },
    {
        "question": " 356億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.551999690714096
    },
    {
        "question": " 85.1億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.930132098270684
    },
    {
        "question": " 472万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.674114869588204
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.005e+06垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.803238379636824
    },
    {
        "question": " 118兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.13469291210089218
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.41京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.087971064291688
    },
    {
        "question": " 573兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.979906570204358
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.9億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.20260853756382424
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.17億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 2.3365936060100037
    },
    {
        "question": " 1083億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.034714708486296
    },
    {
        "question": " 1763万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.808528824581952
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.44年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.100041562930457
    },
    {
        "question": " 264年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.141503862835057
    },
    {
        "question": " 109年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.536747329264392
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.22億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.522875384582119
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.7万日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.504290936915412
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.17兆時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.394616535534153
    },
    {
        "question": " 114万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.678423444194367
    },
    {
        "question": " 7万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.62294585173547
    },
    {
        "question": " 36.1万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.114190218741138
    },
    {
        "question": " 22時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.898821630599462
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.3兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.367579648625886
    },
    {
        "question": " 2464億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.233289598816175
    },
    {
        "question": " 801分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1255623956235206
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.57分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.330389723621158
    },
    {
        "question": " 24.8分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.17234882728748
    },
    {
        "question": " 280億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.947868897312439
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.25兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.415766915581865
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.1兆秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.677755191287174
    },
    {
        "question": " 9169万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.1841902933180615
    },
    {
        "question": " 879万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.943937179257457
    },
    {
        "question": " 1713京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.73484487387332
    },
    {
        "question": " 2956億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.5342238337900858
    },
    {
        "question": " 36.8億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.0094455301392964
    },
    {
        "question": " 4719億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.89570642399058
    },
    {
        "question": " 1001万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.000553944580293
    },
    {
        "question": " 29.7万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.473327695368969
    },
    {
        "question": " 599京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.278341353043495
    },
    {
        "question": " 1247兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.159531767267426
    },
    {
        "question": " 956京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.424279758683344
    },
    {
        "question": " 6739万usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.05044271256494093
    },
    {
        "question": " 1301万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1142918303965743
    },
    {
        "question": " 1648億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.217069700555133
    },
    {
        "question": " 2080usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.3180188143858995
    },
    {
        "question": " 2033垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.809284969063834
    },
    {
        "question": " 619兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8548487587351139
    },
    {
        "question": " 105京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.465312765637361
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.34京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.087696981053034
    },
    {
        "question": " 124京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.092720433899048
    },
    {
        "question": " 2483億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.395055542237542
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.05万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 1.0230172321494402
    },
    {
        "question": " 27.5年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.000916547377338
    },
    {
        "question": " 3282年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.458674987630761
    },
    {
        "question": " 1548億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.627592683584652
    },
    {
        "question": " 462日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.044529789470655
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.72万日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.506654239213612
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.57万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.46744016500001373
    },
    {
        "question": " 22.1万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.965008728422373
    },
    {
        "question": " 18.7万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.0488432561252266
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.11万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.601580655937329
    },
    {
        "question": " 240時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.937293556545585
    },
    {
        "question": " 24.1億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.661977996369492
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.01兆分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.847441213364478
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.64万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.2057236036158554
    },
    {
        "question": " 92.4分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.7436650525146673
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.36分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.150739427536823
    },
    {
        "question": " 3258万秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.014123275749116093
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.05億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.084680577617732
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.53万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6281074013682186
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.24億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.7323882607302235
    },
    {
        "question": " 42.6秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.629260863714815
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.75秒は何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.941856852513796
    },
    {
        "question": " 225京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.852521682154513
    },
    {
        "question": " 6755兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.893114346460647
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.11億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4906556827448036
    },
    {
        "question": " 5858万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9896082265771584
    },
    {
        "question": " 2323万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.366027398943181
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.1垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.585141198799149
    },
    {
        "question": " 56.1兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.812079588125668
    },
    {
        "question": " 1439億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6017418202783384
    },
    {
        "question": " 381億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8024842390508153
    },
    {
        "question": " 1974億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.295349437996778
    },
    {
        "question": " 65.8万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 2.8180061645958565
    },
    {
        "question": " 163万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.213127017412061
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.1垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.541811700280608
    },
    {
        "question": " 93.2兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.03271662263336195
    },
    {
        "question": " 1841京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.708639378420237
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.73垓nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.896369328945132
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.99兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.2998098269374476
    },
    {
        "question": " 2110兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.324208411611995
    },
    {
        "question": " 5433万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.735021954119759
    },
    {
        "question": " 7126年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.4151239057054905
    },
    {
        "question": " 106万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.969379679147778
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.81年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.402585336989503
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.89年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.187684933179275
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.04兆日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.92109175606459
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.02億日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.390597129634603
    },
    {
        "question": " 25.3日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.561861967061698
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.91万日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.529196186577236
    },
    {
        "question": " 122億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.145187213596712
    },
    {
        "question": " 28.1億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.068879118437406
    },
    {
        "question": " 6387万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.583434133953684
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.43時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.7125173531304787
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.58億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6907279893041682
    },
    {
        "question": " 1347億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.971066027321431
    },
    {
        "question": " 1104万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.264759818963327
    },
    {
        "question": " 1540分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.965770161121786
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.38京秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.424692640789253
    },
    {
        "question": " 21.1億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.388167524912326
    },
    {
        "question": " 46.4万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.109765498279479
    },
    {
        "question": " 3236億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.731824087349615
    },
    {
        "question": " 212秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.326432477808703
    },
    {
        "question": " 43.5秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.638687990948016
    },
    {
        "question": " 131京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.619164094970074
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.05京msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.76640029511354
    },
    {
        "question": " 466億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.112216212596639
    },
    {
        "question": " 369万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7888172591881668
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.39万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5308120664929359
    },
    {
        "question": " 1096msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.039908433957416
    },
    {
        "question": " 546京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.238037967911849
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.4兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9330235371227156
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.84京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.8965183609724034
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.1億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3376023555880756
    },
    {
        "question": " 27.6兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.440670696147511
    },
    {
        "question": " 69.6万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 2.8428153166924055
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.72万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 7.827432648410268
    },
    {
        "question": " 9100京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.460211979311322
    },
    {
        "question": " 501京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.763029716738197
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.13京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.7726898076535464
    },
    {
        "question": " 154兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.408928295613589
    },
    {
        "question": " 46.9兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.671520529725514
    },
    {
        "question": " 74.7兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.873325356064814
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.4万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 2.128244317321484
    },
    {
        "question": " 205年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.873897320331103
    },
    {
        "question": " 136億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.572318399601699
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.34日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5075233887499817
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.8日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.606125272086129
    },
    {
        "question": " 18.5日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.203424672498981
    },
    {
        "question": " 43.6万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.697194963162395
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.8万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.690212480393561
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.55時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.488235414847356
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.24億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3718909293981927
    },
    {
        "question": " 200万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.142973907900526
    },
    {
        "question": " 4162万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.841194991309901
    },
    {
        "question": " 5765万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.538917837809688
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.24億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5943667303394584
    },
    {
        "question": " 30.4兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.546159305442442
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.13万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2969255252020484
    },
    {
        "question": " 1418億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.373541776374298
    },
    {
        "question": " 70.5兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.349087937167371
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.03京msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.968022352819261
    },
    {
        "question": " 224億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.7929782764805573
    },
    {
        "question": " 259万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6354598745448412
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.58億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.660987331801026
    },
    {
        "question": " 245msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 8.388892190238032
    },
    {
        "question": " 63垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.300390087998075
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.93垓usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.530990477571272
    },
    {
        "question": " 5611億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.192705584120959
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.82兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.671599808524799
    },
    {
        "question": " 188万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.27343897585753285
    },
    {
        "question": " 2192億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.340935841562256
    },
    {
        "question": " 6355京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.304318871610624
    },
    {
        "question": " 112垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.113659765604034
    },
    {
        "question": " 958京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.425271696982718
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.79兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6669506695204372
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.95京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.5960595303339264
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.83兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.451659680481851
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.4万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 2.0580299241570756
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.14年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.179427589128674
    },
    {
        "question": " 1483日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6087874891526068
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.15億日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.441717330957795
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.3日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.2722895208056046
    },
    {
        "question": " 760日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.817451173339514
    },
    {
        "question": " 9836時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.05029836408706467
    },
    {
        "question": " 115時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6789582016813345
    },
    {
        "question": " 64.2万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.585858686747329
    },
    {
        "question": " 51.3時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.266610036286256
    },
    {
        "question": " 41.4億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.895932236095522
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.05万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8611617619062939
    },
    {
        "question": " 18.2万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.4826586781607394
    },
    {
        "question": " 159兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.702647277552885
    },
    {
        "question": " 1144億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.1219658992398065
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.75兆秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.685614002628922
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.12万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.272528168676269
    },
    {
        "question": " 5974秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.7762454455455785
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.4兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6605209581708356
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.88兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.652705486200439
    },
    {
        "question": " 4462億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.093223503869862
    },
    {
        "question": " 257億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.632274926329042
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.43億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.1550244793303355
    },
    {
        "question": " 3752msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.574291124863586
    },
    {
        "question": " 1215兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5857269128970786
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.3京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.176910280542851
    },
    {
        "question": " 794京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.343377481169187
    },
    {
        "question": " 1309億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.3386599670793373
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.13兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.496033942908635
    },
    {
        "question": " 1991万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.299057481491763
    },
    {
        "question": " 303万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.482007373131623
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.338e+04垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.627621386322766
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.3京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4253897195676566
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.49京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.37240283953206
    },
    {
        "question": " 69.3兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.062464508335384
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.35京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.638005605613294
    },
    {
        "question": " 1883億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.274813094094384
    },
    {
        "question": " 4407万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.644153113512611
    },
    {
        "question": " 25.2万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.964226089222838
    },
    {
        "question": " 35.5年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.493221755766794
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.89億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.20792214558767
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.02万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.159934591469508
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.2万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.243310702467912
    },
    {
        "question": " 23.6万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4302904560393526
    },
    {
        "question": " 1443億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.779116983558428
    },
    {
        "question": " 1439万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.936169505129461
    },
    {
        "question": " 1302兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.393856720055222
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.7億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.945285179512786
    },
    {
        "question": " 3014分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.700964691644835
    },
    {
        "question": " 56.6万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.531215029183951
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.29分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.1373069478855085
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.43億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6559445892320748
    },
    {
        "question": " 1085万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.0989794777448
    },
    {
        "question": " 229万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8027102916022075
    },
    {
        "question": " 4344秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8597253910295042
    },
    {
        "question": " 296秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.47131814057901
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.4京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.517092157577182
    },
    {
        "question": " 188億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3380087553758
    },
    {
        "question": " 2601兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.858855681651681
    },
    {
        "question": " 72.3兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.080737945213343
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.5億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.161062252142022
    },
    {
        "question": " 1520msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.181754633027307
    },
    {
        "question": " 165兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7174055378359889
    },
    {
        "question": " 87.1京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.003695754785745
    },
    {
        "question": " 117億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.512308745408111
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.53兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.878370560942731
    },
    {
        "question": " 6442兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.809048426382267
    },
    {
        "question": " 1392億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.14364831482688
    },
    {
        "question": " 24.2万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 8.383852029286189
    },
    {
        "question": " 94.3垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.475637876555917
    },
    {
        "question": " 1708兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2960579731727317
    },
    {
        "question": " 4057兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.051939574894005
    },
    {
        "question": " 2327兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.588569856092003
    },
    {
        "question": " 123京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.089103640330817
    },
    {
        "question": " 4005万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.6025612373881726
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.3兆nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.113036701851374
    },
    {
        "question": " 63.1年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.362597370082888
    },
    {
        "question": " 1027年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.954080354477372
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.03年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.676415745612161
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.15万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.149131059761913
    },
    {
        "question": " 3252万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.892380762592973
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.9万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.74993024559687
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.8日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.107007955359737
    },
    {
        "question": " 3387億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.587342909305458
    },
    {
        "question": " 1090万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.657119265210703
    },
    {
        "question": " 9732万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.76634511042639
    },
    {
        "question": " 160時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.759463863010343
    },
    {
        "question": " 43.9兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.921349825797749
    },
    {
        "question": " 5968億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.61747399234256
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.67億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.443504095248577
    },
    {
        "question": " 24万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.157681903035936
    },
    {
        "question": " 1588兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.701996328579997
    },
    {
        "question": " 1670万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2861964748670296
    },
    {
        "question": " 170億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.67439951469165
    },
    {
        "question": " 357万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.774298344718481
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.29秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.7986080703265546
    },
    {
        "question": " 703京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.348115254096085
    },
    {
        "question": " 1415億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.21429472753041
    },
    {
        "question": " 28億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8907321482069026
    },
    {
        "question": " 2042万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5318742301371144
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.15兆msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.05904177996376
    },
    {
        "question": " 99.6垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.499414933692135
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.05京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.548107208141869
    },
    {
        "question": " 1426億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.597890871542229
    },
    {
        "question": " 577兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.983011865078624
    },
    {
        "question": " 5580兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.746632681937141
    },
    {
        "question": " 6440usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 0.8088858230875207
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.65usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 3.216583832644729
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.25垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.596566295895708
    },
    {
        "question": " 177京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.3122250086449965
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.9兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6962265487072927
    },
    {
        "question": " 4071京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.831601147782509
    },
    {
        "question": " 5940億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.773779493323728
    },
    {
        "question": " 296兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.470780809596416
    },
    {
        "question": " 3145nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 0.4975926753056148
    },
    {
        "question": " 40年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.164355264314315
    },
    {
        "question": " 560万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.185522954618407
    },
    {
        "question": " 176日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.62548581368309
    },
    {
        "question": " 110万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.200374538886413
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.58億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.255859718053205
    },
    {
        "question": " 57.8億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.381980799615928
    },
    {
        "question": " 226万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.91131012272427
    },
    {
        "question": " 224時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.906916331615435
    },
    {
        "question": " 20.3億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.5868445288905604
    },
    {
        "question": " 3101億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.33317349396464
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.54万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.626826101029894
    },
    {
        "question": " 1億分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.779254899300247
    },
    {
        "question": " 4526万秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.15687808052414653
    },
    {
        "question": " 874万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.0049627430914683
    },
    {
        "question": " 6194億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.23569799185664
    },
    {
        "question": " 29億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.684375304923
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.8秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.072640595711999
    },
    {
        "question": " 121京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.585372908211353
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.3億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0762541863827646
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.46億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1811910570938062
    },
    {
        "question": " 39.5億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.818276354846098
    },
    {
        "question": " 7746msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8890579232490026
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.42msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 3.1515930699001227
    },
    {
        "question": " 6006兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2797599205539276
    },
    {
        "question": " 238兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.4407365589145944
    },
    {
        "question": " 521億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1608203223218372
    },
    {
        "question": " 32.4億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7327281009751616
    },
    {
        "question": " 791兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.898341472501485
    },
    {
        "question": " 945億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.975520223507409
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.4万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 7.924340179519894
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.38垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.473398702763673
    },
    {
        "question": " 48.8垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.752205779904047
    },
    {
        "question": " 275垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.883333577359144
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.41兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.09158900854878
    },
    {
        "question": " 2385兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.377421040831489
    },
    {
        "question": " 1352億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.130963541302986
    },
    {
        "question": " 1326億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.122546253471569
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.3年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.576565162624866
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.58万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.140836580746186
    },
    {
        "question": " 3496年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.264177567270362
    },
    {
        "question": " 1790日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6904529940425352
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.7日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.381156183538767
    },
    {
        "question": " 70.8万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9078329646822645
    },
    {
        "question": " 227億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.975886853221217
    },
    {
        "question": " 3400万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.30960868334042
    },
    {
        "question": " 22.6万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.910037248182737
    },
    {
        "question": " 266億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.704478176977447
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.85兆分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.109964920116717
    },
    {
        "question": " 44.4万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.8696292476953342
    },
    {
        "question": " 4127万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.393796312962658
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.09万分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.48450645826188
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.32京秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.621580612161372
    },
    {
        "question": " 126万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1639881564218157
    },
    {
        "question": " 1797万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.698293853633401
    },
    {
        "question": " 4519万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.876899791249066
    },
    {
        "question": " 2027秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.3067573797250205
    },
    {
        "question": " 4583億msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1623888588238596
    },
    {
        "question": " 191兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.345466913682492
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.37億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5813981775672858
    },
    {
        "question": " 19.8億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.518271525539276
    },
    {
        "question": " 84.1億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.92488997954282
    },
    {
        "question": " 3494msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.54337214721337
    },
    {
        "question": " 253兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9043503658954932
    },
    {
        "question": " 190兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.341257110416258
    },
    {
        "question": " 1259京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.54377012195071
    },
    {
        "question": " 8228万usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.13716413956291862
    },
    {
        "question": " 181兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.258536508385792
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.68兆usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.670127140480492
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.94usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 3.951577778736415
    },
    {
        "question": " 410垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.113554515690096
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.9垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.139789821832197
    },
    {
        "question": " 46.3垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.108997567003673
    },
    {
        "question": " 362京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.780147745787245
    },
    {
        "question": " 72.7兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.861634238439319
    },
    {
        "question": " 19.5兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.289318079828687
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.04万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 1.4834679420251917
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.4万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.709465187917419
    },
    {
        "question": " 65.4万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.758385051597143
    },
    {
        "question": " 1987万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.735798340343602
    },
    {
        "question": " 370万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.948299717378088
    },
    {
        "question": " 343万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.693430930278623
    },
    {
        "question": " 122日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.022289519079628
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.23日は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.731320484245598
    },
    {
        "question": " 25.7兆時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.467727184618122
    },
    {
        "question": " 7523時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.496206519148126
    },
    {
        "question": " 16時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.982163427510256
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.01時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.562393494984758
    },
    {
        "question": " 47.7億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.9577178499044043
    },
    {
        "question": " 3781分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.4192086231394143
    },
    {
        "question": " 36.3億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.781297491050919
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.4分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.835321069570231
    },
    {
        "question": " 120兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.581616823793304
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.4億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.278576125386358
    },
    {
        "question": " 2380万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.8202807005173014
    },
    {
        "question": " 5314億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.947264782406378
    },
    {
        "question": " 22.1秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.344113710805698
    },
    {
        "question": " 212兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.826967668250197
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.8億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3141545976361213
    },
    {
        "question": " 19.3兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.728202255709526
    },
    {
        "question": " 30.3兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.703811335556534
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.49万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.173286723214968
    },
    {
        "question": " 3851msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.585530073106522
    },
    {
        "question": " 25.7垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.910563551468446
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.55垓usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.25482068842059
    },
    {
        "question": " 42.6兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.072667049176281
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.83兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.115370817598755
    },
    {
        "question": " 2515兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.400517243084838
    },
    {
        "question": " 5329usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 0.7266120273360233
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.63usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 3.2120889898537373
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.851e+06垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.956231306129236
    },
    {
        "question": " 2836兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5162161106110872
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.2兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5310904938568239
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.66垓nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.441914131491524
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.08京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.958291214492287
    },
    {
        "question": " 174万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 0.2404499105653013
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.32万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 1.9692153285320435
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.04年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.2643976633993086
    },
    {
        "question": " 1772年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.969154269163477
    },
    {
        "question": " 604日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.2186835214315408
    },
    {
        "question": " 229日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.7398713827745156
    },
    {
        "question": " 415万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.776913431561182
    },
    {
        "question": " 4580万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.718373589230871
    },
    {
        "question": " 133時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7433686281471619
    },
    {
        "question": " 194兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.566207694247625
    },
    {
        "question": " 23.6万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.215064291215932
    },
    {
        "question": " 4464億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.871566068831402
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.33億分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.902243948194315
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.29分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.41059738395452
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.45兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.149343920285335
    },
    {
        "question": " 861万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9982561043254476
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.3億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.07755355039145
    },
    {
        "question": " 1448万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.382703518456814
    },
    {
        "question": " 3582秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.554149223912042
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.05兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.349409700508022
    },
    {
        "question": " 9543兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.043186428713181
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.3兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.566862712957727
    },
    {
        "question": " 302万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7014178527836954
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.2億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.151200422541305
    },
    {
        "question": " 27.3msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.435465591269201
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.08垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.818444470686905
    },
    {
        "question": " 1415兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.2142572583381614
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.19兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5194572649170333
    },
    {
        "question": " 9490億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.199103534623566
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.05億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.0206020715357886
    },
    {
        "question": " 94.5億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.9753985994313075
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.79万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 7.252686253731228
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.142e+04垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.212313644605072
    },
    {
        "question": " 6661京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.887061385619411
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.7京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.611323081049049
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.03兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5299534066198928
    },
    {
        "question": " 562京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.749537664158733
    },
    {
        "question": " 2740億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.43768329096705
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.36万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 1.1327357951892814
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.83年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.824611069544465
    },
    {
        "question": " 34.1年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.252923930347396
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.07年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.527248612251951
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.24万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5324037377956068
    },
    {
        "question": " 93.5万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.351207977340542
    },
    {
        "question": " 377日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.734261427936235
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.35日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.574808748035976
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.9億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.648338354384554
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.5億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.640409083498271
    },
    {
        "question": " 1034時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.792639603366319
    },
    {
        "question": " 3404時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.088283253629154
    },
    {
        "question": " 230万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6413005469329991
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.94万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.615567545118628
    },
    {
        "question": " 889億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.170784164354318
    },
    {
        "question": " 39.5万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.374566804372563
    },
    {
        "question": " 5803分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.541777165517944
    },
    {
        "question": " 3480兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.042758356334772
    },
    {
        "question": " 2688万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4928900978413138
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.5兆秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.539920973115473
    },
    {
        "question": " 732万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.086209206904293
    },
    {
        "question": " 462秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.664821095531853
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.2秒は何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.623520327976948
    },
    {
        "question": " 998億msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.500126654048042
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.14億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9742913544151577
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.55兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.63316294374305
    },
    {
        "question": " 1714億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.455735006344813
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.32兆msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.969195420244896
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.1msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.006158514078555
    },
    {
        "question": " 980msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 8.991193910824713
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.5垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.376025361055504
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.23兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7821498003519076
    },
    {
        "question": " 216京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.777958433986468
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.49億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6176103396124555
    },
    {
        "question": " 233万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.36769693078267496
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.05億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.781750075738632
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.857e+04垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.957036478882523
    },
    {
        "question": " 935兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0344476879457254
    },
    {
        "question": " 19.4兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7311540165375063
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.34兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.348331311576626
    },
    {
        "question": " 117兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.066406771574878
    },
    {
        "question": " 1507万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.1780344455543723
    },
    {
        "question": " 8366nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 0.922510408507542
    },
    {
        "question": " 7286年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.4247915803603695
    },
    {
        "question": " 965年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.926921865203387
    },
    {
        "question": " 188年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.993721713163813
    },
    {
        "question": " 32.2年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.006429668679615
    },
    {
        "question": " 5733日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1960693987070625
    },
    {
        "question": " 36.5万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.9429749687045135
    },
    {
        "question": " 1643日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.373988094540012
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.64兆時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.809151182927996
    },
    {
        "question": " 5432時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.354761383473819
    },
    {
        "question": " 206万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.09208560478554
    },
    {
        "question": " 182時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.81591380015463
    },
    {
        "question": " 8214万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.193885091450183
    },
    {
        "question": " 638億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.646377415453619
    },
    {
        "question": " 38.9億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.812266825393971
    },
    {
        "question": " 1336分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.903931875386437
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.52億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0480286660491833
    },
    {
        "question": " 22.2兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.410090490754019
    },
    {
        "question": " 1805億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.7002733504426395
    },
    {
        "question": " 142万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.374026842137411
    },
    {
        "question": " 101秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.003609996522968
    },
    {
        "question": " 55.5兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.2457267147474775
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.6兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.268651895299994
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.29京msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.961338616233151
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.56兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.414964286622734
    },
    {
        "question": " 6893万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.838387178298717
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.92msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.996367538527407
    },
    {
        "question": " 1711京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.734478039930437
    },
    {
        "question": " 4747京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.739887812636379
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.08京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.477532153345734
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.56億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.4146406471167907
    },
    {
        "question": " 2824億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.450842525189426
    },
    {
        "question": " 798万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.9022091533563783
    },
    {
        "question": " 1590usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.201456643652329
    },
    {
        "question": " 145京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6634669002405988
    },
    {
        "question": " 112京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.1141239053541865
    },
    {
        "question": " 1293京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.555208761620593
    },
    {
        "question": " 4213京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.84641496755948
    },
    {
        "question": " 247京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.391972177354837
    },
    {
        "question": " 174万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 0.2404166316648093
    },
    {
        "question": " 124億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.093000266217726
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.33万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.28922343863093
    },
    {
        "question": " 121万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.519326833274923
    },
    {
        "question": " 551日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.12165033668729
    },
    {
        "question": " 90.7億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.014926206868559
    },
    {
        "question": " 934万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.590243194783127
    },
    {
        "question": " 22時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.1201227150343644
    },
    {
        "question": " 770兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.165654370896334
    },
    {
        "question": " 8998分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7957735743088146
    },
    {
        "question": " 6803分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.054571395164456
    },
    {
        "question": " 76.7分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.663081221087058
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.6分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.943000520390413
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.9京秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.754889451104662
    },
    {
        "question": " 2148万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3954979379038988
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.65兆秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.266552054237563
    },
    {
        "question": " 31万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.71270013584832
    },
    {
        "question": " 34.6万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.539253338302082
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.35兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.871638383089872
    },
    {
        "question": " 11億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1058806223295214
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.33億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9657701377395398
    },
    {
        "question": " 234兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.591185017774732
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.88兆msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.994703085836036
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.9msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.227823324761253
    },
    {
        "question": " 176兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7458026106151661
    },
    {
        "question": " 2324億usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.4298264934555107
    },
    {
        "question": " 29.1京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.907603832737866
    },
    {
        "question": " 213兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.550247131930847
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.61億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6632441797624162
    },
    {
        "question": " 25.1億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.399386728548059
    },
    {
        "question": " 129万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.111589315590447
    },
    {
        "question": " 9829垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.493702059313283
    },
    {
        "question": " 43.3垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.700239180094001
    },
    {
        "question": " 157兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6387397684595062
    },
    {
        "question": " 33.4兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.745179498434427
    },
    {
        "question": " 30.5京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.484921197707534
    },
    {
        "question": " 810兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.90855230278711
    },
    {
        "question": " 62.1億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.792892378767733
    },
    {
        "question": " 87.7年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.441760046077047
    },
    {
        "question": " 3401億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.96932563424293
    },
    {
        "question": " 425日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.0082416791568996
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.76万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.404500883680409
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.37万日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.740873174610092
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.33日は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.573035312524693
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.44億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.5935086841940596
    },
    {
        "question": " 5371万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.349838760932367
    },
    {
        "question": " 38.9兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.869229262025758
    },
    {
        "question": " 311億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.334069061866116
    },
    {
        "question": " 15万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.396616667200706
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.97万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.67945468838091
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.62分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.196280176528468
    },
    {
        "question": " 271兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.934570239156414
    },
    {
        "question": " 58.4兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.830079155365116
    },
    {
        "question": " 28.1億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.891994682657621
    },
    {
        "question": " 4773万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.900674627489323
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.62万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.6648768160313265
    },
    {
        "question": " 230兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.863064232090493
    },
    {
        "question": " 8811億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.008544950779427
    },
    {
        "question": " 161億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.6507812533628603
    },
    {
        "question": " 1341億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.349365761469134
    },
    {
        "question": " 739万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.8688081326806367
    },
    {
        "question": " 21.7万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.336490069843247
    },
    {
        "question": " 9657msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.984831036352169
    },
    {
        "question": " 49.7京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.197544788391671
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.2京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.779435784073204
    },
    {
        "question": " 303兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.925145547722897
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.99京usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.519986527385559
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.35億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9214304672292792
    },
    {
        "question": " 3973万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.599173070722263
    },
    {
        "question": " 492垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.193064575879507
    },
    {
        "question": " 117垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.132093206931259
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.06垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.292272391611208
    },
    {
        "question": " 739兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.0902225802173895
    },
    {
        "question": " 25.8億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.4121153404025657
    },
    {
        "question": " 22.8兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.35755810459477
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.1万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 1.0410274214797988
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.12万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.651673049181344
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.9年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.57269430584265
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.2万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4850083030266146
    },
    {
        "question": " 139万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.301581511553747
    },
    {
        "question": " 5015日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.636747241905057
    },
    {
        "question": " 46.2兆時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.722228451639682
    },
    {
        "question": " 2847時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.0741197322764924
    },
    {
        "question": " 44万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.421906883163826
    },
    {
        "question": " 85.6時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.488576223864544
    },
    {
        "question": " 169兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.507326589185674
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.45万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2308926312231416
    },
    {
        "question": " 370分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7905080900261696
    },
    {
        "question": " 5428分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.512776605354308
    },
    {
        "question": " 28.4京秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.954986505617539
    },
    {
        "question": " 189万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3400396998552588
    },
    {
        "question": " 7843億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.338205132841814
    },
    {
        "question": " 350秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7662923880428751
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.76万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.244839289570107
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.98秒は何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.599623794806767
    },
    {
        "question": " 3885億msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.090561606371595
    },
    {
        "question": " 243億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4495411471350614
    },
    {
        "question": " 1028億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.455609000722487
    },
    {
        "question": " 4197万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8447591006399375
    },
    {
        "question": " 3003万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.477530194789971
    },
    {
        "question": " 367msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 5.564475770403886
    },
    {
        "question": " 7692兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3872517378096303
    },
    {
        "question": " 94.7京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.0398453478837055
    },
    {
        "question": " 359億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9989055481746822
    },
    {
        "question": " 230億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5840499141575846
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.46億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1637037066307907
    },
    {
        "question": " 1273usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 0.10482797596642057
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.543e+04垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.050512145343843
    },
    {
        "question": " 1956垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.354876092397216
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.25兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.30397476286855407
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.7兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2504560515648944
    },
    {
        "question": " 887兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.947835814194878
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.31億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 2.86409995259308
    },
    {
        "question": " 2672億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.42689654494525
    },
    {
        "question": " 103万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.57622363843877
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.89年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.89148231714098
    },
    {
        "question": " 2909年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.184352554194938
    },
    {
        "question": " 1385億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.579265984699473
    },
    {
        "question": " 4767日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.05842252836429
    },
    {
        "question": " 477日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.836584881565802
    },
    {
        "question": " 78.1日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.829237961584739
    },
    {
        "question": " 2444万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.445614021758394
    },
    {
        "question": " 301万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.098037395391431
    },
    {
        "question": " 4070万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.387766007067256
    },
    {
        "question": " 267億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.705511529909344
    },
    {
        "question": " 7749分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7309128556677214
    },
    {
        "question": " 1023万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.231734730630487
    },
    {
        "question": " 341万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.31142012717745
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.79分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.45881887952021
    },
    {
        "question": " 1698兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.731087395216482
    },
    {
        "question": " 9338億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.03374900499457
    },
    {
        "question": " 261万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.860816991779381
    },
    {
        "question": " 1341秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3494319902839902
    },
    {
        "question": " 9765秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.989690336510646
    },
    {
        "question": " 41.9京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.123761125680691
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.61京msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.479542854511052
    },
    {
        "question": " 465億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.111309114698809
    },
    {
        "question": " 250兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.61935170105351
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.71億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.234116037824022
    },
    {
        "question": " 45万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.653602252463111
    },
    {
        "question": " 855垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.433242789293336
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.26京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.693120587841296
    },
    {
        "question": " 252京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.844588379334153
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.85京usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.116916117094162
    },
    {
        "question": " 6541億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.815618650355233
    },
    {
        "question": " 24.9億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.395633128734818
    },
    {
        "question": " 515usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 5.712049246742251
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.47垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.312085905560777
    },
    {
        "question": " 3021京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.543668054548872
    },
    {
        "question": " 31.6京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.943372610122517
    },
    {
        "question": " 2670億nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6482839861416068
    },
    {
        "question": " 4284兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.631894137930782
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.18億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 2.0730318188076744
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.17兆nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.912430031191379
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.63万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.31307124996433
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.32万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5572647503125858
    },
    {
        "question": " 28日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8268039674536984
    },
    {
        "question": " 61.6日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.947847505221404
    },
    {
        "question": " 61.7日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.7269939551682265
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.16億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.019486027794631
    },
    {
        "question": " 157時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8167298866539829
    },
    {
        "question": " 82.5万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.694357861140748
    },
    {
        "question": " 658時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.374244581368528
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.29億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.1977957110010538
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.04億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.858572449806575
    },
    {
        "question": " 23.1万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.585132486286935
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.61分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.335918105449423
    },
    {
        "question": " 82.2分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.69279422897226
    },
    {
        "question": " 138億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6412028020295395
    },
    {
        "question": " 750万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.93879569480514
    },
    {
        "question": " 285億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.898770521869712
    },
    {
        "question": " 36.4億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.783092935358856
    },
    {
        "question": " 39.8万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.599360158311605
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.9京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.728351178311868
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.19京msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.778618806002697
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.61億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.650649480210532
    },
    {
        "question": " 1259万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3218671522831933
    },
    {
        "question": " 465億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.667307886036465
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.04万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.606785335883491
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.21京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.4652903683301615
    },
    {
        "question": " 27.2兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4980913257377733
    },
    {
        "question": " 2080兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.761784387278906
    },
    {
        "question": " 18.2京usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.480955118389097
    },
    {
        "question": " 227万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.35533723431240505
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.25万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.5120050361857196
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.51usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 3.741430714527495
    },
    {
        "question": " 212垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.8267382306984015
    },
    {
        "question": " 21.9京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.403188092655344
    },
    {
        "question": " 4871兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.1313571223817283
    },
    {
        "question": " 42.6京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.8515787251614215
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.5億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.16027203195012607
    },
    {
        "question": " 1142万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.057503978642056
    },
    {
        "question": " 155万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 3.189750309916868
    },
    {
        "question": " 31.5万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.060120833621163
    },
    {
        "question": " 162年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.7087797147998
    },
    {
        "question": " 231万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.801072566641878
    },
    {
        "question": " 104万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.395731120515153
    },
    {
        "question": " 501万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.857826646761215
    },
    {
        "question": " 866億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.995068199495192
    },
    {
        "question": " 4047万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.226978607364874
    },
    {
        "question": " 523時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.496947810855404
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.37時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.931541686035308
    },
    {
        "question": " 40.4兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.886042293561055
    },
    {
        "question": " 151億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.019392338229661
    },
    {
        "question": " 113分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.2742989454077316
    },
    {
        "question": " 19.8万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.073768230541699
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.61兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.250384155391621
    },
    {
        "question": " 85.9兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.997613904040458
    },
    {
        "question": " 800万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.3469308549192824
    },
    {
        "question": " 8367万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.144403365190829
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.45万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.160606730788167
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.07秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.028129331453169
    },
    {
        "question": " 28.6京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.956803967495376
    },
    {
        "question": " 50.7京msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.768230712755539
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.2億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.531171439561372
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.36億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.356732907378955
    },
    {
        "question": " 48.5万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.686145864240599
    },
    {
        "question": " 2933msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.46724990306509
    },
    {
        "question": " 394兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0966524747029527
    },
    {
        "question": " 55兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.803943206722488
    },
    {
        "question": " 3039億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9263960478026254
    },
    {
        "question": " 37.4億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7942998321529713
    },
    {
        "question": " 6860兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.836295817775072
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.68兆usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.754612859970631
    },
    {
        "question": " 64.2万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 8.80782710817997
    },
    {
        "question": " 71.4垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.3549094510578765
    },
    {
        "question": " 1713兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2971698925355502
    },
    {
        "question": " 5719京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.20099890715963
    },
    {
        "question": " 84兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.1460988621859265
    },
    {
        "question": " 596京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.775504223104459
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.01億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 2.7002095875659693
    },
    {
        "question": " 114億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.058058192894382
    },
    {
        "question": " 3222年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.450656768469158
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.41年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.368535520745986
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.87万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7086373114550035
    },
    {
        "question": " 2157万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.713955314526903
    },
    {
        "question": " 66.2万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.979085089240218
    },
    {
        "question": " 10日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.936741612776649
    },
    {
        "question": " 78.4兆時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.951640212612123
    },
    {
        "question": " 311億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.11216861533426
    },
    {
        "question": " 23.5万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.149084723147539
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.81時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.2383240345839415
    },
    {
        "question": " 761時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.437731400108449
    },
    {
        "question": " 130兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.392075737193506
    },
    {
        "question": " 384万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.425478102890449
    },
    {
        "question": " 526万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.942904071772375
    },
    {
        "question": " 45.4分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.435551259846307
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.02兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.8058731286407665
    },
    {
        "question": " 1294億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.175583027121062
    },
    {
        "question": " 20兆秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.745124296943333
    },
    {
        "question": " 351億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.767660834109318
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.21兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5856070229467323
    },
    {
        "question": " 50.5京msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.766535800790688
    },
    {
        "question": " 116兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.50657426148409
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.91兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.5034778759005425
    },
    {
        "question": " 259億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.4139957635321485
    },
    {
        "question": " 36.9msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.5673882463875115
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.76msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.245003459685398
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.71京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7340365751922944
    },
    {
        "question": " 253兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.467454318169901
    },
    {
        "question": " 53.4兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.171284019820116
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.17億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.559038655335381
    },
    {
        "question": " 356万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5514669678555395
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.85万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.4550179238830596
    },
    {
        "question": " 3511usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.545388405361846
    },
    {
        "question": " 33.4京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0251133141097046
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.97京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3569611000243382
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.53兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.3745501426929665
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.31京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.340681581320849
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.36兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.1320007860995194
    },
    {
        "question": " 43.1億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.634795012135031
    },
    {
        "question": " 18.5億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.26826541768855
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.43年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.097331464593396
    },
    {
        "question": " 1763年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.188649508516706
    },
    {
        "question": " 26.9年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.928729746053351
    },
    {
        "question": " 8416日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3627941673247157
    },
    {
        "question": " 490日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.070082315454972
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.5日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.8120029409494762
    },
    {
        "question": " 3420億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.591523607604649
    },
    {
        "question": " 317億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.121500159012763
    },
    {
        "question": " 3180時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.280521253248496
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.08億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7672452045394804
    },
    {
        "question": " 3411分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.37451185756724903
    },
    {
        "question": " 174分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.4631025262553601
    },
    {
        "question": " 40.7万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.387558658458025
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.27万分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.133665207488587
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.86兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.95793712516768
    },
    {
        "question": " 324兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.573574009556866
    },
    {
        "question": " 9969秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.4423669463435509
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.94億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.689485383275203
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.25京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.2209621926499405
    },
    {
        "question": " 633兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.864974911180408
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.96億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.395852968782637
    },
    {
        "question": " 180億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.477870314729234
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.46万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1632928113734031
    },
    {
        "question": " 3051msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.484371751096388
    },
    {
        "question": " 7775msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.890696511697357
    },
    {
        "question": " 2760京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.9420400915650795
    },
    {
        "question": " 35.5兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6142175921921282
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.63京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.862881416439233
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.82京usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.803660238036224
    },
    {
        "question": " 2744兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.438462357446312
    },
    {
        "question": " 174万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.241186308938644
    },
    {
        "question": " 254万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.404506882850267
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.453e+04垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.663323299156273
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.73垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.499505140752505
    },
    {
        "question": " 1918兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.726538385553414
    },
    {
        "question": " 268京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.650049084253383
    },
    {
        "question": " 380億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5799810425574012
    },
    {
        "question": " 102億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.00700235067159
    },
    {
        "question": " 4455nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 0.6488409585415478
    },
    {
        "question": " 62.9万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.741038965903659
    },
    {
        "question": " 223年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.068844708472309
    },
    {
        "question": " 114万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.4929283996265594
    },
    {
        "question": " 252日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.560388198036403
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.58万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.25665808838847615
    },
    {
        "question": " 33.2万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.140920778607261
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.46万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.720200588000068
    },
    {
        "question": " 101兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.283484448065177
    },
    {
        "question": " 2971億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.314557876849216
    },
    {
        "question": " 5903億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.992948963110587
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.11分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4867305370771877
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.29分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.889006872019031
    },
    {
        "question": " 131億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.618368284378586
    },
    {
        "question": " 1669億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.285867618105132
    },
    {
        "question": " 50.6万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.147623874050897
    },
    {
        "question": " 2684万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.650674254421465
    },
    {
        "question": " 1534秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.185731335405039
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.39垓msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.880294463997181
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.91京msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.344338957569647
    },
    {
        "question": " 53.6億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.1730125583407096
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.99兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.919689043902952
    },
    {
        "question": " 133万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.123042573398128
    },
    {
        "question": " 92.5万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.965940766036693
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.69京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.068775159684135
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.42兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7093443262354602
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.06兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4684151062299033
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.34京usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.745438207553356
    },
    {
        "question": " 6126億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.787188924924566
    },
    {
        "question": " 5150億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.711845773555607
    },
    {
        "question": " 131京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6178360013920434
    },
    {
        "question": " 454京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.7202111053580325
    },
    {
        "question": " 3528京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.991276257636833
    },
    {
        "question": " 7398億nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.090962620648388
    },
    {
        "question": " 136兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.132687845931109
    },
    {
        "question": " 661億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.819959226123239
    },
    {
        "question": " 222万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 3.345790253023254
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.48万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.2134211398667825
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.03年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.2016725608545595
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.88億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.712675199704808
    },
    {
        "question": " 5658日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.132845283666249
    },
    {
        "question": " 5068億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.762291994805066
    },
    {
        "question": " 78.3億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.513536086323008
    },
    {
        "question": " 414時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.39550019121496
    },
    {
        "question": " 227億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.635227895653213
    },
    {
        "question": " 7265分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7028845813534901
    },
    {
        "question": " 58.9万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.9918354189802185
    },
    {
        "question": " 5192万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.493484954025464
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.56万分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.185619808766582
    },
    {
        "question": " 2億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8028821306650358
    },
    {
        "question": " 38.7億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.651116219394251
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.3億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.655175763694941
    },
    {
        "question": " 68.6億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.058372077397344
    },
    {
        "question": " 98.5兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.494633090564615
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.33億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.43022967529873
    },
    {
        "question": " 1095億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.483207723028661
    },
    {
        "question": " 1348億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.351453691706997
    },
    {
        "question": " 9019msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9551344020951957
    },
    {
        "question": " 33.6msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.526678532494657
    },
    {
        "question": " 3358msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.526023602375036
    },
    {
        "question": " 780京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.393250517211586
    },
    {
        "question": " 8761兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.0060703774844235
    },
    {
        "question": " 2996兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.920210822422906
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.5兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.381947627748474
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.36億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3736512692540837
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.5億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.097569992138818
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.37usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 3.640400229005496
    },
    {
        "question": " 6716垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.328279896877882
    },
    {
        "question": " 5777垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.825214576252142
    },
    {
        "question": " 3138京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.940417378693234
    },
    {
        "question": " 291兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.6861647533269473
    },
    {
        "question": " 397京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.598263725275519
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.38億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 2.7306032887312126
    },
    {
        "question": " 45億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.653067677662996
    },
    {
        "question": " 1378年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.701551645762207
    },
    {
        "question": " 588年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.7116490701106635
    },
    {
        "question": " 5883万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.207328385887741
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.12万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.428234030803879
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.1日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.067031886064094
    },
    {
        "question": " 913日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.897205569811028
    },
    {
        "question": " 76.9日は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.822466995324778
    },
    {
        "question": " 40.1万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6609938870393892
    },
    {
        "question": " 160億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.824741424567614
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.46万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.366239360432319
    },
    {
        "question": " 124時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.6489533583795
    },
    {
        "question": " 306億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.765067212057889
    },
    {
        "question": " 105万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.864071335646945
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.07億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.250529094819198
    },
    {
        "question": " 1474分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.946539981678684
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.55分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.9697550202900045
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.25兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.012468928080099
    },
    {
        "question": " 3800万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6433267909226577
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.57億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.638568481924741
    },
    {
        "question": " 971秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2091524002258813
    },
    {
        "question": " 60.4京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.282310529777073
    },
    {
        "question": " 1737億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.3032100654184093
    },
    {
        "question": " 3176億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.945519220139674
    },
    {
        "question": " 9256万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.188296111292975
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.41億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.806867828887273
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.3万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.124064991983929
    },
    {
        "question": " 5437京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.236575759062525
    },
    {
        "question": " 12京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.143607196358972
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.2兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.678666944612028
    },
    {
        "question": " 316兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.721776645491481
    },
    {
        "question": " 1247兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.095885126662393
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.24兆usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.627719356459119
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.57usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 3.5523441332533254
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.79京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.07981569543868527
    },
    {
        "question": " 5539垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.806953286513087
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.5京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.8420845550633853
    },
    {
        "question": " 19兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5013286852121053
    },
    {
        "question": " 3977兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.599505226857052
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.49億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 2.812098775733981
    },
    {
        "question": " 23万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 2.3623210962871433
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.39万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.706147045476128
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.44万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.81410356531801
    },
    {
        "question": " 1113年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.767040530957456
    },
    {
        "question": " 895日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.38931253250427456
    },
    {
        "question": " 9184万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.343239000726753
    },
    {
        "question": " 727日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.020151510318731
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.46万日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.74705332978563
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.39万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.4359551756513913
    },
    {
        "question": " 9870時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6141071676809724
    },
    {
        "question": " 42.1時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.4025053076902614
    },
    {
        "question": " 81.6時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.467866050290699
    },
    {
        "question": " 26.9億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.708990459901913
    },
    {
        "question": " 7450万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.713822486946082
    },
    {
        "question": " 3237万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.732030501174462
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.36分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7496217689106617
    },
    {
        "question": " 2808兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.94963818574333
    },
    {
        "question": " 8506億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.993208908227445
    },
    {
        "question": " 940万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.4169068298373872
    },
    {
        "question": " 1630秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4340310916264887
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.13京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.354033197622434
    },
    {
        "question": " 9451億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.038957409172484
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.3億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.455528679649601
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.43億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.1961659506236115
    },
    {
        "question": " 1610万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.20689063394571
    },
    {
        "question": " 4843msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.6850836066451444
    },
    {
        "question": " 1264msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.101860647650266
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.41京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.4748801696223075
    },
    {
        "question": " 1530億usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.24823034999147509
    },
    {
        "question": " 122億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5284832084195823
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.66兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.442462004481248
    },
    {
        "question": " 215億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.331720428320769
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.83兆usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.451836860405137
    },
    {
        "question": " 720usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 5.857434056449384
    },
    {
        "question": " 32.8京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0174927408202328
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.7垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.231509444030802
    },
    {
        "question": " 39.1京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.035961375127249
    },
    {
        "question": " 17京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.452925797231978
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.6兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.221251582211648
    },
    {
        "question": " 2526億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.402378555467453
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.91万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 1.2803056947815006
    },
    {
        "question": " 48.1万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.244685227180712
    },
    {
        "question": " 679年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.55250567093246
    },
    {
        "question": " 2401日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8181605657456437
    },
    {
        "question": " 3459日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.919125860389837
    },
    {
        "question": " 79.1兆時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.955704299880054
    },
    {
        "question": " 295億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.089960396931904
    },
    {
        "question": " 2138万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.108200203603767
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.3時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.610428828407959
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.73時間は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.794886755265889
    },
    {
        "question": " 321兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.785940974706767
    },
    {
        "question": " 190億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.120508133416667
    },
    {
        "question": " 530分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9463105873621946
    },
    {
        "question": " 4995分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.476720769662101
    },
    {
        "question": " 77.5兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.390445632907086
    },
    {
        "question": " 67.5億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.892800126239427
    },
    {
        "question": " 5497億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.183789640016226
    },
    {
        "question": " 153秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.40666664388941953
    },
    {
        "question": " 50.6万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.70395802949292
    },
    {
        "question": " 68.6秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.836567197046012
    },
    {
        "question": " 3808兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.081865462883798
    },
    {
        "question": " 216億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.397993499103409
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.24京msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.538023732584746
    },
    {
        "question": " 1165億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.288266331553346
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.3万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7239245065098319
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.33万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.522503972078775
    },
    {
        "question": " 40.8京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.112328675251117
    },
    {
        "question": " 564京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.814627077357587
    },
    {
        "question": " 22.9京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.803812897426226
    },
    {
        "question": " 2141億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.552415816256965
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.59兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.5551140600623325
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.26兆usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.721212456725436
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.07万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 7.849598180911919
    },
    {
        "question": " 2755垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.941285121193781
    },
    {
        "question": " 665兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8865129488704593
    },
    {
        "question": " 1176京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.514097786821621
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.56兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.0386238318327496
    },
    {
        "question": " 338億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5284062376253882
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.91兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.7714784386925615
    },
    {
        "question": " 425万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 3.628895362303969
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.6年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.626788290075389
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.54年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.242355020533884
    },
    {
        "question": " 2108万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.761623070136226
    },
    {
        "question": " 764日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.263048287716819
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.97日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.934373363229642
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.85兆時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.642796978619833
    },
    {
        "question": " 320億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.124298105707041
    },
    {
        "question": " 7013時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.6240341963235805
    },
    {
        "question": " 39.7時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.1552604616565025
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.05時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.040578461675196
    },
    {
        "question": " 5745億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.038639816931148
    },
    {
        "question": " 161億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.048143454427803
    },
    {
        "question": " 245万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.610402047349136
    },
    {
        "question": " 27.6分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.219199900383324
    },
    {
        "question": " 2316分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.142834768998595
    },
    {
        "question": " 43.7億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.142053972263298
    },
    {
        "question": " 1019億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.071813026859724
    },
    {
        "question": " 77.6万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3335802174911633
    },
    {
        "question": " 80.9万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.12973719008649
    },
    {
        "question": " 181秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.257328566876639
    },
    {
        "question": " 215兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.8346200345536676
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.12兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.110921534562577
    },
    {
        "question": " 628万msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.24195671494879445
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.28億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.852886691786934
    },
    {
        "question": " 3989万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.600904703809777
    },
    {
        "question": " 150msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 5.176327514441057
    },
    {
        "question": " 234msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 8.369744001172466
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.73垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.25966541945326
    },
    {
        "question": " 3966兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.661883466740626
    },
    {
        "question": " 45.7京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.103362353440085
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.14兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.010092974953145
    },
    {
        "question": " 1345万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1287842651587143
    },
    {
        "question": " 3182万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.502762521318088
    },
    {
        "question": " 39.5万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 8.596716403038599
    },
    {
        "question": " 7178垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.357184208848896
    },
    {
        "question": " 194京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.3507256068421025
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.61京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.6499982786112852
    },
    {
        "question": " 139兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.3657150467198638
    },
    {
        "question": " 310億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.491309202833676
    },
    {
        "question": " 138億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.138535999806915
    },
    {
        "question": " 1627nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 0.21125814916042818
    },
    {
        "question": " 2397万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.817379048154256
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.39日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7594588525704857
    },
    {
        "question": " 67.8万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.989797351139085
    },
    {
        "question": " 711日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.788089335416474
    },
    {
        "question": " 53.5万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.785678973105439
    },
    {
        "question": " 216時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9546694412740142
    },
    {
        "question": " 163万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.989091486965087
    },
    {
        "question": " 1237時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.648682511730522
    },
    {
        "question": " 105万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.301653646461828
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.29億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.640506734591103
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.2万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.185724876556674
    },
    {
        "question": " 18.5兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.768561435218167
    },
    {
        "question": " 1296万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1760445191240296
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.17万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2342809911417485
    },
    {
        "question": " 27億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.653851534696222
    },
    {
        "question": " 340万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.531712469431591
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.1秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.0448218718301545
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.78垓msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.751728131454776
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.1億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8487535924569689
    },
    {
        "question": " 82.7億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.3609444344567994
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.89億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.216974362518343
    },
    {
        "question": " 234億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.369525242030594
    },
    {
        "question": " 26.1万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.41687214318541
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.37京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8759926953370742
    },
    {
        "question": " 1347兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.1927104022021595
    },
    {
        "question": " 593京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.216736922533176
    },
    {
        "question": " 401億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.825228206966204
    },
    {
        "question": " 2499億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.397777993528354
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.37万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.3747895315338565
    },
    {
        "question": " 1075京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5324770702899038
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.3京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.1868513836728996
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.18京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.7817816385931033
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.47兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8719302458392229
    },
    {
        "question": " 72.8京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.862052089304276
    },
    {
        "question": " 3939万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.5954198252741358
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.78兆nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.444556935091214
    },
    {
        "question": " 703万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.409089144638523
    },
    {
        "question": " 4313年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.5772968255906195
    },
    {
        "question": " 4469億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.08789824490418
    },
    {
        "question": " 7131日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.233332942485442
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.3日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.0497020876539
    },
    {
        "question": " 1576万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.254996817088119
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.19万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.960766413528461
    },
    {
        "question": " 25.4万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.1823551450628695
    },
    {
        "question": " 50.4時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.258861910839624
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.9時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.667608460701225
    },
    {
        "question": " 23.2兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.644516841207089
    },
    {
        "question": " 2450万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.230783924703934
    },
    {
        "question": " 188分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.49623671730859575
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.35万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.910081076291736
    },
    {
        "question": " 45.2兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.156030226215773
    },
    {
        "question": " 404万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6699782368127647
    },
    {
        "question": " 1060万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.4691200906008532
    },
    {
        "question": " 1005秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.22397406972088
    },
    {
        "question": " 27.3秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.435762572104618
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.3秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.112724306514639
    },
    {
        "question": " 21.4京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.8323616095576964
    },
    {
        "question": " 93.2兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.032936152135784
    },
    {
        "question": " 4677兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.113647731315094
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.69兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.652132460562973
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.88億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.588821496752648
    },
    {
        "question": " 26.2万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.418144019666192
    },
    {
        "question": " 7945京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.401294800517835
    },
    {
        "question": " 2015兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.367721721091287
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.91兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.0359502759143684
    },
    {
        "question": " 560億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9702016163480627
    },
    {
        "question": " 3959兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.597620115019485
    },
    {
        "question": " 252万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.4013891828157536
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.022e+04垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.806926476667423
    },
    {
        "question": " 7788垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.954927700452233
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.54京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.25905895982162
    },
    {
        "question": " 45兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8747919888139895
    },
    {
        "question": " 156兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.193486400949876
    },
    {
        "question": " 1576万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.1975568776855083
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.34万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 1.6378985000053092
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.25万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.6592105199771545
    },
    {
        "question": " 4791万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.118115939186842
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.3日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.503188980055252
    },
    {
        "question": " 121万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.24035613228899
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.62兆時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.475712579997511
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.24万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.713242671119999
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.31時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1410597952009045
    },
    {
        "question": " 214万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6094495546220247
    },
    {
        "question": " 26.3億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.262136439497267
    },
    {
        "question": " 1133万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.275999603410253
    },
    {
        "question": " 1856万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.046841510655083
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.92京秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.09416224636614
    },
    {
        "question": " 117億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.133505301287346
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.71万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1999602400181997
    },
    {
        "question": " 220秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.565133970976549
    },
    {
        "question": " 400秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.60244873516147
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.34秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.637592708010942
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.82兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7610560745555748
    },
    {
        "question": " 2811億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.512408907373421
    },
    {
        "question": " 2632兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.863919657079084
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.6兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.970031847064608
    },
    {
        "question": " 56.4万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.751205973866738
    },
    {
        "question": " 1msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 3.0009457188077415
    },
    {
        "question": " 1490兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6744214875531738
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.62兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7279547203243528
    },
    {
        "question": " 67.9兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.2754441944806505
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.43兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.608061320912151
    },
    {
        "question": " 4232万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6265813260219397
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.31兆usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.519828034929299
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.47万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 7.16657383828328
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.7京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.569369434703979
    },
    {
        "question": " 8234京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.979089075146307
    },
    {
        "question": " 1116兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4912550667956337
    },
    {
        "question": " 877兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.164703968205274
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.44兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.808938221376091
    },
    {
        "question": " 3165兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.500427002896481
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.6万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 2.1002128196645256
    },
    {
        "question": " 526年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.283290499230421
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.79年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.834318982942522
    },
    {
        "question": " 1903日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7170671997996125
    },
    {
        "question": " 8324日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.300548662881979
    },
    {
        "question": " 118万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.228469561813554
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.57万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.25224989598947256
    },
    {
        "question": " 147時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7870480518557188
    },
    {
        "question": " 253時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.959149997357526
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.65億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.841263072171749
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.49万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4943393177544484
    },
    {
        "question": " 3533分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.770001701392443
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.59万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.332743117281706
    },
    {
        "question": " 373億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.073136052705502
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.7兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.132566236391852
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.13兆秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.49843293267672
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.09億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.2601155807792095
    },
    {
        "question": " 217万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.336194563881236
    },
    {
        "question": " 1117億msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5493433428317274
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.1兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.384862365317279
    },
    {
        "question": " 7335万msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3091111185454074
    },
    {
        "question": " 30.6億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.7073267976442255
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.2億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.342296077319565
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.72万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.434145278760928
    },
    {
        "question": " 193msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 8.284808854882149
    },
    {
        "question": " 38兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.08059922525665786
    },
    {
        "question": " 340兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.5943784051077365
    },
    {
        "question": " 2507京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.842937438804448
    },
    {
        "question": " 48.7兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.909694085887487
    },
    {
        "question": " 72.2億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.858691654699463
    },
    {
        "question": " 182万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.2608775994881745
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.23垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.127730853303181
    },
    {
        "question": " 657兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8807882713243131
    },
    {
        "question": " 2088京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.763400970698753
    },
    {
        "question": " 70.9京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.072206277423375
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.9京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.251853833032738
    },
    {
        "question": " 2057万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.3132224078257992
    },
    {
        "question": " 5982万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.776860245556332
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.9万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.763916490766549
    },
    {
        "question": " 6102年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.728004982921387
    },
    {
        "question": " 3350年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.245687653432457
    },
    {
        "question": " 30.1年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.977616187780669
    },
    {
        "question": " 1649万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.655043559423592
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.69万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.947676345445013
    },
    {
        "question": " 25.6日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.5658524042273445
    },
    {
        "question": " 155億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.2488134592074545
    },
    {
        "question": " 29.7万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.0919934757384215
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.6万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.972322932223416
    },
    {
        "question": " 407時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.166160141354119
    },
    {
        "question": " 23.9時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.934377575405471
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.83億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.730914194909065
    },
    {
        "question": " 850億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.770847663060455
    },
    {
        "question": " 1108分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2662590018973918
    },
    {
        "question": " 2136分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.107672009084615
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.39億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8792179637529141
    },
    {
        "question": " 570万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8192465956955062
    },
    {
        "question": " 27.5万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8822687078845135
    },
    {
        "question": " 46.6万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.890601704966208
    },
    {
        "question": " 4783京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.180919763511032
    },
    {
        "question": " 5827億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.8289684659130288
    },
    {
        "question": " 61.4億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.231966655909817
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.2兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.232533926873483
    },
    {
        "question": " 193億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.286318225481205
    },
    {
        "question": " 84.7万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.927694607744291
    },
    {
        "question": " 34.5垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.038805724555045
    },
    {
        "question": " 5335京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.79063302338495
    },
    {
        "question": " 382兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.025562449757846
    },
    {
        "question": " 346億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.761371586176582
    },
    {
        "question": " 664億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.822446667075146
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.3万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 2.0540700454787264
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.12usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 3.7867011340105283
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.5垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.560272460038436
    },
    {
        "question": " 1043京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.081867430766703
    },
    {
        "question": " 71.2京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.296467939834101
    },
    {
        "question": " 1757億nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.46652022380136215
    },
    {
        "question": " 4720兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.673937223138013
    },
    {
        "question": " 41.3兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.616177683961376
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.37億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 5.640763292609337
    },
    {
        "question": " 1148万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.622080727332309
    },
    {
        "question": " 821年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.857077286432468
    },
    {
        "question": " 77.3億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.325607440888691
    },
    {
        "question": " 221日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.7246400429990665
    },
    {
        "question": " 747日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.0317290252531865
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.44億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.593590429216993
    },
    {
        "question": " 2539時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.0244871715469914
    },
    {
        "question": " 43.7万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.196590998655687
    },
    {
        "question": " 1266万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3818855192016577
    },
    {
        "question": " 116万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9055767450570302
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.5億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.382779969990074
    },
    {
        "question": " 50.2分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.478580420595039
    },
    {
        "question": " 1382分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.918691145867351
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.09分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.736629391861502
    },
    {
        "question": " 476億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.1789589298070986
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.67兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.887544098080528
    },
    {
        "question": " 65.8億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.262172730479641
    },
    {
        "question": " 35.5億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.772431013281858
    },
    {
        "question": " 51.8秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.714200098127559
    },
    {
        "question": " 52.9兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.2249464198648115
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.1億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6762988532086289
    },
    {
        "question": " 1202兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.523661632647784
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.8億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.802059610232831
    },
    {
        "question": " 2046億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.310941152874472
    },
    {
        "question": " 450msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 8.653252706263094
    },
    {
        "question": " 105兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5229651428129656
    },
    {
        "question": " 14兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2098623820574534
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.13京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.059809596352615
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.35京usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.746769265160884
    },
    {
        "question": " 3054万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4848812863535
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.53兆usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.185944857464364
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.59usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 3.2026350783914226
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.528e+04垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.68529118140736
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.8京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.1702549243039915
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.05京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.466767004730463
    },
    {
        "question": " 476兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.8990856093964066
    },
    {
        "question": " 236億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3722236353316508
    },
    {
        "question": " 150億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.17623270435114
    },
    {
        "question": " 2409万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.38177769651044
    },
    {
        "question": " 3329年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.4648260596072555
    },
    {
        "question": " 4085万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.048923424113827
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.84万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.8329043138839864
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.98兆時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.35449210200481
    },
    {
        "question": " 374億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.192232771092826
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.54億時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.965162758930369
    },
    {
        "question": " 293時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.023217661131346
    },
    {
        "question": " 3447億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.81677829326265
    },
    {
        "question": " 1423億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.994857943541924
    },
    {
        "question": " 2361億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.594869628600941
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.68万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.003312977739272
    },
    {
        "question": " 163分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.989433178097509
    },
    {
        "question": " 1253兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.59923015192416
    },
    {
        "question": " 412兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.677897323961048
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.1万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6502883879261643
    },
    {
        "question": " 6481万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.033476867032679
    },
    {
        "question": " 9470秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.976360080655909
    },
    {
        "question": " 1461兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.665699522728773
    },
    {
        "question": " 1877兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.336975440724695
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.47億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4202104747527766
    },
    {
        "question": " 46.2億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.886145791577472
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.05億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.70347762588672
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.86万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.269107562606764
    },
    {
        "question": " 3211msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.506606910658245
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.39垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.645264863349142
    },
    {
        "question": " 3991億usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6645761417250651
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.19京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.517709659316431
    },
    {
        "question": " 3850兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.807295288082151
    },
    {
        "question": " 4121兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.614995615626977
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.7億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.069484773313409
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.01万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 7.002976746862228
    },
    {
        "question": " 115京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.563406852254845
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.23京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7823512872017373
    },
    {
        "question": " 8791兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.387736706469595
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.68垓nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.650475612429716
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.22京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.964844156625819
    },
    {
        "question": " 1125兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.05106923404974
    },
    {
        "question": " 3535億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.54836024911924
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.36年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.075424939744639
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.64万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.42172685071251
    },
    {
        "question": " 3234万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.889935319330089
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.5兆時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.11992918271471
    },
    {
        "question": " 384億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.20369097183232
    },
    {
        "question": " 438時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.419977187242071
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.16時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.620290109451335
    },
    {
        "question": " 430万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9129262596391485
    },
    {
        "question": " 125億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.940051547863366
    },
    {
        "question": " 3566億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.77405651238639
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.08万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.8116567862891735
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.9万分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.97910701261693
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.27京秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.60648691603163
    },
    {
        "question": " 2787億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.50867599037006
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.27兆秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.54857373800159
    },
    {
        "question": " 560万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.970353636295605
    },
    {
        "question": " 22.1万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.344744235799343
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.31京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.020674984412615
    },
    {
        "question": " 863億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9994200686513928
    },
    {
        "question": " 163億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.656330003705693
    },
    {
        "question": " 118万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2948043463167125
    },
    {
        "question": " 170億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.23077370586843
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.09万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.850830082862037
    },
    {
        "question": " 657兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3186105490566646
    },
    {
        "question": " 2880兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.522932944453652
    },
    {
        "question": " 132億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.56534780643409
    },
    {
        "question": " 158兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.419286624110353
    },
    {
        "question": " 2517億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.400893726258415
    },
    {
        "question": " 115億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.062459580025818
    },
    {
        "question": " 165京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7180048478877208
    },
    {
        "question": " 1217兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1487691315604454
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.54京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.630597432725321
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.8京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.3299412996169835
    },
    {
        "question": " 347京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.540369687789852
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.4億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 2.924256005546554
    },
    {
        "question": " 20.1万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 2.3031903696437404
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.07万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.1715195951256945
    },
    {
        "question": " 38.8年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.531318069831597
    },
    {
        "question": " 1573年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.917355508637536
    },
    {
        "question": " 1303万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.552797979309108
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.63万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.040894586258261
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.27日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.5664280495672
    },
    {
        "question": " 59.7日は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.712386365357519
    },
    {
        "question": " 3749万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.6313631624197296
    },
    {
        "question": " 232億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.985973388555115
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.53万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.325866314507734
    },
    {
        "question": " 1100時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.597582916605889
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.34兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.081588787514409
    },
    {
        "question": " 3622億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.400610680041385
    },
    {
        "question": " 411分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8359497852329967
    },
    {
        "question": " 1331万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.90231196266723
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.93分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.064317282149032
    },
    {
        "question": " 4690兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.17233375956533
    },
    {
        "question": " 30.4万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.545819738597354
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.8兆秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.582244863664164
    },
    {
        "question": " 1015秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2282884582774778
    },
    {
        "question": " 749万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.874635415748727
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.3京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.300414579505946
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.28京msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.78601529912952
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.85兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.711042839456754
    },
    {
        "question": " 772万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1094835005793664
    },
    {
        "question": " 638億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.805159676920905
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.2万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.079591596570996
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.26京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8554244720031416
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.14京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.121257542912481
    },
    {
        "question": " 213兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.772259381195779
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.03億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.23671037236246306
    },
    {
        "question": " 4387万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6421842778073659
    },
    {
        "question": " 3184usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 0.5029566521302786
    },
    {
        "question": " 17usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 4.231389084886778
    },
    {
        "question": " 53.1垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.226694346040718
    },
    {
        "question": " 33.1垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.582817690648261
    },
    {
        "question": " 33京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.9619701342298015
    },
    {
        "question": " 6307兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.021683143135758
    },
    {
        "question": " 46.2億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6642073002887339
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.45兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.538089959561608
    },
    {
        "question": " 36.2億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.558994578146423
    },
    {
        "question": " 9616年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.545307363663417
    },
    {
        "question": " 32.2万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.450669019744819
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.02億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.447728666965598
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.48万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.552548513189334
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.41日は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.084974492420612
    },
    {
        "question": " 1770億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.305367761905787
    },
    {
        "question": " 1308億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.736298117709165
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.34時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1481322608128774
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.01時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.511132534702511
    },
    {
        "question": " 87.6億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.2218072910653115
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.66億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.060612171580498
    },
    {
        "question": " 2656分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6460558640428757
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.69分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.449353405135666
    },
    {
        "question": " 212億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.828477902920868
    },
    {
        "question": " 21.4兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.394272074425329
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.8兆秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.694810593961133
    },
    {
        "question": " 1903万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.50122356971819
    },
    {
        "question": " 57.1万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.756690165963382
    },
    {
        "question": " 1293兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.612686478760311
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.65億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0005827783327725
    },
    {
        "question": " 32兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.948765259500936
    },
    {
        "question": " 56億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.970025016947847
    },
    {
        "question": " 290億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.462053625629796
    },
    {
        "question": " 3991msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.601126657959545
    },
    {
        "question": " 3598京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.057198963041978
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.2京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.921106138747977
    },
    {
        "question": " 71.3京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.296834170430028
    },
    {
        "question": " 697億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.0648033891135897
    },
    {
        "question": " 741兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.869912277107762
    },
    {
        "question": " 2億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.301541624795042
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.88京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.338692149959382
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.53京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4674284484841147
    },
    {
        "question": " 143垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.598832265235963
    },
    {
        "question": " 60兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.999713001171478
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.5京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.019197773869502
    },
    {
        "question": " 108兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.03371486769117
    },
    {
        "question": " 6310nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 0.7999968360105458
    },
    {
        "question": " 2652万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.985838952239893
    },
    {
        "question": " 448年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.593822663965177
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.98年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.0174417277322645
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.94万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3891717037519244
    },
    {
        "question": " 3591日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.935417820622866
    },
    {
        "question": " 3428日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.693382535768072
    },
    {
        "question": " 270億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.489567847628972
    },
    {
        "question": " 80.6億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.526229353763581
    },
    {
        "question": " 52.5万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.498186249114615
    },
    {
        "question": " 57万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.311858362731545
    },
    {
        "question": " 480億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.960643566312578
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.29万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9505889375613419
    },
    {
        "question": " 672億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.049173780912904
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.02万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.6825792234177435
    },
    {
        "question": " 781分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.670907592621971
    },
    {
        "question": " 114億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5591874239245147
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.01兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.068033262630652
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.89兆秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.719995469457137
    },
    {
        "question": " 459億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.883295330945021
    },
    {
        "question": " 35.9秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.554979982352261
    },
    {
        "question": " 103兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.5145461825371926
    },
    {
        "question": " 304億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5465380418263317
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.18兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.514086369614023
    },
    {
        "question": " 161万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.427586872217973
    },
    {
        "question": " 57.8億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.762289686214955
    },
    {
        "question": " 904万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.955974016538757
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.08京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.532814323481294
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.1垓usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.971744112219245
    },
    {
        "question": " 115京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.502580498683312
    },
    {
        "question": " 3279億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.7376554252533656
    },
    {
        "question": " 90.2兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.9553821034266985
    },
    {
        "question": " 1093億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.038757049834942
    },
    {
        "question": " 105京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5223068944240126
    },
    {
        "question": " 273垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.4998583350993
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.74垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.016852091877686
    },
    {
        "question": " 733京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.08700940928518
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.89京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.27756475208587
    },
    {
        "question": " 1190兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.075647203897034
    },
    {
        "question": " 218億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.338081932563045
    },
    {
        "question": " 29.3万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.029857679931318
    },
    {
        "question": " 358年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.49626616944747
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.7年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.7284432992621985
    },
    {
        "question": " 69.5億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.279436322641716
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.4日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.596188806475838
    },
    {
        "question": " 79.2万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.057269713312806
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.5兆時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.454659842971392
    },
    {
        "question": " 953億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.598969975907416
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.35万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.5807231657895
    },
    {
        "question": " 190億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.5571853473011315
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.05万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.544931906973629
    },
    {
        "question": " 500分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9211744084435969
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.6分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9121428218578496
    },
    {
        "question": " 22.7分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.133347113479719
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.2兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.51043499454679
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.1兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.104815109518664
    },
    {
        "question": " 3466億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.983538849189067
    },
    {
        "question": " 546秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9587094781864591
    },
    {
        "question": " 211万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.32479718686371
    },
    {
        "question": " 448億msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.15283317328377066
    },
    {
        "question": " 626兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.860096708829514
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.8兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.613795235831939
    },
    {
        "question": " 84.7万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1498244963964555
    },
    {
        "question": " 1879msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.27388516472902524
    },
    {
        "question": " 1015msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.006326379761786
    },
    {
        "question": " 132兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6209952328848134
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.53京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.466573074214155
    },
    {
        "question": " 52.1兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.160789468356941
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.52京usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.768619696667328
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.53兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.655986579927457
    },
    {
        "question": " 4915万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.691500572923264
    },
    {
        "question": " 5103垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.209055326718455
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.81垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.321720992070454
    },
    {
        "question": " 2027京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.750503915714486
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.07京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.708880052488635
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.39兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.142761160164228
    },
    {
        "question": " 2013兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.303927666542943
    },
    {
        "question": " 372億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.570690722522972
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.25年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6587034186723777
    },
    {
        "question": " 105年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.964966183072598
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.4億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.968765365548529
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.93億日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.974210197199014
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.69日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.725183181152303
    },
    {
        "question": " 4872億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.745188123809376
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.9億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.082080511114265
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.4万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.572660434077918
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.3兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.434801900737437
    },
    {
        "question": " 441億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.485601446237487
    },
    {
        "question": " 84.6分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.14928323157064605
    },
    {
        "question": " 67.5万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.607494127164652
    },
    {
        "question": " 542分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.511924408697337
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.99億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4551102969057816
    },
    {
        "question": " 25.4万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.46812422992735137
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.89億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.1333996073647015
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.42万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.866985080653779
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.45兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.039529207263824
    },
    {
        "question": " 91.8億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.0262293199801085
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.78京msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.693989155973998
    },
    {
        "question": " 342万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.755502745458487
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.2億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.050471098157701
    },
    {
        "question": " 448万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.651487434309301
    },
    {
        "question": " 28.8垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.96132946546375
    },
    {
        "question": " 815兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.974408481753542
    },
    {
        "question": " 139京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.587740563964575
    },
    {
        "question": " 28.8兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.6810693187794445
    },
    {
        "question": " 42.1億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.6243291900134142
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.12兆usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.709363314649018
    },
    {
        "question": " 332usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 5.521143898899323
    },
    {
        "question": " 455京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.158739340952105
    },
    {
        "question": " 33.1京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.5827456442082175
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.09垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.22833132196411
    },
    {
        "question": " 1942京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.510030877396556
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.82兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.5819393736434915
    },
    {
        "question": " 143億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.156550690412326
    },
    {
        "question": " 569億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.75521664348727
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.92万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.15520122641645
    },
    {
        "question": " 126年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.041713182957874
    },
    {
        "question": " 791年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.618633846720684
    },
    {
        "question": " 63.7億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.241515738485943
    },
    {
        "question": " 6768日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.210686639371116
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.2日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.368826165384028
    },
    {
        "question": " 41.5日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.554868890947445
    },
    {
        "question": " 18.8日は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.21040063719565
    },
    {
        "question": " 258万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4686590803847155
    },
    {
        "question": " 2079億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.937747991746706
    },
    {
        "question": " 33.8時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.084647891913936
    },
    {
        "question": " 386時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.142922167283158
    },
    {
        "question": " 130兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.394844375483826
    },
    {
        "question": " 818億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.754328730902861
    },
    {
        "question": " 1802億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.477680185049948
    },
    {
        "question": " 157万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.974485379742036
    },
    {
        "question": " 106分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.803272003635596
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.29分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.888744370182273
    },
    {
        "question": " 955億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.481194075244555
    },
    {
        "question": " 222億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.408954497350256
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.7億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.874470427381523
    },
    {
        "question": " 1506億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.399581055695677
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.18秒は何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.963016614259798
    },
    {
        "question": " 243京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.887370312981358
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.1京msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.065985309366697
    },
    {
        "question": " 883兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.389774337819544
    },
    {
        "question": " 53.8万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9525811146587382
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.02兆msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.954999810779782
    },
    {
        "question": " 7982msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.9021038843439
    },
    {
        "question": " 345京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.03952155240753
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.36垓usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.197914754421205
    },
    {
        "question": " 44億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.08711379319142676
    },
    {
        "question": " 21.4京usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.552175961954187
    },
    {
        "question": " 120兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.078470174407371
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.18億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.501756552465685
    },
    {
        "question": " 3535京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.0495780863434394
    },
    {
        "question": " 4952京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.758309026773862
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.15垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.94240796974921
    },
    {
        "question": " 5472京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.959969649077182
    },
    {
        "question": " 1311兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.117557918252745
    },
    {
        "question": " 1121兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.0495598590693
    },
    {
        "question": " 30億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.476589400402048
    },
    {
        "question": " 43.8万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.584310169459751
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.61万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9955554171378354
    },
    {
        "question": " 2619日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.798360507648201
    },
    {
        "question": " 2991日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.412292007356834
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.85兆時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.324272478589622
    },
    {
        "question": " 243万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.0056002388913265
    },
    {
        "question": " 26.4時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.200258351851082
    },
    {
        "question": " 1701時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.7870835187228105
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.42時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.481567502155061
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.42億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9245042707218873
    },
    {
        "question": " 270億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.272276889455622
    },
    {
        "question": " 1673億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.445219882651788
    },
    {
        "question": " 127分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.880633436046171
    },
    {
        "question": " 7034億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.348387321751419
    },
    {
        "question": " 363万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.623799316870782
    },
    {
        "question": " 9769秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.43353083478429477
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.3億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.311363425519266
    },
    {
        "question": " 91.5万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.961266935512556
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.86兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7701144965150073
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.95兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.905283425230462
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.96京msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.915656707908408
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.8兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.391420521209692
    },
    {
        "question": " 798万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.9020988806397927
    },
    {
        "question": " 2msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 3.3009418497159535
    },
    {
        "question": " 5916兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2732100183812323
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.81兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3221685462602906
    },
    {
        "question": " 34.1兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.9760701877002056
    },
    {
        "question": " 84.9兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.150904382876586
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.9億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5915785468192967
    },
    {
        "question": " 288億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.4593775323879985
    },
    {
        "question": " 273usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 5.436956003947195
    },
    {
        "question": " 3517京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.047312850413494
    },
    {
        "question": " 345兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6008896661598562
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.96垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.735090001325538
    },
    {
        "question": " 2915兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.686491241931438
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.6兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.165040822426685
    },
    {
        "question": " 234兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.36963411025879
    },
    {
        "question": " 914万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 3.9609092185982453
    },
    {
        "question": " 239万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.940725620737158
    },
    {
        "question": " 328万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.9534521807290304
    },
    {
        "question": " 377日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.956681991643748
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.4日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.318166042240521
    },
    {
        "question": " 8606万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.9923126139363574
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.92億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.311496605634832
    },
    {
        "question": " 90.2時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.733582172168466
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.44兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.254157573762212
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.7万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.0907675822391414
    },
    {
        "question": " 72.9億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.084557582408426
    },
    {
        "question": " 7943万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.678115762821518
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.26万分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.877076605843197
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.3兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.686818809711336
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.13億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.1177755204011746
    },
    {
        "question": " 19.8億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.741048054789632
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.14万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.933150645843481
    },
    {
        "question": " 461万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.663480444861143
    },
    {
        "question": " 884億msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.44784972915667076
    },
    {
        "question": " 12兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.141015628586621
    },
    {
        "question": " 20.2億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.749963879924727
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.41億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.3717130284988075
    },
    {
        "question": " 9277億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.967397545380472
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.98msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.297494685605084
    },
    {
        "question": " 37.2兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.07137126588878884
    },
    {
        "question": " 211兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.38879399376499
    },
    {
        "question": " 8975億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.396719399033561
    },
    {
        "question": " 11兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.262949217738678
    },
    {
        "question": " 41.8兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.621584565083507
    },
    {
        "question": " 8828usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 0.9458688968924722
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.28usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 3.8619156464510596
    },
    {
        "question": " 2719京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.935649745629656
    },
    {
        "question": " 379京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.642332569588092
    },
    {
        "question": " 1148京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.503464111639508
    },
    {
        "question": " 131京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.340376821568925
    },
    {
        "question": " 708億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8500037016970416
    },
    {
        "question": " 4984億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.697575296443192
    },
    {
        "question": " 26.5億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.42338078178909
    },
    {
        "question": " 656年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.379499825494563
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.3年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.589285584886783
    },
    {
        "question": " 4015万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.041363431715272
    },
    {
        "question": " 4579日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.040940358569882
    },
    {
        "question": " 53.1万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.883749945516142
    },
    {
        "question": " 94.6日は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.912392543271576
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.71兆時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.8840201505354
    },
    {
        "question": " 89.5時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5713900147995743
    },
    {
        "question": " 136万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.688428904057476
    },
    {
        "question": " 111時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.601627654652688
    },
    {
        "question": " 152万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.46198742366578394
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.11兆分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.887857811728125
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.91億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.502606898265393
    },
    {
        "question": " 55万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.518476518655934
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.33分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.414962218383177
    },
    {
        "question": " 132億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.621897027344734
    },
    {
        "question": " 1173億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.1327944625813675
    },
    {
        "question": " 28.3万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8950405122700376
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.33億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.858385604125226
    },
    {
        "question": " 3501秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.544224798797723
    },
    {
        "question": " 370秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.56844187544141
    },
    {
        "question": " 237兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.87612703283032
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.01京msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.542514824451539
    },
    {
        "question": " 32.3兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.9527741357373944
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.05兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.00331111286482
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.39兆msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.378175784451084
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.94msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.287763131636785
    },
    {
        "question": " 109兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5393510120890732
    },
    {
        "question": " 2260京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.417538287033175
    },
    {
        "question": " 1618兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.652601169166486
    },
    {
        "question": " 3京usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.698822176876227
    },
    {
        "question": " 1265億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.101954562731507
    },
    {
        "question": " 292万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.465751631195956
    },
    {
        "question": " 943万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.97445933604997
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.062e+05垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.527307310644831
    },
    {
        "question": " 2783垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.508078231646316
    },
    {
        "question": " 1423京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.59677151326744
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.73垓nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.658281881752602
    },
    {
        "question": " 62.1京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.793038761435945
    },
    {
        "question": " 166万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 0.2190457763311715
    },
    {
        "question": " 24.9万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 2.3965958514036076
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.25万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.190356529720722
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.14兆日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.934496577880791
    },
    {
        "question": " 205日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.692946874171933
    },
    {
        "question": " 106万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.181850316531861
    },
    {
        "question": " 31.3兆時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.55332732583427
    },
    {
        "question": " 93.1万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.588727165164782
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.71万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.765504617447984
    },
    {
        "question": " 186時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.826565569189778
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.78兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.530934772282324
    },
    {
        "question": " 342万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.3750695206997996
    },
    {
        "question": " 2295億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.582659482652598
    },
    {
        "question": " 5815万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.54266925890254
    },
    {
        "question": " 37.1兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.071070342886338
    },
    {
        "question": " 1574万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2604882088144826
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.62億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.653026927480216
    },
    {
        "question": " 1988万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.5201676722901585
    },
    {
        "question": " 316秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.499418966613191
    },
    {
        "question": " 3677京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.066706679262996
    },
    {
        "question": " 50.8兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.76936284302259
    },
    {
        "question": " 4174万msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0642716954900544
    },
    {
        "question": " 3403万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7536631818808543
    },
    {
        "question": " 1305msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.11557484615921099
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.83京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.763057916293633
    },
    {
        "question": " 647兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.8744636149701597
    },
    {
        "question": " 7160億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2986031326757494
    },
    {
        "question": " 144億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3790384969944944
    },
    {
        "question": " 6867兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.836794474697355
    },
    {
        "question": " 497億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.696710149541247
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.5万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 8.217527524230517
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.419e+04垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.146523031065986
    },
    {
        "question": " 315兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5612827872239057
    },
    {
        "question": " 11垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.486315485725042
    },
    {
        "question": " 814京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.132209113682064
    },
    {
        "question": " 109兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.0383460141644445
    },
    {
        "question": " 33.9兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.530014218992259
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.04兆nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.482251795497072
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.59年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.92433480913099
    },
    {
        "question": " 1138年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.776639999716908
    },
    {
        "question": " 27.3年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.935708007216316
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.08万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2875949084291403
    },
    {
        "question": " 4337日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.017377688346711
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.03日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.950897044537807
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.8万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1306192470118048
    },
    {
        "question": " 631万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.4197414155714565
    },
    {
        "question": " 28.6時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.2341263584772117
    },
    {
        "question": " 19.3時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.841152869753861
    },
    {
        "question": " 80.2億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.183787343109822
    },
    {
        "question": " 9254万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.807999804144341
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.45万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.383539885339067
    },
    {
        "question": " 427兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.1312454598914226
    },
    {
        "question": " 4719万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.737352215018581
    },
    {
        "question": " 411万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.0575000159159327
    },
    {
        "question": " 566秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9748882780950063
    },
    {
        "question": " 738秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.868100501307719
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.57秒は何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.41072341851317
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.7兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3270642303034714
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.74億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.739678085635036
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.92億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2839877549630105
    },
    {
        "question": " 28.9兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.682826585918287
    },
    {
        "question": " 80.4億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.90523342334468
    },
    {
        "question": " 85.2万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.930188244307203
    },
    {
        "question": " 22.1垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.846516315835029
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.18兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1358121413410838
    },
    {
        "question": " 539億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.174907762306987
    },
    {
        "question": " 986億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.215882878652355
    },
    {
        "question": " 1380兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.139738513604076
    },
    {
        "question": " 7189万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.856690240796634
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.982e+05垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.101333606229273
    },
    {
        "question": " 3960垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.661154660619673
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.29京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.802615661563853
    },
    {
        "question": " 118京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.293418235012003
    },
    {
        "question": " 807兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.90695179211325
    },
    {
        "question": " 164万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 0.21453598368309623
    },
    {
        "question": " 1098nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 0.04068607600415497
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.02年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.342189563806172
    },
    {
        "question": " 57.3年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.700501492071208
    },
    {
        "question": " 19.9年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.798561667518497
    },
    {
        "question": " 169億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.665362534780055
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.18万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.451236974968169
    },
    {
        "question": " 85.7日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.869529310629537
    },
    {
        "question": " 4706億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.730120772516238
    },
    {
        "question": " 2372億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.99489911253091
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.39万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.698243173863445
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.7兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.414608560700117
    },
    {
        "question": " 3035万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.323795621570793
    },
    {
        "question": " 2251億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.574231641789511
    },
    {
        "question": " 362分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.336946044236253
    },
    {
        "question": " 49.5分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.472491537827777
    },
    {
        "question": " 31.6兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.001042043759119
    },
    {
        "question": " 104万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0788860419570168
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.24万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5354881309118387
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.8万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.3908880396402785
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.3秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.1834306012667355
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.43秒は何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.155322001433627
    },
    {
        "question": " 33.5京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.026492195206529
    },
    {
        "question": " 6090億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.848104988935562
    },
    {
        "question": " 469億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.115297308248158
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.3億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.4053984554921835
    },
    {
        "question": " 25.6億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.407687952384352
    },
    {
        "question": " 2288msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.359409952336877
    },
    {
        "question": " 118msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 8.07254342500139
    },
    {
        "question": " 222垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.847905105243251
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.55京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.721799110905268
    },
    {
        "question": " 184兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.709097735779898
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.64兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.973184939965193
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.04億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7025086952137087
    },
    {
        "question": " 2790usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 0.4456789279560347
    },
    {
        "question": " 105京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5214382774640722
    },
    {
        "question": " 25京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.4609831415609573
    },
    {
        "question": " 206垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.758619236824229
    },
    {
        "question": " 3116億nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7154557837286901
    },
    {
        "question": " 40.1億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6035428173299295
    },
    {
        "question": " 99.2億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.9966916319408208
    },
    {
        "question": " 1424nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 0.1536003531244945
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.02年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.727865823466337
    },
    {
        "question": " 533億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.16445579488987
    },
    {
        "question": " 5863日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.1483035031114355
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.95万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9577791939193459
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.3万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.7084008359431886
    },
    {
        "question": " 2545時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.183816943717712
    },
    {
        "question": " 624時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.351830507227302
    },
    {
        "question": " 129億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.389348141521234
    },
    {
        "question": " 7183万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.697941684517712
    },
    {
        "question": " 78.1分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.11452114468024743
    },
    {
        "question": " 2533分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.1818600232626855
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.5万分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.955390079551709
    },
    {
        "question": " 36億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.057732066684621
    },
    {
        "question": " 1556万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.255499158392179
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.13兆秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.059202384242107
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.34万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3503582246519583
    },
    {
        "question": " 64.1秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.807021452893158
    },
    {
        "question": " 6827兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.335404699459549
    },
    {
        "question": " 42.9京msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.695792325638342
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.9兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.4805610377177745
    },
    {
        "question": " 66.8兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.046750389152624
    },
    {
        "question": " 56.1億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.748967465217915
    },
    {
        "question": " 43万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.633533714182333
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.6msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 7.192845922967367
    },
    {
        "question": " 1850垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.76831671141287
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.62京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.271972820049237
    },
    {
        "question": " 4912億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1349742785163803
    },
    {
        "question": " 1384兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.362995857170194
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.2億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.234423874128598
    },
    {
        "question": " 34.2万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 2.5338582913583907
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.62e+04垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.383170526805353
    },
    {
        "question": " 521垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.780015485987734
    },
    {
        "question": " 3966京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.0421017726230755
    },
    {
        "question": " 142兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.372796175415832
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.74京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.4376064142701015
    },
    {
        "question": " 6901億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.838891759319569
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.8億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.032468767476744
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.8万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.141672054537459
    },
    {
        "question": " 58.8万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.711701468433658
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.67年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.484350703617737
    },
    {
        "question": " 2035億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.746183199644388
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.49万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.554126757991088
    },
    {
        "question": " 63.8日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.962973468135102
    },
    {
        "question": " 2681億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.485709764962232
    },
    {
        "question": " 1983億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.917199681232226
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.05万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.799538370754212
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.01万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.859405879792741
    },
    {
        "question": " 54.7時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.294375557033797
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.8億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.3509265966299715
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.16万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7534418003334207
    },
    {
        "question": " 1825万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.483161980632168
    },
    {
        "question": " 22.5分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.130357278216569
    },
    {
        "question": " 5548億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.245295014667424
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.23兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.689978623454592
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.84億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.707572295481183
    },
    {
        "question": " 57億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.9775529476122164
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.69秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.8255832869177473
    },
    {
        "question": " 1354秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.131491202663675
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.52垓msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.903391982790984
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.41億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7964434881918758
    },
    {
        "question": " 241億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.826272317009444
    },
    {
        "question": " 33.5兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.74727252117011
    },
    {
        "question": " 1711msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.23314629184135405
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.87msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 3.272974940820829
    },
    {
        "question": " 18.5京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.7672449693970957
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.15垓usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.775044872745188
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.61京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.001768789149164
    },
    {
        "question": " 5310兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.946956563226131
    },
    {
        "question": " 7195万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8570139141422204
    },
    {
        "question": " 1506億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.177761272757264
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.838e+05垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.765473504287458
    },
    {
        "question": " 32.5京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.5751247298256894
    },
    {
        "question": " 75.8京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.323258180333674
    },
    {
        "question": " 342兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.755367811961751
    },
    {
        "question": " 1501兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.176386696460971
    },
    {
        "question": " 160兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.203171497779461
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.81億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 5.256816098764244
    },
    {
        "question": " 795年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.4625187355775715
    },
    {
        "question": " 20.1万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.246486522486308
    },
    {
        "question": " 1018日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.44563734025945156
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.06日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6934327196515664
    },
    {
        "question": " 22.2日は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.282256687958483
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.65万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.48152079336915343
    },
    {
        "question": " 82.8万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.537714813593631
    },
    {
        "question": " 612万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.565183043349137
    },
    {
        "question": " 330億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.797925800078147
    },
    {
        "question": " 232万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.207126864006784
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.82万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.1673305935148455
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.4万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.906417398465038
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.81分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.358579700591703
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.25京秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.013530300209698
    },
    {
        "question": " 26.5万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.4868118932679988
    },
    {
        "question": " 81億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.352039564484279
    },
    {
        "question": " 2741万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.6597521007072435
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.1秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.149925459403457
    },
    {
        "question": " 336兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.027741526380316
    },
    {
        "question": " 175億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.306381562727969
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.28億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9590522363492469
    },
    {
        "question": " 1224億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.309507514030628
    },
    {
        "question": " 135万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.129078517166217
    },
    {
        "question": " 33.6msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.526170299300043
    },
    {
        "question": " 71.5兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.3557492539656548
    },
    {
        "question": " 5420兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.797524579365202
    },
    {
        "question": " 489兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.132670281614984
    },
    {
        "question": " 99.7億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2205739754660856
    },
    {
        "question": " 506兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.704294888842938
    },
    {
        "question": " 424億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.627612791846988
    },
    {
        "question": " 328万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.51634918820329
    },
    {
        "question": " 2470京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8938968460522796
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.78垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.31372283096383
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.87兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.2807711317688977
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.79京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.475842983409191
    },
    {
        "question": " 242兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.3839360233376565
    },
    {
        "question": " 115万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 0.060134508469310566
    },
    {
        "question": " 3443nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 0.5369294953938009
    },
    {
        "question": " 41.2万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.557206236470252
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.99万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.282061842280949
    },
    {
        "question": " 20.8日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.698940653131751
    },
    {
        "question": " 578万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.920335422726481
    },
    {
        "question": " 222日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.282253841435863
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.92兆時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.74970456110716
    },
    {
        "question": " 42.4億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.247119358762301
    },
    {
        "question": " 60.1万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.557259553474653
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.17時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.057117951833619
    },
    {
        "question": " 132億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.401035114427029
    },
    {
        "question": " 134億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.970347314697377
    },
    {
        "question": " 110億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.264466653454473
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.31万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.412355070172687
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.12万分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.687856463198784
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.01億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9791691420002258
    },
    {
        "question": " 24.4億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.450593279125334
    },
    {
        "question": " 827億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.361327664162242
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.87万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9904270714348256
    },
    {
        "question": " 169秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.226703315555875
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.38兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3692044750086474
    },
    {
        "question": " 5464兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.8009823169980566
    },
    {
        "question": " 5671万msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.197387177442909
    },
    {
        "question": " 37.7億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.798234410524664
    },
    {
        "question": " 9858万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.993805849697917
    },
    {
        "question": " 904万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.956385666481735
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.2垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.683516082892979
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.51垓usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.60869627771358
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.64兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.3804308010370465
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.62兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.204811696078525
    },
    {
        "question": " 626兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.796688292557127
    },
    {
        "question": " 3166億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.500447121962004
    },
    {
        "question": " 985垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.494493572731842
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.66京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.816416000132431
    },
    {
        "question": " 219兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7834728591355298
    },
    {
        "question": " 34.3兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.757250053869087
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.54京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.815294682292524
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.6兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.203508379465177
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.89億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 5.4603908567234685
    },
    {
        "question": " 153年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.128521456127062
    },
    {
        "question": " 51.5億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.149186189125041
    },
    {
        "question": " 2628日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.799905137144657
    },
    {
        "question": " 3962日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.7563058205534166
    },
    {
        "question": " 26.8日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.364239702186239
    },
    {
        "question": " 41.3日は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.552764291485317
    },
    {
        "question": " 60.1億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.836476615536061
    },
    {
        "question": " 470億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.292222631941936
    },
    {
        "question": " 97万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.543101043292099
    },
    {
        "question": " 9663万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.264437325740868
    },
    {
        "question": " 208億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.1596157062223895
    },
    {
        "question": " 329億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.73874349741251
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.94分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.0653386134812814
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.15万分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.56719655521462
    },
    {
        "question": " 97.2分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.765840227738009
    },
    {
        "question": " 28.4億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9542143665916878
    },
    {
        "question": " 58.4万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8300844055522449
    },
    {
        "question": " 1014億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.449687772740877
    },
    {
        "question": " 7749万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.111122182191936
    },
    {
        "question": " 2628秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.419673333709119
    },
    {
        "question": " 27京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.9332358564237575
    },
    {
        "question": " 22.4兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.413980886913993
    },
    {
        "question": " 38.7億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.031057914702102
    },
    {
        "question": " 1048億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.242409479823011
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.05万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3109526402666682
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.46msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 3.927576800992721
    },
    {
        "question": " 2273兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8578034127147258
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.44垓usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.935077317810094
    },
    {
        "question": " 99.2億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.4401276696672629
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.42兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.867085477526372
    },
    {
        "question": " 583兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.765522736050448
    },
    {
        "question": " 2205億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.34331770321192
    },
    {
        "question": " 2969垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.973757454608896
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.8垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.204786222703757
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.19兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.4071733801030586
    },
    {
        "question": " 393京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.816031637022062
    },
    {
        "question": " 226京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.353161229821898
    },
    {
        "question": " 1082億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.0343390735336175
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.85万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 1.4547196635353654
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.05年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.426310027948079
    },
    {
        "question": " 1485万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.609491009890412
    },
    {
        "question": " 103日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.3911276618748563
    },
    {
        "question": " 166万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.378711937203592
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.68兆時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.88251563332097
    },
    {
        "question": " 39.2時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.213363100830386
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.28万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.27922059863442
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.72時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.792255881562155
    },
    {
        "question": " 54.9万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.019240233701514065
    },
    {
        "question": " 5592万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.589222460206486
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.84億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.67533607152026
    },
    {
        "question": " 1443分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.937401824382134
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.47万分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.94651646357688
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.79京秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.445084321049155
    },
    {
        "question": " 1539万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.250867185751292
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.44兆秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.601056326924482
    },
    {
        "question": " 9891万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.217084002818256
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.9秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.277669827601203
    },
    {
        "question": " 31.8兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.0034870677281047
    },
    {
        "question": " 29.4京msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.531415636921137
    },
    {
        "question": " 4136万msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.060263693300476
    },
    {
        "question": " 21.3万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5509961797759
    },
    {
        "question": " 797億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.901539697999351
    },
    {
        "question": " 194万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.28721892674964
    },
    {
        "question": " 46.8垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.17121596483145
    },
    {
        "question": " 2210京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.407845538052278
    },
    {
        "question": " 119億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5176503534785171
    },
    {
        "question": " 46.3京usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.887753806792176
    },
    {
        "question": " 643兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.808154170880847
    },
    {
        "question": " 7719usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 0.8875494785669624
    },
    {
        "question": " 46.8usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 4.670516191211234
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.271e+06垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.857356613693822
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.49垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.460371254647706
    },
    {
        "question": " 309兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9332868447599183
    },
    {
        "question": " 4994兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.920294227738385
    },
    {
        "question": " 6067億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.78296606206354
    },
    {
        "question": " 9792億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.990853280768746
    },
    {
        "question": " 173万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 3.2385783034690565
    },
    {
        "question": " 49.6年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.257524338166595
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.9万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.085372081870329
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.2億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.515335133582193
    },
    {
        "question": " 130日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.493268756863097
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.98日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.233002869656892
    },
    {
        "question": " 1457億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.221065818635436
    },
    {
        "question": " 763億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.502219252954799
    },
    {
        "question": " 2740時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.994021419306115
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.09億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.769283985971863
    },
    {
        "question": " 4224分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.4673815547221083
    },
    {
        "question": " 5947億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.996134541003773
    },
    {
        "question": " 21兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.823781089147748
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.58億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.7247826334945264
    },
    {
        "question": " 2666億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.869584423495221
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.07万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2494699668599996
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.4秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.215462991731821
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.21秒は何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.081171354697174
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.35京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.63011943073017
    },
    {
        "question": " 550億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8038851827965217
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.01億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.0463763653105707
    },
    {
        "question": " 474万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8974872364109008
    },
    {
        "question": " 8623億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.93563484077365
    },
    {
        "question": " 190msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 5.279147192059119
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.4垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.659969276019881
    },
    {
        "question": " 5037兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.765659857181856
    },
    {
        "question": " 31.7兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.9442801412514585
    },
    {
        "question": " 33.8京usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.750200372655076
    },
    {
        "question": " 198万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.2963094686616319
    },
    {
        "question": " 33.5億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.52566614743109
    },
    {
        "question": " 1918usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.282797973642324
    },
    {
        "question": " 6874垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.3384178346971165
    },
    {
        "question": " 413兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6797593702916815
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.28垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.549868602510983
    },
    {
        "question": " 8405億nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1463912902002926
    },
    {
        "question": " 161兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.206980731362066
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.96億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 2.2917485911091227
    },
    {
        "question": " 190万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 3.277708818687283
    },
    {
        "question": " 243万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.947410260832376
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.22万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.02959711805038
    },
    {
        "question": " 2337日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8063037795142192
    },
    {
        "question": " 6394万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.185945587639798
    },
    {
        "question": " 70.5兆時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.905863752636467
    },
    {
        "question": " 398億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.219600909399709
    },
    {
        "question": " 3490万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.320997852829416
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.18兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.782179173240177
    },
    {
        "question": " 334億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.364914568406849
    },
    {
        "question": " 8633万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.158025401430569
    },
    {
        "question": " 421分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.402161695930803
    },
    {
        "question": " 552兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.2433802808689505
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.7億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.259718371153651
    },
    {
        "question": " 65.9万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2627251013531713
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.38万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7508219063908737
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.05秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.484831371341949
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.66秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.2192823925493705
    },
    {
        "question": " 4524兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.156749259516028
    },
    {
        "question": " 101億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.066848869388785
    },
    {
        "question": " 43.1兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.0782424855544495
    },
    {
        "question": " 1765万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4686483836575626
    },
    {
        "question": " 1772億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.248347567120035
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.18msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 3.338614890486248
    },
    {
        "question": " 286兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9581557623860515
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.86兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8314157383707153
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.59兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.3240899642601986
    },
    {
        "question": " 155億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4129926752203756
    },
    {
        "question": " 51.3兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.710027170446701
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.61万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.2071636728449342
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.36万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 7.133843778413683
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.324e+04垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.227425347494835
    },
    {
        "question": " 155兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.254124817657676
    },
    {
        "question": " 4790京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.124047084112588
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.54兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7704139995979973
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.98京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.5997601109096
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.32億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 2.1190972721842325
    },
    {
        "question": " 8255万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.916741143647375
    },
    {
        "question": " 30.1万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.04018977357633
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.64年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.935025714329248
    },
    {
        "question": " 178年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.75042117598085
    },
    {
        "question": " 122万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.52461516023952
    },
    {
        "question": " 2188万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.720174412010092
    },
    {
        "question": " 4912日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.627771557503744
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.73万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.2967008768611079
    },
    {
        "question": " 1982時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9168080165024848
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.8時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9768820908967863
    },
    {
        "question": " 82時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.469891347253157
    },
    {
        "question": " 372億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.849490643278135
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.88億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.301332615202777
    },
    {
        "question": " 1479分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3917262183938905
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.99万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.378686777494811
    },
    {
        "question": " 3065億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.987566112331712
    },
    {
        "question": " 90.6万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0208465531279098
    },
    {
        "question": " 4759万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.121184449466517
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.35億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.350617163862346
    },
    {
        "question": " 18.4秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.26573490724657
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.88秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.837757897888455
    },
    {
        "question": " 181兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.7593244760145303
    },
    {
        "question": " 25.9億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4773081280197353
    },
    {
        "question": " 118兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.516574503529453
    },
    {
        "question": " 301万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.699695972356231
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.39万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9727746615316655
    },
    {
        "question": " 27.4msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.43723802049517
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.81京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.082015041830007
    },
    {
        "question": " 2577兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.474653028259179
    },
    {
        "question": " 2693億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.873889781932374
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.51京usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.401128712931275
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.3億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.237338598115799
    },
    {
        "question": " 782万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.893006122171924
    },
    {
        "question": " 410usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 5.613077098736682
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.7京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.3270270797355346
    },
    {
        "question": " 32.2京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.571934502283214
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.2兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5956333178074802
    },
    {
        "question": " 1601億nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.42623344526993123
    },
    {
        "question": " 54.2兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.733652349729845
    },
    {
        "question": " 79.5億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.90025578422458
    },
    {
        "question": " 151万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 3.179475063591901
    },
    {
        "question": " 73.5万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.428593741012689
    },
    {
        "question": " 5417日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1714301263968263
    },
    {
        "question": " 46.7万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.049224716822274
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.7万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.726025634924229
    },
    {
        "question": " 183日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.1992035950597515
    },
    {
        "question": " 19.8万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3534684719468038
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.66億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.183049529084182
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.51時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.736087124126378
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.13時間は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.607571167067134
    },
    {
        "question": " 3751億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.853519184465145
    },
    {
        "question": " 5862分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6097230828456168
    },
    {
        "question": " 477万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.9000728543712855
    },
    {
        "question": " 42.8万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.409468643379866
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.7万分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.846067866857904
    },
    {
        "question": " 1538億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.688079522140714
    },
    {
        "question": " 55.3兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.80635505255449
    },
    {
        "question": " 5283秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.16659028171868706
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.67万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4451077352451045
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.72万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.57063113418179
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.7兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7239776375375033
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.44兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.989804819931434
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.01京msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.448189137975213
    },
    {
        "question": " 65.9万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.040458250329379
    },
    {
        "question": " 914万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.961082370437703
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.34万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.637493893006319
    },
    {
        "question": " 1699msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.230255238242421
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.26垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.6004896212719
    },
    {
        "question": " 105京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.083565228843262
    },
    {
        "question": " 70.7兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.293415354723979
    },
    {
        "question": " 3736億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.7942884619989634
    },
    {
        "question": " 181億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.257594631849917
    },
    {
        "question": " 5475億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.738360825264147
    },
    {
        "question": " 735万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.866134595753476
    },
    {
        "question": " 20.8垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.819924552588195
    },
    {
        "question": " 2483兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4584824347349379
    },
    {
        "question": " 14垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.59092349347766
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.53垓nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.964230074062554
    },
    {
        "question": " 243兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.3863722662752895
    },
    {
        "question": " 637兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.803810325997862
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.39兆nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.141818165607079
    },
    {
        "question": " 135万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.694209758980643
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.37年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.3171079513989845
    },
    {
        "question": " 31.9万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9417010186270387
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.6万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.443710967398317
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.41万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.307825344531915
    },
    {
        "question": " 18.6兆時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.325944816554824
    },
    {
        "question": " 20.4億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.929099335509436
    },
    {
        "question": " 26.1時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.1952739295902557
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.04時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.25870251510836
    },
    {
        "question": " 1692億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.5077602102142675
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.28万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9473055111690531
    },
    {
        "question": " 8320分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.141975721048006
    },
    {
        "question": " 2904万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.241137233390402
    },
    {
        "question": " 27.1分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.2104066742737585
    },
    {
        "question": " 62.1兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.2943772849594986
    },
    {
        "question": " 125兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.159781424351413
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.31億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.562548195869425
    },
    {
        "question": " 764万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.104884749321429
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.21万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.624661878873209
    },
    {
        "question": " 6106秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.785748033115135
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.64秒は何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.561636840220558
    },
    {
        "question": " 5668億msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2546441006534814
    },
    {
        "question": " 2億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.3639561757467913
    },
    {
        "question": " 36.9億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.011081670176412
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.75兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.898470086152423
    },
    {
        "question": " 31.3万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.495948588273995
    },
    {
        "question": " 5759msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.76037057132859
    },
    {
        "question": " 333msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 8.522986878221664
    },
    {
        "question": " 1533兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6868690560079957
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.4兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4438569896380482
    },
    {
        "question": " 609京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.227972502568072
    },
    {
        "question": " 105兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.242727920323016
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.82億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2600451853525785
    },
    {
        "question": " 4128万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.615703292383068
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.05usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 3.848350595526411
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.805e+05垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.334027754079642
    },
    {
        "question": " 104兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.07986888183980967
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.62兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.37901943641992175
    },
    {
        "question": " 29.7京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.695026708614574
    },
    {
        "question": " 144兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.158227432871982
    },
    {
        "question": " 25.5兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.40618753868747
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.07万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 1.029527347744431
    },
    {
        "question": " 809年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.850689891024723
    },
    {
        "question": " 28.2年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.171589111981243
    },
    {
        "question": " 46.8年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.169128112414814
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.25万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5343759354084885
    },
    {
        "question": " 8289万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.298720210274405
    },
    {
        "question": " 116日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.223023630674869
    },
    {
        "question": " 106億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.084034894764474
    },
    {
        "question": " 84.4億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.546231159064773
    },
    {
        "question": " 374万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.351457500758311
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.42億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.924870174224936
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.96万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6842022721285643
    },
    {
        "question": " 83.4億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.142984901109521
    },
    {
        "question": " 241万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.160001427533963
    },
    {
        "question": " 35.9分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.333424681933177
    },
    {
        "question": " 2221億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.847735164430055
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.62億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.8128747938350296
    },
    {
        "question": " 9716億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.431206645061957
    },
    {
        "question": " 4693万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.893338291140873
    },
    {
        "question": " 744万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.871796088445322
    },
    {
        "question": " 1678秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.224912082340571
    },
    {
        "question": " 89.4兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.4526923914430085
    },
    {
        "question": " 1022億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.0730376861859163
    },
    {
        "question": " 3396万msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9747314783588279
    },
    {
        "question": " 831万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.141529573609293
    },
    {
        "question": " 1006msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.002570750526680321
    },
    {
        "question": " 524万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.7190397945593
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.51京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6812566686657524
    },
    {
        "question": " 4524億usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7190205196337962
    },
    {
        "question": " 73.9京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.312616522962951
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.47京usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.094930604092639
    },
    {
        "question": " 179億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.2524898686303745
    },
    {
        "question": " 19.4万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 2.2869067458794445
    },
    {
        "question": " 2733usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.436639859210268
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.57京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.2473009664911785
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.63京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.047189028347097
    },
    {
        "question": " 6080京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.227591330771781
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.21兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5653486919405701
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.59兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.200106307202745
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.66億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 2.563574556446848
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.75兆nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.57371927209503
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.4年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.960064401615782
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.79億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.118254013807759
    },
    {
        "question": " 1833万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.643396583531462
    },
    {
        "question": " 595万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8319469851144516
    },
    {
        "question": " 76.6億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.504024831434222
    },
    {
        "question": " 3998万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.379953434267764
    },
    {
        "question": " 64.4万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.36488339435028
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.4時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.612498884822324
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.88兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.1757672389838305
    },
    {
        "question": " 57.9万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6043557711673038
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.67億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.786831744458782
    },
    {
        "question": " 851分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.707958442888687
    },
    {
        "question": " 173兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.73989593521929
    },
    {
        "question": " 138億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.202090767355311
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.38兆秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.584473600411448
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.81億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.9861257655838696
    },
    {
        "question": " 5427京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.235785431584226
    },
    {
        "question": " 4359兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.7028857572112175
    },
    {
        "question": " 68.1億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.2769492518491306
    },
    {
        "question": " 78.3万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.115493123946193
    },
    {
        "question": " 9988億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.999459594222584
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.42垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.035272340512671
    },
    {
        "question": " 224京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.414163887179201
    },
    {
        "question": " 3266京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.957666189936136
    },
    {
        "question": " 8569万usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.15476750087387026
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.91億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.691405692172201
    },
    {
        "question": " 669億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.825734086400806
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.12万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 7.615009152909025
    },
    {
        "question": " 1140京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5580035333945474
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.94京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5319024543395696
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.65垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.110943094639623
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.21兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9385144306735902
    },
    {
        "question": " 315億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.498927221058176
    },
    {
        "question": " 19億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.277920418495197
    },
    {
        "question": " 32.5万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 2.511786631507067
    },
    {
        "question": " 1143万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.620222680504636
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.09年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.427461612875013
    },
    {
        "question": " 61.1年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.284658153704694
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.63億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.188466216177368
    },
    {
        "question": " 1704日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.611682526903737
    },
    {
        "question": " 357日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.710989724298634
    },
    {
        "question": " 99.3万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.0544524309824608
    },
    {
        "question": " 21.3万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.9482349235446277
    },
    {
        "question": " 81.9万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.19250300314801017
    },
    {
        "question": " 327億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.356747396294473
    },
    {
        "question": " 2104万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.5449921918235
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.6分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.879831013709931
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.07万分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.09321993084601
    },
    {
        "question": " 942億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.475030635903723
    },
    {
        "question": " 82.1万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9780735961278775
    },
    {
        "question": " 2568万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.8532508108964816
    },
    {
        "question": " 1116万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.269345068206376
    },
    {
        "question": " 85.6秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.932394109754073
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.18兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5725889096895573
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.33億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.18798433278457316
    },
    {
        "question": " 150億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.6212271650299144
    },
    {
        "question": " 873万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.162888710378766
    },
    {
        "question": " 470万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.672014452808592
    },
    {
        "question": " 372msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 5.570234660260742
    },
    {
        "question": " 1104垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.544126395393233
    },
    {
        "question": " 25.4京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.468286653817445
    },
    {
        "question": " 661兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.264109065538567
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.1京usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.303903830364732
    },
    {
        "question": " 33.7億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.527798715993616
    },
    {
        "question": " 152万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.1807151571586214
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.3万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 8.1254515357219
    },
    {
        "question": " 1376垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.639769324727349
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.87京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3349554889473776
    },
    {
        "question": " 1320兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.564403654822808
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.12垓nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.272209275938266
    },
    {
        "question": " 3953兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.596906263836849
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.17兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.335485695736827
    },
    {
        "question": " 225万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 3.3521642856917575
    },
    {
        "question": " 143万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.717227092424544
    },
    {
        "question": " 103年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.957311708094229
    },
    {
        "question": " 8729日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3786560662013936
    },
    {
        "question": " 7万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.902608581961114
    },
    {
        "question": " 574時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3787008004460466
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.02時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.036233315020217
    },
    {
        "question": " 239時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.933870011969727
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.76兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.720914551967478
    },
    {
        "question": " 231億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.205741546016837
    },
    {
        "question": " 2030万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.529284703911275
    },
    {
        "question": " 3367分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.305382402226176
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.77分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.026433845238253
    },
    {
        "question": " 87.6億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.443554648320716
    },
    {
        "question": " 82.7兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.980858329054332
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.33兆秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.413506708782194
    },
    {
        "question": " 1346億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.350854318496346
    },
    {
        "question": " 366秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.563676525270504
    },
    {
        "question": " 560兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.249473999957988
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.23京msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.573255142787245
    },
    {
        "question": " 117兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.513607595089468
    },
    {
        "question": " 81.2兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.13151287012337
    },
    {
        "question": " 935万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.970965632032879
    },
    {
        "question": " 617万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.790389770459957
    },
    {
        "question": " 5109msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.708345988093894
    },
    {
        "question": " 32.7京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.0160413891174676
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.31京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.698460553213086
    },
    {
        "question": " 47.5京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.119985619647647
    },
    {
        "question": " 510億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9296456696635023
    },
    {
        "question": " 1e+03億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.999911541338977
    },
    {
        "question": " 242億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.383416225327901
    },
    {
        "question": " 232usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 5.365805442148222
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.6垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.664959695072058
    },
    {
        "question": " 8569垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.996434491247166
    },
    {
        "question": " 27.3兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8805708758351616
    },
    {
        "question": " 60.1兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.0008796767776036
    },
    {
        "question": " 225京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.351449729608758
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.11億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 2.3237637901804153
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.48兆nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.170003557718875
    },
    {
        "question": " 9547年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.542161893651027
    },
    {
        "question": " 6816億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.271235361403878
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.6万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.513699566797909
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.7日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.4069546015460475
    },
    {
        "question": " 9994億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.057222311080753
    },
    {
        "question": " 6402万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.426102316611955
    },
    {
        "question": " 19万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.057967009757219
    },
    {
        "question": " 2310億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.642978264780099
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.4兆分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.710611944182338
    },
    {
        "question": " 514億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.932589348667504
    },
    {
        "question": " 326分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.291351093612496
    },
    {
        "question": " 3178兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.003381322270362
    },
    {
        "question": " 618億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.854721933362027
    },
    {
        "question": " 1467億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.610254707442121
    },
    {
        "question": " 872億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.162317892819015
    },
    {
        "question": " 58.9万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.7703500563391
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.27秒は何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.104201507555414
    },
    {
        "question": " 1647京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.717856870164614
    },
    {
        "question": " 9324億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.03309749159018
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.44億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8317820652073014
    },
    {
        "question": " 18.9万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.49830983010112684
    },
    {
        "question": " 27.5万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.439161967997312
    },
    {
        "question": " 42万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.623043010327885
    },
    {
        "question": " 135兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6318201601857509
    },
    {
        "question": " 904京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.019514705119157
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.2京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.565608488426275
    },
    {
        "question": " 1006億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.2243711183461543
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.7兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.029648733193098
    },
    {
        "question": " 9377usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 0.9720743500809914
    },
    {
        "question": " 114京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5575824894290946
    },
    {
        "question": " 30.6京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.549583705714409
    },
    {
        "question": " 32.1京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.949953792279582
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.2垓nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.29968975569913
    },
    {
        "question": " 225億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3528753830366347
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.86兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.26911733412379
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.53億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 5.185571498705693
    },
    {
        "question": " 19.5年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.8521445273273525
    },
    {
        "question": " 79.5年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.842715096571347
    },
    {
        "question": " 3856年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.306766963987103
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.29万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.070096680005112
    },
    {
        "question": " 262日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.7984978224048493
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.25日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.1242609453559655
    },
    {
        "question": " 108日は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.968879269333188
    },
    {
        "question": " 169万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2857889224037056
    },
    {
        "question": " 3146万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.117500775672213
    },
    {
        "question": " 98.2時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.7702841289514932
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.1時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.599005559925833
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.2時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.563229193619383
    },
    {
        "question": " 619万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.071111376656596
    },
    {
        "question": " 26.8億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.269943667831934
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.21億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.938637254749875
    },
    {
        "question": " 5828万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.543677237220276
    },
    {
        "question": " 20.3兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.809030946633004
    },
    {
        "question": " 262万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.481854400610667
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.51万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1849359509922675
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.64億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.6438252087629195
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.27京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.604911274848288
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.19兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.137669983470371
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.8億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.615289809592541
    },
    {
        "question": " 104兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.239526503388136
    },
    {
        "question": " 1105msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.043515762188889306
    },
    {
        "question": " 150msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 5.177354305466128
    },
    {
        "question": " 32.3京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.010277961204814
    },
    {
        "question": " 61.8兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.854803208640372
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.1京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.524866164767988
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.18兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.294273689213489
    },
    {
        "question": " 687兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.836798460950888
    },
    {
        "question": " 197億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.294494022848057
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.55万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 7.744041161001246
    },
    {
        "question": " 709京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.352041513723302
    },
    {
        "question": " 113京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.115887537487463
    },
    {
        "question": " 9633兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.4274428049595507
    },
    {
        "question": " 2490億nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6181181167440464
    },
    {
        "question": " 1696兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.229542573326481
    },
    {
        "question": " 112億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.050935152058772
    },
    {
        "question": " 78.4億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.8944891524430565
    },
    {
        "question": " 271万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.994965804846696
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.26万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.042471240584106
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.58年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.132910156953697
    },
    {
        "question": " 47.1万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.1111308025380255
    },
    {
        "question": " 6554日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.196696307117021
    },
    {
        "question": " 55.9万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.905790982418845
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.2億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.562716425465171
    },
    {
        "question": " 291時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.083595044887815
    },
    {
        "question": " 2081万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.09638697536803
    },
    {
        "question": " 1024時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.566568489784288
    },
    {
        "question": " 5480億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.018127191811985
    },
    {
        "question": " 753万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.7186219071421354
    },
    {
        "question": " 73.6億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.088897685026753
    },
    {
        "question": " 2999万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.2551275196668
    },
    {
        "question": " 1277分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.884340165127575
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.15兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.560510383958249
    },
    {
        "question": " 19.1兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.34487217517392
    },
    {
        "question": " 1028万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.455678173712906
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.01万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2259955329600034
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.44秒は何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.735831226273616
    },
    {
        "question": " 78.6兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.3965415985543324
    },
    {
        "question": " 313兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.559430943933381
    },
    {
        "question": " 8327億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.364182381338423
    },
    {
        "question": " 12億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.300314106861869
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.67万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.222557004652961
    },
    {
        "question": " 53msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.724516268267211
    },
    {
        "question": " 4229msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.626254249685452
    },
    {
        "question": " 219垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.84082141987118
    },
    {
        "question": " 837兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.9864827265514235
    },
    {
        "question": " 64.5兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.2533615316549405
    },
    {
        "question": " 69.4兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.063069142894058
    },
    {
        "question": " 120万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.08031833014330192
    },
    {
        "question": " 119億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.075819621575924
    },
    {
        "question": " 86.7usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 4.937805741979734
    },
    {
        "question": " 92.9京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.469009671531385
    },
    {
        "question": " 20.5垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.374820364807571
    },
    {
        "question": " 53.7京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.173439781708161
    },
    {
        "question": " 1971兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.516436242095554
    },
    {
        "question": " 25.8京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.412065916118328
    },
    {
        "question": " 350億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.543978768195664
    },
    {
        "question": " 3131万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.495663685746485
    },
    {
        "question": " 1605年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.147988978874556
    },
    {
        "question": " 1088年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.757462757146028
    },
    {
        "question": " 509日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.1440246731685524
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.92日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.6241104265440227
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.48兆時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.22853907089949
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.73億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.50800257992408
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.1時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9862863124310337
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.85時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.451008646671722
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.7時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.623489756068223
    },
    {
        "question": " 4539兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.936333383722703
    },
    {
        "question": " 404億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.448357906512831
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.55億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.412504178861188
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.6分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9986758160311378
    },
    {
        "question": " 4307万秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.1353395861981055
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.22兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.857126964958809
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.49万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6169242744135961
    },
    {
        "question": " 1002億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.222778481592902
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.2京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.578813235144763
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.34兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.433492543843553
    },
    {
        "question": " 3270兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.958257118331389
    },
    {
        "question": " 6076億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.005437726201038
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.1万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4914867695639011
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.3msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.361240124897273
    },
    {
        "question": " 99.2京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.497917259006739
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.03京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.545394605947898
    },
    {
        "question": " 36.2京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.002693530989527
    },
    {
        "question": " 7845兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.116467118646703
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.25億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7198797374860026
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.82万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.6826944240660124
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.98usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 3.4742817237901855
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.79垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.9463637824113675
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.9京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.0997127794407864
    },
    {
        "question": " 875兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3854982467175967
    },
    {
        "question": " 241兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.6044151094308488
    },
    {
        "question": " 527京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.721965835246722
    },
    {
        "question": " 282兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.450174537182603
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.19万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 1.7152414885114364
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.59年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.116803196188104
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.03万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.547996988090762
    },
    {
        "question": " 9787億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.428356895202558
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.44日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.251969643547398
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.98日は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.838284552161808
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.1万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0608144987373225
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.5万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.7177101211653096
    },
    {
        "question": " 34.9時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.320628375558883
    },
    {
        "question": " 3249時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.06805209189734
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.49兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.451094592926953
    },
    {
        "question": " 2683万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.270316383645031
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.58億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.7758357765461525
    },
    {
        "question": " 199万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.07808491327409
    },
    {
        "question": " 102分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.786593327464945
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.22兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.8466193641196975
    },
    {
        "question": " 34.2億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.597357331602694
    },
    {
        "question": " 51億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.150996182745725
    },
    {
        "question": " 106億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.248653974402407
    },
    {
        "question": " 287秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.457380545389528
    },
    {
        "question": " 4686京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.172000974486075
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.35兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.929873502801204
    },
    {
        "question": " 6535兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.258942356295845
    },
    {
        "question": " 159兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.424401319061632
    },
    {
        "question": " 7115万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.8521766579706815
    },
    {
        "question": " 24.3京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.8864967160893404
    },
    {
        "question": " 1797億usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.31813759222684035
    },
    {
        "question": " 712京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.295934512929504
    },
    {
        "question": " 21.9兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.562876745085163
    },
    {
        "question": " 34兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.53167808853661
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.79万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.4449169823713603
    },
    {
        "question": " 51.4万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 8.711300231195859
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.561e+05垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.160282980594413
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.98京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.760862279839894
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.84垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.707605747829197
    },
    {
        "question": " 4489億nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.873967240933522
    },
    {
        "question": " 1338億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.126406129706533
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.67兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.22271354889599
    },
    {
        "question": " 29.7万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 2.473164231380951
    },
    {
        "question": " 1819年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.822221793925509
    },
    {
        "question": " 447年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.593259584527868
    },
    {
        "question": " 65.8年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.539078164674099
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.4年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.556954937453925
    },
    {
        "question": " 39.4万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.032850955204116
    },
    {
        "question": " 69.2日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.220496497474854
    },
    {
        "question": " 553日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.900889626389136
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.7兆時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.15970677354794
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.8万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8744570406075143
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.54時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6553026003963422
    },
    {
        "question": " 39時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.147154315220522
    },
    {
        "question": " 62.5時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.351975175706466
    },
    {
        "question": " 309兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.769748399930107
    },
    {
        "question": " 20.3万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.150043938258366
    },
    {
        "question": " 68.2億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.055332158163981
    },
    {
        "question": " 1298分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.891363325163368
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.9兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.755211352420352
    },
    {
        "question": " 516兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.776061696544083
    },
    {
        "question": " 883億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.389656982073168
    },
    {
        "question": " 1953万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.512564294023175
    },
    {
        "question": " 724万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.859750269488849
    },
    {
        "question": " 20.9秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.3197565236584206
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.2垓msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.579979512940945
    },
    {
        "question": " 25.6億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4724859569852011
    },
    {
        "question": " 807億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.350588521761786
    },
    {
        "question": " 285万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6762367822686008
    },
    {
        "question": " 568万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.754090085218941
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.97垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.344130813037558
    },
    {
        "question": " 272京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.4973305829589885
    },
    {
        "question": " 5832兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.20954540460355
    },
    {
        "question": " 2690兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.651606551158405
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.59億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4129359896782496
    },
    {
        "question": " 2486億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.39545207025746
    },
    {
        "question": " 105万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.020961642201739
    },
    {
        "question": " 43.6京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1404533752243884
    },
    {
        "question": " 38.1垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.644403050792144
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.2京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.680125617799041
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.7垓nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.893558794829753
    },
    {
        "question": " 7033億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8471109736790314
    },
    {
        "question": " 306億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.485243252373705
    },
    {
        "question": " 69万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 2.838669236619511
    },
    {
        "question": " 2133年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.89135328219152
    },
    {
        "question": " 70.9万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.793257616537769
    },
    {
        "question": " 4085年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.331839638871184
    },
    {
        "question": " 39.2年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.092611951580418
    },
    {
        "question": " 51.3万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.147550544620099
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.65日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1323761659895943
    },
    {
        "question": " 5763万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.8181782992228728
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.16万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.683605256096496
    },
    {
        "question": " 27.6万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.219627649867158
    },
    {
        "question": " 6320億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.080064756225372
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.8兆分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.94905645155342
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.17万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8417530824258708
    },
    {
        "question": " 253分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.181542156338888
    },
    {
        "question": " 363兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.060992475867271
    },
    {
        "question": " 68万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8962748137944176
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.75億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.432823994590132
    },
    {
        "question": " 314億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.718723963626973
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.14垓msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.55791450319691
    },
    {
        "question": " 6737億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.891971046960995
    },
    {
        "question": " 459兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.105848651222257
    },
    {
        "question": " 105万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2409768068730187
    },
    {
        "question": " 1533億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.185661185073446
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.3msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 3.362460015120927
    },
    {
        "question": " 57.6垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.261756997842593
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.58兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4747742890239857
    },
    {
        "question": " 212兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.7697410677203225
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.57京usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.881740962835465
    },
    {
        "question": " 364兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.560594002282055
    },
    {
        "question": " 4478億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.65112532191771
    },
    {
        "question": " 311万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.492945326051466
    },
    {
        "question": " 8493京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.430254196629672
    },
    {
        "question": " 89.2垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.014031026248281
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.02京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.7486869795021205
    },
    {
        "question": " 51.8京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.936482574914988
    },
    {
        "question": " 2913億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.464361732426681
    },
    {
        "question": " 222兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.346931385272576
    },
    {
        "question": " 125億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.096888651350664
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.09年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.2690396739725314
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.41年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.364977191113712
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.97億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.036231301439806
    },
    {
        "question": " 504万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.082562009132488
    },
    {
        "question": " 43.8日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.578022071323051
    },
    {
        "question": " 183万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3198645648635186
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.69万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.0499192480774084
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.81時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.0356572958229027
    },
    {
        "question": " 51.9時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.27131042189669
    },
    {
        "question": " 1121万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3287727799648608
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.2万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9282426806295738
    },
    {
        "question": " 1835分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.485420178644199
    },
    {
        "question": " 222分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.12476714737049
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.17万分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.11483908587784
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.21分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.123306224042077
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.07兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.816359281643388
    },
    {
        "question": " 135兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.193197246560644
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.63兆秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.656598226957358
    },
    {
        "question": " 116秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.28712948330741117
    },
    {
        "question": " 38.4万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.584766153241471
    },
    {
        "question": " 7147兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.355346486570541
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.62兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.274308251470039
    },
    {
        "question": " 530万msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.1679066556043196
    },
    {
        "question": " 26.6万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6463286948002089
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.86万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4563586743382784
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.48msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 3.1710769463895936
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.4垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.716942897157103
    },
    {
        "question": " 93.7京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.035027208431467
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.3兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5573229449036883
    },
    {
        "question": " 348兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.764005171847795
    },
    {
        "question": " 7947万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.900193033480857
    },
    {
        "question": " 3243万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.510991682330494
    },
    {
        "question": " 36.2万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 8.55906500264304
    },
    {
        "question": " 31.5垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.999883877869747
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.6京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.28269383900175
    },
    {
        "question": " 3024兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.924303304985693
    },
    {
        "question": " 34.5京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.760214062037663
    },
    {
        "question": " 1560兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.193033956075431
    },
    {
        "question": " 1040兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.016905187330735
    },
    {
        "question": " 531万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 3.7253103621961516
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.8年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.7017294331102333
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.5年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.186280925338179
    },
    {
        "question": " 377年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.297363124275654
    },
    {
        "question": " 3020万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.91765083794805
    },
    {
        "question": " 253万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.782632200518539
    },
    {
        "question": " 1858日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.20560443472594
    },
    {
        "question": " 1377億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.1963822446044485
    },
    {
        "question": " 1295時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.731977085450267
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.51時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7562762797520177
    },
    {
        "question": " 58.5時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.323260607348736
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.94時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.024131234113888
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.2兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.784600480996206
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.17兆分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.178573410513948
    },
    {
        "question": " 14万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.366635826881532
    },
    {
        "question": " 24分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.1579412007364613
    },
    {
        "question": " 169兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.729792512324342
    },
    {
        "question": " 346万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6024656824883499
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.54万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8478114849681839
    },
    {
        "question": " 2768万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.664058476274464
    },
    {
        "question": " 122万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.087331379664032
    },
    {
        "question": " 4840秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.684813096710736
    },
    {
        "question": " 7320億msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3657265052179202
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.33京msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.790222079588432
    },
    {
        "question": " 2063万msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7583008707274996
    },
    {
        "question": " 164億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.437157460339694
    },
    {
        "question": " 7645億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.883355175313612
    },
    {
        "question": " 55.9万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.747785772601942
    },
    {
        "question": " 1457msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.163598535652795
    },
    {
        "question": " 239垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.879680800735596
    },
    {
        "question": " 545京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.799559571999772
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.76兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.2041663552324593
    },
    {
        "question": " 844兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.1480114019473
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.16兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.619131411016151
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.9億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.200063747130312
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.88万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 7.769494049072899
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.71垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.9349317736913347
    },
    {
        "question": " 3990京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.664485726620051
    },
    {
        "question": " 81.5京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.3548073383564985
    },
    {
        "question": " 1712億nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.45527076262053434
    },
    {
        "question": " 364京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.560996111810454
    },
    {
        "question": " 717兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.855273945246774
    },
    {
        "question": " 1433万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.156347316830575
    },
    {
        "question": " 98.9年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.55747215075588
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.6年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.041762794587906
    },
    {
        "question": " 151年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.899435644333441
    },
    {
        "question": " 49.2年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.190371199964462
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.1万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.553479297711445
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.4日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5379170233531454
    },
    {
        "question": " 4829日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.842193226171202
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.11万日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.980082789507343
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.3兆時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.212487120653543
    },
    {
        "question": " 226時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9741015870230241
    },
    {
        "question": " 56.9時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.533042998307362
    },
    {
        "question": " 171時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.789326927609006
    },
    {
        "question": " 6455万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.089261328881596
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.3兆分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.96642949014445
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.9億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.395584518137868
    },
    {
        "question": " 28.1分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.227084230532704
    },
    {
        "question": " 30.2分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.258346028971985
    },
    {
        "question": " 4218億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.126290649003944
    },
    {
        "question": " 240億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.443462376044682
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.3万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4544693383213592
    },
    {
        "question": " 1045秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.240985581476376
    },
    {
        "question": " 831秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.919558105384917
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.31秒は何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.1183601923794
    },
    {
        "question": " 2235京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.850547035502924
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.6億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.26669985940321883
    },
    {
        "question": " 484億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.128550804192138
    },
    {
        "question": " 227兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.578554396313567
    },
    {
        "question": " 957万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.9808942018585167
    },
    {
        "question": " 4832msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.684126314853346
    },
    {
        "question": " 7884京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.397929668276773
    },
    {
        "question": " 1382兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.203974689442918
    },
    {
        "question": " 264京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.86604299632872
    },
    {
        "question": " 5857億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.9895228527302864
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.64兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.56100247321775
    },
    {
        "question": " 43.4万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 2.6374834073796007
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.6万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 8.165052353856844
    },
    {
        "question": " 243京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8867369773034748
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.44京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.872695465236401
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.2垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.450375113974697
    },
    {
        "question": " 5744兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.9810809122617
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.8億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.1691963718881473
    },
    {
        "question": " 96.7億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.985286207296297
    },
    {
        "question": " 299億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.4763261062249615
    },
    {
        "question": " 8789年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.506223536107271
    },
    {
        "question": " 4895年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.632299916745598
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.89年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.996122290415704
    },
    {
        "question": " 2034日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7460168265722023
    },
    {
        "question": " 1976万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.67605841016598
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.24万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.251721678379912
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.82日は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.51829116501683
    },
    {
        "question": " 247億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.449891983644318
    },
    {
        "question": " 186億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.889864240673823
    },
    {
        "question": " 41.7万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.397896911640145
    },
    {
        "question": " 37.6時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.131382862204471
    },
    {
        "question": " 63.8億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.084168752223399
    },
    {
        "question": " 76.5万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7255313949201696
    },
    {
        "question": " 66.1億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.042094596433042
    },
    {
        "question": " 28万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.22525557387251
    },
    {
        "question": " 3447兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.038684659795088
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.58億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.261328836505739
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.81兆秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.388697075852495
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.9億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.474583634270236
    },
    {
        "question": " 7921秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.898794594807033
    },
    {
        "question": " 41.3京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.117438391704793
    },
    {
        "question": " 36.5兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.625385441588378
    },
    {
        "question": " 8388万msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3673716615236076
    },
    {
        "question": " 283億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.673797664238159
    },
    {
        "question": " 73.9億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.868782295563464
    },
    {
        "question": " 19.5垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.790848190840899
    },
    {
        "question": " 6932兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.904373411712978
    },
    {
        "question": " 104億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.4606039216674862
    },
    {
        "question": " 22.5兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.573595526340187
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.6億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.1329445701736236
    },
    {
        "question": " 254億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.404565345048168
    },
    {
        "question": " 89.2usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 4.950314517009177
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.458e+05垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.664949389119593
    },
    {
        "question": " 514京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.7747700367376025
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.44垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.831488295875504
    },
    {
        "question": " 4160兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.840986329733123
    },
    {
        "question": " 24.6億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.39030967534233074
    },
    {
        "question": " 44.1億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.6446437862023684
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.9億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.202610919052336
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.38万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.673371907708583
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.32年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.225042290910032
    },
    {
        "question": " 6067万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.220686943909033
    },
    {
        "question": " 3489日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.922887476664407
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.6日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.36164817666082
    },
    {
        "question": " 1954日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.227525953480786
    },
    {
        "question": " 46.6万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.726304073506506
    },
    {
        "question": " 700万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.464665611343635
    },
    {
        "question": " 345万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.315362599829495
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.25万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.652642452240624
    },
    {
        "question": " 86億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.214076008903554
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.7万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9105608031362509
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.69億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.207991298134485
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.12億分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.826227945457829
    },
    {
        "question": " 2920億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.9665701330054004
    },
    {
        "question": " 20.6万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.37758364309932957
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.85兆秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.27928956190912
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.6億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.323452183737375
    },
    {
        "question": " 96.3万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.983659206351371
    },
    {
        "question": " 57秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.7557636146837305
    },
    {
        "question": " 9216京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.465737821572906
    },
    {
        "question": " 1633億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.2765321086033214
    },
    {
        "question": " 2780兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.88778735010324
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.1万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.30535817931842124
    },
    {
        "question": " 56.9万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7551839768631767
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.51万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.179943742215152
    },
    {
        "question": " 171京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.73509199565747
    },
    {
        "question": " 23京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.424449428618414
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.9京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.695742232630179
    },
    {
        "question": " 70.9億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.072603798156938
    },
    {
        "question": " 81.8億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.912657879121398
    },
    {
        "question": " 4875万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.688005331451865
    },
    {
        "question": " 53.3万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 8.726496869477442
    },
    {
        "question": " 48.4垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.186273868157868
    },
    {
        "question": " 1657京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.282702334215864
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.3垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.655370997226905
    },
    {
        "question": " 387京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.809945096975253
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.87京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.587734212942565
    },
    {
        "question": " 36.1億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.5576773055107758
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.75億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 5.676779414377901
    },
    {
        "question": " 210万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.883673695681178
    },
    {
        "question": " 1953年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.233170349129809
    },
    {
        "question": " 4334年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.357543853867526
    },
    {
        "question": " 344万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.9744605308993575
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.2万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.533412135287402
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.03日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.169495310015095
    },
    {
        "question": " 9820日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.928605685569334
    },
    {
        "question": " 459億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.719685112762841
    },
    {
        "question": " 511億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.328637025496331
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.3時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8668695564013658
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.2時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.738968262936176
    },
    {
        "question": " 118兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.350836515560015
    },
    {
        "question": " 4622万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.506434932784563
    },
    {
        "question": " 166億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.443142779882557
    },
    {
        "question": " 1510分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.957182126665762
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.6分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.80340405275484
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.83京秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.335668345935211
    },
    {
        "question": " 2236万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4129530591761084
    },
    {
        "question": " 5472億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.181864455154155
    },
    {
        "question": " 614万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.010305507974894
    },
    {
        "question": " 147兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.669400475385797
    },
    {
        "question": " 333億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.586377117138514
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.42億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.251295179053031
    },
    {
        "question": " 784億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.116048618375778
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.2億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.181120730811356
    },
    {
        "question": " 2237msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.34963030374415
    },
    {
        "question": " 199京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.799697631635419
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.23京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.9224828709572055
    },
    {
        "question": " 446兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.092921652086908
    },
    {
        "question": " 6449兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.031343044839291
    },
    {
        "question": " 7527万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.876619620156641
    },
    {
        "question": " 8810usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 0.9449841867534914
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.206e+06垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.58268660357377
    },
    {
        "question": " 1645兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2796146705822264
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.35京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.8153745138929285
    },
    {
        "question": " 602億nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.0013044174402421227
    },
    {
        "question": " 38.7億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5875794472017071
    },
    {
        "question": " 1086兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.03595568883087
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.97万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 1.6967702108301574
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.6年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.783393523893036
    },
    {
        "question": " 25.6年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.349900916378559
    },
    {
        "question": " 65.2万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.2516787434215857
    },
    {
        "question": " 144日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.096352898417696
    },
    {
        "question": " 863万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.993411106338515
    },
    {
        "question": " 1416万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.770938908551009
    },
    {
        "question": " 444万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.425309129957693
    },
    {
        "question": " 856時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.488892462553661
    },
    {
        "question": " 61.5億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.0679284407330005
    },
    {
        "question": " 8516分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7718750782614181
    },
    {
        "question": " 2658分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6463321618103066
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.66万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.998150278988774
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.14分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.108710947335869
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.19京秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.123683364475681
    },
    {
        "question": " 906億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.0207208319212056
    },
    {
        "question": " 845億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.370544899124914
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.83億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.674295161269593
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.16秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.06527356523963
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.27秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.104075899311862
    },
    {
        "question": " 7884兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.397920447882515
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.52京msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.245744629494421
    },
    {
        "question": " 90.6億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.4010662069341224
    },
    {
        "question": " 1564億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.416166680248701
    },
    {
        "question": " 4565億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.659409398459786
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.4msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.055784886822606
    },
    {
        "question": " 926垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.467995438462559
    },
    {
        "question": " 25.1兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.462440745442339
    },
    {
        "question": " 489京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.132890691670012
    },
    {
        "question": " 882億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.1674901467106356
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.28兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.105999625753223
    },
    {
        "question": " 35万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 2.544629352190272
    },
    {
        "question": " 3134垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.997259633936044
    },
    {
        "question": " 161垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.269356653848664
    },
    {
        "question": " 40.6京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.052078474870485
    },
    {
        "question": " 1945億nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.510800533675505
    },
    {
        "question": " 30.1京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.47871133561188
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.96兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.842459526596986
    },
    {
        "question": " 504億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.702546382010408
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.9年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.16955284073815
    },
    {
        "question": " 3584万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.992075343391575
    },
    {
        "question": " 56.6日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.133130178310309
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.37日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.130315895006591
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.23万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.1468163177813131
    },
    {
        "question": " 283時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0711941414164416
    },
    {
        "question": " 186万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.048620941724685
    },
    {
        "question": " 192万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.839448046945598
    },
    {
        "question": " 585時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.323426497728853
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.46時間は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.721251156996466
    },
    {
        "question": " 11兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.322391567621852
    },
    {
        "question": " 3306億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.360953029163284
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.03億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.82718921168723
    },
    {
        "question": " 1487分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.9505336338355255
    },
    {
        "question": " 1599分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.982133560396866
    },
    {
        "question": " 140分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.924356394742635
    },
    {
        "question": " 87.9兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.445316958048711
    },
    {
        "question": " 169兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.292548099683557
    },
    {
        "question": " 1322億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.565022427118474
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.67万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7870425992520587
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.33兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.22762654825156
    },
    {
        "question": " 39.3京msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.657993600566272
    },
    {
        "question": " 4634万msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1096118350727402
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.9億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.2964108145925834
    },
    {
        "question": " 3164億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.50019672535864
    },
    {
        "question": " 374msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 5.572541789066381
    },
    {
        "question": " 206垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.815197010961285
    },
    {
        "question": " 1169兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.131218212748128
    },
    {
        "question": " 1124兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.494359672385728
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.7京usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.451191094930472
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.99兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.475160537757328
    },
    {
        "question": " 8026億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.904478737584384
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.02usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 3.0106188238177465
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.206e+04垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.465241871738533
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.4京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.08138230649166
    },
    {
        "question": " 34.7京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.984618361380315
    },
    {
        "question": " 1511兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.401161012543642
    },
    {
        "question": " 139兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.141608859051944
    },
    {
        "question": " 486万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 0.686823646154594
    },
    {
        "question": " 7165万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.855224564690487
    },
    {
        "question": " 5110年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.429057487952925
    },
    {
        "question": " 288万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.8972140395817876
    },
    {
        "question": " 99.8日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.379321318071209
    },
    {
        "question": " 12億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.135546266901509
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.41万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.2640518737983726
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.69時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.344920403079467
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.07万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.586138377836775
    },
    {
        "question": " 454時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.213113973905699
    },
    {
        "question": " 539億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.011002746548165
    },
    {
        "question": " 19.6万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.13364073690965
    },
    {
        "question": " 1294億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.333732980861146
    },
    {
        "question": " 2660万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.203062919376947
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.17京秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.837924028225833
    },
    {
        "question": " 58.2万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8283705574768552
    },
    {
        "question": " 39.8億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.043100112349032
    },
    {
        "question": " 38.7万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.8093098358196356
    },
    {
        "question": " 22.9秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.360344058011405
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.03秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.014221958625724
    },
    {
        "question": " 1982兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.798251241513826
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.34兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.790652188984103
    },
    {
        "question": " 121億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.527344927148086
    },
    {
        "question": " 9276億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.18921304980247
    },
    {
        "question": " 1121msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.049593262448082154
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.69msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 3.7548940155400077
    },
    {
        "question": " 168msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 8.225046079486722
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.09垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.540536203978271
    },
    {
        "question": " 21.4兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3946495703122936
    },
    {
        "question": " 341億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9765009262751423
    },
    {
        "question": " 112兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.272195577282008
    },
    {
        "question": " 4677億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.669951803388021
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.31万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.5199823147851577
    },
    {
        "question": " 28.5垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.956439226673439
    },
    {
        "question": " 2241垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.413927436133871
    },
    {
        "question": " 1694兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6725627717471836
    },
    {
        "question": " 173兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.45985740039108
    },
    {
        "question": " 754億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8774643756839826
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.89億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 2.689650861278361
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.59万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 1.200398530883554
    },
    {
        "question": " 481年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.24452595933996
    },
    {
        "question": " 71.3億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.2905265795027505
    },
    {
        "question": " 1927日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.66511770737509
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.64万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.09495094764795
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.71日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.823562955483148
    },
    {
        "question": " 60日は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.714456341945159
    },
    {
        "question": " 1883万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.332433226924434
    },
    {
        "question": " 2634時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.0404459757850613
    },
    {
        "question": " 9341時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.526674977511874
    },
    {
        "question": " 615時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.345031280240141
    },
    {
        "question": " 282万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7292500811426295
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.68万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0680178104978966
    },
    {
        "question": " 34万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.753790274446912
    },
    {
        "question": " 2588分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.191197023716978
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.2兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.508828850027041
    },
    {
        "question": " 399万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6641576387873813
    },
    {
        "question": " 228万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8018962105778025
    },
    {
        "question": " 45.5億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.880209383312408
    },
    {
        "question": " 2684秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.4287659462931686
    },
    {
        "question": " 101秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.00325565764295
    },
    {
        "question": " 6360億msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3046307907425647
    },
    {
        "question": " 51.9億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7785120120051223
    },
    {
        "question": " 675億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.272692812586945
    },
    {
        "question": " 200億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.5239096457638315
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.17兆msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.066827686925583
    },
    {
        "question": " 1170msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.068271352306313
    },
    {
        "question": " 229垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.860835877989615
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.09京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.101423723103719
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.3京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.533326947413402
    },
    {
        "question": " 32.9億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7385500458155556
    },
    {
        "question": " 43.6兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.639065820297458
    },
    {
        "question": " 3915万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.592692433948926
    },
    {
        "question": " 1376京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6397020598728425
    },
    {
        "question": " 8011兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9671907666480792
    },
    {
        "question": " 19垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.723455533810032
    },
    {
        "question": " 175兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.463950932133785
    },
    {
        "question": " 443億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.646469765550539
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.53兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.185310543541141
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.27兆nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.103022304793344
    },
    {
        "question": " 41.5年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.1800479093947915
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.03万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.250509172816127
    },
    {
        "question": " 100年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.721016570727642
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.9万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6646106961195715
    },
    {
        "question": " 55.3日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.123174146593862
    },
    {
        "question": " 1457日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.321675682696006
    },
    {
        "question": " 577日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.697494902665431
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.01兆時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.836409012659757
    },
    {
        "question": " 658時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4381879418543952
    },
    {
        "question": " 402時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.382832322468865
    },
    {
        "question": " 177時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.803819247943776
    },
    {
        "question": " 274万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7170441904917157
    },
    {
        "question": " 32.5万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3531354530804958
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.11万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.269111598358542
    },
    {
        "question": " 302分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.2577430013931465
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.44分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.513427064332015
    },
    {
        "question": " 86.4兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.437664199832342
    },
    {
        "question": " 2587万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4763473058876806
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.52億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.257837441122072
    },
    {
        "question": " 748秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.09566047546366
    },
    {
        "question": " 1797秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.25443479578252
    },
    {
        "question": " 26.6秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.424249891214654
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.3兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.592260277965784
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.79兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.641975718632059
    },
    {
        "question": " 987万msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.43810501447364425
    },
    {
        "question": " 35.5億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.771483834346059
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.72万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2349967441480825
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.37万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.137390415524787
    },
    {
        "question": " 1687兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7282164463009386
    },
    {
        "question": " 46兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.726286034566243
    },
    {
        "question": " 24.6京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.835223128889595
    },
    {
        "question": " 1878億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.4955888267098887
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.95億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.596121210365574
    },
    {
        "question": " 52.9万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 2.7236002051333097
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.62万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 7.209916858779094
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.138e+05垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.354754644027379
    },
    {
        "question": " 85.4垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.994770626194162
    },
    {
        "question": " 145京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.604605590567685
    },
    {
        "question": " 3019京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.701767046265726
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.7兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.430611352555065
    },
    {
        "question": " 426万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 0.629484815400646
    },
    {
        "question": " 387億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.58739674724512
    },
    {
        "question": " 188万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.836631397694868
    },
    {
        "question": " 724年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.802148344659022
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.08年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.426804945881277
    },
    {
        "question": " 2499日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8354372880005578
    },
    {
        "question": " 3832日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.963671073378527
    },
    {
        "question": " 3982万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.657631865869128
    },
    {
        "question": " 69.4時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.4610464370760159
    },
    {
        "question": " 83.2万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.476186058850718
    },
    {
        "question": " 5598万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.0273815188348254
    },
    {
        "question": " 6570分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6592083602808396
    },
    {
        "question": " 391万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.814227552827815
    },
    {
        "question": " 278分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.222865819509635
    },
    {
        "question": " 736分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.644767762819908
    },
    {
        "question": " 1175兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.57125438612869
    },
    {
        "question": " 668億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.888431734816965
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.95万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2859403206506503
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.05億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.242146143766321
    },
    {
        "question": " 473秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.674525394289361
    },
    {
        "question": " 411兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.114839420717783
    },
    {
        "question": " 544億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7992529884962525
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.9億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2826128826826286
    },
    {
        "question": " 434億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.859247904295271
    },
    {
        "question": " 95.6万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.980313234952501
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.65msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 3.75215071872589
    },
    {
        "question": " 4440兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1485465587829444
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.13京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.117870843027866
    },
    {
        "question": " 1032兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.4575190190114276
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.96京usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.514347929588
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.28兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.515693083661955
    },
    {
        "question": " 1181万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.072355572914854
    },
    {
        "question": " 113京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5528621659633257
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.14垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.393333185167515
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.17京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.779882643549376
    },
    {
        "question": " 4224億nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8475539661420706
    },
    {
        "question": " 160億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2038313742394569
    },
    {
        "question": " 939億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.972794341187672
    },
    {
        "question": " 23.9億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.378579196932165
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.2万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.285218769483313
    },
    {
        "question": " 132万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.5577324347658177
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.03日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3926046697678618
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.98万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.758002630646836
    },
    {
        "question": " 739日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.80527352222321
    },
    {
        "question": " 28.2日は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.386843579722585
    },
    {
        "question": " 3476万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.5986294059522486
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.96万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.5207166972242154
    },
    {
        "question": " 23.7万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.930631871329805
    },
    {
        "question": " 702時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.402892637971682
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.75億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5226520804874184
    },
    {
        "question": " 159万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.0426757665262083
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.52万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.768532846215294
    },
    {
        "question": " 19.4万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.06587437103955
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.95分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.473050134875592
    },
    {
        "question": " 31.5兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.9994393167476945
    },
    {
        "question": " 2837万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5163865246828845
    },
    {
        "question": " 730万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.3072639323504074
    },
    {
        "question": " 1984秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5193128732757921
    },
    {
        "question": " 52.2京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.21912504158157
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.71億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7368560803068258
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.08京msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.478005540038954
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.2兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.56455082726273
    },
    {
        "question": " 351億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.545672114338401
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.69msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.42959794201
    },
    {
        "question": " 21.3垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.829551436058039
    },
    {
        "question": " 3671京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.628247199632025
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.3兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5592027449530184
    },
    {
        "question": " 64.3億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.0298185260523827
    },
    {
        "question": " 40.4億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.6061684896480264
    },
    {
        "question": " 6746億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.829075758703247
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.78usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 3.577872013022808
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.791e+05垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.754409256780795
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.57京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2586157470774837
    },
    {
        "question": " 8079兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.351050467185601
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.73兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.460393547423
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.11兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.046714349966626
    },
    {
        "question": " 211億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.323970265179366
    },
    {
        "question": " 1594万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.202576013858248
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.7万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.501934388868924
    },
    {
        "question": " 28.5年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.396940068993045
    },
    {
        "question": " 1422年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.873640721689673
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.08年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.109198456402577
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.85兆日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.704256991532226
    },
    {
        "question": " 314日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.8765895421839036
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.14日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.4885901685702656
    },
    {
        "question": " 114万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1147302289828307
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.46億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.35677494674003
    },
    {
        "question": " 54.9時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.295513242145783
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.15時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.617628722884749
    },
    {
        "question": " 50.4億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.9820888488041772
    },
    {
        "question": " 109万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8786517177361546
    },
    {
        "question": " 2845万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.675958262726998
    },
    {
        "question": " 4881万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.466629506498634
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.85分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.67319116146328
    },
    {
        "question": " 42.5分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.406636043968907
    },
    {
        "question": " 2803兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.948875860960682
    },
    {
        "question": " 60億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.841403966182113
    },
    {
        "question": " 298億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.917481370799337
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.63億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.64137357854735
    },
    {
        "question": " 7621秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.882035109623482
    },
    {
        "question": " 2196京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.842903833910984
    },
    {
        "question": " 45.5兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.721507185953265
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.6億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8581539511348333
    },
    {
        "question": " 45.1万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8761127424247317
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.77兆msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.830589837333948
    },
    {
        "question": " 963msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 5.983499651292825
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.11垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.545905618544559
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.95京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.905327761354673
    },
    {
        "question": " 213京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.771867799427875
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.61億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.4278788349068319
    },
    {
        "question": " 188兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.273271933601448
    },
    {
        "question": " 1428万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.1546778470378865
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.81垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.265034003368577
    },
    {
        "question": " 5686垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.818273269559922
    },
    {
        "question": " 89.1垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.393678784404344
    },
    {
        "question": " 30.1兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7004112345475493
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.76京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.67780882168383
    },
    {
        "question": " 6368兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.80401992177659
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.64兆nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.936671032550569
    },
    {
        "question": " 107年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.590905151045742
    },
    {
        "question": " 995億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.43555175922463
    },
    {
        "question": " 45.2日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.0348753248467295
    },
    {
        "question": " 498日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.855293075726271
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.9万日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.626622690341778
    },
    {
        "question": " 454億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.714893452711509
    },
    {
        "question": " 456万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.278660862748104
    },
    {
        "question": " 153万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.7401880566646
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.53時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.739767813366902
    },
    {
        "question": " 118億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.352426994589313
    },
    {
        "question": " 273億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.277674244268231
    },
    {
        "question": " 142万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.375133273616665
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.83万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.612527799924548
    },
    {
        "question": " 70.3億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3480937179513783
    },
    {
        "question": " 45.7億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.723642205969528
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.4万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5906113201823859
    },
    {
        "question": " 3717億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.792015480807883
    },
    {
        "question": " 138秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.1404369037304605
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.93兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7878329909947133
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.74兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.303542151492156
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.5兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.63377145072102
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.65万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.20629405790146826
    },
    {
        "question": " 2280万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.357987507183049
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.88msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 3.5889551093255734
    },
    {
        "question": " 5038兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2034216507414373
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.11兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6768393045767283
    },
    {
        "question": " 1512兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.623253692010676
    },
    {
        "question": " 242兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.604923686670343
    },
    {
        "question": " 75.5兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.87804021054395
    },
    {
        "question": " 5481億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.738849766470704
    },
    {
        "question": " 7501usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.875116416534739
    },
    {
        "question": " 6762垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.331281659329852
    },
    {
        "question": " 76垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.944192342802214
    },
    {
        "question": " 139垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.58546763802832
    },
    {
        "question": " 37.7兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7986348656314677
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.8京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.250199939674784
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.11兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.046476292715281
    },
    {
        "question": " 58.4億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.766196196683772
    },
    {
        "question": " 2232年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.910951611935909
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.52万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.489218265609836
    },
    {
        "question": " 97.5年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.487806404092899
    },
    {
        "question": " 4016億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.041527823892313
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.33日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5034774351570945
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.04万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.1772730110735905
    },
    {
        "question": " 329万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.574774448488948
    },
    {
        "question": " 18.1万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.8785181578348316
    },
    {
        "question": " 4679万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.448292303001438
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.12万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.60558398384603
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.61時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.7644074161150956
    },
    {
        "question": " 28億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.7264320079066025
    },
    {
        "question": " 1208万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.9238641468731315
    },
    {
        "question": " 1511分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4010000364732744
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.07万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.805970184039451
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.33分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.901079640624793
    },
    {
        "question": " 41.6億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1206878622656813
    },
    {
        "question": " 101兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.066907647280756
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.41万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.59144795626355
    },
    {
        "question": " 1631万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.434216697479155
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.33万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.636007164113749
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.01秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.003750530643163
    },
    {
        "question": " 112兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.551979836027729
    },
    {
        "question": " 5907億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.8348814819835733
    },
    {
        "question": " 2319万msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8090343823526225
    },
    {
        "question": " 794万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1216477912211227
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.2万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0808490919170377
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.21万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.345311980852182
    },
    {
        "question": " 2588兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9141642917311241
    },
    {
        "question": " 2681億usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.49171643315524705
    },
    {
        "question": " 369京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.01039770865794
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.16億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5553633657547663
    },
    {
        "question": " 96.8億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.98594400924683
    },
    {
        "question": " 64.2億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.807728283414448
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.67万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 7.42628745337284
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.84垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.186430791377579
    },
    {
        "question": " 64.4京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.8721175404663963
    },
    {
        "question": " 6729京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.271628567846159
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.14兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2790443488676184
    },
    {
        "question": " 419京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.622028657689727
    },
    {
        "question": " 40.4兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.606422765377786
    },
    {
        "question": " 55.9万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 2.747035908452531
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.01年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.565016037462562
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.1年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.868444490996833
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.2億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.618668663813959
    },
    {
        "question": " 562日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.129979035028878
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.89万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.928316897685939
    },
    {
        "question": " 43.9日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.579056612857979
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.23兆時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.1485554188889
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.9億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.764223837058456
    },
    {
        "question": " 28.2時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.2282470534962493
    },
    {
        "question": " 35.9億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.8338760185063436
    },
    {
        "question": " 643万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.6499397935516
    },
    {
        "question": " 1954万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.512796876269027
    },
    {
        "question": " 601万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.557333160899352
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.76万分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.607962373688352
    },
    {
        "question": " 259億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.914408205465573
    },
    {
        "question": " 300億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.540266100375796
    },
    {
        "question": " 6374億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.248087485668552
    },
    {
        "question": " 69.8秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.06597250562662915
    },
    {
        "question": " 46.6秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.6682482732157125
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.17秒は何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.501462311707003
    },
    {
        "question": " 5125億msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2108559921259088
    },
    {
        "question": " 40.8兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.673719673772921
    },
    {
        "question": " 40.4億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.0497703004301604
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.03万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.12680539684496006
    },
    {
        "question": " 1458万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.163846773980441
    },
    {
        "question": " 36.5msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.562446948491089
    },
    {
        "question": " 46.1京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.164856221208998
    },
    {
        "question": " 1015京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.069789342861993
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.37兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.247639891050734
    },
    {
        "question": " 6544万usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.03766054110428296
    },
    {
        "question": " 604万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7807720518901284
    },
    {
        "question": " 695万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.8418841922741143
    },
    {
        "question": " 69.8万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 8.843734260315445
    },
    {
        "question": " 1584垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.7010675897503615
    },
    {
        "question": " 92.9垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.031557154905213
    },
    {
        "question": " 9277京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.411109283945379
    },
    {
        "question": " 3226億nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7305621412472907
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.7京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.939722562950998
    },
    {
        "question": " 7599万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.880746518980203
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.59兆nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.201377235938663
    },
    {
        "question": " 59.6年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.337449909201339
    },
    {
        "question": " 81.5年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.853674580120214
    },
    {
        "question": " 1178万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.50881734458649
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.98日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9799764305840095
    },
    {
        "question": " 1944日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.447069075310445
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.07万日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.894008933104741
    },
    {
        "question": " 77.4万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9460153029334193
    },
    {
        "question": " 49万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.310067651067344
    },
    {
        "question": " 1513万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.957969707234952
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.7時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.751052540472553
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.15時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.517866419534304
    },
    {
        "question": " 1130兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.33248579192863
    },
    {
        "question": " 228億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.199473855303201
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.07億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.709174661805442
    },
    {
        "question": " 5548分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.522286484309258
    },
    {
        "question": " 6983億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.345215965900904
    },
    {
        "question": " 237万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4379136176814256
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.82万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7042404682345949
    },
    {
        "question": " 2170秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.558338374718229
    },
    {
        "question": " 155秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.190587823596866
    },
    {
        "question": " 48.1京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.183152421884033
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.75京msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.005342344103715
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.2兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.785857214799284
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.05兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.533759535667988
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.72万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2366840156712433
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.25万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.628755347769155
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.16垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.213578409611559
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.86垓usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.831533897419947
    },
    {
        "question": " 1370億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5803618585948753
    },
    {
        "question": " 48.1兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.903986075731068
    },
    {
        "question": " 1485億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.171736082776384
    },
    {
        "question": " 2109usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 0.32402352908416643
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.268e+06垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.604396866259975
    },
    {
        "question": " 228垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.421415490976848
    },
    {
        "question": " 3931京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.038197937721229
    },
    {
        "question": " 1125兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.272861144663751
    },
    {
        "question": " 34.8億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5418371759039886
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.45兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.537504584749549
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.55億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 5.4058142734362065
    },
    {
        "question": " 69.3年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.783469009003457
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.6年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.691319589737693
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.73万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6754289629907804
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.5万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.120385405237365
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.81日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.4161693574842076
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.07日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.843539041893129
    },
    {
        "question": " 639万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.862860239835613
    },
    {
        "question": " 889万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.568858127553962
    },
    {
        "question": " 62.2万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.571757460714352
    },
    {
        "question": " 5233時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.275055597148301
    },
    {
        "question": " 3502万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8236928078766546
    },
    {
        "question": " 257億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.252032582127591
    },
    {
        "question": " 3017分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7014547946443281
    },
    {
        "question": " 223分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.126038460393809
    },
    {
        "question": " 170兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.73212948193301
    },
    {
        "question": " 1085億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.099114063857261
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.54兆秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.631694414073367
    },
    {
        "question": " 2460億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.61286661167324
    },
    {
        "question": " 1160億msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5655563134191688
    },
    {
        "question": " 1251億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.160784380752223
    },
    {
        "question": " 623億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.238415651493458
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.38兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.863392068682553
    },
    {
        "question": " 3530msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5477576283530738
    },
    {
        "question": " 5444msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.7359123996958346
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.5垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.524268649685201
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.34兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7909493950219346
    },
    {
        "question": " 115億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.50407437050074
    },
    {
        "question": " 33.5億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7464426106725495
    },
    {
        "question": " 29.1億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.463730872417571
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.1億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.003926338570582
    },
    {
        "question": " 138usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 5.141226218596469
    },
    {
        "question": " 1465京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6671791920670804
    },
    {
        "question": " 1656京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.282578180666908
    },
    {
        "question": " 59.7京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.2197642315723485
    },
    {
        "question": " 759京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.10191536344229
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.65兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.4226033831828873
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.14兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.055659984097473
    },
    {
        "question": " 24.7億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.392763376760265
    },
    {
        "question": " 1994年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.8619592230884
    },
    {
        "question": " 957年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.92335645260444
    },
    {
        "question": " 114億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.4934108726971065
    },
    {
        "question": " 263日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.800934435285508
    },
    {
        "question": " 101日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.161590953869222
    },
    {
        "question": " 59.7日は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.712575552039887
    },
    {
        "question": " 124億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.150691323769356
    },
    {
        "question": " 56.4万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.371106714670384
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.87万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.36601148224289
    },
    {
        "question": " 143時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.712187501690742
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.06時間は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.87008926894939
    },
    {
        "question": " 96.3万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.26303094058752197
    },
    {
        "question": " 470億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.51343902429006
    },
    {
        "question": " 254分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6266897862076348
    },
    {
        "question": " 4719万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.451988847201545
    },
    {
        "question": " 517億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.2144382397394655
    },
    {
        "question": " 683億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.898185549805733
    },
    {
        "question": " 4880秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.13207820237514878
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.31万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5854856740026513
    },
    {
        "question": " 621秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.79307105307398
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.3兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5156602899613336
    },
    {
        "question": " 1239億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.156566962734443
    },
    {
        "question": " 2139億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.773815269718389
    },
    {
        "question": " 323万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.731144210443114
    },
    {
        "question": " 96.4万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.983952488757957
    },
    {
        "question": " 19.5京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.7914340957170345
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.76兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9532784143290327
    },
    {
        "question": " 169兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.671633505436965
    },
    {
        "question": " 40.2京usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.82570990627881
    },
    {
        "question": " 39.2兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.593725081837164
    },
    {
        "question": " 696億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.842644709290292
    },
    {
        "question": " 734万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.865941177415168
    },
    {
        "question": " 2139垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.831496828154889
    },
    {
        "question": " 1040京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.080530243023942
    },
    {
        "question": " 23.8垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.82042760842101
    },
    {
        "question": " 430京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.8557292514164185
    },
    {
        "question": " 116億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.064299359092351
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.06億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 2.608934106469757
    },
    {
        "question": " 3063億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.486092489534073
    },
    {
        "question": " 28.4万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.3955178087511
    },
    {
        "question": " 476日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.11565598027275525
    },
    {
        "question": " 50万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.07911848345161
    },
    {
        "question": " 652日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.972373850131283
    },
    {
        "question": " 3104万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.549434269700449
    },
    {
        "question": " 232億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.984523720807973
    },
    {
        "question": " 38時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.3576154798782634
    },
    {
        "question": " 676兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.109429510306736
    },
    {
        "question": " 71.8万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.697618245497763
    },
    {
        "question": " 157万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.4164003560015574
    },
    {
        "question": " 161分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.985986764968288
    },
    {
        "question": " 128分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.886458602286389
    },
    {
        "question": " 84.3億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4268854851332766
    },
    {
        "question": " 7497億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.938379100240688
    },
    {
        "question": " 7070万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.29313715728253
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.43億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.378334543225842
    },
    {
        "question": " 50.8万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.7057678426147
    },
    {
        "question": " 3687億msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0678447271903235
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.5兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.124200875789554
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.5億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6604082140559235
    },
    {
        "question": " 939億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.194489436171656
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.3億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.053295405650116
    },
    {
        "question": " 102万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.009567089563578
    },
    {
        "question": " 38.8msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 7.589319007140868
    },
    {
        "question": " 533兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.227904571234909
    },
    {
        "question": " 41.1京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.676930554540162
    },
    {
        "question": " 111億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.4905788914086995
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.8京usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.903382820275818
    },
    {
        "question": " 1131億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.053476576156418
    },
    {
        "question": " 1516億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.180584117369348
    },
    {
        "question": " 108万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.031472031883501
    },
    {
        "question": " 8669垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.439152564406549
    },
    {
        "question": " 565京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.815292864407056
    },
    {
        "question": " 359京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.998931895321173
    },
    {
        "question": " 4140京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.838835512459765
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.98京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.600063040645244
    },
    {
        "question": " 2244万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.3509705520625082
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.06兆nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.608058391808452
    },
    {
        "question": " 7045年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.410161483789219
    },
    {
        "question": " 237年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.31715035992496
    },
    {
        "question": " 8623年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.65632804375542
    },
    {
        "question": " 249年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.894604584546752
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.26万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.791419727575836
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.6万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.626880655156508
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.61日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.978223736315228
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.09億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.764046980504069
    },
    {
        "question": " 5683万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.3743437415727735
    },
    {
        "question": " 53.5万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.50645808550707
    },
    {
        "question": " 6789万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1111579024842833
    },
    {
        "question": " 287万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.2997695106669367
    },
    {
        "question": " 198億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.51921791993158
    },
    {
        "question": " 24.3分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.1631707292209876
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.7京秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.529899799065442
    },
    {
        "question": " 211億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.388695731602406
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.74万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3323298927694882
    },
    {
        "question": " 327億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.735774572295787
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.95秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.59708457380762
    },
    {
        "question": " 711億msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.3529106751354494
    },
    {
        "question": " 42.6兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.693310458920048
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.9億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6959909432023577
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.17兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.5586552416164485
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.98億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.473669058780391
    },
    {
        "question": " 462万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.664591778437131
    },
    {
        "question": " 1754京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.745106330263514
    },
    {
        "question": " 1348億usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.19314796501277098
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.07京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.93105106116702
    },
    {
        "question": " 195億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5111179729985897
    },
    {
        "question": " 2860億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.456293166033025
    },
    {
        "question": " 6121万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.7867896186276395
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.2usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 3.342925508225283
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.825e+04垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.762357739556046
    },
    {
        "question": " 22.5京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.4165407776564196
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.2垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.786145862178983
    },
    {
        "question": " 1684兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.4480757150888595
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.14兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.497403726586088
    },
    {
        "question": " 261億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.415846745780522
    },
    {
        "question": " 126億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.102012802445973
    },
    {
        "question": " 1493万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.736485250103557
    },
    {
        "question": " 4566万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.097187309339698
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.15日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.995687567928878
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.81日は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.769374773915745
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.21億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.141509431453524
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.38万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.149042274100784
    },
    {
        "question": " 814時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.688882678021211
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.29億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.390337572979244
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.98万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3152136350023291
    },
    {
        "question": " 379億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.80090648998744
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.22万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.572212468832086
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.81億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4926886486958901
    },
    {
        "question": " 167億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.285794106123839
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.22兆秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.951869628837084
    },
    {
        "question": " 572億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.979266262014896
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.06兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9864081620896135
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.99億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0170593943796558
    },
    {
        "question": " 9093億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.402395718149538
    },
    {
        "question": " 5772万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9831825147006708
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.67兆msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.56455407150601
    },
    {
        "question": " 333msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 5.522629447299315
    },
    {
        "question": " 975msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 8.989132045634268
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.7垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.73269978562121
    },
    {
        "question": " 392京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.657198209269074
    },
    {
        "question": " 3076京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.931730265967088
    },
    {
        "question": " 991兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.217997467336128
    },
    {
        "question": " 151億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.177712510816903
    },
    {
        "question": " 2兆usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.301712684045716
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.07万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 7.029592408266566
    },
    {
        "question": " 1517垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.682232803637875
    },
    {
        "question": " 196垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.356638114204731
    },
    {
        "question": " 2308兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8069565216191394
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.58兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.968200223185158
    },
    {
        "question": " 61.4兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.788287013871058
    },
    {
        "question": " 4753億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.676930884312529
    },
    {
        "question": " 8520億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.930414741495136
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.21年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.2269786565175345
    },
    {
        "question": " 581日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.20155719635062574
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.59日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7926760137108355
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.3万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.249633823645793
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.13日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.646374365533529
    },
    {
        "question": " 2597万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.4718880460656933
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.49億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.016550991587702
    },
    {
        "question": " 133時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.900872941607939
    },
    {
        "question": " 232万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.921737106056867
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.26時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.909778627772882
    },
    {
        "question": " 594兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.0528493080282
    },
    {
        "question": " 50.7億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.546760820658648
    },
    {
        "question": " 9634万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.205676569350578
    },
    {
        "question": " 349分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.321044165157312
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.6万分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.8023041043326
    },
    {
        "question": " 157分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.975378848191745
    },
    {
        "question": " 18.5兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.768624576773935
    },
    {
        "question": " 8026億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.967993687310013
    },
    {
        "question": " 691億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.282923268810338
    },
    {
        "question": " 44.6万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.87097942792796
    },
    {
        "question": " 108万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.035168411646689
    },
    {
        "question": " 95.1秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.977955887056755
    },
    {
        "question": " 2467兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.893295557090013
    },
    {
        "question": " 75.1兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.939348711893642
    },
    {
        "question": " 409兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.055331783120113
    },
    {
        "question": " 44.6兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.870998417136
    },
    {
        "question": " 9483億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.976940045627464
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.55京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6917158826051555
    },
    {
        "question": " 24.3京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.4489825523799285
    },
    {
        "question": " 1857兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.71252723427274
    },
    {
        "question": " 155兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.411351486330778
    },
    {
        "question": " 5535億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.743095535875895
    },
    {
        "question": " 1184億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.073292787527315
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.02usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 3.7793218289639263
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.376e+05垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.305725455251517
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.13京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6797031325724205
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.3垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.306980093270575
    },
    {
        "question": " 363兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.7811588546595267
    },
    {
        "question": " 330億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5188871880878985
    },
    {
        "question": " 37.8兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.577135688799918
    },
    {
        "question": " 1049nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 0.020846619042117487
    },
    {
        "question": " 875万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.504532357733382
    },
    {
        "question": " 1373年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.858289645991453
    },
    {
        "question": " 3866万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.024923993045198
    },
    {
        "question": " 298万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.854487584679774
    },
    {
        "question": " 6129日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.945761029870107
    },
    {
        "question": " 1368日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.072633632352009
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.21万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.14034853548043014
    },
    {
        "question": " 1005時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.621848891044475
    },
    {
        "question": " 99.9万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.777555884141436
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.06時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.404906456510943
    },
    {
        "question": " 2314兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.643655006925474
    },
    {
        "question": " 5149億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.553386741721397
    },
    {
        "question": " 21.4億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.552234286690397
    },
    {
        "question": " 101分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.781129269795173
    },
    {
        "question": " 2343兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.870898726862061
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.91兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.834938700454766
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.4兆秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.571259683878479
    },
    {
        "question": " 268億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.65020925252156
    },
    {
        "question": " 133万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.122488476084447
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.2秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.007212675901705
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.92兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7853986675994793
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.2億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1145719795638953
    },
    {
        "question": " 1001万msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.44402350912966404
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.58兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.101792953953456
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.91万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.28019589479195
    },
    {
        "question": " 53.7msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.729671995933621
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.4msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 7.0555347777885835
    },
    {
        "question": " 199京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.800358917825173
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.53垓usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.994396329658363
    },
    {
        "question": " 22.3京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.791272096770719
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.62京usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.157597256730659
    },
    {
        "question": " 260万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.414956601913149
    },
    {
        "question": " 167億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.222997917200683
    },
    {
        "question": " 1108usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.044439102476954
    },
    {
        "question": " 1341垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.628526992369087
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.95垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.061404754653968
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.1垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.150848827350393
    },
    {
        "question": " 58.6京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.989507790102529
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.6億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.027032209241129035
    },
    {
        "question": " 5618万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.7496057843435586
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.5万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 2.0610013251102566
    },
    {
        "question": " 1267年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.823472824711128
    },
    {
        "question": " 19.6年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.791874558504421
    },
    {
        "question": " 8715億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.377953424733578
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.35億日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.905025957528315
    },
    {
        "question": " 5515日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.899866137998658
    },
    {
        "question": " 105日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.958143796174708
    },
    {
        "question": " 1917万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.3401379406824807
    },
    {
        "question": " 233億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.987171653113402
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.28万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.886424698996082
    },
    {
        "question": " 303時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.0373341852609546
    },
    {
        "question": " 8056億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.185475889564856
    },
    {
        "question": " 428万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.4730349610013023
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.33億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.346299740727222
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.86分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.614408250114673
    },
    {
        "question": " 88.2億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.446723688752143
    },
    {
        "question": " 469兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.734704956087132
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.48万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1827216048615652
    },
    {
        "question": " 62.3億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.01621227486136
    },
    {
        "question": " 141秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.148385738313758
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.09秒は何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.907738788731722
    },
    {
        "question": " 4868兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.1885383902264355
    },
    {
        "question": " 47.7兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.742203050220115
    },
    {
        "question": " 82.9兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.362110618729317
    },
    {
        "question": " 2613万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6390004890518637
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.83億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.582837672651384
    },
    {
        "question": " 162万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.210632525338063
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.65msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.883913665233763
    },
    {
        "question": " 37.5兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.07551644404522384
    },
    {
        "question": " 141京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.212256746663002
    },
    {
        "question": " 18.1京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.702498243025171
    },
    {
        "question": " 42.5京usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.85051322121114
    },
    {
        "question": " 1343億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.127947106337758
    },
    {
        "question": " 350万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.5442063495103584
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.4京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5162298556875622
    },
    {
        "question": " 894垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.014859257751503
    },
    {
        "question": " 71.5兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2980079385348198
    },
    {
        "question": " 383兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.805016970794152
    },
    {
        "question": " 210億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.322982449880814
    },
    {
        "question": " 49兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.690002188370919
    },
    {
        "question": " 14億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.145468188445471
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.72万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.997251174166809
    },
    {
        "question": " 20.6年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.034851858607729
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.7年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.566788017439512
    },
    {
        "question": " 2515億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.8381536898584
    },
    {
        "question": " 3418日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.91397070888439
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.5兆時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.079680444260669
    },
    {
        "question": " 28万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.067636571609782
    },
    {
        "question": " 184万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.042932160190407
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.18時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.519110117527836
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.39億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4221948389919556
    },
    {
        "question": " 246万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.2323428645698837
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.18万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.294139217875518
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.2分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8986353542036305
    },
    {
        "question": " 3250万秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.013066044696835588
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.52億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.245794266025234
    },
    {
        "question": " 34.1万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9761891447360591
    },
    {
        "question": " 49.8万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.9190985236137643
    },
    {
        "question": " 607秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.783166234659964
    },
    {
        "question": " 127京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.604769217490794
    },
    {
        "question": " 179億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.317530869257445
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.2億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.53077180096016
    },
    {
        "question": " 79.4億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.1214667489817085
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.84兆msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.263726443359783
    },
    {
        "question": " 173msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 5.237447071183179
    },
    {
        "question": " 7396京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.37016352379642
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.64京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.729830937156368
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.07京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.474208837529067
    },
    {
        "question": " 1467億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.3883377927449585
    },
    {
        "question": " 78億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.892021442877116
    },
    {
        "question": " 42.5億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.628612497141155
    },
    {
        "question": " 521垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.217704654825323
    },
    {
        "question": " 2477京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.457427637630847
    },
    {
        "question": " 1235兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5355376438128365
    },
    {
        "question": " 4821億nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9049861638531331
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.14京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.055605234542844
    },
    {
        "question": " 4945万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.6942049220286404
    },
    {
        "question": " 476万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 3.6777475755078894
    },
    {
        "question": " 2080万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.880360943023437
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.45年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.368910087700732
    },
    {
        "question": " 76.4億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.320632735026887
    },
    {
        "question": " 206日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.694046036558066
    },
    {
        "question": " 63.6万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.961584022330646
    },
    {
        "question": " 987日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.930728730775678
    },
    {
        "question": " 37.1日は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.506011824604037
    },
    {
        "question": " 4142億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.674679166242992
    },
    {
        "question": " 1429万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.774884286057972
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.39時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9204490614590441
    },
    {
        "question": " 178時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.805912914308454
    },
    {
        "question": " 95.8万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.26063660332498073
    },
    {
        "question": " 24万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.221880012228067
    },
    {
        "question": " 12億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.300817769473438
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.42分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.931048372517491
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.38分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.155437614823162
    },
    {
        "question": " 41.4億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1186265480625144
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.21兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.569417929794623
    },
    {
        "question": " 2905万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.90688129013808
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.12億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.5488527720457
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.93万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.950708622884276
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.2秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.051046829061018
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.57京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.160826784798989
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.04兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.372986384975052
    },
    {
        "question": " 20.8兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.761731673216644
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.98兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.518847934150625
    },
    {
        "question": " 64.5億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.809833629076177
    },
    {
        "question": " 4455msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.648869583330287
    },
    {
        "question": " 25.8垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.9130962991353515
    },
    {
        "question": " 50.4京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.765925428195856
    },
    {
        "question": " 229億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8037675052841764
    },
    {
        "question": " 40.7兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.831345249705024
    },
    {
        "question": " 195万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.29043436582772864
    },
    {
        "question": " 1147usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 0.05954051722193654
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.45usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 3.8094347845906884
    },
    {
        "question": " 177垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.750369067200168
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.95京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.905557993081529
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.06垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.350017344824188
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.03京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.1266655925288225
    },
    {
        "question": " 134億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1282384464641149
    },
    {
        "question": " 12兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.078874642801631
    },
    {
        "question": " 6757万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.829749182848715
    },
    {
        "question": " 959年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.544210566570763
    },
    {
        "question": " 48.9万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.631380009714718
    },
    {
        "question": " 332万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.9592511755743454
    },
    {
        "question": " 21.6日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.715533886639765
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.14日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.654929208458536
    },
    {
        "question": " 8738億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.998900133402436
    },
    {
        "question": " 190億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.899111670735543
    },
    {
        "question": " 7666万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.662695475673818
    },
    {
        "question": " 30.5時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.0407777358244275
    },
    {
        "question": " 1814時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.814884799816495
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.18時間は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.628435306461839
    },
    {
        "question": " 210億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.602514314939051
    },
    {
        "question": " 230億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.202732492324159
    },
    {
        "question": " 463億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.887018643114601
    },
    {
        "question": " 30.1分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.25650686374799
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.99兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.102567070862635
    },
    {
        "question": " 860兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.998229292926707
    },
    {
        "question": " 1365億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.578744064059886
    },
    {
        "question": " 949億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.199042331046314
    },
    {
        "question": " 782億msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.3943465650564415
    },
    {
        "question": " 7783兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.954653625015078
    },
    {
        "question": " 608万msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.2273501758374885
    },
    {
        "question": " 28.9億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.682333482595196
    },
    {
        "question": " 3090億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.490023045285195
    },
    {
        "question": " 97.6msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.989251337350896
    },
    {
        "question": " 867兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.43906432558647
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.86垓usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.89952987225672
    },
    {
        "question": " 139京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.586231389123597
    },
    {
        "question": " 6677万usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.04640946135471613
    },
    {
        "question": " 7074万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8496812108678995
    },
    {
        "question": " 6765万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.83027552660633
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.792e+05垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.75460045967054
    },
    {
        "question": " 2垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.3636920791875715
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.8兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6686753563402226
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.13京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.275376688586924
    },
    {
        "question": " 20.1億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.3035599482142326
    },
    {
        "question": " 95.8億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.981207488547324
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.21億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 5.505909205673866
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.69万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.791038989011842
    },
    {
        "question": " 1414年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.0930366196705155
    },
    {
        "question": " 46.4億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.103991185832133
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.55億日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.93052896003763
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.64日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.142398148201916
    },
    {
        "question": " 205日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.247218590285636
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.06兆時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.014710170843566
    },
    {
        "question": " 1883時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.894708699498191
    },
    {
        "question": " 177時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.026395019690156
    },
    {
        "question": " 125時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.6517863294527295
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.54兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.82830603396957
    },
    {
        "question": " 2188万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.181741316411171
    },
    {
        "question": " 698万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.06566333837457
    },
    {
        "question": " 123万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.866440444027974
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.18億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.572707520228114
    },
    {
        "question": " 1838億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.327740496409815
    },
    {
        "question": " 64.1万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2506393041456607
    },
    {
        "question": " 5377秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9524055248552097
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.53垓msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.686171930641446
    },
    {
        "question": " 74.9億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9377245792043307
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.27京msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.54894958270905
    },
    {
        "question": " 38.4万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8060498710841957
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.23兆msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.08831728684776
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.06万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.02719763126809
    },
    {
        "question": " 554msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 8.743462519789512
    },
    {
        "question": " 105垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.521496627165204
    },
    {
        "question": " 154兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.2512319975010975
    },
    {
        "question": " 2636億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8646878775399067
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.51兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.875719368630826
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.78億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.577690523694506
    },
    {
        "question": " 38.4億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.584167870829817
    },
    {
        "question": " 234usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 5.368785717182716
    },
    {
        "question": " 9527垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.480172040603424
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.29垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.174157776956886
    },
    {
        "question": " 2003兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.745375812879345
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.8兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4776594002983678
    },
    {
        "question": " 1127億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.0520420310478116
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.25兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.095347380507031
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.62億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 5.4178794899236316
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.8年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.5066963812060092
    },
    {
        "question": " 613年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.7302077747308005
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.8年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.970162694573247
    },
    {
        "question": " 5687日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1926093513226343
    },
    {
        "question": " 89.7万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.332825854983352
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.97万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.6315568842306005
    },
    {
        "question": " 25.3兆時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.460591038888179
    },
    {
        "question": " 167時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8429025650190913
    },
    {
        "question": " 128万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.886657138740546
    },
    {
        "question": " 31.5時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.053950137738431
    },
    {
        "question": " 888万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2275720914780808
    },
    {
        "question": " 188億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.114906735773454
    },
    {
        "question": " 282億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.671712020189204
    },
    {
        "question": " 5702分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.534158773922089
    },
    {
        "question": " 9850億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.494641480628209
    },
    {
        "question": " 800兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.966485591299941
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.86億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.900807143849687
    },
    {
        "question": " 156秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.41420873642134426
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.04万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.017195829962262
    },
    {
        "question": " 257秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.410690133661834
    },
    {
        "question": " 1022億msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5104355573424768
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.9京msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.098941075394624
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.69億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8739792137690703
    },
    {
        "question": " 24.5億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.611730312902767
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.12兆msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.909316295686514
    },
    {
        "question": " 358万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.553883924129089
    },
    {
        "question": " 39.6msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 7.5971947881501265
    },
    {
        "question": " 324兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0119679211340604
    },
    {
        "question": " 65兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8763935329373878
    },
    {
        "question": " 6980億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2875727480293175
    },
    {
        "question": " 19.5兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.512247864973378
    },
    {
        "question": " 4547万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6577202926697931
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.32億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.364768136602467
    },
    {
        "question": " 191万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.279941561396985
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.413e+06垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.883817456028591
    },
    {
        "question": " 275垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.502669417813388
    },
    {
        "question": " 9013京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.398568473135255
    },
    {
        "question": " 8966京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.174449867396051
    },
    {
        "question": " 372億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5700444850341477
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.99億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 2.2984016590805014
    },
    {
        "question": " 294万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 3.4676696298613905
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.7万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.882020817581981
    },
    {
        "question": " 777億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.328282816650047
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.48万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.549956390630978
    },
    {
        "question": " 213億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.38492371091537
    },
    {
        "question": " 609時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4046390815658039
    },
    {
        "question": " 560時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.5267123110170395
    },
    {
        "question": " 102万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.565769279338086
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.66時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.775393286173569
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.31億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6430056074783304
    },
    {
        "question": " 4364億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.48153939807711
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.02億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.527242231920417
    },
    {
        "question": " 33.1分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.298540944312199
    },
    {
        "question": " 3300億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.0197671252681495
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.17兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.919304186646721
    },
    {
        "question": " 27.7万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8866539238857905
    },
    {
        "question": " 25.4万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.6266798289305333
    },
    {
        "question": " 108秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.033731258490276
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.87秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.5874705999383085
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.79秒は何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.252279672243871
    },
    {
        "question": " 29.6兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.971886295090096
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.44億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.4507901153858085
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.79京msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.69540189526626
    },
    {
        "question": " 254兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.626940445249861
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.2万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.008754534736099
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.4msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 7.159486587410724
    },
    {
        "question": " 757垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.380374538950413
    },
    {
        "question": " 259兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.476287598667894
    },
    {
        "question": " 1583億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6430876771103964
    },
    {
        "question": " 23兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.584037026478654
    },
    {
        "question": " 8138億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.910492691050421
    },
    {
        "question": " 2590usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 0.4133670603311035
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.314e+05垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.420981382008872
    },
    {
        "question": " 19.6垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.355268278160984
    },
    {
        "question": " 91京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.402852480129049
    },
    {
        "question": " 36.5兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.784257660611514
    },
    {
        "question": " 396億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5974529902243606
    },
    {
        "question": " 8803兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.944637022599775
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.26億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 5.721021269197095
    },
    {
        "question": " 861万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.497135158864014
    },
    {
        "question": " 1460年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.884920043919324
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.4億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.4567735362822045
    },
    {
        "question": " 39.6万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.978312593421158
    },
    {
        "question": " 3188日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.661873701201511
    },
    {
        "question": " 7762億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.947440341269928
    },
    {
        "question": " 2728万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.055659579386184
    },
    {
        "question": " 126万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.877947347302418
    },
    {
        "question": " 5172時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.269999484950799
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.86兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.548265509332895
    },
    {
        "question": " 856億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.773979201151333
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.1万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.2246391545072584
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.56兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.693442672474285
    },
    {
        "question": " 984億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.056342152897524
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.07万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.47186703165923105
    },
    {
        "question": " 214万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.551738666927348
    },
    {
        "question": " 719京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.358215853139827
    },
    {
        "question": " 4兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.665947249463686
    },
    {
        "question": " 62.6億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.2400430165585394
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.81億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.671003981302162
    },
    {
        "question": " 2564万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.408893799715794
    },
    {
        "question": " 9391msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.9727294579933545
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.36京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8747430392993567
    },
    {
        "question": " 576兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.8238445310482527
    },
    {
        "question": " 4109億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.0574383889882117
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.65億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.4394937550734679
    },
    {
        "question": " 820億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.913825697153809
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.37万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.136230735712822
    },
    {
        "question": " 21.5usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 4.333354750230506
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.16垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.120752561767541
    },
    {
        "question": " 491兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7548192642530738
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.47京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.610071984613783
    },
    {
        "question": " 320兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.7270289681802007
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.23京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.090157752380915
    },
    {
        "question": " 3621万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.5588164538046512
    },
    {
        "question": " 50.5億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.703320063048688
    },
    {
        "question": " 19.3万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.227751689215278
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.15万年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.783038325254594
    },
    {
        "question": " 1295億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.550022001918817
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.5万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.598248827706441
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.97日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.8550817578387973
    },
    {
        "question": " 74日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.805670136453134
    },
    {
        "question": " 168億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.282440370710321
    },
    {
        "question": " 1181億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.692064620463732
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.87万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.0505896318779016
    },
    {
        "question": " 303時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.037476375272586
    },
    {
        "question": " 3953億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.876264888368489
    },
    {
        "question": " 6636億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.663543204569468
    },
    {
        "question": " 1499億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.397756252975636
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.39億分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.922122356243841
    },
    {
        "question": " 162兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.711935821110169
    },
    {
        "question": " 365兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.625991899910883
    },
    {
        "question": " 556億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.188933402324031
    },
    {
        "question": " 9084万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.180126741375097
    },
    {
        "question": " 69.3万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.84064278744905
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.12京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.116267383548134
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.8京msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.64306838813594
    },
    {
        "question": " 485万msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.12926274973162122
    },
    {
        "question": " 3334万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7447917706368896
    },
    {
        "question": " 935億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.9709450896082865
    },
    {
        "question": " 266万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.425286175383993
    },
    {
        "question": " 849垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.430107446767874
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.96兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8385471391906905
    },
    {
        "question": " 1015億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4503103152169838
    },
    {
        "question": " 200億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.523643618087339
    },
    {
        "question": " 4627兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.665283389503823
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.9万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 2.2003890617620514
    },
    {
        "question": " 18usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 4.2546155342007
    },
    {
        "question": " 2212京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8459486114324073
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.7垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.286306896987643
    },
    {
        "question": " 3807京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.024226907490267
    },
    {
        "question": " 170兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.4523068937454324
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.35兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.728233823034932
    },
    {
        "question": " 526万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 0.7210090524024859
    },
    {
        "question": " 2181万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.3386398101033
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.9年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.7628883383284917
    },
    {
        "question": " 1411億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.587093654273563
    },
    {
        "question": " 3381日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.687381094317185
    },
    {
        "question": " 33.4日は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.460196706350274
    },
    {
        "question": " 105万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.079031772826877
    },
    {
        "question": " 6012時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.39879215944356
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.83時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4619914755824555
    },
    {
        "question": " 262時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.973925495875076
    },
    {
        "question": " 1545兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.468161201645946
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.1兆分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.454377480520744
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.64万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.644136692341582
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.69万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.345059493052
    },
    {
        "question": " 326分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.291785898164464
    },
    {
        "question": " 48.6分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.464710744290846
    },
    {
        "question": " 19.1京秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.781420131336233
    },
    {
        "question": " 83.2億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.983535408646954
    },
    {
        "question": " 1698万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.6736005541427175
    },
    {
        "question": " 150億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.39896761700871
    },
    {
        "question": " 561万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.749073834123488
    },
    {
        "question": " 62.6兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.298046096629342
    },
    {
        "question": " 75.4兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.940875569614919
    },
    {
        "question": " 1013万msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.4493760598029961
    },
    {
        "question": " 795万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.122242795874679
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.08万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0334474008773376
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.3msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.014895486892475
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.36msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.803225846850422
    },
    {
        "question": " 677京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.331470248985548
    },
    {
        "question": " 1421兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.21615503430072
    },
    {
        "question": " 1742億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.684773800162589
    },
    {
        "question": " 4153億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.8401632365674168
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.34億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6371673357497585
    },
    {
        "question": " 34億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.532045832360279
    },
    {
        "question": " 1815usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.258959612520493
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.175e+06垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.57141264174427
    },
    {
        "question": " 1140兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.120478864358947
    },
    {
        "question": " 3704京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.012390819014966
    },
    {
        "question": " 62.4兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.0171108366316868
    },
    {
        "question": " 38.4兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.584102098284124
    },
    {
        "question": " 162万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 0.2087248849206691
    },
    {
        "question": " 2469億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.392591360151727
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.13万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.5229307215999
    },
    {
        "question": " 111万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.989105633811125
    },
    {
        "question": " 349億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.980351832404617
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.08万日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.425422376750692
    },
    {
        "question": " 109万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.09393883631962
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.79億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.064971201204195
    },
    {
        "question": " 546万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.515073358263061
    },
    {
        "question": " 32.7億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.794361512482868
    },
    {
        "question": " 123万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.930660351504785
    },
    {
        "question": " 120万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.30019780247941
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.33分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.90128905147817
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.9分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.952751454442474
    },
    {
        "question": " 42.3億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1272616724185345
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.24億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.4132334530016384
    },
    {
        "question": " 624万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.238961324368522
    },
    {
        "question": " 81.1秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.13071942025007388
    },
    {
        "question": " 108京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.532957306383208
    },
    {
        "question": " 52.6兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.784590515750937
    },
    {
        "question": " 30.6億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.929689813050187
    },
    {
        "question": " 367万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7860566330220706
    },
    {
        "question": " 33.5億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.525333851498761
    },
    {
        "question": " 139万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.14288763696644
    },
    {
        "question": " 160兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7058585406287077
    },
    {
        "question": " 1425兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.217254044532263
    },
    {
        "question": " 319京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.947575622340857
    },
    {
        "question": " 645億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.031533518091077
    },
    {
        "question": " 56.6兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.752644523472034
    },
    {
        "question": " 29.4億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.468396632303516
    },
    {
        "question": " 3567京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.05348372942174
    },
    {
        "question": " 42.2京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.6883566612881924
    },
    {
        "question": " 1127京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.495470890130271
    },
    {
        "question": " 3356兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.747715989687124
    },
    {
        "question": " 1243兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.094313544379607
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.23億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 2.9652022984695936
    },
    {
        "question": " 1456万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.163096903688851
    },
    {
        "question": " 2209年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.286694046272252
    },
    {
        "question": " 607億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.221119496273348
    },
    {
        "question": " 127万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.485573993945801
    },
    {
        "question": " 37.4万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.730995090344662
    },
    {
        "question": " 3368日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.463822032089789
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.42万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.4420572036254633
    },
    {
        "question": " 48.8億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.308448522288664
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.63万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.991547241181083
    },
    {
        "question": " 177万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.805144451232868
    },
    {
        "question": " 387万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.866773345631664
    },
    {
        "question": " 6065万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.6245017800917365
    },
    {
        "question": " 6788分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.053584637068193
    },
    {
        "question": " 808万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.685607470325387
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.6兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.694171542514961
    },
    {
        "question": " 145兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.225676547882985
    },
    {
        "question": " 7725万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.33160998380779
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.53億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.406492471480865
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.85万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.267363680758593
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.1秒は何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.32144939213186
    },
    {
        "question": " 9180億msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4640447220100439
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.27兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.419167822841735
    },
    {
        "question": " 1195万msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5211219120389232
    },
    {
        "question": " 721万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.0799372193640764
    },
    {
        "question": " 530億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.724179008248987
    },
    {
        "question": " 1182msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.072753383223652
    },
    {
        "question": " 234垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.870383909531164
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.6兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2838297969965407
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.34兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.413844585728525
    },
    {
        "question": " 8736億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.16318250825125
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.21億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.793161139786612
    },
    {
        "question": " 8694億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.939231446423117
    },
    {
        "question": " 175万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.243115978239597
    },
    {
        "question": " 243垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.887252765136251
    },
    {
        "question": " 5863兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8316538325581944
    },
    {
        "question": " 1492京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.617607016569011
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.63京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.4347966582574205
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.26兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.721072517061109
    },
    {
        "question": " 564万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 0.751455173683514
    },
    {
        "question": " 371万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 3.5693996864320985
    },
    {
        "question": " 185万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.829210430546674
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.51万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.121567159337584
    },
    {
        "question": " 827億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.355383958287108
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.49万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.3316488691290775
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.26万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.411846929493741
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.93万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.0863089387411446
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.3時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.6450845147205015
    },
    {
        "question": " 396時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.153615237757949
    },
    {
        "question": " 2984兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.754155560799354
    },
    {
        "question": " 2208分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.18568892612255583
    },
    {
        "question": " 44.8万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.873172941303845
    },
    {
        "question": " 460分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.441336450453001
    },
    {
        "question": " 239分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.155859855411084
    },
    {
        "question": " 47.8兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.180284909196498
    },
    {
        "question": " 46.4万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7297853334146642
    },
    {
        "question": " 134万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.570131970292521
    },
    {
        "question": " 801秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1256310357306243
    },
    {
        "question": " 351秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.544744102955944
    },
    {
        "question": " 7357兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.367908566764079
    },
    {
        "question": " 34.9兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.606845335869979
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.67兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.429133745595056
    },
    {
        "question": " 71.3万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0751167756769398
    },
    {
        "question": " 8万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9031534284274954
    },
    {
        "question": " 57.1msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.75654389051717
    },
    {
        "question": " 1462垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.666028926934354
    },
    {
        "question": " 3137京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.560080861776996
    },
    {
        "question": " 27兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.874322577957824
    },
    {
        "question": " 16京usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.426036693413472
    },
    {
        "question": " 322万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5084121317013823
    },
    {
        "question": " 291億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.463782823843016
    },
    {
        "question": " 53.4万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 8.727466225565587
    },
    {
        "question": " 4486垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.153097247786077
    },
    {
        "question": " 218京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.401189234430916
    },
    {
        "question": " 43.3京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.080017240692589
    },
    {
        "question": " 642億nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.029415245376663846
    },
    {
        "question": " 43.6億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6399551812489357
    },
    {
        "question": " 134兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.126743854059043
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.59兆nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.41307017463931
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.38年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.8602413719677955
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.21兆日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.781653523075828
    },
    {
        "question": " 1728日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.617696253134882
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.75日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.5975468515458697
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.54万日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.75235042641933
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.1万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2372164992267698
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.95万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.908881719640716
    },
    {
        "question": " 47.8万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.235800273603402
    },
    {
        "question": " 7173万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1350382845862157
    },
    {
        "question": " 268万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.270427040487368
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.94億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.995742470990186
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.88万分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.052543256634108
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.25兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.597251005654945
    },
    {
        "question": " 89.2億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.013870447278203
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.3万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6563938692787694
    },
    {
        "question": " 25.9万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.6357419411185354
    },
    {
        "question": " 498秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.697123011242001
    },
    {
        "question": " 2265京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.856345944288371
    },
    {
        "question": " 316兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.562811925589521
    },
    {
        "question": " 6502万msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2567687304928077
    },
    {
        "question": " 29.6億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.693362405884788
    },
    {
        "question": " 1685msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.22656200298817764
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.23msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.348993549039395
    },
    {
        "question": " 1265京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.603350683900273
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.46兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6022772649453731
    },
    {
        "question": " 2013兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.747590940003472
    },
    {
        "question": " 173億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4586981643628825
    },
    {
        "question": " 2016兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.30438464432876
    },
    {
        "question": " 1716万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.23449461615432
    },
    {
        "question": " 1830usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.262340960926494
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.08垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.9894102140541454
    },
    {
        "question": " 2455京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.453626133698059
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.48垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.838634743376832
    },
    {
        "question": " 81.2兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.131503606689332
    },
    {
        "question": " 213兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.327466595965891
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.61兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.558103315609266
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.58億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 5.199606943084746
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.21年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9067596275784924
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.05万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.426585565505993
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.96年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.192146307497869
    },
    {
        "question": " 513億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.147737206358563
    },
    {
        "question": " 139日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.5228573693060348
    },
    {
        "question": " 57.6日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.918636586543716
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.41万日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.085612548656497
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.05万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.08059566101476401
    },
    {
        "question": " 126万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.720136627174648
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.07万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.265883385195105
    },
    {
        "question": " 65.4時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.371759244144729
    },
    {
        "question": " 445万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9274128697571449
    },
    {
        "question": " 1891億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.118377115118765
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.2万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.230616372569397
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.95分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.248566041618083
    },
    {
        "question": " 123兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.592470581467861
    },
    {
        "question": " 5589億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.810830931132794
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.02億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.398732751000702
    },
    {
        "question": " 3222秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7299785564546566
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.36秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.373405124190122
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.02垓msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.980656371602448
    },
    {
        "question": " 1570億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.2594402538519986
    },
    {
        "question": " 2054億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.756292579344401
    },
    {
        "question": " 5413億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.955269221569806
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.99兆msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.698351565595946
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.9万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.075211618327305
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.15垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.9994269553499855
    },
    {
        "question": " 127兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.1677359012929074
    },
    {
        "question": " 517京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.157239934049716
    },
    {
        "question": " 18.9兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.49760356255768
    },
    {
        "question": " 790兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.897829207499814
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.31兆usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.117079190420728
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.2京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5506560303459285
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.11垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.386832470657627
    },
    {
        "question": " 7131京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.296827552607077
    },
    {
        "question": " 64.9兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.0338704509768166
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.9兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.8388883889166534
    },
    {
        "question": " 5729万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.7580629352325283
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.3万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 2.0547499706295023
    },
    {
        "question": " 134年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.69014856940116
    },
    {
        "question": " 31.1万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.434592717873937
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.9年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.9994396388753
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.56年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.315805502816167
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.34万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8077289201939761
    },
    {
        "question": " 1328万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.503386507739544
    },
    {
        "question": " 309万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.647718849913128
    },
    {
        "question": " 2日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.237449117254479
    },
    {
        "question": " 30.9日は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.426758742029433
    },
    {
        "question": " 32.2億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.565703108937452
    },
    {
        "question": " 6104時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.40543151754816
    },
    {
        "question": " 1123万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.828545474608395
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.66時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.776595561999638
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.4億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.148290490958554
    },
    {
        "question": " 3403万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.373494145111746
    },
    {
        "question": " 368万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.787936913924387
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.9万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.0054465100522645
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.11分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.822692895916816
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.52京秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.902831957311198
    },
    {
        "question": " 35.2万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6094404442250134
    },
    {
        "question": " 45.6億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.102565902568693
    },
    {
        "question": " 2334万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.58997681575419
    },
    {
        "question": " 76.8兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.386614071271752
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.89兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.340767328320433
    },
    {
        "question": " 274億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.8820442759424054
    },
    {
        "question": " 22.4兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.571804624552948
    },
    {
        "question": " 9546万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.979814502689628
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.87msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.270904370888925
    },
    {
        "question": " 593京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.274502737821978
    },
    {
        "question": " 2726兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.499092989356196
    },
    {
        "question": " 34.5京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.981814072808996
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.18兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.723797778073708
    },
    {
        "question": " 20.8億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.3186471926710737
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.2億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.08526035998328
    },
    {
        "question": " 91.4垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.462069319407128
    },
    {
        "question": " 8572垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.996598319944852
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.06垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.757255638775665
    },
    {
        "question": " 508京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.927704567657613
    },
    {
        "question": " 791億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8983312481901837
    },
    {
        "question": " 1110億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.0453824146977135
    },
    {
        "question": " 2179万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.33818694882822
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.11万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.556549901655192
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.93年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.188049992177211
    },
    {
        "question": " 16億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.6420651432516555
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.75万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.402264677584034
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.41万日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.08630503289525
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.6兆時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.123113589972835
    },
    {
        "question": " 8040万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.525081565872039
    },
    {
        "question": " 250万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.176014361562183
    },
    {
        "question": " 1340時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.683506434760794
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.93時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.329333739358455
    },
    {
        "question": " 73.9兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.147812625166686
    },
    {
        "question": " 9116億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.801450513144529
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.11万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.1310440599124822
    },
    {
        "question": " 132万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.90033497757608
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.09分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.098405454709676
    },
    {
        "question": " 1540億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.6887045713395827
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.01億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.666673076038971
    },
    {
        "question": " 139億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.586360768441587
    },
    {
        "question": " 122秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.30698238452321225
    },
    {
        "question": " 8394秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.923955703264123
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.51秒は何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.180331623572975
    },
    {
        "question": " 5146兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.212634563189037
    },
    {
        "question": " 3534兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.611749296115381
    },
    {
        "question": " 2584億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.856067358115571
    },
    {
        "question": " 70.5兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.069787039918872
    },
    {
        "question": " 485万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.6853553653743876
    },
    {
        "question": " 142万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.15232577563119
    },
    {
        "question": " 68.5兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.33695302107617175
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.1垓usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.10544862789214
    },
    {
        "question": " 2771億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.886399381707704
    },
    {
        "question": " 438兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.862884107277352
    },
    {
        "question": " 169兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.229129347334993
    },
    {
        "question": " 2983usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 0.4746404511925484
    },
    {
        "question": " 279万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.445614055181018
    },
    {
        "question": " 5821京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.2661646402104094
    },
    {
        "question": " 1391垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.20693782733688
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.7兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.2698543922055463
    },
    {
        "question": " 149兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.3964134145900204
    },
    {
        "question": " 327兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.5150642952045885
    },
    {
        "question": " 4604万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.6631686794046996
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.6億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.098736383494662
    },
    {
        "question": " 772年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.449723716154531
    },
    {
        "question": " 1131日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.49113538032075965
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.16万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.224373672131837
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.53億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.4599613382109835
    },
    {
        "question": " 4438時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2669606479096336
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.45万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.650415894614935
    },
    {
        "question": " 9249時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.522382590880914
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.36億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.008275751823677
    },
    {
        "question": " 352万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.388048362777857
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.38万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.59909866853019
    },
    {
        "question": " 47.3万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.452782941052824
    },
    {
        "question": " 573分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.53642812463333
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.6兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.745608025454349
    },
    {
        "question": " 6421億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.871110895744053
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.83億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.389597279272744
    },
    {
        "question": " 424秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8493506397941841
    },
    {
        "question": " 18.2秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.260365340475305
    },
    {
        "question": " 4178兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.122186199850228
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.76億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6384916516472106
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.37兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.366274146260212
    },
    {
        "question": " 712億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.074297123316058
    },
    {
        "question": " 6383msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.804998363743048
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.96京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.972945679698177
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.45兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.935408145101909
    },
    {
        "question": " 179京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.697657896724161
    },
    {
        "question": " 92.5億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1878019657742467
    },
    {
        "question": " 299兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.475140996165681
    },
    {
        "question": " 7690億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.88593167964877
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.24京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.012374982598772899
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.7京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.2313758683979774
    },
    {
        "question": " 460京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.106374915982702
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.1垓nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.543266110092901
    },
    {
        "question": " 7211兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.857982067427971
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.99億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 2.6005047505964884
    },
    {
        "question": " 61.5億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.788750997834654
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.49万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.1155293985891
    },
    {
        "question": " 365億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.000122447414984
    },
    {
        "question": " 65.3万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.973116444842109
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.97万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.3515729067700024
    },
    {
        "question": " 774億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.508482337163525
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.15億時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.837800006000906
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.87時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.8287051343513054
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.39兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.203363223735588
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.7万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8721975182780548
    },
    {
        "question": " 2803億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.669520924484704
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.72分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.013825047836002
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.2億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8431112270787111
    },
    {
        "question": " 87.8万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0068905408259066
    },
    {
        "question": " 86.9万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3827526900046836
    },
    {
        "question": " 376万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.797067245670633
    },
    {
        "question": " 28秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.446746291093899
    },
    {
        "question": " 342兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.034626189222351
    },
    {
        "question": " 2816兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.513163184947736
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.7兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.667135166470248
    },
    {
        "question": " 493兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.914738527833688
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.6億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.027100219534109
    },
    {
        "question": " 234msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 8.368966798704928
    },
    {
        "question": " 29.7垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.973872428505988
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.71兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.0505754947352517
    },
    {
        "question": " 81.6兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.355409450592175
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.35兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.143724505338785
    },
    {
        "question": " 214万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.3299510256262894
    },
    {
        "question": " 686億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.836100081440081
    },
    {
        "question": " 288usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 5.458815415917806
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.1垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.650236546055018
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.37垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.7036950711779255
    },
    {
        "question": " 81.1垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.352650146119261
    },
    {
        "question": " 2垓nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.523696350077364
    },
    {
        "question": " 1370億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.136668068352283
    },
    {
        "question": " 3181万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.502495565542944
    },
    {
        "question": " 1628nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 0.21157863588651016
    },
    {
        "question": " 503万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.139303872833895
    },
    {
        "question": " 1099万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.421087248212785
    },
    {
        "question": " 22.2日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.282248918505515
    },
    {
        "question": " 9906時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.05337421592365055
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.24万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.714361320013329
    },
    {
        "question": " 1033時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.7922260367156895
    },
    {
        "question": " 1729時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.794206536894466
    },
    {
        "question": " 317万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7801976381374642
    },
    {
        "question": " 39.5万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.438621494768011
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.8億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.477504441943856
    },
    {
        "question": " 842分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.703618208550476
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.83京秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.952593711908651
    },
    {
        "question": " 57.1万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8199511559268402
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.39兆秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.248999235061271
    },
    {
        "question": " 238億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.599128000440697
    },
    {
        "question": " 162秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.210381781779443
    },
    {
        "question": " 18.9京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.776984457018585
    },
    {
        "question": " 3083兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.5524123964305705
    },
    {
        "question": " 31.4億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9409684973255033
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.14兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.1829662566764
    },
    {
        "question": " 328万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.515687417104373
    },
    {
        "question": " 176万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.24660523458255
    },
    {
        "question": " 5365msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.72956065796355
    },
    {
        "question": " 1889京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.777418557214929
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.1兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2410552228349667
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.91兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.2151831464048564
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.8兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.114011291823014
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.37兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.135890924808153
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.18億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.339146492370707
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.67usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 3.4267234711567585
    },
    {
        "question": " 242垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.885113246070384
    },
    {
        "question": " 3281京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.579507724369553
    },
    {
        "question": " 1135京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.4988765567269136
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.87京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.909708209138737
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.31兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.5192175471506526
    },
    {
        "question": " 1376億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.138662884522395
    },
    {
        "question": " 41.3万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 2.6159533038036886
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.71万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.131959615071648
    },
    {
        "question": " 99.1年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.938383826607275
    },
    {
        "question": " 7400年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.589915256893466
    },
    {
        "question": " 1473日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6059213539367014
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.7日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6289781745803245
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.81万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.415096799616169
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.39万日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.909008165915482
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.22日は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.901059479940335
    },
    {
        "question": " 32.2億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.564895862976568
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.93億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.9044038669341115
    },
    {
        "question": " 1993時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.077714539408262
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.8時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.002762888713893
    },
    {
        "question": " 156万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.47172236189471195
    },
    {
        "question": " 1370万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.9782469730085
    },
    {
        "question": " 69.5分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.06386942996029821
    },
    {
        "question": " 51.3分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.488130841208623
    },
    {
        "question": " 46兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.164022651542547
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.2億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.214266881150576
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.9億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.58758834895723
    },
    {
        "question": " 1084億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.256877052761586
    },
    {
        "question": " 126秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.101172590301363
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.1京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.506995358691523
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.38億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5918555067001996
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.84億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1283465730625872
    },
    {
        "question": " 52万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9380632403920519
    },
    {
        "question": " 41.6万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6193290872159825
    },
    {
        "question": " 234msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 5.3684815068331995
    },
    {
        "question": " 32.5msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 7.512547431573528
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.68垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.255580792389451
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.64兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2777371429677475
    },
    {
        "question": " 25.8京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.85561584644608
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.99京usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.519955662029213
    },
    {
        "question": " 7503億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.875252201333979
    },
    {
        "question": " 1131usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 0.053519561319825826
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.08usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 3.7840835308682963
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.23e+04垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.360315431620824
    },
    {
        "question": " 185兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.3302658517297574
    },
    {
        "question": " 1229京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.53314423848165
    },
    {
        "question": " 616京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.01142580215382
    },
    {
        "question": " 164億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2140007632804928
    },
    {
        "question": " 637万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 0.803806648794475
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.49兆nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.395362306135764
    },
    {
        "question": " 1423万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.715577353617023
    },
    {
        "question": " 817年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.854987643347895
    },
    {
        "question": " 20.3万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.745412281682895
    },
    {
        "question": " 140万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.525628847606659
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.61日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.575777597612185
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.29日は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.048545830697263
    },
    {
        "question": " 233万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.424114411185716
    },
    {
        "question": " 1517億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.800859068409945
    },
    {
        "question": " 122時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.8653250012940066
    },
    {
        "question": " 1441時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.714923136367132
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.96億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.180459879814621
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.47万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0099668357143587
    },
    {
        "question": " 19.5億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.512452160897403
    },
    {
        "question": " 25.6分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.1866570305037953
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.93分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.063853820022511
    },
    {
        "question": " 5233億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.219955922526653
    },
    {
        "question": " 33.2万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5847687547023783
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.59億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.190893276253471
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.1億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.40197174995727
    },
    {
        "question": " 510億msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.2085845462665048
    },
    {
        "question": " 1106兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.107402738491385
    },
    {
        "question": " 3億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.920349278623309
    },
    {
        "question": " 116億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.285055906323769
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.31万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.117935353309758
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.89msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 3.4604091181884646
    },
    {
        "question": " 521兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2177381430796497
    },
    {
        "question": " 6092億usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8482516449374167
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.38京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.085524401919573
    },
    {
        "question": " 56.5兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.973828045283941
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.4兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.532077305946342
    },
    {
        "question": " 25.4万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 2.405033785637807
    },
    {
        "question": " 829京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4197598616184335
    },
    {
        "question": " 106垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.089537381603431
    },
    {
        "question": " 209垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.764179052570878
    },
    {
        "question": " 303兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.7030414591410032
    },
    {
        "question": " 7816兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.8929892070776155
    },
    {
        "question": " 20.2兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.305291497525951
    },
    {
        "question": " 1815nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 0.25889472315420603
    },
    {
        "question": " 1924年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.226801662925495
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.55年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.127114821780246
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.84億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.702318453408188
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.68億日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.946344192640575
    },
    {
        "question": " 41.4万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.77580528927342
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.74兆時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.885835730995183
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.47億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.269934372212989
    },
    {
        "question": " 49.3時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.4709848541800783
    },
    {
        "question": " 1531億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.464287474721941
    },
    {
        "question": " 4456億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.490607065853533
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.49億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.394965403638344
    },
    {
        "question": " 735分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.644387802004291
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.8分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.541776359102326
    },
    {
        "question": " 2675兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.928444902058851
    },
    {
        "question": " 100兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.064627109919865
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.2万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0664926842254396
    },
    {
        "question": " 162万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.4312672758347595
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.1秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.234201216820761
    },
    {
        "question": " 105兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.5221359851072656
    },
    {
        "question": " 248兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.458596584440771
    },
    {
        "question": " 160億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.6479590615521698
    },
    {
        "question": " 188万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4969517040555425
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.93億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.899467484797497
    },
    {
        "question": " 65.5msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.816252462326683
    },
    {
        "question": " 258兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9131481521240281
    },
    {
        "question": " 32.1京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.570448505270377
    },
    {
        "question": " 683億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2780582326135292
    },
    {
        "question": " 4824兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.905248506243074
    },
    {
        "question": " 8941兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.951368338935012
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.77万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.5764812607767775
    },
    {
        "question": " 516京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.214197661534137
    },
    {
        "question": " 486兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7500236230828594
    },
    {
        "question": " 1485京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.615296131037706
    },
    {
        "question": " 159兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.4226848515924404
    },
    {
        "question": " 5089億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.706598587804694
    },
    {
        "question": " 6818兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.833647928100959
    },
    {
        "question": " 91.4万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 2.9607332119518626
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.2万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.743115477963787
    },
    {
        "question": " 35.3年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.4907283689281865
    },
    {
        "question": " 84.3年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.646284364802436
    },
    {
        "question": " 7818億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.33080253587199
    },
    {
        "question": " 107日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.186924679868479
    },
    {
        "question": " 273億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.494135604215893
    },
    {
        "question": " 9737時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6082314205513657
    },
    {
        "question": " 294万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.246674211290557
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.88万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.015718918744241
    },
    {
        "question": " 8707万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2192169385427896
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.57億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.252038726285237
    },
    {
        "question": " 259万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.634813397319947
    },
    {
        "question": " 29.9万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.254505983974595
    },
    {
        "question": " 1901億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.78028404017288
    },
    {
        "question": " 1099万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1044557951082856
    },
    {
        "question": " 18.2兆秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.702630956063084
    },
    {
        "question": " 20億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.522660175276225
    },
    {
        "question": " 84.4万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.926301559815876
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.47京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.89416852082408
    },
    {
        "question": " 271兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.495952598857016
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.56京msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.851655731020951
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.06兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.830638712371757
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.62億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.7499388948733445
    },
    {
        "question": " 248万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.394449493227636
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.85京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.0872171181102104
    },
    {
        "question": " 324京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.5746695981954195
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.05京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.928491450184868
    },
    {
        "question": " 829億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.140473427101742
    },
    {
        "question": " 245億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.38829282060793
    },
    {
        "question": " 1490億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.173291845559426
    },
    {
        "question": " 626万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.796831768254732
    },
    {
        "question": " 12垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.578721993567729
    },
    {
        "question": " 903京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.019143488590774
    },
    {
        "question": " 21.4京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.774418007924534
    },
    {
        "question": " 1739兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.462030556739702
    },
    {
        "question": " 619億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.791390845679558
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.75億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 2.43951316518804
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.54万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 1.5494144573224966
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.1年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.5661645884266546
    },
    {
        "question": " 828年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.638692769300455
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.09億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.2882791020678885
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.57万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.933469308721511
    },
    {
        "question": " 70.4万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.006004216397073
    },
    {
        "question": " 65.4日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.752321470949379
    },
    {
        "question": " 79万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.954891984672098
    },
    {
        "question": " 31.8時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.12258905704887968
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.4時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.835457954074693
    },
    {
        "question": " 2332万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6469945764696137
    },
    {
        "question": " 133億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.9649010793708825
    },
    {
        "question": " 433億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.8583751197413
    },
    {
        "question": " 28.9万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.238538116124227
    },
    {
        "question": " 18.2分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.038043043241518
    },
    {
        "question": " 3459兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.040205882159459
    },
    {
        "question": " 6172万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.853934617041448
    },
    {
        "question": " 7979万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.3456457504647865
    },
    {
        "question": " 896億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.174381317071703
    },
    {
        "question": " 70.5万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.848309520231354
    },
    {
        "question": " 7718億msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.388709097213402
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.97京msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.358008668021231
    },
    {
        "question": " 680兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.276459407879788
    },
    {
        "question": " 9427万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.196238563732101
    },
    {
        "question": " 21.2億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.326117616794702
    },
    {
        "question": " 44.9万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.652400942283897
    },
    {
        "question": " 7245京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.361244704206274
    },
    {
        "question": " 227兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.4197041949410343
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.39京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.973290407100845
    },
    {
        "question": " 83.3億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1425724612872967
    },
    {
        "question": " 33.3兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.522783106581047
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.74万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.4374590956835742
    },
    {
        "question": " 185usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 5.267608413283837
    },
    {
        "question": " 42.6京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1305522504490884
    },
    {
        "question": " 2023垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.369538313170965
    },
    {
        "question": " 589兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.213899515812198
    },
    {
        "question": " 4241億nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8492682235529092
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.78兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.4446166937036082
    },
    {
        "question": " 3571兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.552844754014679
    },
    {
        "question": " 703億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.8469586261789335
    },
    {
        "question": " 45.2万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.217711799798245
    },
    {
        "question": " 1536年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.90697433358277
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.03万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7449461041208192
    },
    {
        "question": " 1597万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.583377137632812
    },
    {
        "question": " 4568日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.59618657875558
    },
    {
        "question": " 88.8日は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.884890778657624
    },
    {
        "question": " 5360万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.7866675073923517
    },
    {
        "question": " 58.6億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.387981330822951
    },
    {
        "question": " 176時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.800940565304696
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.84億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.963914044494823
    },
    {
        "question": " 2627億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.261139461458283
    },
    {
        "question": " 1409万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.370862427418418
    },
    {
        "question": " 183兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.762560459942044
    },
    {
        "question": " 41.5万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6819789711873991
    },
    {
        "question": " 27.3万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.880389944924149
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.1万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.3703914996904825
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.61兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9186341140001217
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.95兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.353605821228939
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.95億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.285838670179693
    },
    {
        "question": " 813億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.131930031460416
    },
    {
        "question": " 845億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.927010162734147
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.53万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.185054869828048
    },
    {
        "question": " 393兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0950557371144565
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.73兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3004555076944968
    },
    {
        "question": " 159兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.644284961704514
    },
    {
        "question": " 27.3億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6580666903322994
    },
    {
        "question": " 916兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.961713059845424
    },
    {
        "question": " 6208usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 0.7929574621007507
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.79万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 7.578189894023996
    },
    {
        "question": " 814垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.41199099388274
    },
    {
        "question": " 239垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.441285249405947
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.76京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.885078334729508
    },
    {
        "question": " 428兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.853220853950745
    },
    {
        "question": " 334京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.524380828820759
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.01億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 2.0058197922858056
    },
    {
        "question": " 1325万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.122065143746342
    },
    {
        "question": " 697年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.785507935416608
    },
    {
        "question": " 139年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.862442501239567
    },
    {
        "question": " 203億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.7457170445444445
    },
    {
        "question": " 386万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.967172358845921
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.09日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.8646979956625307
    },
    {
        "question": " 4219億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.6826972401191975
    },
    {
        "question": " 27.1億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.053059460830239
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.86万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.36509101205295
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.33時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.6785969650777983
    },
    {
        "question": " 677万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.109631531338905
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.23億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.757175508854075
    },
    {
        "question": " 4925分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9142969013177313
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.5億分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.955492543048443
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.05分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.799977749909974
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.58分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.439468415094964
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.01京秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.279888844592175
    },
    {
        "question": " 166万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2826712836996113
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.73億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.68229603626451
    },
    {
        "question": " 187億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.49295598246411
    },
    {
        "question": " 220秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.341978860676856
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.96垓msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.792710894394759
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.57京msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.616119506038784
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.22兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.35879852573151
    },
    {
        "question": " 4785万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9017224851538237
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.72兆msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.235945836625149
    },
    {
        "question": " 5703京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.257310669016464
    },
    {
        "question": " 4149京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.681458042833706
    },
    {
        "question": " 62億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.23590116640178405
    },
    {
        "question": " 3143億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.71923714447733
    },
    {
        "question": " 350億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.54411560656494
    },
    {
        "question": " 9690億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.986319302541961
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.36京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.14103020236342356
    },
    {
        "question": " 8355兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9854576325947315
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.51兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.4218577961505676
    },
    {
        "question": " 407京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.831378200524217
    },
    {
        "question": " 458京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.661324880406688
    },
    {
        "question": " 1362兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.134064927896794
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.69億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 5.671195646650529
    },
    {
        "question": " 628年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.360045584628685
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.28年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.416840064419764
    },
    {
        "question": " 39万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.02911194057802
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.7万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.6020052515478
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.22日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.243564092389708
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.29日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.296976601354823
    },
    {
        "question": " 17日は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.167409290883615
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.3兆時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.24295029858082
    },
    {
        "question": " 37.4万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.1926808752612725
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.67万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.3425970094086415
    },
    {
        "question": " 57.9万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.319292636223754
    },
    {
        "question": " 64.8兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.090753281241096
    },
    {
        "question": " 74.7億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.714822915703987
    },
    {
        "question": " 772億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.10920618932171
    },
    {
        "question": " 330分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.296737222832091
    },
    {
        "question": " 293分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.2447950457681145
    },
    {
        "question": " 3303万秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.02014328571050661
    },
    {
        "question": " 103万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0765355207232141
    },
    {
        "question": " 19.2兆秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.727608433290976
    },
    {
        "question": " 97.4秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.2104611770218623
    },
    {
        "question": " 1622秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.210154604850185
    },
    {
        "question": " 209京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.820393646929096
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.13億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.11805017374436066
    },
    {
        "question": " 98.9億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.439006513255729
    },
    {
        "question": " 775万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1112908771966223
    },
    {
        "question": " 997億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.998608666626454
    },
    {
        "question": " 552msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 5.742217187856511
    },
    {
        "question": " 1343msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.127998966974992
    },
    {
        "question": " 328兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0169336476686608
    },
    {
        "question": " 2160京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.398016500648936
    },
    {
        "question": " 681億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.276945968321359
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.71億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.161699474055452
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.84兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.264996949101715
    },
    {
        "question": " 2968usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 0.4724996865992892
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.261e+04垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.222234335119031
    },
    {
        "question": " 2437垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.450401111747045
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.6京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.859222094710244
    },
    {
        "question": " 1440億nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.38019968866264797
    },
    {
        "question": " 58.1億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7644760596698985
    },
    {
        "question": " 234億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.368413968338397
    },
    {
        "question": " 4893nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 0.6895768630046684
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.34年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.0857089821711514
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.59年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.356218957505408
    },
    {
        "question": " 40.1年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.323757590290131
    },
    {
        "question": " 35.6年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.050634922505264
    },
    {
        "question": " 24.8万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8327427566609256
    },
    {
        "question": " 36.4日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.498158245965849
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.44日は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.862899059751282
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.15万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.11833727617867162
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.83万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.385536426696407
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.83万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.230633580594779
    },
    {
        "question": " 182万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.81646260842825
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.3兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.641705021051349
    },
    {
        "question": " 3839億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.425814583102927
    },
    {
        "question": " 230万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.582699539181617
    },
    {
        "question": " 27.9分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.224390722642385
    },
    {
        "question": " 444兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.148577215571914
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.5億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.192259117043223
    },
    {
        "question": " 628億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.241429078812508
    },
    {
        "question": " 949万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.199303032532986
    },
    {
        "question": " 384万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.584864416703194
    },
    {
        "question": " 5007億msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.200738052355138
    },
    {
        "question": " 8354億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.985401209994557
    },
    {
        "question": " 5006兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.143191042361178
    },
    {
        "question": " 82.4億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.137824189271592
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.5万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1753489364147673
    },
    {
        "question": " 215msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 5.331518099896914
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.8msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 7.070365061744522
    },
    {
        "question": " 5434兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2363468110479365
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.8京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.169281244680871
    },
    {
        "question": " 5164兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.156686813642667
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.23億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.3113193646140433
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.45兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.809404627898742
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.02億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.700528657161743
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.1万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 7.040397034226284
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.723e+05垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.389001412055318
    },
    {
        "question": " 1835京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.327149602533437
    },
    {
        "question": " 1043兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.461932724158485
    },
    {
        "question": " 40.7京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.8315361195092725
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.22兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.8584064635940685
    },
    {
        "question": " 22億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.342164058328038
    },
    {
        "question": " 55.1万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 2.7409021131679667
    },
    {
        "question": " 963万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.545823988934195
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.06万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.968142902833295
    },
    {
        "question": " 228年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.078381693896686
    },
    {
        "question": " 780億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.329549898752935
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.56万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.572407671617788
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.86日は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.20544833851238
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.8兆時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.254897676586443
    },
    {
        "question": " 47.2億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.293340052720021
    },
    {
        "question": " 26.4万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.199521465655522
    },
    {
        "question": " 428時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.1873258671545175
    },
    {
        "question": " 7169万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1348060473136945
    },
    {
        "question": " 141万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9908514607830936
    },
    {
        "question": " 33.2億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.743307178322937
    },
    {
        "question": " 2707分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.210664354821243
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.8京秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.492409528835624
    },
    {
        "question": " 1046万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.0830085707972312
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.54兆秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.375315064314979
    },
    {
        "question": " 6870秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.058798038876554
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.63秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.750178440911217
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.51兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9010589312767279
    },
    {
        "question": " 23.5兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.433961227209208
    },
    {
        "question": " 2630万msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8636473183976168
    },
    {
        "question": " 22.6万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5750880725017804
    },
    {
        "question": " 66.7万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8239505039682467
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.08垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.285137949718516
    },
    {
        "question": " 2099億usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.38556261687585525
    },
    {
        "question": " 29.6兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.9155693029930405
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.42京usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.756438976637824
    },
    {
        "question": " 5761兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.76048783671004
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.79億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.831740350544027
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.901e+04垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.272135631527224
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.55垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.253500884996618
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.6兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5440827328357012
    },
    {
        "question": " 47.2京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.8956235332269165
    },
    {
        "question": " 312京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.49361568711213
    },
    {
        "question": " 339億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.529879759215457
    },
    {
        "question": " 1118万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.048288933663045
    },
    {
        "question": " 377年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.138789249439197
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.4兆日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.969050786904464
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.39日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5218054263137704
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.28万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.125936294157187
    },
    {
        "question": " 1209日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.01892238591077
    },
    {
        "question": " 146億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.221651580745922
    },
    {
        "question": " 2276時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.976957572885023
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.42時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.707223940287875
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.9億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.3178924624910766
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.61万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0484130722308072
    },
    {
        "question": " 5029万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.923347035220623
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.69分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.20823232579869
    },
    {
        "question": " 179兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.754427708932605
    },
    {
        "question": " 5460億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.800659324896101
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.95万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.040661686683757
    },
    {
        "question": " 46.3億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.887539076739916
    },
    {
        "question": " 22.1兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8463704443063884
    },
    {
        "question": " 2555兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.470875054569074
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.81京msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.891817302404153
    },
    {
        "question": " 7797万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.113781146033504
    },
    {
        "question": " 7160msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8548852341388424
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.3msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 7.123009556069376
    },
    {
        "question": " 290兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9631286230526237
    },
    {
        "question": " 4344億usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7014171140314618
    },
    {
        "question": " 118兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.516507573572448
    },
    {
        "question": " 6578万usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.0399753313891027
    },
    {
        "question": " 2395億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.379260730042251
    },
    {
        "question": " 29.7万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 2.472492712786668
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.88usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 3.274574520062896
    },
    {
        "question": " 448京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.152198924809259
    },
    {
        "question": " 28.7京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.5207307726434345
    },
    {
        "question": " 22.2兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7891497398201075
    },
    {
        "question": " 7318兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.0862317286093965
    },
    {
        "question": " 20.7京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.31509697881281
    },
    {
        "question": " 71.9億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.8564829204678643
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.46億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 5.649477561734507
    },
    {
        "question": " 1545年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.751121841822578
    },
    {
        "question": " 52.3年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.661336545120401
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.61億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.995123504168745
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.52日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.562824454418238
    },
    {
        "question": " 20.7万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.473535194071186
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.1万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.263087512273554
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.78億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.61022002989089
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.98時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.030976905217802
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.62時間は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.765434757171349
    },
    {
        "question": " 71.1億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.131274001632196
    },
    {
        "question": " 29.3億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.309082936148524
    },
    {
        "question": " 4989分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9198702798484768
    },
    {
        "question": " 62.3兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.295570889124925
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.56万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.043798436627623394
    },
    {
        "question": " 142万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5955304939675647
    },
    {
        "question": " 394秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8170522646566458
    },
    {
        "question": " 103万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.010753418579522
    },
    {
        "question": " 3447京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.03868192942997
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.44京msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.989818417313266
    },
    {
        "question": " 3497万msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.987440191327299
    },
    {
        "question": " 23.4兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.590170299503072
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.6億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.880932378863148
    },
    {
        "question": " 260msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 5.4152317448179685
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.3msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 7.238817844060401
    },
    {
        "question": " 2379垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.877500600756626
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.18垓usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.401376114087817
    },
    {
        "question": " 206兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.758337490105014
    },
    {
        "question": " 277億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.66432377370125
    },
    {
        "question": " 393兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.594048413462733
    },
    {
        "question": " 89.3億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.950843866853031
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.2垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.550765116527749
    },
    {
        "question": " 153垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.2468873600589
    },
    {
        "question": " 2546兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8495933801225304
    },
    {
        "question": " 82.5京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.13850564727746
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.7億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.10406825529880592
    },
    {
        "question": " 123兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.088397920490829
    },
    {
        "question": " 604億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.781037199169301
    },
    {
        "question": " 2428年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.947628272841348
    },
    {
        "question": " 247年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.334441208446045
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.63万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9971979284418762
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.2万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.096044093945415
    },
    {
        "question": " 62.8日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.734685255908048
    },
    {
        "question": " 128万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.165490041993187
    },
    {
        "question": " 1313億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.7380553806826
    },
    {
        "question": " 666万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.601713298680497
    },
    {
        "question": " 78.4時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.450581958623072
    },
    {
        "question": " 288兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.739155101397868
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.4万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9365146436367986
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.96億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.819365965128333
    },
    {
        "question": " 21.5分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.111251077704405
    },
    {
        "question": " 117分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.847307688721132
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.88兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.089558929059638
    },
    {
        "question": " 58.1億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.827990937204248
    },
    {
        "question": " 82.1億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.358115354658038
    },
    {
        "question": " 540万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.954575641756707
    },
    {
        "question": " 3805秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.580364124804379
    },
    {
        "question": " 5142兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.212351918698314
    },
    {
        "question": " 18.7京msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.334958650847664
    },
    {
        "question": " 576億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.2044083350440165
    },
    {
        "question": " 1558万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.414338897283036
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.07万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.316064791162781
    },
    {
        "question": " 392京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.094611516960538
    },
    {
        "question": " 5740京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.822437793900566
    },
    {
        "question": " 59.9兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.220831132105873
    },
    {
        "question": " 33.8兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.750868283639753
    },
    {
        "question": " 5247万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7199069722892224
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.68億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.754116680132192
    },
    {
        "question": " 40垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.103147077228583
    },
    {
        "question": " 3284兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.57987182205238
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.9兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.03473448676744706
    },
    {
        "question": " 45.9京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.8839708317127535
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.68京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.5654091079166985
    },
    {
        "question": " 3041億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.482992260728508
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.09兆nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.490569901461274
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.52年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.3766120409776668
    },
    {
        "question": " 31.8万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.445408627629607
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.58万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.370995574647272
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.03日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.171404866100269
    },
    {
        "question": " 1114万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.1045415093726114
    },
    {
        "question": " 1886億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.895434526068009
    },
    {
        "question": " 2636時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.199083425989701
    },
    {
        "question": " 291兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.743101474496944
    },
    {
        "question": " 8234分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7572523626734695
    },
    {
        "question": " 858万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.155553989832282
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.83万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.543850068768188
    },
    {
        "question": " 3870兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.088892212178939
    },
    {
        "question": " 193兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.348053995441228
    },
    {
        "question": " 7198秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.30088171615165193
    },
    {
        "question": " 112億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.270796177521166
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.8万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.07158613099937
    },
    {
        "question": " 112京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.548925601366276
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.83兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.055914155855589
    },
    {
        "question": " 196兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.736765940388743
    },
    {
        "question": " 21.1兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.546993732403207
    },
    {
        "question": " 373億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.571643535750535
    },
    {
        "question": " 123msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 5.0911189835879975
    },
    {
        "question": " 2896垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.96304672283259
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.76垓usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.893308998281263
    },
    {
        "question": " 805京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.349651583978899
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.02京usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.82659381475223
    },
    {
        "question": " 147万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.16711313545736517
    },
    {
        "question": " 2819億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.450143557506893
    },
    {
        "question": " 759usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 5.880144437587526
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.285e+04垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.859993098433277
    },
    {
        "question": " 7279京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.925597148255574
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.03兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.14538064103224002
    },
    {
        "question": " 33.5京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.747506334327015
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.99兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.4763512149262112
    },
    {
        "question": " 6699億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.826019752298654
    },
    {
        "question": " 114億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.057679196712217
    },
    {
        "question": " 67.5万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.391759561157754
    },
    {
        "question": " 8546年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.652434706919422
    },
    {
        "question": " 1495日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6121965468362112
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.55日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9304838195602148
    },
    {
        "question": " 8458日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.085609876630917
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.56日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.814847329123566
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.99億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.011238488654971
    },
    {
        "question": " 150億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.79731845012772
    },
    {
        "question": " 7819時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.671295045638293
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.6兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.37904706277148
    },
    {
        "question": " 9243分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.807484079842441
    },
    {
        "question": " 1440万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.380362244813412
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.61万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.59830451514344
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.65億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7189217822628935
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.99兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.363105291270843
    },
    {
        "question": " 683億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.2783094335174265
    },
    {
        "question": " 314億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.71887253809792
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.96万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.471426114743647
    },
    {
        "question": " 1275兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.606749469938947
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.39兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.442585003663319
    },
    {
        "question": " 2033億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.751822832734357
    },
    {
        "question": " 2958億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.692799690761506
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.44兆msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.159413242897816
    },
    {
        "question": " 39.6京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.09925273227304
    },
    {
        "question": " 3563京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.615259628763312
    },
    {
        "question": " 44.8兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.094676870712566
    },
    {
        "question": " 663億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.0436709493177636
    },
    {
        "question": " 1075兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.031301251070914
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.67兆usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.221543050059516
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.1万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 7.958937300233807
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.47垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.428887431122995
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.64垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.2785396251591985
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.1垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.651510559565034
    },
    {
        "question": " 923兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.186848707603598
    },
    {
        "question": " 40.3億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6052335798747666
    },
    {
        "question": " 717億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.855232319037124
    },
    {
        "question": " 3262億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.513452671771406
    },
    {
        "question": " 1325万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.684486717204962
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.15億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.399089878965059
    },
    {
        "question": " 2306日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.7430809883983365
    },
    {
        "question": " 118万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.230279951577785
    },
    {
        "question": " 20日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.238565618165143
    },
    {
        "question": " 1545万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.2464095725987385
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.63億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.831894989568083
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.4時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9653628054708605
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.1時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.5966944579500817
    },
    {
        "question": " 59.3時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.329386723692279
    },
    {
        "question": " 136万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.4133598464897803
    },
    {
        "question": " 120億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.92059678075886
    },
    {
        "question": " 354分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7711387887192778
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.12京秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.99593955220532
    },
    {
        "question": " 671万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8902403571048565
    },
    {
        "question": " 4505億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.097403760601882
    },
    {
        "question": " 27.4億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.659605264374818
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.54兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6884481929691786
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.88億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.33682461958745136
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.58兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.997682783977462
    },
    {
        "question": " 107兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.24929840420331
    },
    {
        "question": " 422億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.6247996649156855
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.93msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 3.9970285855639243
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.27垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.6037034851292145
    },
    {
        "question": " 1垓usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.0638057646888
    },
    {
        "question": " 3480京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.985298313101296
    },
    {
        "question": " 6559億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.038681673628368
    },
    {
        "question": " 604万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7807570574449585
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.33万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.7271277582239852
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.4万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 8.214988497133218
    },
    {
        "question": " 341垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.0336955610744845
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.78垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.053990265434088
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.1垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.677746863632716
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.21垓nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.305305419468283
    },
    {
        "question": " 30.7兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.486954262775436
    },
    {
        "question": " 776億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.8898245404657015
    },
    {
        "question": " 3720億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.570521300297244
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.55万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.751582333274177
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.35万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5680052972638736
    },
    {
        "question": " 614日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.1685233625406575
    },
    {
        "question": " 69.2万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.998236164248166
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.78日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.615813655373226
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.9日は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.399368797930624
    },
    {
        "question": " 2兆時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.358235538278006
    },
    {
        "question": " 628億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.417709811588837
    },
    {
        "question": " 121万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.859683251245038
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.77万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.8050387626419475
    },
    {
        "question": " 66.5万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.10198185564476714
    },
    {
        "question": " 1853億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.109542245679137
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.13万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.717497688907089
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.1分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8210974859580198
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.33兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.626162492872298
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.34兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.9290798715484145
    },
    {
        "question": " 322万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9509838142327016
    },
    {
        "question": " 7751万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.111184186482772
    },
    {
        "question": " 21.6万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.334646460781304
    },
    {
        "question": " 12京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.578791940362867
    },
    {
        "question": " 757兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.942338729725947
    },
    {
        "question": " 33.2兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.964895637142833
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.24兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.849373934407962
    },
    {
        "question": " 28.2億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.450321450410992
    },
    {
        "question": " 2856京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.956946020556892
    },
    {
        "question": " 102兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.072578692759673
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.94兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.2851494782613155
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.32京usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.587851851777407
    },
    {
        "question": " 528億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.722954528713377
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.16億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.33453796751211
    },
    {
        "question": " 18.1万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 8.257612341118197
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.748e+04垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.743616074444711
    },
    {
        "question": " 37.7垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.639322472465891
    },
    {
        "question": " 37兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0120545978257023
    },
    {
        "question": " 73.8京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.089799963610717
    },
    {
        "question": " 150京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.175867745977099
    },
    {
        "question": " 20.8億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.3175056315803433
    },
    {
        "question": " 355万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 3.550407446973546
    },
    {
        "question": " 18.6年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.211516162635111
    },
    {
        "question": " 8977日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3908314454077364
    },
    {
        "question": " 203日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.687980488394369
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.81万日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.194075084382712
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.7日は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.965351418089039
    },
    {
        "question": " 4478万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.708581911711991
    },
    {
        "question": " 5303時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3443620623577655
    },
    {
        "question": " 5472時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.516330549166736
    },
    {
        "question": " 2247兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.630989639842843
    },
    {
        "question": " 9999分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8415856499398633
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.57億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.774500773121107
    },
    {
        "question": " 112万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.826314840229718
    },
    {
        "question": " 462分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.44250669436703
    },
    {
        "question": " 19.3分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.064608628527065
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.96京秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.793168709437905
    },
    {
        "question": " 1500億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.23952709512741
    },
    {
        "question": " 1854万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.71174502818286
    },
    {
        "question": " 5012億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.921881962047653
    },
    {
        "question": " 87.3万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.941115248167876
    },
    {
        "question": " 8463秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.927524852621945
    },
    {
        "question": " 1857京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.770071398154473
    },
    {
        "question": " 1596億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.2664266927265926
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.72億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.200876300233788
    },
    {
        "question": " 3303万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.740754954957091
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.07億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.783447945196932
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.8京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.756021184038242
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.04垓usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.766315312088638
    },
    {
        "question": " 178億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.693282271781166
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.14億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.27756927839355794
    },
    {
        "question": " 141兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.149449256596803
    },
    {
        "question": " 2483万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.394908521613071
    },
    {
        "question": " 38.9usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 4.589478351509355
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.3京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7126290304254967
    },
    {
        "question": " 8364京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.9859338094911685
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.07京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.148922084777389
    },
    {
        "question": " 890億nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.17138927876339083
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.15兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.617534508200965
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.11億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 2.0434029736034387
    },
    {
        "question": " 132億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.121487324512485
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.08万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.173264631641716
    },
    {
        "question": " 19.9年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.798563714442125
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.13万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4899224475676298
    },
    {
        "question": " 2459日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.770996919437574
    },
    {
        "question": " 8127日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.846403617148134
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.44日は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.093668096724693
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.2億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.1434655740026205
    },
    {
        "question": " 172時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8545418814134476
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.4万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.159000943060033
    },
    {
        "question": " 72.4万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.416231718358338
    },
    {
        "question": " 152時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.739237794394198
    },
    {
        "question": " 19億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.557252791990402
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.59兆分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.043012932074735
    },
    {
        "question": " 88.5万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.168658695646478
    },
    {
        "question": " 4650万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.445560852632767
    },
    {
        "question": " 6700分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.604215934829902
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.19京秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.293185482390498
    },
    {
        "question": " 57.5兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.823136180552897
    },
    {
        "question": " 4469億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.093923077530311
    },
    {
        "question": " 4209秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8460137932894594
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.02京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.105877876060477
    },
    {
        "question": " 74.7兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.936707663702889
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.44京msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.83067648927006
    },
    {
        "question": " 1381万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3619175166641537
    },
    {
        "question": " 1883万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.274802009828699
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.6msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 3.66294589211402
    },
    {
        "question": " 48.4兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.1858068849868666
    },
    {
        "question": " 226兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.417199248575643
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.8京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.694802433513475
    },
    {
        "question": " 4334兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.858742322774686
    },
    {
        "question": " 61.5億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.788743718191354
    },
    {
        "question": " 388億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.588919194217444
    },
    {
        "question": " 16万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 8.20346497886348
    },
    {
        "question": " 51.9京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2164490795012661
    },
    {
        "question": " 1076京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.09514729177303
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.47京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.83715379597128
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.33垓nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.344266541761007
    },
    {
        "question": " 23.5京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.371277167289946
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.3億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.122713733601671
    },
    {
        "question": " 2529nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 0.40288067953977436
    },
    {
        "question": " 751日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.3131302509938727
    },
    {
        "question": " 4947万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.074542261785
    },
    {
        "question": " 787日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.054280891236595
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.41万日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.669309769748317
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.1億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.063682057988
    },
    {
        "question": " 582億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.384592311094178
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.68時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.38117135214045
    },
    {
        "question": " 3810兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.860279068635354
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.33万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9651502857375183
    },
    {
        "question": " 9454分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1974596608155794
    },
    {
        "question": " 45.2万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.4333588291196495
    },
    {
        "question": " 403分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.383575357599767
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.1京秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.505927981197031
    },
    {
        "question": " 540兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.796289096442168
    },
    {
        "question": " 4422秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.08935457222070675
    },
    {
        "question": " 777万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.112505265351517
    },
    {
        "question": " 171万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.232038431073766
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.6秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.414521254143914
    },
    {
        "question": " 52.4京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.220686438778882
    },
    {
        "question": " 36兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.619810281427068
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.04京msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.461781088022025
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.43億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.376102759409224
    },
    {
        "question": " 126億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.099354178390097
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.86msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 3.686878848908235
    },
    {
        "question": " 1212垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.584800135530143
    },
    {
        "question": " 2138億usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.39342711313965717
    },
    {
        "question": " 910億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4029213443997324
    },
    {
        "question": " 1744億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.4632730377428764
    },
    {
        "question": " 53兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.724259557726819
    },
    {
        "question": " 42.1億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.624469051497014
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.96万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 7.4708641624978025
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.873e+06垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.959519094625911
    },
    {
        "question": " 161兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.27023200083449495
    },
    {
        "question": " 28兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8904039019451182
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.14垓nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.279804262984506
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.39兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.6421834193855576
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.62億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 2.8817748969230026
    },
    {
        "question": " 28.1億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.448366078785716
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.22年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9084878882018117
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.31万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.058673384349667
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.8万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6642666845792453
    },
    {
        "question": " 427日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.010542134124738
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.74万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.730670002252037
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.3日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.298927314146328
    },
    {
        "question": " 3718万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.6277906412694048
    },
    {
        "question": " 340億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.150940947068792
    },
    {
        "question": " 1617時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.986761214629325
    },
    {
        "question": " 3647万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8412302946900527
    },
    {
        "question": " 34億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.373369476685918
    },
    {
        "question": " 1820万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.48193510806099
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.6分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9417458155760148
    },
    {
        "question": " 551分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.519623480825737
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.91兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.782669075274159
    },
    {
        "question": " 286億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.519991519927306
    },
    {
        "question": " 205万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7546218485170435
    },
    {
        "question": " 524億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.941537036680694
    },
    {
        "question": " 30.3京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.9825673932285355
    },
    {
        "question": " 346億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6029576243899455
    },
    {
        "question": " 6414万msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2508462596307368
    },
    {
        "question": " 758万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1014537852587143
    },
    {
        "question": " 176億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.244644379715358
    },
    {
        "question": " 24.5万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.38867436217896
    },
    {
        "question": " 24.9msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 7.395818338331573
    },
    {
        "question": " 2616兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9188867434609214
    },
    {
        "question": " 70.7兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9131444325433176
    },
    {
        "question": " 676兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.273457446975394
    },
    {
        "question": " 2595億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.636012568279101
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.33億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8012040116240833
    },
    {
        "question": " 20.9万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 2.320149337135339
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.07垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.350378179040001
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.96垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.96450924679482
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.55垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.260133063571178
    },
    {
        "question": " 1825億nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.48308510256384385
    },
    {
        "question": " 34.7億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.540149997586068
    },
    {
        "question": " 31.4億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.4968541032217337
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.74万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 1.888842138714082
    },
    {
        "question": " 226年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.917069053927791
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.01年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.505167961340916
    },
    {
        "question": " 1622日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6476238268972445
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.68日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8084654470493289
    },
    {
        "question": " 133日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.061029893400367
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.27日は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.451492922945384
    },
    {
        "question": " 6722万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.8850220225386445
    },
    {
        "question": " 157万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.816431658405474
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.58時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9760233975102826
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.06億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.593573399036211
    },
    {
        "question": " 21.6万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1754100811722132
    },
    {
        "question": " 6914万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.0615995711103405
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.42万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.929072949075177
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.22分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.286071839536502
    },
    {
        "question": " 550兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.24162783963381
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.21兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.407936431680509
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.2万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5213027756245525
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.41万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3714027674188953
    },
    {
        "question": " 154万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.186523371092633
    },
    {
        "question": " 132秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.1211840015076
    },
    {
        "question": " 4023億msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1057949371595244
    },
    {
        "question": " 769兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.949687514550712
    },
    {
        "question": " 414兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.061086953401844
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.2億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.2309960284736
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.3万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.18364993768506
    },
    {
        "question": " 320兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.005781422201184
    },
    {
        "question": " 227京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.41986113583876
    },
    {
        "question": " 84.8億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.3719072520052935
    },
    {
        "question": " 217兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.558990325265811
    },
    {
        "question": " 7988億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.902424463347854
    },
    {
        "question": " 1407usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 0.14825624325563114
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.41垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.145264878871715
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.21垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.780158716120698
    },
    {
        "question": " 2558兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.851541316786792
    },
    {
        "question": " 997京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.220562882312324
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.92兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.950332102705485
    },
    {
        "question": " 1636億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.213846927585237
    },
    {
        "question": " 34.7億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.540460768855949
    },
    {
        "question": " 35.1年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.108073728839328
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.7万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.686881900820488
    },
    {
        "question": " 175万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.624464354697333
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.28日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.020193114311717
    },
    {
        "question": " 9099億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.01647454427459
    },
    {
        "question": " 154時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8066943175915553
    },
    {
        "question": " 65時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.590732291454164
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.5兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.375111787897591
    },
    {
        "question": " 1509万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.020396616690674
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.83億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.987442663605363
    },
    {
        "question": " 70分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.6230248350320107
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.74分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.21665288400101
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.03兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.512761415670331
    },
    {
        "question": " 290兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.52541575056418
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.5億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.841227934649154
    },
    {
        "question": " 808秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1289985552174264
    },
    {
        "question": " 1950京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.79127181269779
    },
    {
        "question": " 5985億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.8405667198497992
    },
    {
        "question": " 40.9兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.055577774965424
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.15億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.933557399911108
    },
    {
        "question": " 126万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.099901112313488
    },
    {
        "question": " 553msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 5.74303254295654
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.23垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.591534933671143
    },
    {
        "question": " 172京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.298690457034681
    },
    {
        "question": " 1147億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5031825055449932
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.75京usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.111093352584469
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.89兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.6895352281797384
    },
    {
        "question": " 87万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 2.9395782267893766
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.89usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 3.8379949252756997
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.83垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.395015814718603
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.26垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.163638134738187
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.69兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.43007301645404006
    },
    {
        "question": " 50.6兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9255872368700455
    },
    {
        "question": " 120兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.080252849022563
    },
    {
        "question": " 3122万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.4944454801810647
    },
    {
        "question": " 5944万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.774073003950511
    },
    {
        "question": " 855年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.494338676037095
    },
    {
        "question": " 1315日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5566880835185462
    },
    {
        "question": " 34日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9115851807279935
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.3万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.169363162547095
    },
    {
        "question": " 312万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5520752104817532
    },
    {
        "question": " 45.8時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.2809436547803157
    },
    {
        "question": " 714時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.63210725132366
    },
    {
        "question": " 30.9時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.04650537051171
    },
    {
        "question": " 4455兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.928218536996724
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.66億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.061086026575804
    },
    {
        "question": " 2018億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.526845465185856
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.18万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.690652627389914
    },
    {
        "question": " 4282分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.409754843184327
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.84分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.544419913941862
    },
    {
        "question": " 1982億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.7982925416827094
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.16兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.397266882671037
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.72億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.878630456222453
    },
    {
        "question": " 263万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.642278964777501
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.4万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.057841229909801
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.7秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.222349535751852
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.68兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9301272972826367
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.08億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.0986293728664378
    },
    {
        "question": " 828兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.361744122304767
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.52億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.097790205118176
    },
    {
        "question": " 35.3万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.54772924907806
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.06万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.02607004831907
    },
    {
        "question": " 3123兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9957016331319544
    },
    {
        "question": " 181兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.3215627381596855
    },
    {
        "question": " 5342兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.171437774513188
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.12兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.547688384466209
    },
    {
        "question": " 6936兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.841123627648821
    },
    {
        "question": " 877億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.942870066925263
    },
    {
        "question": " 3940usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.595509622448098
    },
    {
        "question": " 283垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.952980217628672
    },
    {
        "question": " 22.9垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.4242599468973
    },
    {
        "question": " 1431兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5991940439689474
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.14京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.2798965522732
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.95兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.5960841362349294
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.5兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.062148814909644
    },
    {
        "question": " 3787nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 0.5782480822710612
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.29年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9223755612694235
    },
    {
        "question": " 90.9年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.679052835066814
    },
    {
        "question": " 77.2万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.3254775568038952
    },
    {
        "question": " 827日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.297670395263877
    },
    {
        "question": " 425万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.787075350625894
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.03日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.244791737297812
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.37万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.1934914672470056
    },
    {
        "question": " 874億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.561186718933095
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.96時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.02769048872042
    },
    {
        "question": " 18.4億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.5450960004143797
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.32兆分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.761997120586685
    },
    {
        "question": " 5934億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.995232901731248
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.5分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5181722732448577
    },
    {
        "question": " 67.1億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3280038829234173
    },
    {
        "question": " 102兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.07248497257211
    },
    {
        "question": " 521億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.16037743403115
    },
    {
        "question": " 1881秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4963321411220365
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.6兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.635272551700262
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.03億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.37032446894062154
    },
    {
        "question": " 21.5兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.775974945217311
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.6兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.041441056363107
    },
    {
        "question": " 3434msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5358156078341381
    },
    {
        "question": " 102京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.509064965786203
    },
    {
        "question": " 9116億usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0232901016949814
    },
    {
        "question": " 2969億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9163341858513672
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.81京usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.802421283996924
    },
    {
        "question": " 10億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.0005839227946662
    },
    {
        "question": " 1517usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 0.18100834248223618
    },
    {
        "question": " 1163usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.065468885917744
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.266e+04垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.603563694793528
    },
    {
        "question": " 85.8垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.996986495125372
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.3京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.455935028727962
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.01兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.0004772567104903
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.4京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.531131271230418
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.9兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.462770091563856
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.21兆nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.344149814485531
    },
    {
        "question": " 89.6万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.514750515513386
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.9年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.713564139058073
    },
    {
        "question": " 3924億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.031396061167316
    },
    {
        "question": " 3149日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.878320869874892
    },
    {
        "question": " 3311日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.678345551638212
    },
    {
        "question": " 206万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3712720148393993
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.2億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.125562013251194
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.06時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8048759276549986
    },
    {
        "question": " 558時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.303220269709563
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.78兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.529105165179761
    },
    {
        "question": " 467億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.511289736882356
    },
    {
        "question": " 76.5万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.105745722634393
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.11万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.6872307931383626
    },
    {
        "question": " 30.3京秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.982501908521792
    },
    {
        "question": " 403億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.668441540771939
    },
    {
        "question": " 2773万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.8866690595855924
    },
    {
        "question": " 370億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.78995552601395
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.1万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.491526837644051
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.02垓msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.51052836635614
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.7京msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.631177819048983
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.47億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3170282759421887
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.53兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.407468395473464
    },
    {
        "question": " 1328万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.123228466646866
    },
    {
        "question": " 44万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.64320508004478
    },
    {
        "question": " 21.9京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.841575059634655
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.1兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.104334444388414
    },
    {
        "question": " 18.1兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.7006494876642195
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.8兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.328438064365034
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.11億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.0452798628902946
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.61兆usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.416441643650648
    },
    {
        "question": " 58.8万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 8.769541682274545
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.61e+05垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.164899041798549
    },
    {
        "question": " 2400垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.443786130053434
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.44垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.6021733126137025
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.93兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.0625889037836864
    },
    {
        "question": " 26.4兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.421768111512156
    },
    {
        "question": " 3075万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.4878206602144206
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.13万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 1.0521774673114215
    },
    {
        "question": " 765年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.446185093845579
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.4万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.00073817528318
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.97万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7329545355091647
    },
    {
        "question": " 140日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.527090890481066
    },
    {
        "question": " 9731日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.146526292532202
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.28日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.042847614672576
    },
    {
        "question": " 295億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.527792072545885
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.16億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.118955685264564
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.75時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.454993153582935
    },
    {
        "question": " 119万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.3539659984789323
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.05億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.449635016958059
    },
    {
        "question": " 115万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.28161030015829
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.62分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4427702291730826
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.38分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.917497517356774
    },
    {
        "question": " 100億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5029757425684007
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.59兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.264826182319959
    },
    {
        "question": " 15万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6211918914004164
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.1億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.268136120098026
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.6秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.20507701989998
    },
    {
        "question": " 322秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.508490381596227
    },
    {
        "question": " 3863億msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0881595329328975
    },
    {
        "question": " 46億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7265801347525767
    },
    {
        "question": " 2755兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.883818529735333
    },
    {
        "question": " 2097億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.543466318670413
    },
    {
        "question": " 56.2億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.749758658058132
    },
    {
        "question": " 37.8垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.07851831161024
    },
    {
        "question": " 563兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.8141218715178535
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.06京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.470598411783533
    },
    {
        "question": " 6441億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.030781777596356
    },
    {
        "question": " 841億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.9249857762100655
    },
    {
        "question": " 2998usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 0.47683089036934745
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.64usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 3.5609360556035172
    },
    {
        "question": " 9531京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.4803244976215675
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.76京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.006234090681784
    },
    {
        "question": " 16兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6475995222736086
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.4京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.380754716318378
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.47京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.167662582695047
    },
    {
        "question": " 49.1億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.6911686994738027
    },
    {
        "question": " 8345nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 0.9214113206576269
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.59万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.144161453064553
    },
    {
        "question": " 94.7年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.696910690520769
    },
    {
        "question": " 2166億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.773266784566399
    },
    {
        "question": " 6688日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.983623116019986
    },
    {
        "question": " 1425万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.211407939710335
    },
    {
        "question": " 585万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.387001439967692
    },
    {
        "question": " 2308時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.14135145520398
    },
    {
        "question": " 190時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.834255174466165
    },
    {
        "question": " 1873万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5519009703316111
    },
    {
        "question": " 3806億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.422068187846858
    },
    {
        "question": " 908分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1800460086635989
    },
    {
        "question": " 8191分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.691460436179799
    },
    {
        "question": " 357分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.33081126085481
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.01分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.080992021526525
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.1億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5478972255161105
    },
    {
        "question": " 146兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.227723135661472
    },
    {
        "question": " 8194万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.357175218656032
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.49億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.394037498189224
    },
    {
        "question": " 52万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.716065725769232
    },
    {
        "question": " 5048秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.70313689803284
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.51秒は何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.17974502355052
    },
    {
        "question": " 38.5京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.086536619806768
    },
    {
        "question": " 30京msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.540961120632334
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.12億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.353229808141296
    },
    {
        "question": " 7616万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.103575845955869
    },
    {
        "question": " 9791億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.990844718527375
    },
    {
        "question": " 93.3万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.970013645968917
    },
    {
        "question": " 706msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 8.849014020356712
    },
    {
        "question": " 704兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3490178207247894
    },
    {
        "question": " 1413兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.213627661706757
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.96兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.3445891700214103
    },
    {
        "question": " 9865億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.215955603239424
    },
    {
        "question": " 31.3兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.495572026386183
    },
    {
        "question": " 25.2億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.402053665313575
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.27usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 3.8617489299676935
    },
    {
        "question": " 9904京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.497005309794453
    },
    {
        "question": " 5121京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.772841620189245
    },
    {
        "question": " 70.2兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2903244294768335
    },
    {
        "question": " 30.5京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.7060389115092285
    },
    {
        "question": " 36.1兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.557268517547759
    },
    {
        "question": " 2512兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.40000598627936
    },
    {
        "question": " 9736万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.988400422634319
    },
    {
        "question": " 215年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.275595435953958
    },
    {
        "question": " 785年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.6155366952847
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.05万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4607257649442473
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.1億日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.70149001230875
    },
    {
        "question": " 49.2万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.850290092119184
    },
    {
        "question": " 6084日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.720679893816186
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.2億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.108448831019034
    },
    {
        "question": " 272時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0547432260304501
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.98時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7315215416730876
    },
    {
        "question": " 6937時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.39745694116422
    },
    {
        "question": " 33.7億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.807500867032547
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.37万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2158312498695378
    },
    {
        "question": " 2335万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.59005514292612
    },
    {
        "question": " 14分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9258069603241177
    },
    {
        "question": " 7121分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.63067199543747
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.08京秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.819646791767122
    },
    {
        "question": " 33万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5821014747795472
    },
    {
        "question": " 3138万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.9403913304978677
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.27万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.578222759218699
    },
    {
        "question": " 27.1秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.43376396621758
    },
    {
        "question": " 19.7秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.295504324112169
    },
    {
        "question": " 829兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.419760391410806
    },
    {
        "question": " 5574億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.809650069286008
    },
    {
        "question": " 1840万msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.708482506483592
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.58兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.42137257877882
    },
    {
        "question": " 1004万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.001681332790236
    },
    {
        "question": " 579万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.76250321862623
    },
    {
        "question": " 199兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.799892275994516
    },
    {
        "question": " 497兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.7595105847866863
    },
    {
        "question": " 604兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.2250867703533945
    },
    {
        "question": " 1378億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.360960649855854
    },
    {
        "question": " 1710兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.232993978295834
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.56億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.192280344714005
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.95垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.790322387290156
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.8垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.202199001969935
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.98兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.04376413079466124
    },
    {
        "question": " 9606億nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2043880480558722
    },
    {
        "question": " 537京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.729781588477548
    },
    {
        "question": " 795万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 0.9003364640019607
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.26兆nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.628915724922885
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.05万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.468344627158389
    },
    {
        "question": " 1180年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.79245779661215
    },
    {
        "question": " 691億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.277478516772623
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.31日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.105099725339157
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.45万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.54748279408195
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.65億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.480767132525772
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.17万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.333610996611689
    },
    {
        "question": " 3153時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.276865499887496
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.88時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.244801101671918
    },
    {
        "question": " 1155万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3419596011605828
    },
    {
        "question": " 228万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.20010857375841
    },
    {
        "question": " 876億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.164538520201365
    },
    {
        "question": " 18.2万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.0390972294438425
    },
    {
        "question": " 4713分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.451453553244278
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.4億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6470382967415422
    },
    {
        "question": " 14万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.2103477094036732
    },
    {
        "question": " 620万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.236339363537625
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.98億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.919455685696333
    },
    {
        "question": " 45.1万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.653873850066553
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.21秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.964323452364544
    },
    {
        "question": " 131兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.6172695209380645
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.09兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.553594353034288
    },
    {
        "question": " 94億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.4167329480909414
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.83億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.4852766729888174
    },
    {
        "question": " 2329億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.367139172483665
    },
    {
        "question": " 40.6msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.608984456385066
    },
    {
        "question": " 151msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 8.180207120431614
    },
    {
        "question": " 1805垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.757615260463018
    },
    {
        "question": " 6039兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.844491535614864
    },
    {
        "question": " 39.9京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.04496309869617
    },
    {
        "question": " 346兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.761515829672873
    },
    {
        "question": " 27.6億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.441438883753066
    },
    {
        "question": " 4064usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 0.6089122787481416
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.3万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 8.123387235664838
    },
    {
        "question": " 3039京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.983934493299447
    },
    {
        "question": " 3701京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.631849160687372
    },
    {
        "question": " 86.6垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.38106382880791
    },
    {
        "question": " 871億nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.16189193341480057
    },
    {
        "question": " 5238兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.719197284412662
    },
    {
        "question": " 21兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.321341931617031
    },
    {
        "question": " 110万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 3.040389438413378
    },
    {
        "question": " 2669年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.988705682945916
    },
    {
        "question": " 7万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.787361809721709
    },
    {
        "question": " 174年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.961804186830507
    },
    {
        "question": " 9567万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.418465858061548
    },
    {
        "question": " 134日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.5060342031699667
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.85万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.425372613687998
    },
    {
        "question": " 6031日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.71689420095018
    },
    {
        "question": " 104億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.073886166378589
    },
    {
        "question": " 161億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.826129453838407
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.5時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.907722036483661
    },
    {
        "question": " 23.7時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.931528286580942
    },
    {
        "question": " 1562億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.473127147155167
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.34万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.568869918736715
    },
    {
        "question": " 941億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.19559859831986
    },
    {
        "question": " 25.2分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.1791122740992606
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.3兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.51497933348044
    },
    {
        "question": " 319兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.567462392688233
    },
    {
        "question": " 15億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.619478626207549
    },
    {
        "question": " 65.7億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.039653325326567
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.2秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.0782054636631906
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.82秒は何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.261240772214839
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.15垓msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.834362794868206
    },
    {
        "question": " 91.9兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.026972656298771
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.6億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8588190966690488
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.7兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.653569120613489
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.5億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.544235053060397
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.5京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.7441350710595334
    },
    {
        "question": " 1846京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.329799629222984
    },
    {
        "question": " 5576兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.190053951984808
    },
    {
        "question": " 19.6兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.513964098366374
    },
    {
        "question": " 814万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9108327167954344
    },
    {
        "question": " 23万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 2.362640874922237
    },
    {
        "question": " 67.9垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.333246999225794
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.07京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.091054268358156
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.22京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.237537462048766
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.62京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.886222698194523
    },
    {
        "question": " 1143兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.057994320590696
    },
    {
        "question": " 37億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.567625756555297
    },
    {
        "question": " 1072万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.030016623523038
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.9万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.705430096339221
    },
    {
        "question": " 6807年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.553597677612958
    },
    {
        "question": " 2029日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7449903875726005
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.67億日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.807023282696864
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.05億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.370182835662325
    },
    {
        "question": " 6277時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4175436472308265
    },
    {
        "question": " 8156時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.689619636003181
    },
    {
        "question": " 961時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.538843669640514
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.07兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.307949101998318
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.72億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.27615875545162
    },
    {
        "question": " 188億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.49587266489102
    },
    {
        "question": " 11万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.818805719209924
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.31兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.021178379857584
    },
    {
        "question": " 87兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.003022933219095
    },
    {
        "question": " 5118万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.15278203150661
    },
    {
        "question": " 2308万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.58516350465711
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.24秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.3502636119424856
    },
    {
        "question": " 56.5秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.751715177266893
    },
    {
        "question": " 8631億msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.437238358090539
    },
    {
        "question": " 224億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4139611653203543
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.62億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1086412559635415
    },
    {
        "question": " 18.2兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.482144240514769
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.4億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.158662525350257
    },
    {
        "question": " 48.2万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.683388031144295
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.88msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.769387877958257
    },
    {
        "question": " 91.1兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.4607636360206635
    },
    {
        "question": " 404兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.670270943962394
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.21京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.236445301594196
    },
    {
        "question": " 143億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3785606520945644
    },
    {
        "question": " 33.2億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.5212820833815837
    },
    {
        "question": " 890万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.9494485773360912
    },
    {
        "question": " 43.9垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.143892768556054
    },
    {
        "question": " 71.6垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.918338146144438
    },
    {
        "question": " 179兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.69598587821997
    },
    {
        "question": " 17兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4522536514615934
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.2京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.622736102857254
    },
    {
        "question": " 134万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 0.12658728888202297
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.98万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 1.2976936614460521
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.27万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.3594462739705016
    },
    {
        "question": " 182万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.698934807567311
    },
    {
        "question": " 3554万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.930868431076481
    },
    {
        "question": " 311日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.651099170971091
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.77万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0005602126704771
    },
    {
        "question": " 4356時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2588650796535314
    },
    {
        "question": " 1799万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.033099310460335
    },
    {
        "question": " 38.8時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.145299001620934
    },
    {
        "question": " 541時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.28944402528444
    },
    {
        "question": " 1541億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.4672690080265784
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.64兆分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.663629372216572
    },
    {
        "question": " 18.9億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.497533851029315
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.78万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.027682836700764
    },
    {
        "question": " 211分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.103402723165924
    },
    {
        "question": " 45.5億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1595954857717956
    },
    {
        "question": " 35.3万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6114555486985429
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.31億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.363136340621405
    },
    {
        "question": " 180秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.4767493187954486
    },
    {
        "question": " 3751秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.574166756385057
    },
    {
        "question": " 2647秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.422705562546195
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.6秒は何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.81964350008282
    },
    {
        "question": " 53.1兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.2263063648939583
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.61兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.271549981152768
    },
    {
        "question": " 1956万msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7351335260726721
    },
    {
        "question": " 67.7億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.052641133960946
    },
    {
        "question": " 65.9億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.81860055936962
    },
    {
        "question": " 31.5垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.999190922860112
    },
    {
        "question": " 5944兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.837600421440394
    },
    {
        "question": " 281兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.89222859524988
    },
    {
        "question": " 174兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.462301203953028
    },
    {
        "question": " 2072兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.316379175861947
    },
    {
        "question": " 1559億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.192968302302159
    },
    {
        "question": " 6136usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.787861691020007
    },
    {
        "question": " 310京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9930647696932946
    },
    {
        "question": " 42.2垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.688719188115186
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.8垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.584953389187543
    },
    {
        "question": " 6322兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.0226722112717965
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.79兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.251827999195341
    },
    {
        "question": " 5203億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.716250274414547
    },
    {
        "question": " 802億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.903942125550284
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.79万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.388452039606872
    },
    {
        "question": " 29.6万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.908439790067302
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.86億日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.65052255622283
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.4日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.372006611747027
    },
    {
        "question": " 30億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.535010152509404
    },
    {
        "question": " 43.6万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.259546758616591
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.29万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.696686691438382
    },
    {
        "question": " 1032億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.293197814652956
    },
    {
        "question": " 9607億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.824258027969272
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.62万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9713757268296437
    },
    {
        "question": " 32.4分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.288211751744412
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.69分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.006207665441353
    },
    {
        "question": " 16億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7058790838002236
    },
    {
        "question": " 535万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7915476834510213
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.57万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6385817671901095
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.19万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2961818339127493
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.13兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.211236463954621
    },
    {
        "question": " 9658兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.048372083138242
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.35億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.08254940672314
    },
    {
        "question": " 954万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2016030376930473
    },
    {
        "question": " 94.1億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.973485507757112
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.61msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 3.7487535200276003
    },
    {
        "question": " 452兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1567014311734147
    },
    {
        "question": " 220京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.405763949403331
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.62京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.861764219368171
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.47億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.38849449818548987
    },
    {
        "question": " 318兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.502817912823941
    },
    {
        "question": " 5783usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 0.7621241914320365
    },
    {
        "question": " 633万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.801125655455849
    },
    {
        "question": " 18.4京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7649735850289763
    },
    {
        "question": " 134京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.189943505452347
    },
    {
        "question": " 2452兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.833192878616797
    },
    {
        "question": " 48.2兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9046037712151582
    },
    {
        "question": " 79.1億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8982767922081358
    },
    {
        "question": " 7415万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.8701126913746358
    },
    {
        "question": " 1695nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 0.22919629408487574
    },
    {
        "question": " 814万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.47313342645538
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.68万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.508100444467871
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.11年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.044684100616189
    },
    {
        "question": " 1652日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.655699691127728
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.85億日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.6477629599575
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.54日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.9022095871624973
    },
    {
        "question": " 74日は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.805949337965595
    },
    {
        "question": " 59.8兆時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.834179459883227
    },
    {
        "question": " 203万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.927613127874093
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.2万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.691900028130854
    },
    {
        "question": " 22.3万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.904787299816196
    },
    {
        "question": " 290時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.019050141691727
    },
    {
        "question": " 964万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2633060594124679
    },
    {
        "question": " 2696万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.272384672873409
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.3億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.434913588012111
    },
    {
        "question": " 4221分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.403527140664983
    },
    {
        "question": " 86.5分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.715414108759754
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.5兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.898438928346733
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.9万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.10220025719042014
    },
    {
        "question": " 239億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.821821838495844
    },
    {
        "question": " 6411秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.028806304041014
    },
    {
        "question": " 86.3万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.936125680220318
    },
    {
        "question": " 8062億msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4076285918082088
    },
    {
        "question": " 44.6京msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.713307146891575
    },
    {
        "question": " 66.4億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.2655529724645502
    },
    {
        "question": " 283兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.673667549209723
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.53億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.930892440448168
    },
    {
        "question": " 88.8msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.948652040810631
    },
    {
        "question": " 583垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.267217634610615
    },
    {
        "question": " 988億usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.05811383964162253
    },
    {
        "question": " 4455億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.0925789867128044
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.32億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.34390037041860944
    },
    {
        "question": " 3036兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.482241302569264
    },
    {
        "question": " 2277億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.35735064989645
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.63垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.484781272200786
    },
    {
        "question": " 28.6京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.520099319159357
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.2京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.6799454736001955
    },
    {
        "question": " 3068億nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7086849159734732
    },
    {
        "question": " 9041兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.956205895813735
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.86兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.895501244496868
    },
    {
        "question": " 3944nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 0.59589867926236
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.34万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.483388717441776
    },
    {
        "question": " 38.5年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.5279583430902255
    },
    {
        "question": " 5276万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.159989785112233
    },
    {
        "question": " 105日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.400043545206115
    },
    {
        "question": " 47.8日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.615789332251399
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.49億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.454198476631667
    },
    {
        "question": " 1987万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.918076705344426
    },
    {
        "question": " 1689万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.005656709716403
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.39時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.697950710415172
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.1億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.427415838750375
    },
    {
        "question": " 5146億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.5530878927296
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.41万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6033299772501084
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.15分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.567129881788013
    },
    {
        "question": " 2522兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.90292607140057
    },
    {
        "question": " 80.8億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.970682053459096
    },
    {
        "question": " 44.2万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.089261118718139
    },
    {
        "question": " 21.4万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.552589392529807
    },
    {
        "question": " 1248秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.096081309240436
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.52京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.682149277320696
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.01京msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.06613858651486
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.5兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.605877398503361
    },
    {
        "question": " 25.7万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6324098010208645
    },
    {
        "question": " 1303億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.114961839494738
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.09垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.20780506767011
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.91京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.7546655960675865
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.8京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.4349391648986
    },
    {
        "question": " 18.9億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4973727387764035
    },
    {
        "question": " 54.9兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.739857978355924
    },
    {
        "question": " 23.8億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.377418247421847
    },
    {
        "question": " 4697usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.6718441998419
    },
    {
        "question": " 1502垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.677908315383997
    },
    {
        "question": " 106垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.08806559325846
    },
    {
        "question": " 199兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7432860241335468
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.81垓nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.986340820578059
    },
    {
        "question": " 80京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.903079184317802
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.06兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.7825216596951545
    },
    {
        "question": " 1681万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.2256880343846905
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.07年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.792148741227954
    },
    {
        "question": " 436年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.360582696050566
    },
    {
        "question": " 2768日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8798425870072402
    },
    {
        "question": " 366万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.722187149054307
    },
    {
        "question": " 49.7日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.6324290560605
    },
    {
        "question": " 9435万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.03224972478915
    },
    {
        "question": " 133万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.744660705240468
    },
    {
        "question": " 886時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.7254045784474314
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.98時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.853817792683914
    },
    {
        "question": " 556万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0243474268026531
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.32万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5678313622414308
    },
    {
        "question": " 544分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9571911953974443
    },
    {
        "question": " 2670万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.204673271892599
    },
    {
        "question": " 513分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.488372286405836
    },
    {
        "question": " 33.2億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.021738003834328
    },
    {
        "question": " 1055億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.086672102385478
    },
    {
        "question": " 256億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.852118443790073
    },
    {
        "question": " 223万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.56986538889852
    },
    {
        "question": " 60.6秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.782774328663631
    },
    {
        "question": " 6661京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.324706098872053
    },
    {
        "question": " 39.8兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.6628501858577565
    },
    {
        "question": " 2776億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.8870907105442445
    },
    {
        "question": " 1195億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.299038559437628
    },
    {
        "question": " 232億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.364608279881223
    },
    {
        "question": " 7290京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.363933924953309
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.51垓usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.939045859430966
    },
    {
        "question": " 44.5億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.0921973650022545
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.26兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.576408374793689
    },
    {
        "question": " 3656億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.562992893472866
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.68億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.427934184633333
    },
    {
        "question": " 145万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.162438804121937
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.12垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.8273084131860413
    },
    {
        "question": " 2792垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.509417416487075
    },
    {
        "question": " 1569兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6392711110752307
    },
    {
        "question": " 689億nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.06027213719863256
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.79兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.445870968960768
    },
    {
        "question": " 2516兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.400743270762108
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.27兆nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.355284395398472
    },
    {
        "question": " 138年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.701915032135102
    },
    {
        "question": " 126年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.0433027878181385
    },
    {
        "question": " 279年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.165994311447824
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.61万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1013221512497404
    },
    {
        "question": " 23.8日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7561800164601524
    },
    {
        "question": " 34.4日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.694626722828206
    },
    {
        "question": " 785日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.8313276911975915
    },
    {
        "question": " 28億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.504114967110063
    },
    {
        "question": " 406時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2279887572772175
    },
    {
        "question": " 26.8時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.2063151650904107
    },
    {
        "question": " 43.6時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.195624252630575
    },
    {
        "question": " 2214億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.624471463076311
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.38億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.981389299775282
    },
    {
        "question": " 395万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.818506945416521
    },
    {
        "question": " 6457万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.58819860049208
    },
    {
        "question": " 1093億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.539748546728946
    },
    {
        "question": " 453兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.720004766019764
    },
    {
        "question": " 18.3億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.706689883508318
    },
    {
        "question": " 1967秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.515744998400067
    },
    {
        "question": " 517秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.713668218715274
    },
    {
        "question": " 363京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.06110046422693
    },
    {
        "question": " 40.4京msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.669808286694838
    },
    {
        "question": " 3703億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.012266411688686
    },
    {
        "question": " 423億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.8486414678437395
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.35兆msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.370295851477458
    },
    {
        "question": " 45.1京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.154977764189194
    },
    {
        "question": " 180兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.3188371276694504
    },
    {
        "question": " 591京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.215357591333
    },
    {
        "question": " 399兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.823261733235949
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.3兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.237317134199698
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.1万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 2.046135732160159
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.63usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 3.5602778253465384
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.13京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.11671761808036751
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.2京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.215433409156704
    },
    {
        "question": " 18.1兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.700221397866102
    },
    {
        "question": " 746兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.094432150502295
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.77兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.76144291321038
    },
    {
        "question": " 42.7兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.63089587708735
    },
    {
        "question": " 52.3億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.718375096349707
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.9年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.15311561103214
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.64年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.381698381262392
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.57万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6333951162654692
    },
    {
        "question": " 82.5万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.29659933851906
    },
    {
        "question": " 236億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.430869673061822
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.64億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.286318628268211
    },
    {
        "question": " 4704時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.450631297786275
    },
    {
        "question": " 379兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.858169050751446
    },
    {
        "question": " 4172分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.46200138961264625
    },
    {
        "question": " 1509万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.400589730090799
    },
    {
        "question": " 1178分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.849345709058581
    },
    {
        "question": " 4557分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.436851422001864
    },
    {
        "question": " 94.6兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.477084822803381
    },
    {
        "question": " 42.4万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6907635838338788
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.04億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.458723521839602
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.16万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2861154477223633
    },
    {
        "question": " 311秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.492434503853193
    },
    {
        "question": " 5299京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.225389784430812
    },
    {
        "question": " 78.1億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9562504000280245
    },
    {
        "question": " 9990兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.44325802460538
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.2兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.403065689606633
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.08万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3173203460732763
    },
    {
        "question": " 168msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 5.2246882776360355
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.6msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 7.024776825794591
    },
    {
        "question": " 842兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4262898593688123
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.84京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.5173348874574755
    },
    {
        "question": " 46.6京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.111953956334236
    },
    {
        "question": " 137兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.35808919310946
    },
    {
        "question": " 1712万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2334995686450911
    },
    {
        "question": " 1億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.001138840687588
    },
    {
        "question": " 87.4万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 8.941286622701565
    },
    {
        "question": " 4611垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.164975822338714
    },
    {
        "question": " 34.7垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.604130381611868
    },
    {
        "question": " 222兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7905386598309003
    },
    {
        "question": " 74.3兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.0927671490190423
    },
    {
        "question": " 1094億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.0390314323677785
    },
    {
        "question": " 5438万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.7354495047020724
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.66万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 1.2213818904678575
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.1万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.945424813891957
    },
    {
        "question": " 18.6年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.9897025974311955
    },
    {
        "question": " 3155日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9367520352773362
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.88万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.218077957405237
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.4日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.1766006325637
    },
    {
        "question": " 30.3日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.417730990011493
    },
    {
        "question": " 257億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.4669333962396225
    },
    {
        "question": " 1030億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.632826673325114
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.97時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.072643146097064
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.96万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.554589380599007
    },
    {
        "question": " 665時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.378951739875841
    },
    {
        "question": " 350兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.82393974738604
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.4億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.082329568720214
    },
    {
        "question": " 77億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.10828555394363
    },
    {
        "question": " 1151万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.839369038992155
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.64分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.444547092509428
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.6京秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.528406423930234
    },
    {
        "question": " 41.3万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6795360731420386
    },
    {
        "question": " 4629万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.109217633046268
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.64万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.43596397806207
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.34秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.5236739686360483
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.32秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.365137454451565
    },
    {
        "question": " 48.4兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.1856378583476164
    },
    {
        "question": " 4146億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.68111945688975
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.98兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.04330684868898
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.37兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.359570123897217
    },
    {
        "question": " 909万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.958779688125719
    },
    {
        "question": " 43.3msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.6363908594704775
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.6京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.633925945139641
    },
    {
        "question": " 7857億usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9587647606293093
    },
    {
        "question": " 72.4億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.3033788547127725
    },
    {
        "question": " 1936億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.5087712243637337
    },
    {
        "question": " 18.8億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.2735287026577353
    },
    {
        "question": " 365万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.561862647289616
    },
    {
        "question": " 1485usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.171647936310842
    },
    {
        "question": " 79.2垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.399813769663253
    },
    {
        "question": " 592垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.835602218619867
    },
    {
        "question": " 2553京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.850791715938981
    },
    {
        "question": " 21京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.545072244818034
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.17京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.500975549371653
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.96兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.597471206216156
    },
    {
        "question": " 38.6万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 2.586964110516421
    },
    {
        "question": " 21.5年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.895316058928512
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.16万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.44225076843509
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.79万年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.972297601629238
    },
    {
        "question": " 131年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.616425469906003
    },
    {
        "question": " 43.1億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.071719705977064
    },
    {
        "question": " 48.4日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.065370239603973
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.18日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.949039471053981
    },
    {
        "question": " 8989時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.011224042596922335
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.45億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.158242296941708
    },
    {
        "question": " 4726時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.4526587525453944
    },
    {
        "question": " 7232時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.415548223107812
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.54時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.487981218993651
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.39億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9220294761469234
    },
    {
        "question": " 2593億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.255423251021556
    },
    {
        "question": " 426億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.851325792938459
    },
    {
        "question": " 181分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.035432344119917
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.6京秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.526174564797863
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.4兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.303688500823881
    },
    {
        "question": " 237億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.81753438548054
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.6万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.468014371162018
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.43秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.3851222424032255
    },
    {
        "question": " 3590兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.056315214529915
    },
    {
        "question": " 5334兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.7905327727311064
    },
    {
        "question": " 1910万msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.724742092262598
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.53兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.625108019365729
    },
    {
        "question": " 56.8億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.754457109666121
    },
    {
        "question": " 170万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.229582072035685
    },
    {
        "question": " 394京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.09672614455237
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.24兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1577409694708962
    },
    {
        "question": " 108京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.47816202891012
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.44兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.380502698891294
    },
    {
        "question": " 496兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.695476219586642
    },
    {
        "question": " 756万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.8785118479462097
    },
    {
        "question": " 2186usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.339749190049398
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.055e+05垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.524526363700508
    },
    {
        "question": " 327京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.577687693570899
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.78垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.888104415763012
    },
    {
        "question": " 7557京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.100205940894265
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.06兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.0237534750759067
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.37兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.867522834491696
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.63兆nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.419302140884122
    },
    {
        "question": " 73.4万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.427902993603709
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.42万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3631028704723778
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.1日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.2749445074072066
    },
    {
        "question": " 9578時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.038758312380602344
    },
    {
        "question": " 923時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.585086321526823
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.43万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.712681746215947
    },
    {
        "question": " 157兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.476380891509255
    },
    {
        "question": " 262億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.260346708640274
    },
    {
        "question": " 209分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5425867912004678
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.09億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.990649701945554
    },
    {
        "question": " 61.5兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.852147757794054
    },
    {
        "question": " 6769万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.274228337431226
    },
    {
        "question": " 8108万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.130762214724552
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.73秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.238792964769072
    },
    {
        "question": " 654億msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.31681604250360484
    },
    {
        "question": " 2458兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.454023308906819
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.4兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.659171946533887
    },
    {
        "question": " 42.1億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.846291135383859
    },
    {
        "question": " 7362万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.867018364418573
    },
    {
        "question": " 41.1msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.613414740587877
    },
    {
        "question": " 597垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.277021866503553
    },
    {
        "question": " 5551京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.80788300104382
    },
    {
        "question": " 2539兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.848302996382824
    },
    {
        "question": " 682兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.055813981743625
    },
    {
        "question": " 740億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.869373176551123
    },
    {
        "question": " 831億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.919793579767643
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.3万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 7.633391753119075
    },
    {
        "question": " 102京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5077119062885347
    },
    {
        "question": " 32京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.5688899162776133
    },
    {
        "question": " 30.5垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.9284286586163
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.38兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3602692810359485
    },
    {
        "question": " 750京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.875348767998997
    },
    {
        "question": " 826万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 0.9169048798072921
    },
    {
        "question": " 201億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.3038777406955555
    },
    {
        "question": " 434年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.579990688014759
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.53年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.683453657832557
    },
    {
        "question": " 25.9万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.850565763660512
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.33億日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.748033770697571
    },
    {
        "question": " 26.3万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.578029568039243
    },
    {
        "question": " 286億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.513288013885607
    },
    {
        "question": " 1177万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.690433720501472
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.11万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.17012795747768
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.1時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.5959551322317775
    },
    {
        "question": " 27兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.7109198310469385
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.24億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.933750184903518
    },
    {
        "question": " 421億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.845759651625881
    },
    {
        "question": " 2246分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.1294704482885
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.2分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.960051033792737
    },
    {
        "question": " 1142兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.559014422811496
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.09兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.675177589691052
    },
    {
        "question": " 3691万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.010900145808394
    },
    {
        "question": " 1490万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.39513969289572
    },
    {
        "question": " 33.2万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.521498450445442
    },
    {
        "question": " 390秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.59121480879757
    },
    {
        "question": " 2610京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.917771828274596
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.51兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.46322250333319
    },
    {
        "question": " 161兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.649533703868576
    },
    {
        "question": " 30.8万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7106024991936966
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.58億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.74689692818443
    },
    {
        "question": " 50.5万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.703419898426684
    },
    {
        "question": " 419京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.12325771611636
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.31京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.426648378373172
    },
    {
        "question": " 113京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.495372077965728
    },
    {
        "question": " 24.9兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.618909012697319
    },
    {
        "question": " 6495兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.812571887193643
    },
    {
        "question": " 135万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.129686432252763
    },
    {
        "question": " 858万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.933644598660518
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.3垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.625011798892974
    },
    {
        "question": " 6046兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8449901900206833
    },
    {
        "question": " 104兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4589844988866163
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.07兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5378966384275894
    },
    {
        "question": " 75.1億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8754050456960483
    },
    {
        "question": " 290億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.462766080033135
    },
    {
        "question": " 1301nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 0.11441095275860347
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.08年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.412227847230771
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.16年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.731872351019178
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.19万年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.794913918522457
    },
    {
        "question": " 38.2年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.08044176215144
    },
    {
        "question": " 4603万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.100748609077705
    },
    {
        "question": " 4084日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.991234206300973
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.6日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.184453283202538
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.43万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7041809863763016
    },
    {
        "question": " 1056万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.6433674974045935
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.24万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.405853783067769
    },
    {
        "question": " 1065兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.306716467241849
    },
    {
        "question": " 904億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.797983088382497
    },
    {
        "question": " 304万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.704495341804459
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.12万分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.827247037412912
    },
    {
        "question": " 3814兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.082568340565869
    },
    {
        "question": " 195万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3539904323508234
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.8兆秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.642590912982406
    },
    {
        "question": " 3539秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.770703674883738
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.56万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.194162712966254
    },
    {
        "question": " 9909秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.996029466365709
    },
    {
        "question": " 3252兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.013329105311673
    },
    {
        "question": " 46億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7258686300077875
    },
    {
        "question": " 1637億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.657720516226265
    },
    {
        "question": " 2562億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.6304031706897355
    },
    {
        "question": " 389万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.5903248746635374
    },
    {
        "question": " 73.3msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.864947812714595
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.5京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.662222861949742
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.7兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.0910783683378975
    },
    {
        "question": " 598兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.220714231106815
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.82兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.481766063287842
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.8億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.198591437519384
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.1兆usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.85121937401454
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.83usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 3.5831682928645767
    },
    {
        "question": " 513京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.210948485291735
    },
    {
        "question": " 2486京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.458962210052421
    },
    {
        "question": " 48.5京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.129657598161778
    },
    {
        "question": " 4932京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.91485821041028
    },
    {
        "question": " 32.1億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5064529392508887
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.23億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 2.0883086778750295
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.59兆nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.55508034640156
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.16万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.626554634691938
    },
    {
        "question": " 1527年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.904576552420648
    },
    {
        "question": " 175年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.742220108810521
    },
    {
        "question": " 1186万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.511749805143842
    },
    {
        "question": " 97.6日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.3695149671254097
    },
    {
        "question": " 3472日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.698882001754665
    },
    {
        "question": " 83.1日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.856153510550584
    },
    {
        "question": " 710万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.908759350889812
    },
    {
        "question": " 5928時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.392685347046384
    },
    {
        "question": " 5954万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.552978274128193
    },
    {
        "question": " 1570万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4753471150825948
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.17万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9081159723664267
    },
    {
        "question": " 140分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.36698592861177715
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.7万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.847786934036143
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.61万分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.19408286628224
    },
    {
        "question": " 8635兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.437469095065444
    },
    {
        "question": " 528億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.786072976589486
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.12兆秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.770978513671992
    },
    {
        "question": " 389億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.811467517778679
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.25万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.6287676292037645
    },
    {
        "question": " 136秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.13425517666014
    },
    {
        "question": " 151兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.6789324861626316
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.43兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.871591116443
    },
    {
        "question": " 598億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.2203967633760975
    },
    {
        "question": " 112億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.269509220317418
    },
    {
        "question": " 6199億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.792288598645552
    },
    {
        "question": " 232msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 5.365135769740514
    },
    {
        "question": " 884京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.447639070350428
    },
    {
        "question": " 63.6京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.8667287797133
    },
    {
        "question": " 635億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2467351222040568
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.84億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.674450630950123
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.25億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6285244210976844
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.82億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.682693952972714
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.94万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 7.2881463029210245
    },
    {
        "question": " 42.7京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1316211389354136
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.8京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.289474267719209
    },
    {
        "question": " 40.4兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0500026996692935
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.6京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.249126628837299
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.09兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.8504811390261273
    },
    {
        "question": " 59.4億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.7739904309271646
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.99万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 1.7777059927393224
    },
    {
        "question": " 7137年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.4158258282957465
    },
    {
        "question": " 91.4年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.459639843371663
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.62億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.995872506958464
    },
    {
        "question": " 422万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.005114331043625
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.4日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.3998201424246055
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.96日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.22801879852754
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.07万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6667264231066483
    },
    {
        "question": " 359時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.174460090546131
    },
    {
        "question": " 598時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.5549691540951684
    },
    {
        "question": " 24.3万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.942370205750878
    },
    {
        "question": " 4544億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.9367727063307125
    },
    {
        "question": " 64.6万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.651701579773694
    },
    {
        "question": " 2518分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6229464937106486
    },
    {
        "question": " 332万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.299491622678234
    },
    {
        "question": " 8561兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.433707226071451
    },
    {
        "question": " 156万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2553573355922665
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.4万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4166883930945973
    },
    {
        "question": " 108億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.254031331165226
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.74秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.828652162641339
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.06兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.350099375619913
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.54億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6129666849968229
    },
    {
        "question": " 286億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.9006874838777894
    },
    {
        "question": " 36兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.77774645634738
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.39兆msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.379248461372388
    },
    {
        "question": " 709万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.850493298746297
    },
    {
        "question": " 1479msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.169845385303073
    },
    {
        "question": " 54.9垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.241020212146054
    },
    {
        "question": " 52.8京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.78654406606166
    },
    {
        "question": " 3525兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.990902528037618
    },
    {
        "question": " 735億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.087962526195045
    },
    {
        "question": " 174兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.240813382450076
    },
    {
        "question": " 168億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.225865939019917
    },
    {
        "question": " 9827usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.992440911456798
    },
    {
        "question": " 341京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.033440805063109
    },
    {
        "question": " 2137兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3933481725149222
    },
    {
        "question": " 4907兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.1344934559233195
    },
    {
        "question": " 5316億nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9474691518016676
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.2億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.08669855268038429
    },
    {
        "question": " 780万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 0.8920462852447553
    },
    {
        "question": " 8813nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 0.9451418974812131
    },
    {
        "question": " 1680年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.787627997166172
    },
    {
        "question": " 94.8万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.919262628108003
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.19年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.061969328356773
    },
    {
        "question": " 614億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.22621452347729
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.83万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.643512676106481
    },
    {
        "question": " 40.3日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.763697683330024
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.18日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.43847184114721
    },
    {
        "question": " 20.3万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.364872369452692
    },
    {
        "question": " 277時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.061652022096452
    },
    {
        "question": " 864兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.215623711348075
    },
    {
        "question": " 18.4万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1062621440974407
    },
    {
        "question": " 354億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.771358838102586
    },
    {
        "question": " 2035万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.086634511624096
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.56分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.97036122686334
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.07億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.350372845128488
    },
    {
        "question": " 5506億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.804312510887018
    },
    {
        "question": " 27.1億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.876342139643242
    },
    {
        "question": " 41万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.8343817156903945
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.34秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.727576503737089
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.65秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.822673047232502
    },
    {
        "question": " 1299京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.61476911637779
    },
    {
        "question": " 497億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.759888268704853
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.25兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.164085363311945
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.82兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.804273683776609
    },
    {
        "question": " 1263msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.10133389163165751
    },
    {
        "question": " 469兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.172258264319348
    },
    {
        "question": " 9987京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.06291657589672
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.32京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.363715274203582
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.09兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.257361870449175
    },
    {
        "question": " 6045兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.78142397760575
    },
    {
        "question": " 51.7億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.713392414865595
    },
    {
        "question": " 28.5万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 8.454147097585922
    },
    {
        "question": " 598京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.277771945013698
    },
    {
        "question": " 339京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.593930726212868
    },
    {
        "question": " 6090兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.2283011253913707
    },
    {
        "question": " 2853京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.677109820455719
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.7兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.7557808141285
    },
    {
        "question": " 240万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 0.380494467428546
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.97億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 5.294429613842556
    },
    {
        "question": " 1092年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.980663062664046
    },
    {
        "question": " 7395年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.589615198486074
    },
    {
        "question": " 31.6年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.999028392207366
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.43億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.97282944808745
    },
    {
        "question": " 858万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.313860163093288
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.87兆時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.745172977459575
    },
    {
        "question": " 7225万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.478640918950712
    },
    {
        "question": " 823万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.693328661415723
    },
    {
        "question": " 69.2時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.396514410521853
    },
    {
        "question": " 2035万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.588011110900126
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.76兆分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.784049371804148
    },
    {
        "question": " 33.3万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.7438091517615932
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.92兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.451413935982162
    },
    {
        "question": " 73.4万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9289417472287398
    },
    {
        "question": " 6834万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.278354091457195
    },
    {
        "question": " 321秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7285223487811177
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.1万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.039418237750472
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.45秒は何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.736569520616802
    },
    {
        "question": " 40.8京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.111638549568201
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.44億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.4513408711054401
    },
    {
        "question": " 1273億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.548571161157232
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.86兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.908525917747155
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.22万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7939645466477083
    },
    {
        "question": " 4659京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.169507939199692
    },
    {
        "question": " 217京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.399064146143951
    },
    {
        "question": " 1471億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6113752196801556
    },
    {
        "question": " 48.8兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.90985049780639
    },
    {
        "question": " 155億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.191725599456902
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.22万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.0881240330435193
    },
    {
        "question": " 26.2usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 4.418208337550937
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.435e+06垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.657910755194166
    },
    {
        "question": " 6616垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.884112514219934
    },
    {
        "question": " 303垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.92528419228606
    },
    {
        "question": " 53京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.946361173960117
    },
    {
        "question": " 3129兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.49534540147859
    },
    {
        "question": " 7061兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.848877190896555
    },
    {
        "question": " 1784nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 0.2514078211603321
    },
    {
        "question": " 28.1年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.011594528479217
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.3年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.811724146568313
    },
    {
        "question": " 34.9億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.980390428140003
    },
    {
        "question": " 598万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.157231382917978
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.71万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.045629412891884
    },
    {
        "question": " 5966億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.833192665060808
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.14億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.117002036885111
    },
    {
        "question": " 1604万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.983380700719227
    },
    {
        "question": " 1404時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.703709803349999
    },
    {
        "question": " 5350億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.007723559404601
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.9万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9158613235527078
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.68億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.892490028084599
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.05億分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.799802649965507
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.26分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.878999697330705
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.5京秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.59639317578483
    },
    {
        "question": " 64.5兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.873188580444186
    },
    {
        "question": " 298億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.917516125899972
    },
    {
        "question": " 8837秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.168140970797375
    },
    {
        "question": " 7332秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.865213701981212
    },
    {
        "question": " 195京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.790360189926181
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.78兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.640744714935509
    },
    {
        "question": " 289億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.9046774847766033
    },
    {
        "question": " 19.4兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.509875549126562
    },
    {
        "question": " 78.8億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.896520090362578
    },
    {
        "question": " 34.6万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.538453901587403
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.8垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.670086897689176
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.52垓usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.718230105189788
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.3京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.362703015861514
    },
    {
        "question": " 1413兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.372066941501077
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.2兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.00741269813712
    },
    {
        "question": " 6552usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 0.8163692694181768
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.062e+05垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.98723289404273
    },
    {
        "question": " 6632垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.885119546105592
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.94京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.7310087070647957
    },
    {
        "question": " 3344億nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7460804497282258
    },
    {
        "question": " 814京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.910864585061347
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.19兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.076939851126227
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.94兆nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.77386298085469
    },
    {
        "question": " 192年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.845122113601073
    },
    {
        "question": " 3500年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.26476570405299
    },
    {
        "question": " 111万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.484628368075746
    },
    {
        "question": " 34.7日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.699280833577047
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.97日は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.632706063719173
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.56万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.46556338917012274
    },
    {
        "question": " 80.6億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.526003780310162
    },
    {
        "question": " 1893時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.833534950863619
    },
    {
        "question": " 1843時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.821719756575481
    },
    {
        "question": " 115兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.340481019274185
    },
    {
        "question": " 21.9億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.181795565045558
    },
    {
        "question": " 323億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.730541515327612
    },
    {
        "question": " 373分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.350362460170935
    },
    {
        "question": " 3160分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.277768800429238
    },
    {
        "question": " 151兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.67962537570859
    },
    {
        "question": " 171億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.295630998625837
    },
    {
        "question": " 26.4万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8654326629385876
    },
    {
        "question": " 5891秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9920330176036039
    },
    {
        "question": " 1069兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.530217202686796
    },
    {
        "question": " 1504兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.240822558258446
    },
    {
        "question": " 87兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.3834072668186055
    },
    {
        "question": " 695億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.064095189726126
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.7万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9395438484753025
    },
    {
        "question": " 6942msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.841502621926247
    },
    {
        "question": " 51.1msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 7.708408388960644
    },
    {
        "question": " 722京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.359832980007614
    },
    {
        "question": " 7546億usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9412389828596934
    },
    {
        "question": " 164京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.659660709605996
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.25京usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.318573539706016
    },
    {
        "question": " 119万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.07720643825525841
    },
    {
        "question": " 278億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.444772281067891
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.48usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 3.6511893022954824
    },
    {
        "question": " 2595垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.9153963558459015
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.7京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.2875099695722643
    },
    {
        "question": " 26垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.859447166201264
    },
    {
        "question": " 74.3兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.0930460653073055
    },
    {
        "question": " 18.1京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.257505454250694
    },
    {
        "question": " 28.7億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.458615412286692
    },
    {
        "question": " 312億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.493858913395343
    },
    {
        "question": " 6163年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.510459305783451
    },
    {
        "question": " 2699億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.868934396850017
    },
    {
        "question": " 219日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.721011565765261
    },
    {
        "question": " 262万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.577405937742318
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.68兆時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.283030540293673
    },
    {
        "question": " 3152万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.118410954586734
    },
    {
        "question": " 110時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.817790836696404
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.82兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.540193284494983
    },
    {
        "question": " 978万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.831994238628366
    },
    {
        "question": " 136万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.355797340692692
    },
    {
        "question": " 386億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.087676162730718
    },
    {
        "question": " 1828億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.325465207172407
    },
    {
        "question": " 361万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.0011789709143533
    },
    {
        "question": " 2537万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.626229357589878
    },
    {
        "question": " 5647秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.75185120746524
    },
    {
        "question": " 5670秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.753549717296778
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.81垓msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.758671537530763
    },
    {
        "question": " 4775兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.7424288288671805
    },
    {
        "question": " 122兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.531686245622086
    },
    {
        "question": " 161億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.427673859969556
    },
    {
        "question": " 61.7億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.790192029853127
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.95万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.470296353709771
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.74垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.7405892991941325
    },
    {
        "question": " 4745兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.739752926418359
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.34京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.570606166982834
    },
    {
        "question": " 1874兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.494587503645373
    },
    {
        "question": " 3728兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.57148015292884
    },
    {
        "question": " 339億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.530453444025174
    },
    {
        "question": " 247万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.392618230374795
    },
    {
        "question": " 8967京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.4538591997475407
    },
    {
        "question": " 35.8京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.6171401097750344
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.48兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.3177606654070675
    },
    {
        "question": " 105京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.243336010214878
    },
    {
        "question": " 928億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.967322123852916
    },
    {
        "question": " 4040兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.606409399834522
    },
    {
        "question": " 2360億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.372979014752321
    },
    {
        "question": " 18.2万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.822045761176113
    },
    {
        "question": " 451年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.596939094589476
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.29兆日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.54859415061917
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.63万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.0458808629254355
    },
    {
        "question": " 1198万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.135805696928222
    },
    {
        "question": " 1191時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6955310499656173
    },
    {
        "question": " 162万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.765923185417332
    },
    {
        "question": " 76.1時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.437729273234297
    },
    {
        "question": " 1741万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5200862304560125
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.78兆分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.732532417026516
    },
    {
        "question": " 2683分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6504927333160468
    },
    {
        "question": " 39.2分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.371110326631308
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.78分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.540135629357692
    },
    {
        "question": " 150兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.676862429405671
    },
    {
        "question": " 245億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.451971466460805
    },
    {
        "question": " 1345万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.572432207768841
    },
    {
        "question": " 266億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.64645224490112
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.12万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.7091689424509635
    },
    {
        "question": " 8911秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.94991889667826
    },
    {
        "question": " 3913兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.09364928248071
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.69億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.4938716081798422
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.94億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7313378297952253
    },
    {
        "question": " 21.7兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.558981186817048
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.9億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.252884845671876
    },
    {
        "question": " 95兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.47911138451698587
    },
    {
        "question": " 5871京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.832229679929647
    },
    {
        "question": " 76.1億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.3252834427616602
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.07兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.250546405571613
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.5億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.0211594438306957
    },
    {
        "question": " 63.3億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.801700293389471
    },
    {
        "question": " 85.7usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 4.932984413197966
    },
    {
        "question": " 6763垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.331340810849921
    },
    {
        "question": " 8688兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.0024362160650497
    },
    {
        "question": " 309垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.933777423846117
    },
    {
        "question": " 1099京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.262687664417314
    },
    {
        "question": " 38.2兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.582559427046256
    },
    {
        "question": " 10兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.999900450061527
    },
    {
        "question": " 588億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.769698423545989
    },
    {
        "question": " 402年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.166378347860744
    },
    {
        "question": " 193億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.723997559628036
    },
    {
        "question": " 263万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.799733955342937
    },
    {
        "question": " 490日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.848207864529993
    },
    {
        "question": " 69.2日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.77640228411433
    },
    {
        "question": " 170万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.287336249052542
    },
    {
        "question": " 2112時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.94448532547701
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.1万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.100939881508179
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.03万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.568011619000581
    },
    {
        "question": " 1305時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.672047886870969
    },
    {
        "question": " 26.8億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.7076431637812446
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.49兆分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.237381052754415
    },
    {
        "question": " 3801分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8016992853296188
    },
    {
        "question": " 7247分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.638328690828608
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.03分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.382947500488067
    },
    {
        "question": " 8716億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.441487890090638
    },
    {
        "question": " 127億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.166206582947454
    },
    {
        "question": " 1845億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.709740658684496
    },
    {
        "question": " 9969万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.2204945732938715
    },
    {
        "question": " 21.7秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.3369985098295665
    },
    {
        "question": " 81.3京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.4113229725597485
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.12京msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.55808286396156
    },
    {
        "question": " 2663億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.869079342438454
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.15兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.284062581747275
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.86億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.456889330671847
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.8垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.536548568428085
    },
    {
        "question": " 9944億usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0610656855751277
    },
    {
        "question": " 671億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2701404767896263
    },
    {
        "question": " 4337兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.859055308097319
    },
    {
        "question": " 400兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.601526152011212
    },
    {
        "question": " 701万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.8454201782147024
    },
    {
        "question": " 33.2垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.022950204997065
    },
    {
        "question": " 29.4京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.5315901981961684
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.86京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.130586388173584
    },
    {
        "question": " 1894京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.499343486915006
    },
    {
        "question": " 58.2京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.76471596577366
    },
    {
        "question": " 28.4兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.453339100544248
    },
    {
        "question": " 1426nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 0.15409354480675708
    },
    {
        "question": " 153年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.747509055236993
    },
    {
        "question": " 27.4年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.379617362330774
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.56年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.479218752662845
    },
    {
        "question": " 814億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.348285659832316
    },
    {
        "question": " 2221日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.726684803846507
    },
    {
        "question": " 307日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.645359896930742
    },
    {
        "question": " 101日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.940068825184916
    },
    {
        "question": " 910万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.0164591842195287
    },
    {
        "question": " 59.6億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.394688332038132
    },
    {
        "question": " 536万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.507000518002423
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.36万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.691148011719383
    },
    {
        "question": " 1024万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2898491265771728
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.5億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.0186583992715805
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.8万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.3299676303600165
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.54分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.655755713560717
    },
    {
        "question": " 7547万秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.3789954156076836
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.58億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.6171062677666734
    },
    {
        "question": " 67.1万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.270310211387485
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.59万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.040866267231074
    },
    {
        "question": " 2454秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.389856066392378
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.14兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9987529739060939
    },
    {
        "question": " 1989億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.362101350714747
    },
    {
        "question": " 3556万msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9946898957409067
    },
    {
        "question": " 37万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7894898867023659
    },
    {
        "question": " 8074万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.907075869910106
    },
    {
        "question": " 6415京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.308359768251719
    },
    {
        "question": " 478兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.743067644151891
    },
    {
        "question": " 90億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.39788327226383036
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.8兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.477890837531657
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.9兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.173170714992182
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.89億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.27611046383625
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.14垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.8310327505555652
    },
    {
        "question": " 1221兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1501988985059752
    },
    {
        "question": " 244兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8309603060133284
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.59兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.423313740913924
    },
    {
        "question": " 434京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.637012357448105
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.4億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.016031077454173
    },
    {
        "question": " 33.6万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 2.5260654676019056
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.11万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.4713722872060595
    },
    {
        "question": " 624年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.515654334070327
    },
    {
        "question": " 4220日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.062958798807434
    },
    {
        "question": " 274万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.8182671666029
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.63億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.477356451241388
    },
    {
        "question": " 271時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0526146091311406
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.2時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.931608824025844
    },
    {
        "question": " 30.8時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.045089891260918
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.18時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.627165353460244
    },
    {
        "question": " 801兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.18324541091118
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.62兆分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.259564065602902
    },
    {
        "question": " 639万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.027075543859433
    },
    {
        "question": " 102万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.786143847901811
    },
    {
        "question": " 53.1億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2265603803681486
    },
    {
        "question": " 1652億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.281546491426441
    },
    {
        "question": " 3010万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.922262575594276
    },
    {
        "question": " 443秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8684206400160566
    },
    {
        "question": " 470万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.672067253290638
    },
    {
        "question": " 4903兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.1916670813967505
    },
    {
        "question": " 7120兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.915976176696596
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.44兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.602955141512417
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.4億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.408807996985285
    },
    {
        "question": " 9918億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.9964230988978
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.1msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 3.4916567270386767
    },
    {
        "question": " 1561京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.694723019210581
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.31兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1818477025154084
    },
    {
        "question": " 1147兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.503399187716371
    },
    {
        "question": " 101億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.224592355910102
    },
    {
        "question": " 452億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.655202383085237
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.99兆usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.844318448811709
    },
    {
        "question": " 659万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.819020399940321
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.61垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.917920979864916
    },
    {
        "question": " 66.3京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.8848777945884527
    },
    {
        "question": " 43.7兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0846042519213506
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.84垓nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.674519247034832
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.81兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.258600347305606
    },
    {
        "question": " 302億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.479753497737699
    },
    {
        "question": " 3102万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.491574878335629
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.94年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.5595667987982194
    },
    {
        "question": " 368年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.286018649784356
    },
    {
        "question": " 157年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.69426657810841
    },
    {
        "question": " 1513億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.617486602736104
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.9万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.41686001241607
    },
    {
        "question": " 32.7万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.672855418471466
    },
    {
        "question": " 48.4日は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.62134885219372
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.5兆時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.23374123188431
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.4万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.999762379464789
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.8万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.670352814305394
    },
    {
        "question": " 162万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.766338307085608
    },
    {
        "question": " 743億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.150100330298569
    },
    {
        "question": " 1381万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.9819549146047595
    },
    {
        "question": " 229億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.582241939681523
    },
    {
        "question": " 223万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.127366212775776
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.09億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8221247576009483
    },
    {
        "question": " 457兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.723803028840253
    },
    {
        "question": " 2050万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.7554704072754044
    },
    {
        "question": " 88秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.16615674036462025
    },
    {
        "question": " 45.1万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.653721820953908
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.3秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.361783752983891
    },
    {
        "question": " 2292京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.861447092706854
    },
    {
        "question": " 161億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.26902010542965
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.7兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.199645444227868
    },
    {
        "question": " 18.2億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.481076859227191
    },
    {
        "question": " 1644億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.216012640166475
    },
    {
        "question": " 9218msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.964628874840618
    },
    {
        "question": " 2291msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.359967430552626
    },
    {
        "question": " 1207垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.582927223212895
    },
    {
        "question": " 1606京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.26912337827697
    },
    {
        "question": " 242京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.827463657568792
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.04京usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.003192435228074
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.51億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7411823783187783
    },
    {
        "question": " 2569万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.409821192672171
    },
    {
        "question": " 219usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 5.340648880673284
    },
    {
        "question": " 50.8垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.207163459887561
    },
    {
        "question": " 18.7垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.334474569681157
    },
    {
        "question": " 173垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.680728900552335
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.75垓nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.46607611849296
    },
    {
        "question": " 55.1兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.741131502948967
    },
    {
        "question": " 117兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.06805969027445
    },
    {
        "question": " 2889万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.460797142197984
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.54万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.966964613083704
    },
    {
        "question": " 2228年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.290406103044022
    },
    {
        "question": " 1924億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.72189030671906
    },
    {
        "question": " 8676日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.096648002343892
    },
    {
        "question": " 7146万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.9115595123967353
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.4億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.778085676691959
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.37億時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.916082997342347
    },
    {
        "question": " 3377時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.084840459162085
    },
    {
        "question": " 272時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.991011939284846
    },
    {
        "question": " 443兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.9257394474007
    },
    {
        "question": " 2280万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.199543956648007
    },
    {
        "question": " 215億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.554388909663066
    },
    {
        "question": " 1200分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.85745753688314
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.4分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.905445523187254
    },
    {
        "question": " 217億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8371167634701164
    },
    {
        "question": " 9万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.017614986723086812
    },
    {
        "question": " 28.7万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.900849163352022
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.93億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.81670931539991
    },
    {
        "question": " 350秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.544552098992965
    },
    {
        "question": " 308秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.488079208061205
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.25京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.598687613437852
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.22京msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.410724453914153
    },
    {
        "question": " 8758億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.386090842856802
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.2兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.342157111489907
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.1万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.206842137577988
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.06msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 3.7044875872441594
    },
    {
        "question": " 344京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.037328661492343
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.89京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.960663321017972
    },
    {
        "question": " 1347京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.573102436938694
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.12京usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.271405192573859
    },
    {
        "question": " 8610億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.934982460845895
    },
    {
        "question": " 601万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.778554334992265
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.345e+06垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.871397667105676
    },
    {
        "question": " 278京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.507578565888436
    },
    {
        "question": " 18.6垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.714350649545988
    },
    {
        "question": " 5146兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.933334543283992
    },
    {
        "question": " 1491兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.173357923572795
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.15兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.961611537144857
    },
    {
        "question": " 7759億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.889803084923697
    },
    {
        "question": " 43.9年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.584868482345189
    },
    {
        "question": " 52.8年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.443380281161893
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.76年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.7432487248107424
    },
    {
        "question": " 3435万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.9736735884702545
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.19万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.171795469330773
    },
    {
        "question": " 459万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.81971975159871
    },
    {
        "question": " 757日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.815399229289211
    },
    {
        "question": " 4870億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.745038420627325
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.8億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.691664027773445
    },
    {
        "question": " 2545時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.183880064786997
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.73万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.992590520203594
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.9兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.506540436616136
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.4兆分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.988442588473259
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.6億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.356270346858586
    },
    {
        "question": " 143分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.9321377483520523
    },
    {
        "question": " 75.9兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.381597207466147
    },
    {
        "question": " 2521万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4650170013232273
    },
    {
        "question": " 5603億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.192151295957293
    },
    {
        "question": " 7948秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.122128258251413
    },
    {
        "question": " 46.8秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.67048268717937
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.2秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.181271802537301
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.62秒は何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.208654850407159
    },
    {
        "question": " 37.9兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.0793265703369013
    },
    {
        "question": " 432兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.699445083345108
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.99京msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.741702515140023
    },
    {
        "question": " 25.7億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.632575384864457
    },
    {
        "question": " 3192msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.504082277364647
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.08万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.611034622630605
    },
    {
        "question": " 8613兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.43632720277719
    },
    {
        "question": " 2132億usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.39234976903406604
    },
    {
        "question": " 476兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.120993863505859
    },
    {
        "question": " 58.3兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.98723074974922
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.91億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6908600440236685
    },
    {
        "question": " 4474億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.650715310514475
    },
    {
        "question": " 13垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.6149553374106915
    },
    {
        "question": " 516垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.77573445701106
    },
    {
        "question": " 1111京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.489306483087115
    },
    {
        "question": " 8766京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.164645353993468
    },
    {
        "question": " 9134兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.9606672199258535
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.54億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 2.9796403726360055
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.02兆nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.304684061010095
    },
    {
        "question": " 228年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.079165796340892
    },
    {
        "question": " 144億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.595392661223274
    },
    {
        "question": " 1137万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.435811180488601
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.79万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.838999774475921
    },
    {
        "question": " 166日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.157483867100071
    },
    {
        "question": " 4564万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.7168316127846257
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.9億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.872116893593686
    },
    {
        "question": " 27.7万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.221077002185553
    },
    {
        "question": " 23.7万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.93047849017054
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.22億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3656659625560463
    },
    {
        "question": " 38.6万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4277370571302193
    },
    {
        "question": " 797分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1232398195533755
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.91分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7744303971733943
    },
    {
        "question": " 195分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.069132646646603
    },
    {
        "question": " 9833万秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.49386281129745524
    },
    {
        "question": " 42.2兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.688808272399699
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.28億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.305956274042536
    },
    {
        "question": " 1170秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.290107937725501
    },
    {
        "question": " 59.7京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.277384301843641
    },
    {
        "question": " 29.8兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.537743574556469
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.41兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.59423907205535
    },
    {
        "question": " 626億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.01822583300764
    },
    {
        "question": " 835万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.9216076073969597
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.98万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.953054820242823
    },
    {
        "question": " 6233msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.794707561411625
    },
    {
        "question": " 3879京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.089905367160643
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.83兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9570263347846029
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.79京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.695582247459456
    },
    {
        "question": " 6508兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.035298242927281
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.45億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7363176786775245
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.07兆usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.029217522760396
    },
    {
        "question": " 88.2usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 4.945264211414172
    },
    {
        "question": " 23.5京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8714692303224958
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.7垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.260335725918548
    },
    {
        "question": " 535兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1719743880903843
    },
    {
        "question": " 233京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.58948922067216
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.43京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.535587551422299
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.54兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.188453126864434
    },
    {
        "question": " 1404万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.147272118381695
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.72万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.502845583001828
    },
    {
        "question": " 2720年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.155251920871697
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.28年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.607223261245424
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.04億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.453221134301897
    },
    {
        "question": " 86.6日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.3175390974610384
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.32万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.27840541817054
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.52日は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.812683298490914
    },
    {
        "question": " 26.7億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.484789778066547
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.93万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.3927375632575876
    },
    {
        "question": " 331時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.298130445047658
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.98時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.156147257546476
    },
    {
        "question": " 1333時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.681161894961223
    },
    {
        "question": " 75.4万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.15681519920318188
    },
    {
        "question": " 722万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.700069860257722
    },
    {
        "question": " 3416億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.75539676501456
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.35万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.416776315521151
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.36分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.150703478756627
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.8京秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.535555390614496
    },
    {
        "question": " 3525億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.610652173814198
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.61億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.001310885159226
    },
    {
        "question": " 3751億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.795950308331683
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.54秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.7438377294731637
    },
    {
        "question": " 8111京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.410275697855823
    },
    {
        "question": " 591億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8352708907556066
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.48億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.0947261796477
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.4億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.380469748703291
    },
    {
        "question": " 27.5億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.438873076494175
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.36msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 3.971490857214921
    },
    {
        "question": " 889兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4499908389901472
    },
    {
        "question": " 54.2兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.797543530209383
    },
    {
        "question": " 663京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.265108950528088
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.22億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.30723745467060803
    },
    {
        "question": " 23.3兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.366845439543381
    },
    {
        "question": " 3911万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.592321538781182
    },
    {
        "question": " 3164usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.500172844697195
    },
    {
        "question": " 1715京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.735508342357412
    },
    {
        "question": " 7828垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.957123607769615
    },
    {
        "question": " 1925兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.728055695789049
    },
    {
        "question": " 29.9兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6980922588044463
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.38兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.8046595498398905
    },
    {
        "question": " 38億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.5796191931712364
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.36兆nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.525798024528788
    },
    {
        "question": " 21年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.885555249849908
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.7万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.374075250134469
    },
    {
        "question": " 60.8年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.504667192939468
    },
    {
        "question": " 55.1億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.17888212393937
    },
    {
        "question": " 2921日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.845689678349077
    },
    {
        "question": " 164日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.374431973097828
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.22日は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.56173731154243
    },
    {
        "question": " 288億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.516620603243393
    },
    {
        "question": " 333万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.142776292785017
    },
    {
        "question": " 35.5時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.3283527503954713
    },
    {
        "question": " 431時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.190808444707864
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.3億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.4339301314224233
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.48億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.492995928228148
    },
    {
        "question": " 597億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.998074118407356
    },
    {
        "question": " 1874分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.051027541501908
    },
    {
        "question": " 7736兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.389736922442957
    },
    {
        "question": " 1441億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.222151165530544
    },
    {
        "question": " 26億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.85790108849098
    },
    {
        "question": " 635秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.024848383550464
    },
    {
        "question": " 1427秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.154529259243253
    },
    {
        "question": " 235秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.370820885314144
    },
    {
        "question": " 49.8京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.198624011083224
    },
    {
        "question": " 173兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.302221773647516
    },
    {
        "question": " 6883兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.281505194193027
    },
    {
        "question": " 19.3億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.5067218208888455
    },
    {
        "question": " 200億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.301805885473708
    },
    {
        "question": " 40.5msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.6079408596904505
    },
    {
        "question": " 774兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.389894275728235
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.1兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.295406233313817
    },
    {
        "question": " 22.9兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.8031847790424655
    },
    {
        "question": " 365兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.783873442826492
    },
    {
        "question": " 931万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9690146571254876
    },
    {
        "question": " 2608万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.4162678042218655
    },
    {
        "question": " 129usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 5.11177274348433
    },
    {
        "question": " 202垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.807540021233485
    },
    {
        "question": " 4356垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.702551664413813
    },
    {
        "question": " 22兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7855370992652633
    },
    {
        "question": " 1018億nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.2297120298460087
    },
    {
        "question": " 361京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.557305332303498
    },
    {
        "question": " 381万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 0.5813420869746067
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.43万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 1.5357694779755238
    },
    {
        "question": " 394年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.158057589564407
    },
    {
        "question": " 179年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.973469228717648
    },
    {
        "question": " 198年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.79503824430205
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.67億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.863665570673455
    },
    {
        "question": " 226万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4124001617715605
    },
    {
        "question": " 930万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.588247984331622
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.09時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8136407785062714
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.65万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.978908724395822
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.02億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2880295613309496
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.24兆分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.468973992316505
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.65万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.159107915275449
    },
    {
        "question": " 9643万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.762352151552118
    },
    {
        "question": " 129分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.890180594944332
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.16京秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.356328302698364
    },
    {
        "question": " 6208万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.856433819906804
    },
    {
        "question": " 128億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.549857566912979
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.6億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.4424428293816325
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.93秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.467171738817868
    },
    {
        "question": " 1196兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.57897133296441
    },
    {
        "question": " 41.8兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.684755630349385
    },
    {
        "question": " 53.1億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.1691049009092707
    },
    {
        "question": " 1351万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3524034890884096
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.29億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.360229577757799
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.17msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.335696581102354
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.17垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.570840170514172
    },
    {
        "question": " 33.4兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5869209468020307
    },
    {
        "question": " 2436京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.830417249166327
    },
    {
        "question": " 954兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.201610716842505
    },
    {
        "question": " 4826兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.683602917190347
    },
    {
        "question": " 2047万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.3111510281696415
    },
    {
        "question": " 115万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.06249117640922
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.57垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.161430285723351
    },
    {
        "question": " 3417垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.597183944941396
    },
    {
        "question": " 1871京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.715696239345665
    },
    {
        "question": " 3672兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.786754548110036
    },
    {
        "question": " 47.5億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6771308869958259
    },
    {
        "question": " 6955兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.842327172144058
    },
    {
        "question": " 6937億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.841166072951886
    },
    {
        "question": " 4725年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.616880257695067
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.27年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.825266007397934
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.88万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.432508522663067
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.98日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.853868843633466
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.3日は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.061038758719176
    },
    {
        "question": " 150億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.232982915553671
    },
    {
        "question": " 1771億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.868036174249417
    },
    {
        "question": " 260時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.192671734882475
    },
    {
        "question": " 3466時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.0961076880377245
    },
    {
        "question": " 548億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.018126353657805
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.06万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8652703412906659
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.34万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.1923627900929805
    },
    {
        "question": " 48万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.459022895587225
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.92万分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.371832327764235
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.35兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.026790727134982
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.7億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.230387627123057
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.3万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4577530036692044
    },
    {
        "question": " 1億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.222264022224028
    },
    {
        "question": " 2161秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.334584012609347
    },
    {
        "question": " 35.3京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.048839417091786
    },
    {
        "question": " 792億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.962201556369627
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.01億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.747914429566979
    },
    {
        "question": " 14億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.367509081458818
    },
    {
        "question": " 325万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.5121804481817263
    },
    {
        "question": " 308msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 5.4885240644206394
    },
    {
        "question": " 160垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.703976704769916
    },
    {
        "question": " 60.6兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8458707351413692
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.54兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.630182775787031
    },
    {
        "question": " 281億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.670274488906287
    },
    {
        "question": " 1438兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.157791702652208
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.34兆usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.524150751084267
    },
    {
        "question": " 3392垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.031691788695374
    },
    {
        "question": " 8640兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.000002041893898
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.4兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5016238798392503
    },
    {
        "question": " 284京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.675017469492608
    },
    {
        "question": " 45.2億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6555023999322862
    },
    {
        "question": " 3269万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.5144263677063052
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.39兆nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.378335336331894
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.09年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.051815563776452
    },
    {
        "question": " 52.7万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.66452377217206
    },
    {
        "question": " 6970万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.2809168043019605
    },
    {
        "question": " 57.5万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.91792723465761
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.5万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.23243470106232622
    },
    {
        "question": " 1045億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.639071689495523
    },
    {
        "question": " 105時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.799625210922911
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.3時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.67895124729913
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.34兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.081522415921885
    },
    {
        "question": " 2951億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.311640680486166
    },
    {
        "question": " 678分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0528452905570196
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.01万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.256972919032286
    },
    {
        "question": " 34.7分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.31824591139599
    },
    {
        "question": " 6855億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.337184814207627
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.06兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.969840825016981
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.24兆秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.163148693894904
    },
    {
        "question": " 4194億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.844511857808143
    },
    {
        "question": " 5082億msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2072626963147337
    },
    {
        "question": " 29.7京msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.536697731273113
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.02兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.7498535646933036
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.7兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.469776230406922
    },
    {
        "question": " 77.1億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.887302863967257
    },
    {
        "question": " 357万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.552225839173094
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.87msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.458620521367821
    },
    {
        "question": " 42.2垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.126058329720921
    },
    {
        "question": " 138京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.20468941919701
    },
    {
        "question": " 1894兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.721063507913561
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.78億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.47157686475707616
    },
    {
        "question": " 2707兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.432565493573035
    },
    {
        "question": " 353万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.5475307646861074
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.15usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 3.332458601671128
    },
    {
        "question": " 589垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.271391549959424
    },
    {
        "question": " 28京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.5108673519357514
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.85垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.129523968566762
    },
    {
        "question": " 490兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.9123890005287167
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.2兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.152578836878816
    },
    {
        "question": " 20.7兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.3169920752467
    },
    {
        "question": " 2906万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.463246848706758
    },
    {
        "question": " 51.8年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.434620566817124
    },
    {
        "question": " 3325億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.959429785641769
    },
    {
        "question": " 1925日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.664543718803831
    },
    {
        "question": " 5227日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.654788212390661
    },
    {
        "question": " 3609万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.614932985870507
    },
    {
        "question": " 2257億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.973326355632752
    },
    {
        "question": " 5149時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.489867483643516
    },
    {
        "question": " 278時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.000704262931853
    },
    {
        "question": " 628兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.077431656605237
    },
    {
        "question": " 5370億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.571596720333964
    },
    {
        "question": " 196万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.5144552850805875
    },
    {
        "question": " 359分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.333789625109814
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.43分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.933082140089351
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.57京秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.910391321552286
    },
    {
        "question": " 242万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4475486630611545
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.23兆秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.953023531080797
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.1億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.428066265408619
    },
    {
        "question": " 143万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.155622079446907
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.6秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.748181733535179
    },
    {
        "question": " 6938京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.34241308714025
    },
    {
        "question": " 1978億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.3596614426496094
    },
    {
        "question": " 7477兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.317411808283731
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.2億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.565016234616948
    },
    {
        "question": " 113万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.0537647370827434
    },
    {
        "question": " 41.6万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.618938781425134
    },
    {
        "question": " 74.9京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.375744307197939
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.88垓usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.337324153069321
    },
    {
        "question": " 63.1兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.243467468932773
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.3兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.583741132119059
    },
    {
        "question": " 135億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.12928759234513
    },
    {
        "question": " 281万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.4485498187324923
    },
    {
        "question": " 316万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.5000877561658
    },
    {
        "question": " 3748京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.0750337476242695
    },
    {
        "question": " 5883垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.83313003455009
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.71垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.270376689558109
    },
    {
        "question": " 554京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.965549557483168
    },
    {
        "question": " 343兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.535573078739926
    },
    {
        "question": " 573兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.758393697230519
    },
    {
        "question": " 4665億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.668866218584762
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.24万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.189371263151858
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.58年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.919249705537055
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.69年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.727088092913117
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.63万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3736283507458977
    },
    {
        "question": " 6386日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.185439078283668
    },
    {
        "question": " 34.9日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.70129603151391
    },
    {
        "question": " 307万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5445451601399194
    },
    {
        "question": " 1708万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.852240334186879
    },
    {
        "question": " 828時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.696139918425165
    },
    {
        "question": " 27.9時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.002357199634908
    },
    {
        "question": " 215時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.887994956250754
    },
    {
        "question": " 3884万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8686235132998408
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.96億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.439109397054218
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.2万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.2693394720699587
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.3万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.9009079242295615
    },
    {
        "question": " 962分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.761420168963149
    },
    {
        "question": " 21.7億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8372437265912855
    },
    {
        "question": " 22万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.4055788521184833
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.45億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.981028493003445
    },
    {
        "question": " 1549万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.4118221798577935
    },
    {
        "question": " 4582秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.661047231463445
    },
    {
        "question": " 4469秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.650189981603406
    },
    {
        "question": " 6322兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.302028989312446
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.2京msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.687046581820486
    },
    {
        "question": " 57.1億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.2004269287574285
    },
    {
        "question": " 261億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.6391678449199
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.69億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.75499035728917
    },
    {
        "question": " 6838msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.8349292319243915
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.98垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.278062654298388
    },
    {
        "question": " 28.7兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5211702927965196
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.68兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.3823805293049203
    },
    {
        "question": " 3021億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.70200038731931
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.93億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.899298205271008
    },
    {
        "question": " 73.6万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 2.8669097524189526
    },
    {
        "question": " 265usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 5.423107050518304
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.37e+06垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.87599030364964
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.5京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.2530760281711224
    },
    {
        "question": " 404兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.0496803153825383
    },
    {
        "question": " 1374億nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.3599220551570792
    },
    {
        "question": " 22.7億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.35532716195496694
    },
    {
        "question": " 262兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.418209846922105
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.57億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 5.195844844121761
    },
    {
        "question": " 20.9年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.8819066822194435
    },
    {
        "question": " 105億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.460590661696589
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.16億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.122189484080966
    },
    {
        "question": " 367万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.184317332281411
    },
    {
        "question": " 287万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.235422513355829
    },
    {
        "question": " 129時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.667250474541559
    },
    {
        "question": " 360万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8361779123611535
    },
    {
        "question": " 27.4億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.280124245243409
    },
    {
        "question": " 35.6万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.7738888807380433
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.71分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.450929881991801
    },
    {
        "question": " 116分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.8407867594582
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.72京秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.935142144390397
    },
    {
        "question": " 128兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.169495507928108
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.85万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4372376910943774
    },
    {
        "question": " 36.2億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.780070636799547
    },
    {
        "question": " 65万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.81317106539285
    },
    {
        "question": " 76秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.880698707862285
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.9秒は何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.77071503706733
    },
    {
        "question": " 996京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.49933580965114
    },
    {
        "question": " 42.2兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.688990070608445
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.85京msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.709950543792514
    },
    {
        "question": " 5175万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9358000927458914
    },
    {
        "question": " 23.6万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3721358998355155
    },
    {
        "question": " 434京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.138791234023419
    },
    {
        "question": " 1040兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.08037430262509
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.03兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.455319576456713
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.8兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.476668195374053
    },
    {
        "question": " 9037億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.956002960215274
    },
    {
        "question": " 1546億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.18909198360875
    },
    {
        "question": " 810usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 5.908446717289829
    },
    {
        "question": " 877垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.444009501593325
    },
    {
        "question": " 7749垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.952750354474519
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.3京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.599392179112596
    },
    {
        "question": " 4887京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.91090198197161
    },
    {
        "question": " 28京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.447300351362077
    },
    {
        "question": " 534万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 0.7274157554802585
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.07万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 1.7828852374052462
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.26年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.2835140149676323
    },
    {
        "question": " 216億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.772925970289114
    },
    {
        "question": " 32.4日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.890553412998208
    },
    {
        "question": " 731日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.022503942133691
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.25兆時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.156057372303895
    },
    {
        "question": " 40.5億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.227781559177608
    },
    {
        "question": " 3584万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.332576730234125
    },
    {
        "question": " 1613時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.76387018321873
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.57時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.302414763353166
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.78兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.269474369464216
    },
    {
        "question": " 7714億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.728949213525697
    },
    {
        "question": " 5542分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9655425588555897
    },
    {
        "question": " 23.3億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8692779695337358
    },
    {
        "question": " 161万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.270922851111731
    },
    {
        "question": " 12万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5229407902221415
    },
    {
        "question": " 6769秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.052385962076065
    },
    {
        "question": " 822秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.914910353824526
    },
    {
        "question": " 4449京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.14943480636417
    },
    {
        "question": " 790億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9613469233792165
    },
    {
        "question": " 161兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.650032568186508
    },
    {
        "question": " 5644億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.973402026283072
    },
    {
        "question": " 34.3万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.535803665236812
    },
    {
        "question": " 259万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.413217083774505
    },
    {
        "question": " 8456兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4283594299910662
    },
    {
        "question": " 3536京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.612026624256814
    },
    {
        "question": " 24.2京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.827473100213852
    },
    {
        "question": " 21.6兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.555830388967207
    },
    {
        "question": " 1564億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.194374410001416
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.13万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.3277088878567567
    },
    {
        "question": " 92.2万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 8.96487838354598
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.17垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.214938653732131
    },
    {
        "question": " 62.3京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.857911702271636
    },
    {
        "question": " 340兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9754825281818678
    },
    {
        "question": " 5377京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.952392199746974
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.9兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.228700356848991
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.39億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 2.529884710175907
    },
    {
        "question": " 75.5億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.877794731304817
    },
    {
        "question": " 1342万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.690002413377822
    },
    {
        "question": " 1317日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5574108591335647
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.83万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.063830181119172
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.54億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.462941068806363
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.74億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.860702236572093
    },
    {
        "question": " 55.1兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.020582956593083
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.7億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.946900555840374
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.59万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.156055408017715
    },
    {
        "question": " 58.6分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.5462018541705276
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.72兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.174689454655409
    },
    {
        "question": " 118億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.136012046544646
    },
    {
        "question": " 501万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.1437290616709577
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.5万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.24370380878198
    },
    {
        "question": " 38.9秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.590020791062539
    },
    {
        "question": " 842秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.925462661357273
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.21秒は何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.08264086739395
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.11垓msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.548152858060371
    },
    {
        "question": " 51.2兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.7726369996589835
    },
    {
        "question": " 6887兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.28173891916761
    },
    {
        "question": " 94.1億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.195325721479348
    },
    {
        "question": " 38.6万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5862001267252452
    },
    {
        "question": " 518msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 8.714705763563593
    },
    {
        "question": " 452京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.1562092970589095
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.72京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.497455024493903
    },
    {
        "question": " 1510京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.622754728368848
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.98兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.175103807651969
    },
    {
        "question": " 5558億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.744893943426181
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.93兆usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.594447226413225
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.4usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 4.1278829135543695
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.86垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.2692754237835615
    },
    {
        "question": " 3408京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.596017614938724
    },
    {
        "question": " 48.8垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.132069092844606
    },
    {
        "question": " 47.8京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.901302215563664
    },
    {
        "question": " 3943兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.595773148648187
    },
    {
        "question": " 281兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.44912710429557
    },
    {
        "question": " 55.2万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 2.7415922980709095
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.15年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.4735304014858204
    },
    {
        "question": " 1276万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.5435244010670015
    },
    {
        "question": " 558万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.126943877679158
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.14日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.724945385343734
    },
    {
        "question": " 55.7日は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.682321464935647
    },
    {
        "question": " 316万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.557462725351475
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.28億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.72676783641223
    },
    {
        "question": " 42.3時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.403992328097641
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.21時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.9007555417286977
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.39兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.809681768908813
    },
    {
        "question": " 38.5億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.427369494761598
    },
    {
        "question": " 346億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.761111364391297
    },
    {
        "question": " 429万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.411046972478179
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.17分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.279866010498479
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.12兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.5516176054168085
    },
    {
        "question": " 83.5億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.984930713138137
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.43億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.25192050458114
    },
    {
        "question": " 3902秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8131565946935535
    },
    {
        "question": " 588万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.769197506049634
    },
    {
        "question": " 6474兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.312341361495813
    },
    {
        "question": " 602兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.843389992848323
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.21兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.52808516879222
    },
    {
        "question": " 45.8兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.882344450318676
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.03兆msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.60539518806068
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.73万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.239293215111916
    },
    {
        "question": " 84.7兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.4289388752722145
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.7京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.260490302421555
    },
    {
        "question": " 1103兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.486446677938133
    },
    {
        "question": " 75.9兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.1019209369515295
    },
    {
        "question": " 3055兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.484963475104854
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.02万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.006640111569328
    },
    {
        "question": " 78.3垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.395136715874824
    },
    {
        "question": " 3302垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.582262369059215
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.19垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.407024778471992
    },
    {
        "question": " 475兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.898680533253515
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.83兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.684112503536636
    },
    {
        "question": " 433万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 0.6368188967818622
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.58億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 5.554114318649317
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.42万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.713220508667218
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.2万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.856409167096974
    },
    {
        "question": " 70.2年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.345187670228247
    },
    {
        "question": " 3860万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.024248203771941
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.72日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.05372374820044
    },
    {
        "question": " 186万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.426927686012528
    },
    {
        "question": " 888日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.885058089606487
    },
    {
        "question": " 108億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.09147638878369
    },
    {
        "question": " 343億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.154979471856183
    },
    {
        "question": " 966万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.763207317884824
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.36時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.929983115228642
    },
    {
        "question": " 635億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.082007136035096
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.65兆分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.50943011653368
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.58億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.634300438203584
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.23万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.28756725677054
    },
    {
        "question": " 863分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.714105975192837
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.41京秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.308283297122625
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.05兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.766980414736836
    },
    {
        "question": " 1468万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.6103919005451734
    },
    {
        "question": " 553万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.964541345319588
    },
    {
        "question": " 2257秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.353480994672958
    },
    {
        "question": " 1234京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.592400919668254
    },
    {
        "question": " 8242兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.979549892913385
    },
    {
        "question": " 97.3兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.431931196753293
    },
    {
        "question": " 322万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7297676671888562
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.89万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2760652887883528
    },
    {
        "question": " 8020msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.904172953083668
    },
    {
        "question": " 77.8兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.39196148350965854
    },
    {
        "question": " 823京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.979041106061143
    },
    {
        "question": " 3738億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.0163972007414968
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.5兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.097107548985692
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.11兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.047269574008408
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.01兆usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.603489433189417
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.9usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 4.074746747404866
    },
    {
        "question": " 335垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.026444473127251
    },
    {
        "question": " 105垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.083985403794319
    },
    {
        "question": " 26.6京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.868293948106163
    },
    {
        "question": " 292兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.6869719326974715
    },
    {
        "question": " 23.4兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.369107112699865
    },
    {
        "question": " 1123億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.050269341175792
    },
    {
        "question": " 111万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 3.0459448003750023
    },
    {
        "question": " 2689万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.991856282807062
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.01年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.420101557904956
    },
    {
        "question": " 115年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.557758176208633
    },
    {
        "question": " 820日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.3512724708918302
    },
    {
        "question": " 84.6日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.3074042298194364
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.72万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.5927870011870136
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.58日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.134708428656079
    },
    {
        "question": " 43.6日は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.575643335669374
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.7万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1256242982289433
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.4億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.766405489832417
    },
    {
        "question": " 1918万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.060977345402002
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.17時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.892409940639885
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.03時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.037711127708288
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.53兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.462747771464237
    },
    {
        "question": " 4451万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.490134558316629
    },
    {
        "question": " 901億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.176499881675982
    },
    {
        "question": " 306万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.26348418439328
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.07万分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.09327718477649
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.51億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6814114356369283
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.82兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.32281307784994
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.96万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7352327103111256
    },
    {
        "question": " 64.7秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.03303813198165528
    },
    {
        "question": " 4715秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.67351369465698
    },
    {
        "question": " 6402京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.307538814025055
    },
    {
        "question": " 2050兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.3753496146760025
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.4京msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.588289026618394
    },
    {
        "question": " 44.3兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.867794252549244
    },
    {
        "question": " 28.4億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.452831926401074
    },
    {
        "question": " 26.7万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.426634848558653
    },
    {
        "question": " 498兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1980063143011588
    },
    {
        "question": " 1761兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.309209821018278
    },
    {
        "question": " 1239京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.536687642753101
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.3兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.345805693715806
    },
    {
        "question": " 237兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.37399028673902
    },
    {
        "question": " 189万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.277435106050801
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.57万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 7.195932312557774
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.751e+05垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.744378030357133
    },
    {
        "question": " 8415兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.988531678899621
    },
    {
        "question": " 2069京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.759377574668757
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.6京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.248635652978665
    },
    {
        "question": " 59.3兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.7729523438156205
    },
    {
        "question": " 795万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 0.9004294468779828
    },
    {
        "question": " 320億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.505313875638022
    },
    {
        "question": " 30.4年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.424895284386863
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.3年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.9318030057479145
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.94万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7257078232915612
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.21兆時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.140024121414186
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.33億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.743217156287917
    },
    {
        "question": " 180万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.033394833773158
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.54時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.433585845725906
    },
    {
        "question": " 774万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1680444949784308
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.32万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9631278543264299
    },
    {
        "question": " 1509分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4004475022287333
    },
    {
        "question": " 261万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.195500977909564
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.61分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.9841734283037145
    },
    {
        "question": " 76.4億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3840115614789803
    },
    {
        "question": " 7821億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.956739565043883
    },
    {
        "question": " 1780万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.6942296874049783
    },
    {
        "question": " 2003秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.523518410714304
    },
    {
        "question": " 209万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.31985025533703
    },
    {
        "question": " 399兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.102330097281119
    },
    {
        "question": " 5705兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.8197884772438195
    },
    {
        "question": " 405兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.051091443795338
    },
    {
        "question": " 2492億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.618368943457746
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.77万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2478294458349437
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.94msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 3.4684721990136125
    },
    {
        "question": " 57.5京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.261179750943043
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.24垓usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.691160995868866
    },
    {
        "question": " 64.3京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.252214753291707
    },
    {
        "question": " 38兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.801165268700546
    },
    {
        "question": " 3652兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.562551608399295
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.16万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.7898854672528963
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.4usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 4.015161848285912
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.77垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.179263439944031
    },
    {
        "question": " 70.4垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.911268930752372
    },
    {
        "question": " 6880兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.281263693314261
    },
    {
        "question": " 3930億nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8162445415058683
    },
    {
        "question": " 6456兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.809967288738219
    },
    {
        "question": " 387兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.587805475108652
    },
    {
        "question": " 6725nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 0.8276849532041031
    },
    {
        "question": " 1728年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.958174724126208
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.87億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.896300248593139
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.71日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6144401982996848
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.77兆時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.49974186330002
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.4億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.63616695470919
    },
    {
        "question": " 1504万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.955372605318882
    },
    {
        "question": " 77.9時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.4479386138983745
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.52億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.093447855652066
    },
    {
        "question": " 158万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.039388751415797
    },
    {
        "question": " 667分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0458727428296966
    },
    {
        "question": " 394万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.373333355149517
    },
    {
        "question": " 7199億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.358471293893289
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.7兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.09461880094124
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.29兆秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.55296413300273
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.5億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.280893365782078
    },
    {
        "question": " 2220秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.346401363412312
    },
    {
        "question": " 8788京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.445081374501143
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.52兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.993891832792421
    },
    {
        "question": " 383億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.027140289278714
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.4億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.0282231069297305
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.25億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.628362448181803
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.1msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.117802471945305
    },
    {
        "question": " 1406msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.148049459995978
    },
    {
        "question": " 332垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.02262980286234
    },
    {
        "question": " 30.9兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.553949626017072
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.5兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9871849119505125
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.53京usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.964366320394339
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.04兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.308927521882711
    },
    {
        "question": " 217万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.335793617838374
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.9usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 3.4623535538067687
    },
    {
        "question": " 31.3垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.996280629818113
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.17垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.564142307525685
    },
    {
        "question": " 369京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.010243151672643
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.98京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.175254516514944
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.8京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.105643386296219
    },
    {
        "question": " 3038兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.482541833968892
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.03万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 1.4819463862052362
    },
    {
        "question": " 114万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.619107658158311
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.83万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.52562911864166
    },
    {
        "question": " 6388年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.526011113085206
    },
    {
        "question": " 2357日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8101231359023486
    },
    {
        "question": " 315万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.879031083279279
    },
    {
        "question": " 51.1万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.866789251553959
    },
    {
        "question": " 1696日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.165922405246183
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.6日は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.81711233753538
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.72兆時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.731496874814855
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.1億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.798461628604841
    },
    {
        "question": " 166万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.999206965739059
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.02万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.257247063222572
    },
    {
        "question": " 36.9兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.845811373974778
    },
    {
        "question": " 83.5億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.76327844321439
    },
    {
        "question": " 1106億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.26560602679949
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.2分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.828651229285344
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.06京秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.81552658472193
    },
    {
        "question": " 2255億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.416601956006382
    },
    {
        "question": " 81.7億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.356184717090352
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.61億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.427876648545525
    },
    {
        "question": " 9685秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.986117922652118
    },
    {
        "question": " 483京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.185168149178867
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.8京msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.28995502302174
    },
    {
        "question": " 47.1兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.116874541814921
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.24兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.3147342724197815
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.2万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1530091137892757
    },
    {
        "question": " 5863msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.768135259949467
    },
    {
        "question": " 123垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.592423818702171
    },
    {
        "question": " 535京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.791744020230591
    },
    {
        "question": " 79.1兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.3420971857732
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.1億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.226568565196251
    },
    {
        "question": " 138億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.140618696141095
    },
    {
        "question": " 72.5万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 2.8604386507151314
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.02万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 7.480222076663578
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.394e+04垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.474054917933959
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.5垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.938571293777416
    },
    {
        "question": " 85.3兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3744929044724352
    },
    {
        "question": " 797兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.12353106117107
    },
    {
        "question": " 37.6兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.574741448982231
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.5億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.062097157712894
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.9億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.173535250167809
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.79万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.242564037748406
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.5年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.133910968094496
    },
    {
        "question": " 441年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.365082027529999
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.48億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.832371221023277
    },
    {
        "question": " 124日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.029244438339546
    },
    {
        "question": " 90.8日は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.894544522603493
    },
    {
        "question": " 24.8兆時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.45271450446943
    },
    {
        "question": " 1932時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9057968168971573
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.5時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.716293633774179
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.93兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.230063610905416
    },
    {
        "question": " 250万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.239481028707626
    },
    {
        "question": " 152万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.402737863283387
    },
    {
        "question": " 2112分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.102940841759875
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.33分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.90040498866364
    },
    {
        "question": " 23.9分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.156321275771887
    },
    {
        "question": " 37.3兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.073082608506053
    },
    {
        "question": " 6162億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.8532117668972266
    },
    {
        "question": " 6663秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.2673611532300557
    },
    {
        "question": " 111秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.2687115965944342
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.99秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.298648126510642
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.17兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.001704982319504
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.21億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9779407763371961
    },
    {
        "question": " 857兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.376906239852218
    },
    {
        "question": " 109億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.259795468040816
    },
    {
        "question": " 4955msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6950330083468237
    },
    {
        "question": " 51.3msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.710322706271253
    },
    {
        "question": " 2216垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.846700654667943
    },
    {
        "question": " 1193億usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.1400529275364304
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.33兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.1704088185406984
    },
    {
        "question": " 6767兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.052263878640689
    },
    {
        "question": " 2708億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.432576367769838
    },
    {
        "question": " 578万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.761673740551017
    },
    {
        "question": " 4307垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.135386284214641
    },
    {
        "question": " 9996兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.06332553929549
    },
    {
        "question": " 922兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.408227135519836
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.88垓nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.810738154451062
    },
    {
        "question": " 89.7億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9526820899990096
    },
    {
        "question": " 1443億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.15922715410184
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.3万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 1.1153140588366761
    },
    {
        "question": " 246年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.953876530717225
    },
    {
        "question": " 5331年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.669354425998122
    },
    {
        "question": " 170億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.6686766992393816
    },
    {
        "question": " 3400日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.91164555738267
    },
    {
        "question": " 93.4日は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.906952045437588
    },
    {
        "question": " 22兆時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.399050283941584
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.3億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.673237766659052
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.45万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.945438490529819
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.03時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.567566330962852
    },
    {
        "question": " 39.5兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.876426356211402
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.55兆分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.031050565408965
    },
    {
        "question": " 122億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.308127340712847
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.08万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.685610304131853
    },
    {
        "question": " 229億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8614543825248298
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.5億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.238241864057386
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.64億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.65804810012652
    },
    {
        "question": " 2228万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.5697784260311565
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.9秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.073962876928157
    },
    {
        "question": " 3秒は何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.477344227002686
    },
    {
        "question": " 234兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.8703180583871233
    },
    {
        "question": " 3183兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.566315370893348
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.31兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.561887867064421
    },
    {
        "question": " 2842億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.675495528184308
    },
    {
        "question": " 730万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.8634214096630846
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.05垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.523617707378998
    },
    {
        "question": " 19京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.34182529534776
    },
    {
        "question": " 1958億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7354873606427157
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.22京usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.307165636626227
    },
    {
        "question": " 830万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9191078754142412
    },
    {
        "question": " 340万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.5320320105905214
    },
    {
        "question": " 20.4垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.811781542526199
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.7垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.284995087772417
    },
    {
        "question": " 393京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.037845506516719
    },
    {
        "question": " 237兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.596750136100323
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.2兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.121531163546074
    },
    {
        "question": " 36.7兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.56501954443651
    },
    {
        "question": " 2450nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 0.3891635652741532
    },
    {
        "question": " 106万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.585904777191576
    },
    {
        "question": " 1669年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.164895267399764
    },
    {
        "question": " 86.5年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.657853079556441
    },
    {
        "question": " 48.4億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.122780725622722
    },
    {
        "question": " 3123万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.874764436360111
    },
    {
        "question": " 39.4日は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.531789345890388
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.6万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.2615863805633267
    },
    {
        "question": " 604万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.400549987941666
    },
    {
        "question": " 12万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.855636371211826
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.51時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.9562497758447295
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.21億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3616342742045293
    },
    {
        "question": " 5881万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.611086494283087
    },
    {
        "question": " 1220億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.308097302331973
    },
    {
        "question": " 18万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.033742985445786
    },
    {
        "question": " 22.8分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.13597756105137
    },
    {
        "question": " 81.7兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.4135758512612675
    },
    {
        "question": " 622億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.857581024297186
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.73億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.271588486376809
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.85億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.989301127430393
    },
    {
        "question": " 1371秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.136997662592658
    },
    {
        "question": " 688兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.338794943337197
    },
    {
        "question": " 2441兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.451040679373156
    },
    {
        "question": " 122兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.5292498459625055
    },
    {
        "question": " 283億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.6742103796616075
    },
    {
        "question": " 76.6億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.884151142590495
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.36msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 3.372404404439057
    },
    {
        "question": " 19.4京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.7880647384044988
    },
    {
        "question": " 314兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.5610874544630153
    },
    {
        "question": " 4152兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.061959433507536
    },
    {
        "question": " 1兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.223905133862194
    },
    {
        "question": " 140億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.147427680198169
    },
    {
        "question": " 2581usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 0.4117624110931095
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.24万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 7.6278056062213295
    },
    {
        "question": " 1279京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6081782382331244
    },
    {
        "question": " 9494京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.0409592992568575
    },
    {
        "question": " 340京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.975229721590811
    },
    {
        "question": " 52.2京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.939411889459275
    },
    {
        "question": " 137京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.136853844257107
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.46兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.649388224764189
    },
    {
        "question": " 2537億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.404350402033998
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.56年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.1139542993749627
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.91万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.405850093555758
    },
    {
        "question": " 129年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.83069683051521
    },
    {
        "question": " 433万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.074421763598382
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.4日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.216527741220913
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.3億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.071712518425461
    },
    {
        "question": " 9690時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6061159726364567
    },
    {
        "question": " 26.4万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.2000347589997835
    },
    {
        "question": " 105時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.577144970761396
    },
    {
        "question": " 130時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.671437548213353
    },
    {
        "question": " 37.5億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.8532788771055726
    },
    {
        "question": " 587万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.6102074465836287
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.02億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.0011105281879775
    },
    {
        "question": " 633分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.5793517673179975
    },
    {
        "question": " 268億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9285594212955433
    },
    {
        "question": " 53.8億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.794158026972508
    },
    {
        "question": " 431億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.0780684606989706
    },
    {
        "question": " 33.4万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.745669842398267
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.32万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.520973492356795
    },
    {
        "question": " 81.7京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.413301697055279
    },
    {
        "question": " 56兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.811971106687136
    },
    {
        "question": " 7529兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.320435655292313
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.13億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.2756077477936163
    },
    {
        "question": " 1294億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.111985481833434
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.9msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.172879292934609
    },
    {
        "question": " 2008msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.302856580888086
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.29京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.22503493438439
    },
    {
        "question": " 6236京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.858435995564498
    },
    {
        "question": " 218億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7816440889933596
    },
    {
        "question": " 468億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.892076575276069
    },
    {
        "question": " 5329億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.726663121523727
    },
    {
        "question": " 4512usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 0.6543787169494175
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.18万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 7.072860872377284
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.511e+04垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.9009772853375235
    },
    {
        "question": " 289垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.524741445615845
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.37垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.366457555994632
    },
    {
        "question": " 2367京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.596109784259212
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.1兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.207733541871466
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.56億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 2.9802960142175094
    },
    {
        "question": " 1646万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.216493919369874
    },
    {
        "question": " 127万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.666977217314937
    },
    {
        "question": " 3254年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.454980543386538
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.96万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.90920175435766
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.29万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.740168025220989
    },
    {
        "question": " 656日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.975162160867318
    },
    {
        "question": " 619日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.728033206276476
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.18兆時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.12957689450704
    },
    {
        "question": " 41.1万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.233327996121847
    },
    {
        "question": " 2005万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.080280332076129
    },
    {
        "question": " 107時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.587363513208218
    },
    {
        "question": " 188億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.552528515179949
    },
    {
        "question": " 3710万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.411050913915081
    },
    {
        "question": " 364億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.782464402081345
    },
    {
        "question": " 333分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.300136267202815
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.85万分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.672859708870666
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.66分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.530754643144165
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.49京秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.153000393538486
    },
    {
        "question": " 39.5兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.659615597457407
    },
    {
        "question": " 39.6億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.040975892835686
    },
    {
        "question": " 110億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.262757689657287
    },
    {
        "question": " 980万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.991052398637322
    },
    {
        "question": " 290兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.963351930245651
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.2億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9772818070607991
    },
    {
        "question": " 555兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.1883734370995
    },
    {
        "question": " 866億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.159571816744859
    },
    {
        "question": " 224万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.3505758164236363
    },
    {
        "question": " 5164msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.71300567113817
    },
    {
        "question": " 312京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.995425291872949
    },
    {
        "question": " 5203京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.779720458991962
    },
    {
        "question": " 6128兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.231005743888602
    },
    {
        "question": " 5966兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.997563252234131
    },
    {
        "question": " 140億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.147250125480219
    },
    {
        "question": " 3134億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.496034181707838
    },
    {
        "question": " 26.5万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 8.422502403265623
    },
    {
        "question": " 87.3垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.442050030467973
    },
    {
        "question": " 395兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6606396100537548
    },
    {
        "question": " 144兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6030965430008715
    },
    {
        "question": " 4701億nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8940862065478683
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.51京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.654522199178077
    },
    {
        "question": " 417億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.6204523868507765
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.51万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 1.6544129533989016
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.37万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.078437726308183
    },
    {
        "question": " 19.6年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.012114247614382
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.12年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.548143923546208
    },
    {
        "question": " 732万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.302105481840533
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.2日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4300778522759128
    },
    {
        "question": " 3845日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.743201839243358
    },
    {
        "question": " 43.9万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7000007497756697
    },
    {
        "question": " 4758万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.297234976442949
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.41万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.585209887269815
    },
    {
        "question": " 479時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.236725979779408
    },
    {
        "question": " 2566兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.688575156967428
    },
    {
        "question": " 190万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.1213299043217635
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.72万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7922923885276543
    },
    {
        "question": " 3719万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.348565628778816
    },
    {
        "question": " 588兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.270643543319086
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.96兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.355140667039884
    },
    {
        "question": " 642億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.251372316804585
    },
    {
        "question": " 2662秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.646989870174007
    },
    {
        "question": " 1238秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.092771890572395
    },
    {
        "question": " 61.3京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.288688354976882
    },
    {
        "question": " 2811兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.51229226160714
    },
    {
        "question": " 45.3兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.099436844286091
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.34兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.948998608157031
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.84万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9930257192276446
    },
    {
        "question": " 26.6万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.424135708275053
    },
    {
        "question": " 47.2msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 7.6739186437524936
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.21垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.007196759803113
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.8京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.289406352197631
    },
    {
        "question": " 39.3億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.03782103758181776
    },
    {
        "question": " 75.4億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.0990539704356106
    },
    {
        "question": " 664万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8221989779310979
    },
    {
        "question": " 18.8万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 2.2740414931080433
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.1usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 3.959275124961157
    },
    {
        "question": " 24垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.881194800129012
    },
    {
        "question": " 266兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.48804974740411233
    },
    {
        "question": " 21.9京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.784422753372922
    },
    {
        "question": " 448京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.873528630346163
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.86兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.767659027975009
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.05億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 2.6079002616019196
    },
    {
        "question": " 86.6億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.9372955247901125
    },
    {
        "question": " 2428万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.947563619504754
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.7万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.079144806316783
    },
    {
        "question": " 7746年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.60973181013156
    },
    {
        "question": " 4800日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1188961855932966
    },
    {
        "question": " 2139日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.710360470738324
    },
    {
        "question": " 20万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.460318675348645
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.46万日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.099527708004421
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.68万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.622920143175798
    },
    {
        "question": " 77.6万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.50941813568082
    },
    {
        "question": " 20.4時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.08839022981233
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.48時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.7272916849855067
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.94時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.3303479518452015
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.1兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.321104846611677
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.52兆分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.024210291540236
    },
    {
        "question": " 43.3万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.8578549777065776
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.63億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9215188635375515
    },
    {
        "question": " 285兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.51837279617468
    },
    {
        "question": " 978万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.4339649369046943
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.3万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.4609555450001652
    },
    {
        "question": " 2垓msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.801723777634974
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.62京msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.481929518091263
    },
    {
        "question": " 28.1億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.892952376945378
    },
    {
        "question": " 32.8兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.737667950297974
    },
    {
        "question": " 1165万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.066403576133672
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.3京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.512195921304028
    },
    {
        "question": " 4708兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.736340853408275
    },
    {
        "question": " 123億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5334057127666347
    },
    {
        "question": " 3221兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.729890951523193
    },
    {
        "question": " 235兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.370384420234087
    },
    {
        "question": " 9632usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 0.9837234023573649
    },
    {
        "question": " 394万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.595462551814633
    },
    {
        "question": " 210垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.823936463912688
    },
    {
        "question": " 694垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.90456677571258
    },
    {
        "question": " 179京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.696742453703832
    },
    {
        "question": " 50.8兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.927619424966993
    },
    {
        "question": " 2970兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.472793826066992
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.26兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.720974679054931
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.39億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 5.731798204717328
    },
    {
        "question": " 25年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.9596296410520884
    },
    {
        "question": " 47.2万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.616452691095622
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.14年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.050709657296286
    },
    {
        "question": " 6739日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2662681399473008
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.04兆時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.368144433626572
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.72万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.854112249388119
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.73万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.444369681889368
    },
    {
        "question": " 288時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.01507817020115
    },
    {
        "question": " 80.1万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.18275060383438624
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.1兆分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.958663648044464
    },
    {
        "question": " 132万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.343060058521168
    },
    {
        "question": " 38.5分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.363094641586672
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.61兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.382692428227709
    },
    {
        "question": " 2011万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3668741278514362
    },
    {
        "question": " 8753秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.3858361187025672
    },
    {
        "question": " 4878秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9100762843182784
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.88兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7756189378977627
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.58京msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.260865462542013
    },
    {
        "question": " 4442億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.091274947352811
    },
    {
        "question": " 35.9億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.777313734119824
    },
    {
        "question": " 45.4億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.657349180350012
    },
    {
        "question": " 126垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.602719292974005
    },
    {
        "question": " 4709兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.73639147611478
    },
    {
        "question": " 9649兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.428202624760977
    },
    {
        "question": " 872億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.1625619699036847
    },
    {
        "question": " 9258兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.966495627364077
    },
    {
        "question": " 1370億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.136647392946136
    },
    {
        "question": " 213usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 5.329082087195904
    },
    {
        "question": " 187垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.774082478689864
    },
    {
        "question": " 492兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7558008898394175
    },
    {
        "question": " 64兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.249800169341524
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.01京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.700737126215677
    },
    {
        "question": " 117京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.066595889370998
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.99億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 2.2995297229279843
    },
    {
        "question": " 6602億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.819675461829073
    },
    {
        "question": " 21.4年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.893437608500437
    },
    {
        "question": " 18.1億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.69492294033676
    },
    {
        "question": " 610万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.165494321707653
    },
    {
        "question": " 8936日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.109474996779371
    },
    {
        "question": " 90.8日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.894607442069171
    },
    {
        "question": " 1208万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.1394837016891266
    },
    {
        "question": " 53.8時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.35089130253957657
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.8万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.03340321666275
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.5時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.578856029171856
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.1億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.601596941828701
    },
    {
        "question": " 66.2万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6624045617706926
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.78万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7997908761458046
    },
    {
        "question": " 1578分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.976201710676059
    },
    {
        "question": " 1853分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.04608992962489
    },
    {
        "question": " 2133億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.8302643449232807
    },
    {
        "question": " 115億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.1245664401279996
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.57億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.854336789554308
    },
    {
        "question": " 290万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.684586878106213
    },
    {
        "question": " 77.7秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.890145047190265
    },
    {
        "question": " 3971秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.598845613363574
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.82兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.761936557213537
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.04兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.0809631250868055
    },
    {
        "question": " 9473万msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.420165550676159
    },
    {
        "question": " 2660万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.64665409643029
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.05兆msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.020489971385594
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.27万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.721663320522147
    },
    {
        "question": " 572msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 8.757432840749532
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.68京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.386579180480153
    },
    {
        "question": " 2996億usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5400605815515991
    },
    {
        "question": " 160兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.6474685825789885
    },
    {
        "question": " 25.6兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.6303784477698695
    },
    {
        "question": " 2779兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.44384236216304
    },
    {
        "question": " 7632usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 0.8826173750349886
    },
    {
        "question": " 997万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.998750853848907
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.357e+04垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.423237677644673
    },
    {
        "question": " 185京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.331216472592024
    },
    {
        "question": " 7050京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.2919171109722045
    },
    {
        "question": " 2943京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.690662494148874
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.45兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.162768397581057
    },
    {
        "question": " 113兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.054379597337979
    },
    {
        "question": " 178億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.251503287360834
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.57年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.441436872897431
    },
    {
        "question": " 7716万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.32510221741345
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.66万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.203770330887336
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.07日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.941827771649077
    },
    {
        "question": " 498万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7545738622083227
    },
    {
        "question": " 2717時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.0539074167804836
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.73時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6661974863920426
    },
    {
        "question": " 57.9万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.04196867116935121
    },
    {
        "question": " 305万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.325708287411846
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.73億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.657580539839909
    },
    {
        "question": " 2015万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.082332654906772
    },
    {
        "question": " 11分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.818480718620103
    },
    {
        "question": " 1627兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.712523577986983
    },
    {
        "question": " 2555億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.470928660459908
    },
    {
        "question": " 4948秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.13815198563431275
    },
    {
        "question": " 241億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.604461675865648
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.04万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.310230964558747
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.8秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.0344956809721015
    },
    {
        "question": " 4371京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.14180705284147
    },
    {
        "question": " 9兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.0178791605958315
    },
    {
        "question": " 111兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.488500424087135
    },
    {
        "question": " 9560万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.2023301064732976
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.35兆msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.130082937942571
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.86万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.836240326315674
    },
    {
        "question": " 2056msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.313117310832553
    },
    {
        "question": " 800兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4041746151226175
    },
    {
        "question": " 7180京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.919646257431118
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.6兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.6375710345009384
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.46億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1493900621351416
    },
    {
        "question": " 121億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.081144048046539
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.97兆usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.472945530141942
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.7京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5291651583902834
    },
    {
        "question": " 5284兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7865012714350281
    },
    {
        "question": " 127京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.548939013670667
    },
    {
        "question": " 197兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.517045494730706
    },
    {
        "question": " 443京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.646807702191595
    },
    {
        "question": " 712兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.852704552934293
    },
    {
        "question": " 3573nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 0.5530762472873796
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.94万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.230958422034497
    },
    {
        "question": " 3123年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.215187639619437
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.3万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.449947287816636
    },
    {
        "question": " 119日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.4562108527396616
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.01日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.160960989989483
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.53万日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.67934027842108
    },
    {
        "question": " 683億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.891745444162163
    },
    {
        "question": " 8886万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.568490842964962
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.12時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8267924578570327
    },
    {
        "question": " 23.4時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.924756994122687
    },
    {
        "question": " 28.7兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.737175888225396
    },
    {
        "question": " 730万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.7052680728232126
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.25万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.574839903437769
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.31億分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.894572302749733
    },
    {
        "question": " 89.1分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.727967463060022
    },
    {
        "question": " 20.7兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.817948900000692
    },
    {
        "question": " 47.9万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7435310169582854
    },
    {
        "question": " 2431万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.8294132271283257
    },
    {
        "question": " 1420億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.37428068181435
    },
    {
        "question": " 501秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.700221154788134
    },
    {
        "question": " 6813億msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3345099038956942
    },
    {
        "question": " 267兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.490199547000647
    },
    {
        "question": " 138兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.584649819132004
    },
    {
        "question": " 322億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.729894127120887
    },
    {
        "question": " 4000億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.602103425171554
    },
    {
        "question": " 24.9京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.8968049742822384
    },
    {
        "question": " 84.7京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.991567113859815
    },
    {
        "question": " 47.6億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.12100799117313987
    },
    {
        "question": " 5438億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.957325259459974
    },
    {
        "question": " 1824億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.260975723029244
    },
    {
        "question": " 326万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.5133328211786763
    },
    {
        "question": " 564usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 5.751012718838831
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.048e+05垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.985202444162168
    },
    {
        "question": " 54.3京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.798454111560039
    },
    {
        "question": " 1563京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.6377794994045844
    },
    {
        "question": " 2174兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.559165112005191
    },
    {
        "question": " 125兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.0977478080684
    },
    {
        "question": " 104億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.016890474118315
    },
    {
        "question": " 2677億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.427638149157426
    },
    {
        "question": " 662年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.382874744656917
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.14万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.272310269373
    },
    {
        "question": " 872年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.66127894827439
    },
    {
        "question": " 1054万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.460493890484417
    },
    {
        "question": " 181万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.63873485653299
    },
    {
        "question": " 19.4万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.445487669990925
    },
    {
        "question": " 744日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.808213369996739
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.32万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.17865426748980617
    },
    {
        "question": " 1349時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7498264242679917
    },
    {
        "question": " 1669万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.000696176904578
    },
    {
        "question": " 3624時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.115521459873406
    },
    {
        "question": " 2時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.856608653880631
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.25時間は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.65360218768324
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.43億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.087701423277701
    },
    {
        "question": " 3772分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.4182400602549208
    },
    {
        "question": " 1086分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2577525486730223
    },
    {
        "question": " 17分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.0086862707996485
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.5億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1544628026882242
    },
    {
        "question": " 709兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.913925658481023
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.1万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2947505911906243
    },
    {
        "question": " 356億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.772832948132917
    },
    {
        "question": " 213秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.329390045802521
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.99秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.475273519444152
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.94秒は何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.596009824132391
    },
    {
        "question": " 2894億msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9627052631771327
    },
    {
        "question": " 45.1億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7178032044965719
    },
    {
        "question": " 3567億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.996009786576536
    },
    {
        "question": " 1384万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.362932447953734
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.65億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.217296774568013
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.09垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.820733077439527
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.79京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.642383549701854
    },
    {
        "question": " 5437兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.179083058428531
    },
    {
        "question": " 3037億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.704342037800956
    },
    {
        "question": " 2200億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.342355821734466
    },
    {
        "question": " 40.8万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 2.610712418971002
    },
    {
        "question": " 4689usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.671060546996794
    },
    {
        "question": " 197京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7960104020834844
    },
    {
        "question": " 122兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.14809386476335118
    },
    {
        "question": " 111兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4886730591461295
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.54京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.770917623098634
    },
    {
        "question": " 215億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3319844591223495
    },
    {
        "question": " 141億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.150624612274408
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.07億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 5.609488445078647
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.2万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.640987070274251
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.86万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.778920248950243
    },
    {
        "question": " 8238年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.636476206411318
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.47年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.149047043209135
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.72万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6729572128125592
    },
    {
        "question": " 1883万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.655044280712998
    },
    {
        "question": " 33.2日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.679386752870583
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.18万日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.849364584143174
    },
    {
        "question": " 499億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.755903560041084
    },
    {
        "question": " 1969時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9140413121175082
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.01時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5569156005467453
    },
    {
        "question": " 38.1時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.137704851415546
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.3億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.4025180735294525
    },
    {
        "question": " 4763億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.519544517078101
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.29億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.582147531958115
    },
    {
        "question": " 111万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.823135275711117
    },
    {
        "question": " 2415兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.884025311796433
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.6億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.227351946108682
    },
    {
        "question": " 128億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.551617166106486
    },
    {
        "question": " 307万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.709013236095062
    },
    {
        "question": " 195万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.289968721357388
    },
    {
        "question": " 40兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.1030898197077637
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.8京msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.170934044378141
    },
    {
        "question": " 187兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.7156076155142
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.74億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.659834614568278
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.33万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1244864730493653
    },
    {
        "question": " 575msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 8.75958369438493
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.8京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.672815749741284
    },
    {
        "question": " 414京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.680943110164322
    },
    {
        "question": " 449億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0954806615499835
    },
    {
        "question": " 4559兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.880748855464069
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.49兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.396252996787174
    },
    {
        "question": " 2400万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.3802158844198145
    },
    {
        "question": " 221usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 5.344124740406837
    },
    {
        "question": " 6237垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.296168816522348
    },
    {
        "question": " 595垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.83789251631937
    },
    {
        "question": " 79.3垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.34279320796368
    },
    {
        "question": " 1794京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.475747568412814
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.6兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.245531672772187
    },
    {
        "question": " 64.8兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.811772324340741
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.64万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 1.4220237325139196
    },
    {
        "question": " 3157年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.21997706660894
    },
    {
        "question": " 3734日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0098482241530549
    },
    {
        "question": " 337万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.907482595011977
    },
    {
        "question": " 851万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9872152717333678
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.91万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.901202968875609
    },
    {
        "question": " 27.4万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.215209745969946
    },
    {
        "question": " 5390時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.28789794816892
    },
    {
        "question": " 144兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.438508801357015
    },
    {
        "question": " 57.3億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.600098643956621
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.07億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.249335324365008
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.11億分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.824256577351608
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.01分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.781023821695152
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.2兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.70936615358066
    },
    {
        "question": " 1兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.064571298740493
    },
    {
        "question": " 2591万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.8571602058246746
    },
    {
        "question": " 3115万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.715255905773086
    },
    {
        "question": " 108万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.032907562034515
    },
    {
        "question": " 62.7秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.797421157538677
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.67秒は何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.426160251243722
    },
    {
        "question": " 8996京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.455237714891677
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.38兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.931823677378745
    },
    {
        "question": " 187兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.715770082680268
    },
    {
        "question": " 59.3兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.995119734527194
    },
    {
        "question": " 4394万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.642841875221643
    },
    {
        "question": " 288msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 5.458761793833448
    },
    {
        "question": " 30.3msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 7.481934216712122
    },
    {
        "question": " 181垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.757936786150886
    },
    {
        "question": " 111京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.106943748228271
    },
    {
        "question": " 116億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5086759161881016
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.54兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.408272463799431
    },
    {
        "question": " 260万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.41473673225285945
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.31億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.117397015425099
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.8usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 3.579808434473594
    },
    {
        "question": " 2071垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.817415630727491
    },
    {
        "question": " 1077垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.095894728647108
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.8兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6132199402175276
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.09兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2598831894145668
    },
    {
        "question": " 2897億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4619129637225945
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.07億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 2.0312302750643116
    },
    {
        "question": " 294億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.467897413595519
    },
    {
        "question": " 1072万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.592513467279502
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.31万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.576944615935414
    },
    {
        "question": " 844億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.36424179376145
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.3日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.502587886503008
    },
    {
        "question": " 42.2万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.783816556981476
    },
    {
        "question": " 273日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.372403561119731
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.66億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.278778444521847
    },
    {
        "question": " 79.3時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5192858683720214
    },
    {
        "question": " 1189万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.853269218629356
    },
    {
        "question": " 283億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.731244795736834
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.74万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6700735509596376
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.03万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7035058030696666
    },
    {
        "question": " 1976万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.073869861671701
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.28分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.294486660207891
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.23分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.8684483377168
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.06億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5278275831165946
    },
    {
        "question": " 477億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.742455146645932
    },
    {
        "question": " 5765万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.204510662906022
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.53億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.405192109288768
    },
    {
        "question": " 22.6秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.354557686960612
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.81秒は何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.682144195652384
    },
    {
        "question": " 378京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.078958532422787
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.31京msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.58302026346694
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.21京msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.526088682348334
    },
    {
        "question": " 236兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.594736079843791
    },
    {
        "question": " 26.9万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.429240322130093
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.08msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 3.489033308300382
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.26垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.855638386832749
    },
    {
        "question": " 6611京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.883776039433823
    },
    {
        "question": " 951兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.421662154864858
    },
    {
        "question": " 1507兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.4000419050558675
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.68兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.754200442241908
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.41億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.7331710010552905
    },
    {
        "question": " 604usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 5.7810256626823335
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.23京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.36007030146659624
    },
    {
        "question": " 3297京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.581588485299449
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.97京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.0428622501413605
    },
    {
        "question": " 346京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.760552050269521
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.33兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.5218435803987145
    },
    {
        "question": " 444万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 0.6477050945374885
    },
    {
        "question": " 846億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.927510707781443
    },
    {
        "question": " 268年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.3709446135438625
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.52年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.902916995696316
    },
    {
        "question": " 1326万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.560265860754926
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.12万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.289883447061049
    },
    {
        "question": " 5711日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.6932290479159
    },
    {
        "question": " 179億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.30993148299837
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.33万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9871698959179427
    },
    {
        "question": " 22.6万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.910929615944607
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.8時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.7273774345145485
    },
    {
        "question": " 15兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.456870545262932
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.95万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3112441597363333
    },
    {
        "question": " 108万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.253281237836789
    },
    {
        "question": " 204万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.087410317958103
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.7分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.604340956383393
    },
    {
        "question": " 629億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.2996694700900973
    },
    {
        "question": " 226兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.417066278446327
    },
    {
        "question": " 3904秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.035251525081332336
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.26億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.575016151660598
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.22万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.086064262068115
    },
    {
        "question": " 43.4秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.637196837834979
    },
    {
        "question": " 387京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.089293532017301
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.54億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.24991283627750605
    },
    {
        "question": " 395兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.040530215978542
    },
    {
        "question": " 285万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.677060286614509
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.56兆msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.408743766759187
    },
    {
        "question": " 481万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.682155227317564
    },
    {
        "question": " 1742兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7421563256852346
    },
    {
        "question": " 2825京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.514503920714189
    },
    {
        "question": " 224億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7943963282914224
    },
    {
        "question": " 9735万usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.21017951731730822
    },
    {
        "question": " 29.1億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.463718901078414
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.57億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.409582209130247
    },
    {
        "question": " 92.2京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4659601468612893
    },
    {
        "question": " 9781京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.053863193717549
    },
    {
        "question": " 816兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.355595195714264
    },
    {
        "question": " 568兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.976043119348293
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.81兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.764120920442572
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.08億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 2.907464172177918
    },
    {
        "question": " 179億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.25173570454259
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.89年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.997129974243495
    },
    {
        "question": " 59.3万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.2104539048838046
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.85日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6465591756507758
    },
    {
        "question": " 9340日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.1286861535785935
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.48日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.477734670732004
    },
    {
        "question": " 216億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.392643689052541
    },
    {
        "question": " 317億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.121476166803523
    },
    {
        "question": " 170万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.009149493445094
    },
    {
        "question": " 34.2万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.090911363113408
    },
    {
        "question": " 1788兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.531697745985737
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.3億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.99560014032935
    },
    {
        "question": " 45万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.8748379865228055
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.59万分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.658604041201658
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.74京秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.177418040245685
    },
    {
        "question": " 587兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.832250187655177
    },
    {
        "question": " 821億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.358186465533999
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.2億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.937640378485527
    },
    {
        "question": " 5702秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.75605869504324
    },
    {
        "question": " 56.3京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.25136638064889
    },
    {
        "question": " 2045兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.37415726572487
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.73京msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.681487907150816
    },
    {
        "question": " 112億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.272785469303498
    },
    {
        "question": " 369億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.56669273410855
    },
    {
        "question": " 8525msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.930681497730134
    },
    {
        "question": " 295msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 8.46973350096256
    },
    {
        "question": " 1642兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7164560162705167
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.17京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.3994734432347755
    },
    {
        "question": " 1153兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.505408279570515
    },
    {
        "question": " 19.5京usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.51098729157445
    },
    {
        "question": " 9501兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.97776617369264
    },
    {
        "question": " 3805億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.580396182807942
    },
    {
        "question": " 71.3usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 4.852844450688955
    },
    {
        "question": " 20.3垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.807864155166798
    },
    {
        "question": " 68垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.896012212182431
    },
    {
        "question": " 108垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.475394234939314
    },
    {
        "question": " 88.9兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.1708302653388696
    },
    {
        "question": " 3026兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.4808761350922826
    },
    {
        "question": " 1056兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.023537303042504
    },
    {
        "question": " 833万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 3.920396953328107
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.1万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.681228311637457
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.2年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.769626527460063
    },
    {
        "question": " 107億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.468272251013874
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.32万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.9014364503156305
    },
    {
        "question": " 97.3万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.146546123634035
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.71万日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.169889378256949
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.33万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7845571579179234
    },
    {
        "question": " 211万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.943535119564278
    },
    {
        "question": " 1600万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.982191993474125
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.18時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.894368875666542
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.93兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.565533869261303
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.94万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.741592236202848
    },
    {
        "question": " 567億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.97570644178155
    },
    {
        "question": " 169分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.0071717283065675
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.73兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.739293666408457
    },
    {
        "question": " 223兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.410879886832374
    },
    {
        "question": " 3090億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.933712737437219
    },
    {
        "question": " 2191万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.5625640759028805
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.25万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.096104634955571
    },
    {
        "question": " 1696億msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7305053068921963
    },
    {
        "question": " 679億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.895200554792907
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.04億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4603510900386385
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.99万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.22161149941810399
    },
    {
        "question": " 1133msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.05427125925111409
    },
    {
        "question": " 296万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.470809991664808
    },
    {
        "question": " 28.6垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.957171559404318
    },
    {
        "question": " 1095億usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.10278817111054384
    },
    {
        "question": " 2625兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.862777127500237
    },
    {
        "question": " 2118兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.547798785428029
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.69兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.566876949934072
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.49兆usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.17405865711803
    },
    {
        "question": " 105京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.520523086058062
    },
    {
        "question": " 30.4京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.5457835879859614
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.92兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.3424998365020948
    },
    {
        "question": " 63.6京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.025399777734985
    },
    {
        "question": " 56.9京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.75524510650383
    },
    {
        "question": " 530億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.724527376368465
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.1万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 1.0411447196328716
    },
    {
        "question": " 383年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.144994555195773
    },
    {
        "question": " 40.1年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.545860299645145
    },
    {
        "question": " 53億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.162265439789296
    },
    {
        "question": " 577日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.141441012379683
    },
    {
        "question": " 25.3万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4601547502274559
    },
    {
        "question": " 168億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.84477689626952
    },
    {
        "question": " 26.9万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.207510089003665
    },
    {
        "question": " 126万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.655576640564425
    },
    {
        "question": " 1067時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.584307283895974
    },
    {
        "question": " 2129万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6075235777363472
    },
    {
        "question": " 34.1億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.374589604888341
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.04万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.1272275468496478
    },
    {
        "question": " 978分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.768620469231763
    },
    {
        "question": " 1567億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.696283292887851
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.73億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.951916733606895
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.61億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.378486182796519
    },
    {
        "question": " 1976億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.51754690297871
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.15秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.7115357675267244
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.3兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.686252076851945
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.75兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.5034763521624495
    },
    {
        "question": " 188億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.717369482682301
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.68億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.1605860976135105
    },
    {
        "question": " 8336msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9209417735697201
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.3万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.799562859173862
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.6垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.52763485765673
    },
    {
        "question": " 1239京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.15656284862619
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.3京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.9625044979009
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.95億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.063631181736202
    },
    {
        "question": " 6725億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.827693706908517
    },
    {
        "question": " 2578usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 0.41129377040509896
    },
    {
        "question": " 893万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.950685707450594
    },
    {
        "question": " 649垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.3132795108310695
    },
    {
        "question": " 952兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.041924003193473
    },
    {
        "question": " 258兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8549440652730054
    },
    {
        "question": " 45京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.875490091528498
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.98京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.474395914068125
    },
    {
        "question": " 21.8億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.337833983429767
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.84億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 5.946498444366361
    },
    {
        "question": " 4226年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.188229287269875
    },
    {
        "question": " 355年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.493294448757309
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.89年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.775034270713542
    },
    {
        "question": " 26.8万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.865435924834502
    },
    {
        "question": " 1509万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.558888630994128
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.73日は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.17511527739648
    },
    {
        "question": " 5853億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.824885592535126
    },
    {
        "question": " 327万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.134929295005385
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.01万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.561726910165771
    },
    {
        "question": " 55兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.019650812360913
    },
    {
        "question": " 156万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.0355202682586313
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.29万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.0205313987785964
    },
    {
        "question": " 1119兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.550006935551339
    },
    {
        "question": " 7397万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9325404846330336
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.5万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6856392285608002
    },
    {
        "question": " 363秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7822308630543517
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.47秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.1671522580068787
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.25垓msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.598077248331883
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.76兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.309821163057091
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.02兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.451006798381824
    },
    {
        "question": " 151億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.400974306027587
    },
    {
        "question": " 3394万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.53068541587689
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.7垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.637428552347172
    },
    {
        "question": " 2368億usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.4378125975507918
    },
    {
        "question": " 41.9億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.06598279921738892
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.52兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.9640113076223225
    },
    {
        "question": " 505億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.703356468752503
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.49万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.1724155432545047
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.123e+04垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.828202576187932
    },
    {
        "question": " 158京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.261873665167717
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.79垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.335475046812629
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.3兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2359133161895706
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.75兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.759340807660897
    },
    {
        "question": " 68.8兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.837757811460264
    },
    {
        "question": " 933億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.969883101537488
    },
    {
        "question": " 636万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.36565880477399
    },
    {
        "question": " 5202年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.658638373543401
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.42万年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.871901514416745
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.33億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.805598216335415
    },
    {
        "question": " 5836万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.14628245535724
    },
    {
        "question": " 3日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.6355095827380826
    },
    {
        "question": " 784日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.830833569848342
    },
    {
        "question": " 5327万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.7839509095732318
    },
    {
        "question": " 131時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7356492951809313
    },
    {
        "question": " 39.4時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.1518678076675
    },
    {
        "question": " 6806億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.11222472174952
    },
    {
        "question": " 20.3億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.149255814806899
    },
    {
        "question": " 9736分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.210235492224941
    },
    {
        "question": " 1727分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.015325768919253
    },
    {
        "question": " 289分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.239724101736927
    },
    {
        "question": " 214億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8319300969385863
    },
    {
        "question": " 19.2億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.347545588999829
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.9兆秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.695640652932973
    },
    {
        "question": " 4676万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.891702141390107
    },
    {
        "question": " 819秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.9131633563573605
    },
    {
        "question": " 431兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.136107531724199
    },
    {
        "question": " 18.5兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.331822330146721
    },
    {
        "question": " 5465万msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1813282761687782
    },
    {
        "question": " 320兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.727221496685463
    },
    {
        "question": " 361万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.557302763148167
    },
    {
        "question": " 3537msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.548576971992831
    },
    {
        "question": " 1021京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.510356532560181
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.8京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.234342856395692
    },
    {
        "question": " 231京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.806692379426387
    },
    {
        "question": " 8855兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.16904466748027
    },
    {
        "question": " 27.5億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.4395890986342192
    },
    {
        "question": " 9161億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.961958289505885
    },
    {
        "question": " 807垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.407818542506113
    },
    {
        "question": " 1108兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1079313294869475
    },
    {
        "question": " 77京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.330191290248499
    },
    {
        "question": " 4464兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.871593447693013
    },
    {
        "question": " 331億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5201763575743665
    },
    {
        "question": " 581万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 0.7641443168664541
    },
    {
        "question": " 22.1億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.344594894067903
    },
    {
        "question": " 35.7万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.495579907833257
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.54万年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.909317530369051
    },
    {
        "question": " 85.7億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.370889592922899
    },
    {
        "question": " 2172日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.717021356757791
    },
    {
        "question": " 46.8日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.828493041315807
    },
    {
        "question": " 4282日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.568190239078703
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.73兆時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.296367376839763
    },
    {
        "question": " 1038時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.636142576564713
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.43万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.163465011953595
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.39時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.287838584405078
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.16億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3426275116505115
    },
    {
        "question": " 53.3万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5685693646600583
    },
    {
        "question": " 91.2億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.181725444916557
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.7万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.80820824536697
    },
    {
        "question": " 159分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.979590244422237
    },
    {
        "question": " 635億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.303999443529322
    },
    {
        "question": " 12兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.1418927463606
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.3兆秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.30673459583372
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.39億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.365138971437756
    },
    {
        "question": " 5738兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.259922274444771
    },
    {
        "question": " 19兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.342735884638942
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.52億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.624892344325124
    },
    {
        "question": " 31.5兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.720683639136434
    },
    {
        "question": " 23.3万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3673407304748983
    },
    {
        "question": " 126京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.603236398797853
    },
    {
        "question": " 810兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.9719911535908325
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.47兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8357767832585457
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.4億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.347878678755996
    },
    {
        "question": " 1515万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1805143742858537
    },
    {
        "question": " 5949usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 0.7744319149257772
    },
    {
        "question": " 2684usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.428739643748186
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.04京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.2822175367873836
    },
    {
        "question": " 132京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.185387253124998
    },
    {
        "question": " 1090兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4809525587846593
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.03兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.126512808701807
    },
    {
        "question": " 61.7兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.790254957926586
    },
    {
        "question": " 19.3億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.2847498220117144
    },
    {
        "question": " 1806億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.256798886421908
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.42年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7146737505385743
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.94万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.537581075870891
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.3万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.452576528936228
    },
    {
        "question": " 1743万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.621433593065227
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.3億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.419620153687081
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.37億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.147937787013873
    },
    {
        "question": " 1567万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.973177276596502
    },
    {
        "question": " 39.4億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.875348744082671
    },
    {
        "question": " 1104万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.884740136503747
    },
    {
        "question": " 15億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.396601606508119
    },
    {
        "question": " 25.9万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.19179931895381
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.05兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.522783192503088
    },
    {
        "question": " 4740億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.739282688122149
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.14兆秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.94119806846435
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.08万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7104189571912105
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.82万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.449698597549951
    },
    {
        "question": " 2164京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.836508025959324
    },
    {
        "question": " 40.5兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.6706996151048275
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.65億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8672901356194982
    },
    {
        "question": " 21.4万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5519738056180379
    },
    {
        "question": " 1146msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.05935820657015367
    },
    {
        "question": " 37.1万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.569184030186461
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.6京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.0576189970029457
    },
    {
        "question": " 6585億usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8820630430109133
    },
    {
        "question": " 116京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.508959526665699
    },
    {
        "question": " 34.9億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.765184239201475
    },
    {
        "question": " 1269億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.1035330773508445
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.09億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.908000070401522
    },
    {
        "question": " 478万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.679868676584096
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.01垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.8041521772368228
    },
    {
        "question": " 89.7京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.016161500965324
    },
    {
        "question": " 86.5垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.380921480318019
    },
    {
        "question": " 2780兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.665829635994966
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.8兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.2246233379818365
    },
    {
        "question": " 7471万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.8733572235675189
    },
    {
        "question": " 65.1億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.813773186743308
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.11万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.0554605641090005
    },
    {
        "question": " 552年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.684572789807791
    },
    {
        "question": " 6377日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2422956493255033
    },
    {
        "question": " 166日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.600965441275057
    },
    {
        "question": " 311億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.550791744173951
    },
    {
        "question": " 6812万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.453051192080376
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.4万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.993515235670065
    },
    {
        "question": " 190時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.834783055991273
    },
    {
        "question": " 257万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6894708804475769
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.4万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.0286064435381546
    },
    {
        "question": " 21.2億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.54862262294794
    },
    {
        "question": " 451分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.4322866167475885
    },
    {
        "question": " 819分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.691551705666813
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.59兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.701679824227954
    },
    {
        "question": " 1260億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.163755802476709
    },
    {
        "question": " 76.4億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.326920009498593
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.13万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.273633927592833
    },
    {
        "question": " 1660秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.220235417634722
    },
    {
        "question": " 61.6兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.2904851618578723
    },
    {
        "question": " 106兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.0869437807509605
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.5億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.604916469519779
    },
    {
        "question": " 2989万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.697323521612709
    },
    {
        "question": " 606万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.782608847832516
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.09msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 3.489346147581096
    },
    {
        "question": " 829兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4198420548363055
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.15垓usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.396578301909226
    },
    {
        "question": " 293京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.911176270320668
    },
    {
        "question": " 41.5億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8403809647700953
    },
    {
        "question": " 4835万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6843999402389709
    },
    {
        "question": " 23.5万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 2.37063142213347
    },
    {
        "question": " 40.2万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 8.604118663969167
    },
    {
        "question": " 1958垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.793077715000578
    },
    {
        "question": " 146兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.22838226304517262
    },
    {
        "question": " 54.9京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.183659606268652
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.24京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.187737154906646
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.18京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.790676996038316
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.72兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.23570797560827
    },
    {
        "question": " 1642nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 0.21542223393718585
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.7万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.700319419196991
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.67万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.766533537329176
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.84年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.48677892532083
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.87万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3854678220458245
    },
    {
        "question": " 39.1万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.972600846401256
    },
    {
        "question": " 893万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.0084520941485735
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.15万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.952858884256001
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.23万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.496721075147751
    },
    {
        "question": " 828時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.474350280144864
    },
    {
        "question": " 106兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.303462625046153
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.83兆分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.607049552143028
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.34万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.143194372353495
    },
    {
        "question": " 105分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.7981799951030446
    },
    {
        "question": " 143分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.9344278976225215
    },
    {
        "question": " 663兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.322417730914909
    },
    {
        "question": " 119億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.137804507707267
    },
    {
        "question": " 3284億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.960116460039019
    },
    {
        "question": " 606万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.00441107581504
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.42秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.151195924832048
    },
    {
        "question": " 392秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.593011544768148
    },
    {
        "question": " 2300兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.862840768021162
    },
    {
        "question": " 77.4兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.952190933966009
    },
    {
        "question": " 21.6兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.779103086056969
    },
    {
        "question": " 83.9億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.14560449874867
    },
    {
        "question": " 2285億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.358870688020502
    },
    {
        "question": " 1401msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.14636232466868
    },
    {
        "question": " 6088msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.784485212741162
    },
    {
        "question": " 1452垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.663072522446761
    },
    {
        "question": " 1499億usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.23917566712706284
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.11京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.9366497620657
    },
    {
        "question": " 34.4億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7582380879518267
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.77兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.247162054143908
    },
    {
        "question": " 34.1万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 2.5325073977291224
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.3万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 8.05379211106224
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.493e+05垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.67515939824579
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.82京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8281395434434264
    },
    {
        "question": " 197兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7372448307080124
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.93垓nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.81580149839052
    },
    {
        "question": " 348兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.5413141490532976
    },
    {
        "question": " 1242億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.093990044472845
    },
    {
        "question": " 836万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 3.922084690122217
    },
    {
        "question": " 2352万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.933689408026646
    },
    {
        "question": " 655年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.7584847709502585
    },
    {
        "question": " 51.6年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.211087241170432
    },
    {
        "question": " 547万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.175532451116675
    },
    {
        "question": " 7313日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.244294187585306
    },
    {
        "question": " 213億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.38516710117751
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.1万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.232064901263171
    },
    {
        "question": " 1891時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.054775525322787
    },
    {
        "question": " 27.2時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.99123863218764
    },
    {
        "question": " 1579時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.754778478476352
    },
    {
        "question": " 197億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.573856555861417
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.23万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4682266712315917
    },
    {
        "question": " 530分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9463449482121733
    },
    {
        "question": " 200万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.079480719484488
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.49分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.321111876385175
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.89兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.450100534410521
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.74億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.303668413078248
    },
    {
        "question": " 124億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.537438598681673
    },
    {
        "question": " 24.1億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.603510011426757
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.82秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.5821812702821143
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.63兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.166570249072447
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.94兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.659268113753142
    },
    {
        "question": " 1233兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.534766942710329
    },
    {
        "question": " 7784億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.113072280813341
    },
    {
        "question": " 159万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.200196616397805
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.38msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 3.3762031271930857
    },
    {
        "question": " 146msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 8.163401132874329
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.5垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.376020116500572
    },
    {
        "question": " 1141億usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.12072271571793691
    },
    {
        "question": " 1066億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4712899768443821
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.2京usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.343333450865487
    },
    {
        "question": " 68.1億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.832902928957388
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.18兆usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.501991614851534
    },
    {
        "question": " 619usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 5.791904746599626
    },
    {
        "question": " 2099垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.82326319196623
    },
    {
        "question": " 3359兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5897673298506088
    },
    {
        "question": " 4895兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.1334848969070936
    },
    {
        "question": " 4777兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.900995540393747
    },
    {
        "question": " 41.5億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6178730619947326
    },
    {
        "question": " 5884億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.76968356912725
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.84兆nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.685267650368843
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.31年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.426029470523021
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.95年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.539564937576306
    },
    {
        "question": " 2639万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.859180045130045
    },
    {
        "question": " 40.8日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.547591545210838
    },
    {
        "question": " 569万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8128368520887537
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.13億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.235682281701314
    },
    {
        "question": " 61.4万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.566433278760911
    },
    {
        "question": " 501時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.255782642305033
    },
    {
        "question": " 52.8億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.001836846015787
    },
    {
        "question": " 206万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.1550595580153673
    },
    {
        "question": " 636万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.025455655858204
    },
    {
        "question": " 315分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.276519569275749
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.2分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.986619160601306
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.13兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.116844753970663
    },
    {
        "question": " 244万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4504076089090945
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.2万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6245817220230774
    },
    {
        "question": " 3728億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.793286622373053
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.08秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.318917129832073
    },
    {
        "question": " 4108秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.613603970000305
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.67秒は何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.22282151317756
    },
    {
        "question": " 1086億msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5368457676972316
    },
    {
        "question": " 23.4兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.43351989671369
    },
    {
        "question": " 37.8億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.0206780437767513
    },
    {
        "question": " 23万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5838401718266462
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.59億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.818693162056363
    },
    {
        "question": " 77.6万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.889779106765577
    },
    {
        "question": " 5008msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.699683072213224
    },
    {
        "question": " 593京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.2745473801335985
    },
    {
        "question": " 7979兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.965456924017936
    },
    {
        "question": " 656京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.26044285600044
    },
    {
        "question": " 9556万usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.2021075014203133
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.5億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7403917958599564
    },
    {
        "question": " 12億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.080347333451472
    },
    {
        "question": " 2219usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.346086892268012
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.11e+04垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.5464425582247845
    },
    {
        "question": " 7415垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.933594901510158
    },
    {
        "question": " 239京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.821714274070015
    },
    {
        "question": " 2803億nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6695374973451462
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.58兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.197965429107615
    },
    {
        "question": " 58.3兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.76592799794555
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.72兆nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.434329657734272
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.85万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.528510691406721
    },
    {
        "question": " 673万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.2657889307435894
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.25億日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.732527800269766
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.02日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.166116646369016
    },
    {
        "question": " 21.9日は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.276061236756156
    },
    {
        "question": " 19.4億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.345993319488245
    },
    {
        "question": " 88.2時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5651687814286654
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.63万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.198261953408394
    },
    {
        "question": " 438時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.197735085801449
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.1兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.319206116775136
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.89兆分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.431552608175405
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.8億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.420523011562076
    },
    {
        "question": " 71.1万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.630143115298692
    },
    {
        "question": " 533分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.505014920195502
    },
    {
        "question": " 457兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.1614065840376275
    },
    {
        "question": " 45.5万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7218375930150767
    },
    {
        "question": " 259万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8568316748939306
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.1億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.30544028996884
    },
    {
        "question": " 32京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.00599316134107
    },
    {
        "question": " 878億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.0069761199410303
    },
    {
        "question": " 2534万msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8475061428848063
    },
    {
        "question": " 4341億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.859479136287016
    },
    {
        "question": " 19.4万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2882796260995244
    },
    {
        "question": " 479msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 8.680017015725653
    },
    {
        "question": " 44.6垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.150198977089989
    },
    {
        "question": " 142兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.2164801498672055
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.2京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.59564945499258
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.12億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9311105707834066
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.3兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.0914056816969975
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.3億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.799430188312745
    },
    {
        "question": " 2193京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.842266455264352
    },
    {
        "question": " 3301垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.582170121558738
    },
    {
        "question": " 1635京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.657165835066979
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.6京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.442463329394496
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.47京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.873573430403309
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.44兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.926598639971781
    },
    {
        "question": " 47.1万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 2.6726036456857525
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.46年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.5380063197158362
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.5年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.851856274623653
    },
    {
        "question": " 94.5億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.4131257012395215
    },
    {
        "question": " 325日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.8921674327307065
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.57万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.46808119807895454
    },
    {
        "question": " 573時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3776190585722048
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.74万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.606736284150511
    },
    {
        "question": " 1198時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.6348154143378535
    },
    {
        "question": " 31.6時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.056201370750658
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.14時間は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.613913048033677
    },
    {
        "question": " 1679万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5044514095724681
    },
    {
        "question": " 2555分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.2490876430895128
    },
    {
        "question": " 2817億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.671605373883573
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.79分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.458748613838009
    },
    {
        "question": " 408分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.389286089386386
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.8分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.94832989761363
    },
    {
        "question": " 8150億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.412335187732264
    },
    {
        "question": " 1164万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.129575327800958
    },
    {
        "question": " 19.5億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.732876367637054
    },
    {
        "question": " 7129万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.074860075202658
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.78秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.443927730851491
    },
    {
        "question": " 635兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.303996510505952
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.5億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3070326444479752
    },
    {
        "question": " 2167万msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7796178156051747
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.27兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.736141705659142
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.16億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.619372568038376
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.35万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.728586551569608
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.29msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.110372203578148
    },
    {
        "question": " 1013兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5068119345196052
    },
    {
        "question": " 4040京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.669876629349783
    },
    {
        "question": " 104兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.460717496108684
    },
    {
        "question": " 6211兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.015021403929026
    },
    {
        "question": " 380兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.579355055421688
    },
    {
        "question": " 18.5億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.266691428421122
    },
    {
        "question": " 142usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 5.151104312108848
    },
    {
        "question": " 362垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.060059939085507
    },
    {
        "question": " 103垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.076599276081577
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.8垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.276218020545675
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.76京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.111690582748331
    },
    {
        "question": " 2751億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.439546310961933
    },
    {
        "question": " 629兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.79860687131867
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.62億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 5.821008782681409
    },
    {
        "question": " 724年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.4220779091460845
    },
    {
        "question": " 49.8万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.63960447487835
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.04万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7474158040923549
    },
    {
        "question": " 1124日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.431139977314917
    },
    {
        "question": " 57.9万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.921270403401941
    },
    {
        "question": " 39.3日は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.530853386255085
    },
    {
        "question": " 3341万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.5813102870318616
    },
    {
        "question": " 1764万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.86627304665643
    },
    {
        "question": " 9893万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.773478845507043
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.57兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.2124004378104045
    },
    {
        "question": " 131億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.958951827108812
    },
    {
        "question": " 31.6万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.721820355372718
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.07万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.807631778759132
    },
    {
        "question": " 6734分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.606412338776313
    },
    {
        "question": " 779億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.392845295566568
    },
    {
        "question": " 22.4兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.413069946361757
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.52億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.185364483692187
    },
    {
        "question": " 3471万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.7622811828372535
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.53万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.815071423565137
    },
    {
        "question": " 164秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.2153114610234
    },
    {
        "question": " 30.6京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.987412059066603
    },
    {
        "question": " 60.6兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.8458619278393815
    },
    {
        "question": " 54.2億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.177315922207181
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.39兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.864377955589684
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.4万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6437329041659188
    },
    {
        "question": " 252万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.400855284016343
    },
    {
        "question": " 1047京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.521179049970017
    },
    {
        "question": " 266兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.488347748848739
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.95京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.913285927896129
    },
    {
        "question": " 9282万usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.1894699889747664
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.49兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.652152325288282
    },
    {
        "question": " 3073万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.4875716997665975
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.18京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.29195185504593546
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.49垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.605868990350486
    },
    {
        "question": " 3821京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.025883529305257
    },
    {
        "question": " 2442京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.609509354688257
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.58京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.199749301009588
    },
    {
        "question": " 283万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 0.4514383979136516
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.8億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.1390179064630885
    },
    {
        "question": " 1016万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.569020600360904
    },
    {
        "question": " 9686年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.706788204063889
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.9年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.751897658508227
    },
    {
        "question": " 82.4万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.3534079662903227
    },
    {
        "question": " 45.8万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.040699834272466
    },
    {
        "question": " 168日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.382432221012589
    },
    {
        "question": " 225万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4090220459601905
    },
    {
        "question": " 1147時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6794558244265523
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.9万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.922419214146654
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.66万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.493571040238757
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.48兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.672938095841867
    },
    {
        "question": " 49.8億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.538839369729757
    },
    {
        "question": " 403億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.826800578873767
    },
    {
        "question": " 52.3分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.496295703037837
    },
    {
        "question": " 319億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.004742723773528
    },
    {
        "question": " 10万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.06408983779682909
    },
    {
        "question": " 83.5億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.365336021338001
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.59万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6350229458496877
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.3秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.013880921874627
    },
    {
        "question": " 6552億msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3175821120807296
    },
    {
        "question": " 50.8億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7691412616145297
    },
    {
        "question": " 137億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.580986275336928
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.28億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.5788760212687567
    },
    {
        "question": " 47万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6720276930407714
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.72万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.2366554926065305
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.7msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 7.166971590599244
    },
    {
        "question": " 25京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.8982707461389667
    },
    {
        "question": " 9713兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.050836608570277
    },
    {
        "question": " 90兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.398096335411974
    },
    {
        "question": " 312億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.716261626616465
    },
    {
        "question": " 55.3兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.742874296131515
    },
    {
        "question": " 65.2万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 2.814365527127889
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.72usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 3.2345134526626818
    },
    {
        "question": " 18.1京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7582500794125591
    },
    {
        "question": " 6599兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8829881024067063
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.21兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.23686493574405998
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.8垓nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.668584301614839
    },
    {
        "question": " 852億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9305052158828495
    },
    {
        "question": " 3087兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.489524719054256
    },
    {
        "question": " 34.7億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.540085490367177
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.02万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.166972379639276
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.19万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.657591328886772
    },
    {
        "question": " 2997年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.197387846686567
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.23年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.464058364360058
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.7万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6674400007380896
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.2日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.427999922169053
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.37万日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.312158528970025
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.4億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.298984604430878
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.09億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.658323548260602
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.26時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.291085485903791
    },
    {
        "question": " 253時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.958614023841093
    },
    {
        "question": " 217兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.61532954608521
    },
    {
        "question": " 29万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.303424758739545
    },
    {
        "question": " 3518万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.768175675476414
    },
    {
        "question": " 7027万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.624914391336338
    },
    {
        "question": " 58.9分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.547898433463687
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.72億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7379023669608942
    },
    {
        "question": " 2885万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5236895913363497
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.91万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4399644198863504
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.01億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.2279853182106475
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.9秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.174102800259463
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.04秒は何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.017112387499322
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.24京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.8513625103117874
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.88億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9600720350985603
    },
    {
        "question": " 804兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.348918873552623
    },
    {
        "question": " 133万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3456233250231797
    },
    {
        "question": " 138万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.141236813938363
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.07msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.906713712959887
    },
    {
        "question": " 62.5京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.296912012863492
    },
    {
        "question": " 208兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.381801383651817
    },
    {
        "question": " 92.8兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.411357172300586
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.53億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7696272227527812
    },
    {
        "question": " 480億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.681549072746983
    },
    {
        "question": " 3993億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.601290041594655
    },
    {
        "question": " 166usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 5.220386440478212
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.6京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5649782012740656
    },
    {
        "question": " 920京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.027382067105632
    },
    {
        "question": " 213兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7725282099324524
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.7兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3260103354782915
    },
    {
        "question": " 5132億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7103257714379225
    },
    {
        "question": " 512兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.70939887538565
    },
    {
        "question": " 1601万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.2044655487644
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.8万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.142534298467705
    },
    {
        "question": " 350年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.486986598228189
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.06年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.522142566268185
    },
    {
        "question": " 17億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.667493683472069
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.78日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6300234551625192
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.3日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.661130993216358
    },
    {
        "question": " 19.1日は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.217680190602579
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.9兆時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.896544714423015
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.31万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.419874528920106
    },
    {
        "question": " 5992万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.55574245259282
    },
    {
        "question": " 1930億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.564807032629461
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.31万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7610431818193417
    },
    {
        "question": " 53.5万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.9500652392822055
    },
    {
        "question": " 143万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.9328126195469455
    },
    {
        "question": " 5357分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.507078527478212
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.21兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.846337518080497
    },
    {
        "question": " 7931億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.9628525869013345
    },
    {
        "question": " 5万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.142787615868226
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.33億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.858217420409186
    },
    {
        "question": " 125兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.5974235737091798
    },
    {
        "question": " 2627億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.482995922261601
    },
    {
        "question": " 1664億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.6648512586141955
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.37兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.144828850182698
    },
    {
        "question": " 171億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.23319851896701
    },
    {
        "question": " 54.7msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.73785961286822
    },
    {
        "question": " 4403msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.643794996616654
    },
    {
        "question": " 958京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.482459776377739
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.81京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.827642284638433
    },
    {
        "question": " 64.1億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.25054919754788796
    },
    {
        "question": " 22.5京usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.573865931530761
    },
    {
        "question": " 7443億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.871751605770122
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.46万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.1635716381137662
    },
    {
        "question": " 103垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.515791175929485
    },
    {
        "question": " 111兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.1069582221857579
    },
    {
        "question": " 226兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7975669602083366
    },
    {
        "question": " 336兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.7482851061619646
    },
    {
        "question": " 6244億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.79545898116789
    },
    {
        "question": " 8359万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.922173789134144
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.08兆nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.850282485388558
    },
    {
        "question": " 194年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.230256299962715
    },
    {
        "question": " 232年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.086440965897214
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.4万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.453674786221928
    },
    {
        "question": " 398万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.979892010952615
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.19日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.015162185062718
    },
    {
        "question": " 7621日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.818500601080373
    },
    {
        "question": " 59.3万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8306793617410289
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.5億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.680006713460893
    },
    {
        "question": " 105万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.799641385077871
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.68万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.310317828615394
    },
    {
        "question": " 258兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.691099395544253
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.37億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.571946021050056
    },
    {
        "question": " 3177万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.723806352265318
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.53分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4339508717078906
    },
    {
        "question": " 28.5分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.233342081326125
    },
    {
        "question": " 198兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.797317703196521
    },
    {
        "question": " 18.1万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.3220985694723377
    },
    {
        "question": " 1387億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.585722765596118
    },
    {
        "question": " 1613億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.429611944262023
    },
    {
        "question": " 22.5万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.352470641502446
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.7兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.487764091916571
    },
    {
        "question": " 1392億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.2070576014553676
    },
    {
        "question": " 228億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.8014941239233946
    },
    {
        "question": " 2248万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.573638471558307
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.42兆msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.383309179162492
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.8万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.19986249159317
    },
    {
        "question": " 719京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.357874703637147
    },
    {
        "question": " 1435億usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.2204658133751436
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.21京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.788543144684605
    },
    {
        "question": " 367兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.78596766592154
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.23兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.089668798667187
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.31億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.634410921336364
    },
    {
        "question": " 3996usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.60162803882586
    },
    {
        "question": " 110京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5411728445929151
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.47垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.604345742047801
    },
    {
        "question": " 335垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.96863873822224
    },
    {
        "question": " 153京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.406447445927018
    },
    {
        "question": " 94.7億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9765090949491928
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.5億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.0225105790047024
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.27万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 1.102503191695089
    },
    {
        "question": " 548年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.300708164588524
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.02万年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.730810331753823
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.73億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.676564685846693
    },
    {
        "question": " 33.7万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.907380144623341
    },
    {
        "question": " 3877日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.746844941807209
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.51日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.336601657888156
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.08兆時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.546378507719218
    },
    {
        "question": " 333時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.142416290699716
    },
    {
        "question": " 1916万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.060514637403521
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.01万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.034192849345828
    },
    {
        "question": " 427兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.90931255213997
    },
    {
        "question": " 7435億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.712920366005587
    },
    {
        "question": " 641億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.028832268652225
    },
    {
        "question": " 698万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.621977596676594
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.91分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.0593517684797344
    },
    {
        "question": " 1088億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.5377639880070353
    },
    {
        "question": " 605億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.845391141490968
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.11兆秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.295605560060773
    },
    {
        "question": " 193万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.508233220363749
    },
    {
        "question": " 74.9万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.874192250118929
    },
    {
        "question": " 70.4秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.847392814369983
    },
    {
        "question": " 5711兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.257911553928734
    },
    {
        "question": " 1182兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.136094601137131
    },
    {
        "question": " 879億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.3875500643019265
    },
    {
        "question": " 865万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1588059183724138
    },
    {
        "question": " 3759万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.575058053411013
    },
    {
        "question": " 1830京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.763544291124637
    },
    {
        "question": " 2375京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.439211401948405
    },
    {
        "question": " 9033億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.39954105553473
    },
    {
        "question": " 164兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.4366951099437255
    },
    {
        "question": " 1085万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.035255982112827
    },
    {
        "question": " 184万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.2646893325278548
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.13usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 3.8530628909656404
    },
    {
        "question": " 4162垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.120475607808129
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.46京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4545507065711822
    },
    {
        "question": " 29兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9058339238766333
    },
    {
        "question": " 74.1兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.091596237797801
    },
    {
        "question": " 261億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4162434205168417
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.8兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.169673954440126
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.71兆nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.433653232065044
    },
    {
        "question": " 1202億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.517579261038934
    },
    {
        "question": " 41.7万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.000464657660114
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.24日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.074016459257973
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.61日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.1430145816114194
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.9日は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.080038216900427
    },
    {
        "question": " 40.1万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6602929720604565
    },
    {
        "question": " 38時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.19991833531353476
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.77万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.0265093269990455
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.87時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.143769509211804
    },
    {
        "question": " 286万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7354117618070943
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.73兆分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.413147834557424
    },
    {
        "question": " 19.5万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.5125004643431215
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.87分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2355802590644123
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.45万分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.315456057673469
    },
    {
        "question": " 174兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.741088423644559
    },
    {
        "question": " 4041万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.670015100519456
    },
    {
        "question": " 89.7億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.3966091693020495
    },
    {
        "question": " 1618万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.430782815914538
    },
    {
        "question": " 524秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.719408744739281
    },
    {
        "question": " 312秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.494440888800739
    },
    {
        "question": " 4173兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.121665644271238
    },
    {
        "question": " 1077億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.0958664661906177
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.98億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9184805949255568
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.45億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.19741157172825
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.74億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.941731345883664
    },
    {
        "question": " 171msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 5.233985544732258
    },
    {
        "question": " 20.4垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.811370260126253
    },
    {
        "question": " 27.3兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4996848567901395
    },
    {
        "question": " 153兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.628805277423407
    },
    {
        "question": " 34.9億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7646330053626524
    },
    {
        "question": " 19.3兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.285411670650399
    },
    {
        "question": " 78億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.8918735040827315
    },
    {
        "question": " 170usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 5.231411492546497
    },
    {
        "question": " 1384京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6422020374217903
    },
    {
        "question": " 650京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.876451757359318
    },
    {
        "question": " 51.7垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.156952532711255
    },
    {
        "question": " 5445兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.957813507878349
    },
    {
        "question": " 7925兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.898989833206274
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.14兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.49689630255504
    },
    {
        "question": " 9828nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 0.9924646913239277
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.3年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.4812292950243986
    },
    {
        "question": " 34.6年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.481718743212206
    },
    {
        "question": " 2740年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.158452490437526
    },
    {
        "question": " 509億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.144102995227145
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.86万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.837123645795296
    },
    {
        "question": " 171万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.391556314570872
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.16日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.435669806439433
    },
    {
        "question": " 190億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.337103419902718
    },
    {
        "question": " 704万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.4672532532641345
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.56時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.434790537050807
    },
    {
        "question": " 28.7兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.73791087392826
    },
    {
        "question": " 1749分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.08451416750684282
    },
    {
        "question": " 9370分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.193598200012347
    },
    {
        "question": " 29.1分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.2415052235170005
    },
    {
        "question": " 6693分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.60374374994702
    },
    {
        "question": " 96.4分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.762166519645794
    },
    {
        "question": " 243兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.887151314132484
    },
    {
        "question": " 483億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.747146250312766
    },
    {
        "question": " 29.9億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.9188937062677915
    },
    {
        "question": " 6178秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.0126852408229254
    },
    {
        "question": " 43秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.6336348842348505
    },
    {
        "question": " 2秒は何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.300522402632836
    },
    {
        "question": " 3780億msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.078691472478004
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.12兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.772826966601062
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.4億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4597800199256934
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.66億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.6474338338405032
    },
    {
        "question": " 433億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.6366504233111865
    },
    {
        "question": " 2223兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8482138146214577
    },
    {
        "question": " 1560兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.2565858089524164
    },
    {
        "question": " 75.7京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.322580244098187
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.02億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7011737464821488
    },
    {
        "question": " 56.8億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.754043912627777
    },
    {
        "question": " 114億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.056853551371728
    },
    {
        "question": " 21.8万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 8.339297597355472
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.76京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.3310735625115968
    },
    {
        "question": " 1543京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.251981319484688
    },
    {
        "question": " 608京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.227898049834182
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.34京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.746008101184964
    },
    {
        "question": " 34.4兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.536533558214746
    },
    {
        "question": " 57.5億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.759814051236906
    },
    {
        "question": " 2906nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 0.4632427412484452
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.03万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.043282953177492
    },
    {
        "question": " 959年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.924232442001632
    },
    {
        "question": " 434年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.358107465106656
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.29万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.546839297616116
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.2万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.42881601999857
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.88万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.432533385814622
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.98万日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.780643630793879
    },
    {
        "question": " 7958万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.958279629513388
    },
    {
        "question": " 615万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.408395523683366
    },
    {
        "question": " 125万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.876133921930412
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.18万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.34742369753963
    },
    {
        "question": " 162億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.488359218470583
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.91万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.837876304938031
    },
    {
        "question": " 14万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.3689672986477137
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.93分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7292098067261605
    },
    {
        "question": " 23.9分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.1570803251255235
    },
    {
        "question": " 52.3分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.496336540678866
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.34億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6298761149586818
    },
    {
        "question": " 1528億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.247701076014255
    },
    {
        "question": " 9085秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.40204503720491225
    },
    {
        "question": " 252秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6240407550171068
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.7秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.2214735842691455
    },
    {
        "question": " 93.6秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.971210656698069
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.25京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.221567945273066
    },
    {
        "question": " 3259兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.57659850587145
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.77億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2741251386250108
    },
    {
        "question": " 189兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.49934080111231
    },
    {
        "question": " 4003msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6023673722609757
    },
    {
        "question": " 1696京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.7306216832581836
    },
    {
        "question": " 39.8兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.663530642905698
    },
    {
        "question": " 516億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1566287280380105
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.76億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9820845705371994
    },
    {
        "question": " 50.1億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.6996264597889605
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.97億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.599170651848797
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.33垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.6253955906251525
    },
    {
        "question": " 1530兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2482041792332454
    },
    {
        "question": " 2378京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.819935441370783
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.26京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.1387214697397585
    },
    {
        "question": " 301兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.478088851650231
    },
    {
        "question": " 925兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.966024582878859
    },
    {
        "question": " 101万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 3.0050193199550157
    },
    {
        "question": " 536万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.29147128663056
    },
    {
        "question": " 181年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.199914286475989
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.29万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7982107266824043
    },
    {
        "question": " 20.7万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.695893806789638
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.88日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.106559332075217
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.22日は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.022705424418213
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.91万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.053421594080075
    },
    {
        "question": " 8218時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5345813055247666
    },
    {
        "question": " 65.4時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.593407774979976
    },
    {
        "question": " 6044時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.3376013262657835
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.53時間は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.741666668653908
    },
    {
        "question": " 3167億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.779990239427686
    },
    {
        "question": " 516万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.5540853173883216
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.57万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.039708514740803
    },
    {
        "question": " 138万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.916458171347184
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.75億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7453438571578386
    },
    {
        "question": " 1234億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.1549073561276515
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.03兆秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.22390983364931
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.22万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5688546458025483
    },
    {
        "question": " 18.1万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.256872104136656
    },
    {
        "question": " 528億msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.22403634455492316
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.8京msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.097495415889057
    },
    {
        "question": " 1362兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.577833996916354
    },
    {
        "question": " 1446億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.3820702591756815
    },
    {
        "question": " 471億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.672593994114361
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.14msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 3.0572703261075507
    },
    {
        "question": " 29.2京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.9668443735435477
    },
    {
        "question": " 95.5京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.0435901099688785
    },
    {
        "question": " 52.9億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.16696993727113418
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.2兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.372772005930936
    },
    {
        "question": " 5466億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.737674326905991
    },
    {
        "question": " 483万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.6842821830864034
    },
    {
        "question": " 513usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 5.710429332997244
    },
    {
        "question": " 7441京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.372832200949085
    },
    {
        "question": " 2953垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.533749428667328
    },
    {
        "question": " 2570京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.853699936452103
    },
    {
        "question": " 1302京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.336557663868483
    },
    {
        "question": " 218兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.339166448364444
    },
    {
        "question": " 2344万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.3698782468636062
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.17兆nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.069199791163324
    },
    {
        "question": " 49.7万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.25885862436757
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.5年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.16083636997859
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.6年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.92608547266651
    },
    {
        "question": " 28.4年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.951788044239956
    },
    {
        "question": " 4485日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0894847303760469
    },
    {
        "question": " 6187万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.17165306971079
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.84万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.9244452269432974
    },
    {
        "question": " 38.8日は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.525089610938
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.34億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.426862960117033
    },
    {
        "question": " 2374億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.995356840453942
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.97時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.0724171131164857
    },
    {
        "question": " 2340時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.9255665805227276
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.9兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.507694460616915
    },
    {
        "question": " 1335万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.967242602495623
    },
    {
        "question": " 537億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.952164155109333
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.47万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.17028970281173
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.1兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.734976604296804
    },
    {
        "question": " 184万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3278628743548737
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.2億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.52140640187928
    },
    {
        "question": " 479秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9017878870303397
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.8秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.251615078521823
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.85垓msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.9561003386295
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.17億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8540498736540536
    },
    {
        "question": " 3997億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.045462788415925
    },
    {
        "question": " 415兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.840211801243875
    },
    {
        "question": " 6189億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.79161461319989
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.83垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.764425553260995
    },
    {
        "question": " 894億usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.01501944456948956
    },
    {
        "question": " 73億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.3072003103036358
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.15兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.840334525454773
    },
    {
        "question": " 2093億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.320778160094982
    },
    {
        "question": " 6758万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.829831629474841
    },
    {
        "question": " 154京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6887071158318967
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.81垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.745870598887759
    },
    {
        "question": " 1386兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.585607482444309
    },
    {
        "question": " 62.3兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.0160789049224612
    },
    {
        "question": " 31.5兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.498514174488806
    },
    {
        "question": " 6170万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.7902640418459292
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.53億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 5.183406564083874
    },
    {
        "question": " 33.8万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.091426312741186
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.23年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.569248210337744
    },
    {
        "question": " 690日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.27623351198207247
    },
    {
        "question": " 557日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.90439198793629
    },
    {
        "question": " 4688日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.607504357775419
    },
    {
        "question": " 1676万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.281684684694668
    },
    {
        "question": " 4719時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.29367914372704
    },
    {
        "question": " 2101時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.1004950760611365
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.41兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.149263834832186
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.95兆分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.615976528845762
    },
    {
        "question": " 205万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.533155431775367
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.23万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.286879461701221
    },
    {
        "question": " 75.8分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.657988030929124
    },
    {
        "question": " 494兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.195194684217734
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.64兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.484637306790171
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.7万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.115992777694752
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.25億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.8499903449990445
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.99京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.345761406647421
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.11兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.556445867507709
    },
    {
        "question": " 18.3億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7052590087687456
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.22億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.3067569201343003
    },
    {
        "question": " 185億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.266293204010821
    },
    {
        "question": " 128兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6079628500519918
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.18京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.565939686419437
    },
    {
        "question": " 49.5億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.1383399930199425
    },
    {
        "question": " 5391兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.953552171898411
    },
    {
        "question": " 2859兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.456259513773592
    },
    {
        "question": " 1139usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 0.056378105087747654
    },
    {
        "question": " 34.5usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 4.538396713091382
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.927e+04垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.785993974003512
    },
    {
        "question": " 343兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5985908909597015
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.6垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.471006855642592
    },
    {
        "question": " 2495億nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6189807202058017
    },
    {
        "question": " 87.7京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.942767595828222
    },
    {
        "question": " 100万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 0.00034296834848790425
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.37億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 5.528109234226798
    },
    {
        "question": " 1610万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.769147624366559
    },
    {
        "question": " 1972年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.237506186587819
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.11年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.765150059339338
    },
    {
        "question": " 57.8億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.19932058526777
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.49万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.192187708800669
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.26日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.2579943792203316
    },
    {
        "question": " 38.5億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.643502168879361
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.23億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.967694549839303
    },
    {
        "question": " 8240時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.69408339594962
    },
    {
        "question": " 3023時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.0367048790908235
    },
    {
        "question": " 179時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.809021585402036
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.12億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.066379280562349
    },
    {
        "question": " 27.6万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.281904306404725
    },
    {
        "question": " 1934億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.508238198183903
    },
    {
        "question": " 272分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.2129043050901736
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.4兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.558836167521493
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.61兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.479566745104559
    },
    {
        "question": " 38億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.023541229113789
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.88万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4967890535361015
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.48万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.651042177787635
    },
    {
        "question": " 2533秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.403562884932184
    },
    {
        "question": " 96.1京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.483911644130132
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.13京msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.118390567457476
    },
    {
        "question": " 3827億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.026580760518674
    },
    {
        "question": " 256億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.629858110516866
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.26億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.720738933995635
    },
    {
        "question": " 515msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 8.712176008335096
    },
    {
        "question": " 31.9京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.004671498421548
    },
    {
        "question": " 7667億usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9481110127810743
    },
    {
        "question": " 385兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.028846107914302
    },
    {
        "question": " 1132億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.275831681240333
    },
    {
        "question": " 94.6億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.9760564143323696
    },
    {
        "question": " 124億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.093725387533356
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.51usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 3.4001102880552536
    },
    {
        "question": " 126京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6029356995168698
    },
    {
        "question": " 42.1垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.687377032393333
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.04垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.399718663032163
    },
    {
        "question": " 28.7兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.680387100047189
    },
    {
        "question": " 363兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.559947317357896
    },
    {
        "question": " 52.7兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.72208401361587
    },
    {
        "question": " 1152万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.061528959278079
    },
    {
        "question": " 33.3年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.242935247056827
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.66億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.658745058329656
    },
    {
        "question": " 182日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.641142985435458
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.98万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.8558397036724354
    },
    {
        "question": " 1211万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.1407210992418557
    },
    {
        "question": " 4997万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.318487930301121
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.08億時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.810862413220274
    },
    {
        "question": " 38.4兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.8635406168846185
    },
    {
        "question": " 5360万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.570800501474476
    },
    {
        "question": " 262億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.640286138813341
    },
    {
        "question": " 62.2万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.572077977411112
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.38分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.1545970529019645
    },
    {
        "question": " 141分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.926369418664798
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.5億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6316500744242624
    },
    {
        "question": " 498億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.7610662596621225
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.05億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.292022608095339
    },
    {
        "question": " 48万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.9029040063811737
    },
    {
        "question": " 2101兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.823672855476074
    },
    {
        "question": " 9628兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.047041540092277
    },
    {
        "question": " 365万msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.0063911076593825555
    },
    {
        "question": " 891万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.171873192879338
    },
    {
        "question": " 514億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.710923540872564
    },
    {
        "question": " 22.2万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.346790402442362
    },
    {
        "question": " 240京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.881577219867028
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.11垓usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.106963315813294
    },
    {
        "question": " 777億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3340213375250543
    },
    {
        "question": " 885億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.168939170285532
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.83億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4515484175626066
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.31億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.519541079009995
    },
    {
        "question": " 966万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.98508985265697
    },
    {
        "question": " 1579垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.699446718827752
    },
    {
        "question": " 5801垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.827013077478837
    },
    {
        "question": " 1522兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6259986985201245
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.3兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2366128591004166
    },
    {
        "question": " 708億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8503237475323797
    },
    {
        "question": " 371万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 0.5692385101348452
    },
    {
        "question": " 27.8万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 2.444575956753096
    },
    {
        "question": " 67.7万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.393084874909544
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.5兆日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.981594750957333
    },
    {
        "question": " 176日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.1816588692742584
    },
    {
        "question": " 70.6日は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.785322336212252
    },
    {
        "question": " 29.7万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5295949909346074
    },
    {
        "question": " 19.3万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.9050959699884635
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.97万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.679492341088686
    },
    {
        "question": " 8290億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.197888141071871
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.76万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.283112647566288
    },
    {
        "question": " 205分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5341185903067536
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.83分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.543666156283062
    },
    {
        "question": " 56.2分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.527844106900911
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.32億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2272398528558626
    },
    {
        "question": " 9847万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.0568193302761792
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.8億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.549598418899491
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.63万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.432879535403859
    },
    {
        "question": " 6620億msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3220283523608023
    },
    {
        "question": " 703兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.910479129371494
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.65兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.327099634388659
    },
    {
        "question": " 1103万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2644781755842214
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.77億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.248604082630045
    },
    {
        "question": " 6634msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.821793152710632
    },
    {
        "question": " 50.7msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 7.705185573785586
    },
    {
        "question": " 2612兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9181148561876482
    },
    {
        "question": " 160兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.267749071775299
    },
    {
        "question": " 290兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.906258967273525
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.14京usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.279755210714665
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.07兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.030404692273325
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.1億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.081801750934808
    },
    {
        "question": " 195usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 5.290305270161313
    },
    {
        "question": " 4202京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.124696944369104
    },
    {
        "question": " 254垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.468276842451798
    },
    {
        "question": " 7168兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.2990930251135464
    },
    {
        "question": " 1911京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.503059775101113
    },
    {
        "question": " 1733兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.238708078491988
    },
    {
        "question": " 99.6兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.998097164474554
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.91兆nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.691214733027365
    },
    {
        "question": " 4145年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.179785459490613
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.09年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.901285988944255
    },
    {
        "question": " 158年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.919588523664024
    },
    {
        "question": " 173年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.737138062990212
    },
    {
        "question": " 6817億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.271277257404428
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.82万日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.196370469643004
    },
    {
        "question": " 406億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.666482526900874
    },
    {
        "question": " 50.1万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.319334911544118
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.32万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.299284813488852
    },
    {
        "question": " 158時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.754443523584715
    },
    {
        "question": " 188時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.829925081399661
    },
    {
        "question": " 69.8兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.123336167510757
    },
    {
        "question": " 9020分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7968753066121304
    },
    {
        "question": " 141億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.372529363473154
    },
    {
        "question": " 499万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.476353904965208
    },
    {
        "question": " 38.5分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.363235927373467
    },
    {
        "question": " 3710兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.070547528208156
    },
    {
        "question": " 1318万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1835439940546166
    },
    {
        "question": " 5208秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.16035279348405207
    },
    {
        "question": " 701万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.067275412586914
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.4万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.05571130559738
    },
    {
        "question": " 2840億msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9545558749240313
    },
    {
        "question": " 2233億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.412366492269231
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.53兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.628157186501978
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.18億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.7245217730935556
    },
    {
        "question": " 6153億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.789069181898148
    },
    {
        "question": " 2098msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.32185363097722
    },
    {
        "question": " 116兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5647197987823871
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.12京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.112742989122473
    },
    {
        "question": " 1098億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4842691518463402
    },
    {
        "question": " 2847億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.6762552396508488
    },
    {
        "question": " 460万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6627689084128874
    },
    {
        "question": " 334万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.523311633932461
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.819e+04垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.334889389950066
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.82垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.828334234666479
    },
    {
        "question": " 2205兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7871040893456165
    },
    {
        "question": " 141兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.3703267141754747
    },
    {
        "question": " 26兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.414508325790642
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.05兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.484748387272468
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.57兆nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.879170859934693
    },
    {
        "question": " 892年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.512777170941046
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.49万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.338936558267761
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.15年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.053279050162999
    },
    {
        "question": " 987万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.432013474139415
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.57日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.197821801414672
    },
    {
        "question": " 65.8万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.976327305543483
    },
    {
        "question": " 101日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.940413969483144
    },
    {
        "question": " 59.9万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8345894606246826
    },
    {
        "question": " 2646万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.042443710276331
    },
    {
        "question": " 22.9時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.13776067722788
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.73時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.127436589918393
    },
    {
        "question": " 1512時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.735970498570827
    },
    {
        "question": " 47.6兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.956643734179353
    },
    {
        "question": " 58.6億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.609652783736248
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.33万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.94828983407439
    },
    {
        "question": " 80.1万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.6815457234966456
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.9億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6743679462797112
    },
    {
        "question": " 983万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.0560889643329583
    },
    {
        "question": " 800万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.346910505994285
    },
    {
        "question": " 2428万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.607080788942708
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.89秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.4614301092265434
    },
    {
        "question": " 2070京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.817216900542634
    },
    {
        "question": " 2770億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.5060291904963803
    },
    {
        "question": " 41.1兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.057733439815124
    },
    {
        "question": " 23.6兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.594137704761618
    },
    {
        "question": " 2036億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.308722155960638
    },
    {
        "question": " 1103msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.042487526660981
    },
    {
        "question": " 19.8京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.7972718266619507
    },
    {
        "question": " 219兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.4047292222266057
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.34京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.081388479391388
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.31京usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.741308950399368
    },
    {
        "question": " 153兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.18469387928932
    },
    {
        "question": " 5349usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 0.7282511799955116
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.78垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.7522961458107407
    },
    {
        "question": " 466兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7319653137315651
    },
    {
        "question": " 30.4兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9267965531626188
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.01垓nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.921780912411679
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.34兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.5231639809331714
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.18億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 2.3377293356346884
    },
    {
        "question": " 756億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.878577326287336
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.6万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.72781947523147
    },
    {
        "question": " 69.2万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.78231570693263
    },
    {
        "question": " 49.2億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.12944766912024
    },
    {
        "question": " 57.1万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.137064693821333
    },
    {
        "question": " 31.2万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.653162986276556
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.17日は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.005624057718784
    },
    {
        "question": " 6907万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.8967865391512646
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.47億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.1601115633734445
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.7時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.974585050329498
    },
    {
        "question": " 47.3時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.2313091414990325
    },
    {
        "question": " 41.2兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.894604440325786
    },
    {
        "question": " 5339分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5690916563496096
    },
    {
        "question": " 297万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.694728136328793
    },
    {
        "question": " 4495万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.430895238918426
    },
    {
        "question": " 15万分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.95433801455154
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.06分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.091067166014392
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.21京秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.584837500138802
    },
    {
        "question": " 531万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7882995621919373
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.73兆秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.202164327558593
    },
    {
        "question": " 130億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.336913986438377
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.05垓msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.813162394482683
    },
    {
        "question": " 113億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1172595961245886
    },
    {
        "question": " 20.4億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.752918110822695
    },
    {
        "question": " 194億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.510756130111481
    },
    {
        "question": " 232億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.36566702351945
    },
    {
        "question": " 6550msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.816255696394792
    },
    {
        "question": " 921msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 8.96442224627178
    },
    {
        "question": " 16垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.705895950998524
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.3兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.116278416190397
    },
    {
        "question": " 2133兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.772751341174665
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.03京usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.703584165282857
    },
    {
        "question": " 532万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7256997264558429
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.8億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.072246594082062
    },
    {
        "question": " 5282usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.722796476143915
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.67垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.170894426413882
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.37垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.201045571940523
    },
    {
        "question": " 86.6兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.381260938005413
    },
    {
        "question": " 1852兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.489394485289193
    },
    {
        "question": " 19.9兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.298174213388801
    },
    {
        "question": " 42.3億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.626213247176179
    },
    {
        "question": " 3604億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.55684162845412
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.3万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.613495916925284
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.5年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.004182191195849
    },
    {
        "question": " 277年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.16347625744325
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.71万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6702746900479604
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.13億日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.431670598594168
    },
    {
        "question": " 599万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.935765713897116
    },
    {
        "question": " 5704日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.69266592397972
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.41万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9822404139159513
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.08万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6544643116347357
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.61兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.6963992337484335
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.16兆分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.696579378720266
    },
    {
        "question": " 387万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.8093223706849955
    },
    {
        "question": " 52.7万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.499983399953635
    },
    {
        "question": " 43.6分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.418014723664848
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.56分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.971081769149906
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.3兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.554521935977917
    },
    {
        "question": " 953億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.042673277214204
    },
    {
        "question": " 24.4億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.831171051754205
    },
    {
        "question": " 35.1億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.766772548372728
    },
    {
        "question": " 2340億msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8703317358820684
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.43京msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.2182045819346
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.38兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.5827932019621915
    },
    {
        "question": " 8561億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.154382321528971
    },
    {
        "question": " 23.2万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.364621375281434
    },
    {
        "question": " 41.7msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 7.619993822135291
    },
    {
        "question": " 2862京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.9578849276476955
    },
    {
        "question": " 1336兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.189448620339026
    },
    {
        "question": " 38.1京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.024896378447039
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.12京usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.716094418066838
    },
    {
        "question": " 46.5兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.667515446873894
    },
    {
        "question": " 45億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.6530030143969
    },
    {
        "question": " 437垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.141671338189822
    },
    {
        "question": " 4468垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.713595612678805
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.44京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.9806409101243325
    },
    {
        "question": " 8650京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.15885036649278
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.9億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.17264331196580662
    },
    {
        "question": " 6936億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.841101751911154
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.7万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 1.6716894697352513
    },
    {
        "question": " 50.1年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.2619905706098
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.78万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6870736786084195
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.93日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.057486503066175
    },
    {
        "question": " 633日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.737826858239724
    },
    {
        "question": " 287万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.515463353902827
    },
    {
        "question": " 563万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.370008667984516
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.35時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.6861086879119362
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.18時間は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.894820468238109
    },
    {
        "question": " 1495万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4538745105385464
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.69万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0698415150653928
    },
    {
        "question": " 592分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9942217316814717
    },
    {
        "question": " 8282万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.696265620468555
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.84分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.724412014187189
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.7兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.637801890279068
    },
    {
        "question": " 5425万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.797918140777116
    },
    {
        "question": " 31億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.934431546169972
    },
    {
        "question": " 148秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.3935292021277892
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.81万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.448788935892021
    },
    {
        "question": " 27.1京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.934170801362213
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.7億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2312586309837725
    },
    {
        "question": " 3040億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.926621174105508
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.18億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.559602589626858
    },
    {
        "question": " 361万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.557720592579392
    },
    {
        "question": " 683msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 5.834720529251155
    },
    {
        "question": " 450msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 8.653652694995932
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.4京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.1445791515994683
    },
    {
        "question": " 2158兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.39761921682606
    },
    {
        "question": " 111兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.487973629206872
    },
    {
        "question": " 69.2兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.061703247414486
    },
    {
        "question": " 839万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9238079575010716
    },
    {
        "question": " 2489usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 0.3960005071913375
    },
    {
        "question": " 594万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.773558176704718
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.227e+05垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.219466952669011
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.83垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.514995185419316
    },
    {
        "question": " 317兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9441449637775776
    },
    {
        "question": " 138兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.361955124350189
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.54京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.9795211584626475
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.3億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 2.518460427891381
    },
    {
        "question": " 2893nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 0.46128185099668095
    },
    {
        "question": " 62.1万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.355489623986491
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.08年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.2604084159920745
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.41年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.232340868689578
    },
    {
        "question": " 75.7万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.3168177085882555
    },
    {
        "question": " 1150日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.441020595654477
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.18日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.01424664191911
    },
    {
        "question": " 28.5日は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.391267680579357
    },
    {
        "question": " 98.2億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.0495165932702655
    },
    {
        "question": " 247時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0132640534474235
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.2時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7877319296844383
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.96時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.457346540905196
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.86兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.547855929909514
    },
    {
        "question": " 2072万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.157963079778376
    },
    {
        "question": " 1563分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4157552427103826
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.71万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.347174627654219
    },
    {
        "question": " 142兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.652237732822402
    },
    {
        "question": " 33.7万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.590802054750521
    },
    {
        "question": " 5581億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.190424102555601
    },
    {
        "question": " 116万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.28493017103056
    },
    {
        "question": " 24.8秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.394374327568052
    },
    {
        "question": " 722億msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.3599148236761651
    },
    {
        "question": " 1025兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.074298051882691
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.18億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.513983642572303
    },
    {
        "question": " 1151億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.282884573846719
    },
    {
        "question": " 34.1万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5326321967982324
    },
    {
        "question": " 393msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 8.59483650652807
    },
    {
        "question": " 4800京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.182411447163519
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.37兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.035274560267556
    },
    {
        "question": " 176兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.688863915570596
    },
    {
        "question": " 6095兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.00682901702796
    },
    {
        "question": " 24.6億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.3901453930813408
    },
    {
        "question": " 1889万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.276158688378068
    },
    {
        "question": " 733usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 5.86517165956157
    },
    {
        "question": " 327京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.015993594543013
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.69京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.29218140791395
    },
    {
        "question": " 275兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8833555608458463
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.72京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.209581107211264
    },
    {
        "question": " 5588億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7472717621764353
    },
    {
        "question": " 3627兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.559512648620075
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.71兆nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.23204121565884
    },
    {
        "question": " 1486年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.734422726756639
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.9年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.981019140968711
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.44万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8243569793753056
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.01億日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.385697608628261
    },
    {
        "question": " 4430万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.703927684946101
    },
    {
        "question": " 377億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.19598306228644
    },
    {
        "question": " 1615万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.986449006244898
    },
    {
        "question": " 92.1時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.520326536792723
    },
    {
        "question": " 260兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.694843760582586
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.18万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7543107646236422
    },
    {
        "question": " 2570分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6317152870638685
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.05分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.263020147083441
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.41万分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.648187994475268
    },
    {
        "question": " 85.3分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.709005135331504
    },
    {
        "question": " 120億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5797338334870457
    },
    {
        "question": " 42.3万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6899733892253157
    },
    {
        "question": " 5136億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.15436297921431
    },
    {
        "question": " 435万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.860614045040112
    },
    {
        "question": " 30.3万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.48102728502908
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.78秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.249831155300157
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.45兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.0384273088547067
    },
    {
        "question": " 2889億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.5242000207578714
    },
    {
        "question": " 783億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.337692408773858
    },
    {
        "question": " 2226万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.569404933362016
    },
    {
        "question": " 21.6億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.334197967352745
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.89msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 3.460402082751237
    },
    {
        "question": " 928京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.468508766566601
    },
    {
        "question": " 8475京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.991623051073992
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.39京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.58818779227977
    },
    {
        "question": " 92.8億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.189412341512692
    },
    {
        "question": " 1740万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2406560723752247
    },
    {
        "question": " 1437万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.157602710795986
    },
    {
        "question": " 29.5万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 8.469964379301736
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.104e+05垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.824239061155101
    },
    {
        "question": " 7851兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.958446870570052
    },
    {
        "question": " 1526兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6273672084621937
    },
    {
        "question": " 1371億nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.35894731576828987
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.8京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.68111607943731
    },
    {
        "question": " 43.9兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.642156298612894
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.7億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.166127417998223
    },
    {
        "question": " 1094万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.601201584589745
    },
    {
        "question": " 22.2万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.289026320185341
    },
    {
        "question": " 766年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.605133716987908
    },
    {
        "question": " 684億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.272620933206316
    },
    {
        "question": " 863日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.316193676635292
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.6日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.684467605725389
    },
    {
        "question": " 1900億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.336160522795371
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.12億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.234603951608873
    },
    {
        "question": " 4906時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.468906953552458
    },
    {
        "question": " 86.7時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.494130063623576
    },
    {
        "question": " 159兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.480806369137406
    },
    {
        "question": " 321億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.34773558477916
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.67億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.045928402484302
    },
    {
        "question": " 9652万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.762774957341428
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.96万分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.070925360299
    },
    {
        "question": " 23.9億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8797577610567506
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.99兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.908173434249233
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.48兆秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.615263680715998
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.13億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.551055829091046
    },
    {
        "question": " 27.5万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.43994118584428
    },
    {
        "question": " 20秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.300589620865077
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.1京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.548046155564567
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.69兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.494046931799362
    },
    {
        "question": " 66.7億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.2680694392133725
    },
    {
        "question": " 197万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5173466914787637
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.4億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.093337447465429
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.34垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.86986520983816
    },
    {
        "question": " 2424億usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.44794375089198035
    },
    {
        "question": " 13兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.556798942954602
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.08兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.539636895207472
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.35兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.129921485837714
    },
    {
        "question": " 6175usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 0.7906458274028738
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.31垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.470196772612286
    },
    {
        "question": " 23.3垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.430108597939398
    },
    {
        "question": " 92.8京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.411456954020075
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.29兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.854054778256179
    },
    {
        "question": " 173京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.238048677924695
    },
    {
        "question": " 1989億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.29861031375947
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.34万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 1.6377255417317227
    },
    {
        "question": " 293万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.028483439114712
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.76年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.550805988250692
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.59万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6403926650467626
    },
    {
        "question": " 6231億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.852021579364474
    },
    {
        "question": " 379時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1982218954057888
    },
    {
        "question": " 361時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.3353624443684975
    },
    {
        "question": " 105兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.300463760005318
    },
    {
        "question": " 5442万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.577413462207697
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.77億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.983226001092447
    },
    {
        "question": " 241万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.16037986287004
    },
    {
        "question": " 20.7分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.093566621935713
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.01分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.623901572838387
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.22京秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.35999842524858
    },
    {
        "question": " 77.7億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.954005854176046
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.71兆秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.876130166123579
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.77億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.47042879748555
    },
    {
        "question": " 1028秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.011898592772623
    },
    {
        "question": " 222秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.346669164936193
    },
    {
        "question": " 645兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.310804380389329
    },
    {
        "question": " 19.9京msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.361846484175976
    },
    {
        "question": " 561兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.192876672317643
    },
    {
        "question": " 202万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.526499563747008
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.18万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0714113789801771
    },
    {
        "question": " 889京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.450321064038899
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.83兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3266972273136002
    },
    {
        "question": " 64.6億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.2537397681302278
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.33億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5899631494227042
    },
    {
        "question": " 5287兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.723206142156664
    },
    {
        "question": " 58.8万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 2.7697440569327423
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.07万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 7.029788934309909
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.955e+06垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.792399664589082
    },
    {
        "question": " 350兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.607080266821135
    },
    {
        "question": " 3022兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9240120926361532
    },
    {
        "question": " 3619億nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7804564682944659
    },
    {
        "question": " 7984兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.902197928783994
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.77億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 2.4423459902060918
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.56万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 1.9322377369986932
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.13万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.890965126383152
    },
    {
        "question": " 53.4年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.2266489161277
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.76億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.87934185506013
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.49億日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.776184546699037
    },
    {
        "question": " 583日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.924119649867078
    },
    {
        "question": " 90.4日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.892883536479374
    },
    {
        "question": " 307億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.54481122318005
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.57億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.172349079942501
    },
    {
        "question": " 1378万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.917411254734155
    },
    {
        "question": " 535時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.284430011070214
    },
    {
        "question": " 412時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.171505126035402
    },
    {
        "question": " 6179億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.0702859009130545
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.7億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.273637799012196
    },
    {
        "question": " 30.3億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.703522080697435
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.93京秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.40046974242755
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.64兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.484723013076745
    },
    {
        "question": " 57万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.199578110873545
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.15億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.010699187783731
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.7万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.137030018455212
    },
    {
        "question": " 500京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.200158305342624
    },
    {
        "question": " 587兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.832344108455773
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.67億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.666323188226736
    },
    {
        "question": " 644億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.030590553110873
    },
    {
        "question": " 3149msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.49817216830293165
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.26msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.353572291798926
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.02垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.510192217875785
    },
    {
        "question": " 3647兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.625460212918312
    },
    {
        "question": " 1412億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5934012435796185
    },
    {
        "question": " 302億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7018905162479334
    },
    {
        "question": " 252万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.4020690023842266
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.55兆usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.190896619684818
    },
    {
        "question": " 164京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.715975227100368
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.41京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.212933342931638
    },
    {
        "question": " 608兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2275085929963834
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.14兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.0096916062868733
    },
    {
        "question": " 41.3兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.616361206254599
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.9兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.897556473029356
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.88兆nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.688505969447153
    },
    {
        "question": " 32.2万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.070701543918585
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.61万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.150588688856578
    },
    {
        "question": " 33.6万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.96390636199094
    },
    {
        "question": " 353万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.928499754145144
    },
    {
        "question": " 804日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.063399662816318
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.08日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.8948182222531
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.43万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7041138920647916
    },
    {
        "question": " 1696億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.849201610437238
    },
    {
        "question": " 31.8万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.280779971408153
    },
    {
        "question": " 536万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0088368717796592
    },
    {
        "question": " 7389億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.710264553367683
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.72億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.456367299035475
    },
    {
        "question": " 4886分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.467074608708032
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.04万分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.480731887982556
    },
    {
        "question": " 40.9分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.390041909343596
    },
    {
        "question": " 7236億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.360690738494174
    },
    {
        "question": " 4836億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.747959037334436
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.93兆秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.21681194702976
    },
    {
        "question": " 102万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.232306250175045
    },
    {
        "question": " 92.5秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.966172100011269
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.9秒は何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.278900641176119
    },
    {
        "question": " 4008京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.104073255125568
    },
    {
        "question": " 81.6京msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.975188246276105
    },
    {
        "question": " 82億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.357363274725038
    },
    {
        "question": " 19.2兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.506032701382308
    },
    {
        "question": " 171億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.233956930759023
    },
    {
        "question": " 2011msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.303510007667038
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.35京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8717305969220828
    },
    {
        "question": " 3838京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.647593943614332
    },
    {
        "question": " 4504兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.097305148190215
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.64兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.888552906733278
    },
    {
        "question": " 662万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8208824711596518
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.23万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.9651389846814538
    },
    {
        "question": " 868万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.938401497848215
    },
    {
        "question": " 65.2垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.315211467010799
    },
    {
        "question": " 39.4京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.6585842992495152
    },
    {
        "question": " 116兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5070152216889876
    },
    {
        "question": " 186兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.4902871782034683
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.3億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.1860108313985409
    },
    {
        "question": " 4867万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.68725095972582
    },
    {
        "question": " 5801万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.763537090560855
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.18万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.634011376045056
    },
    {
        "question": " 9142年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.903527895985879
    },
    {
        "question": " 1608年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.927022045245556
    },
    {
        "question": " 187万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.7106270127259844
    },
    {
        "question": " 182日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.639218637825948
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.57日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.347133965532212
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.1日は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.978635605277628
    },
    {
        "question": " 103万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.071064808860301
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.45億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.267754445297095
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.27億時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.88283778102368
    },
    {
        "question": " 60.2万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.335786674424387
    },
    {
        "question": " 240億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.659836314266931
    },
    {
        "question": " 6305万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.641365528929083
    },
    {
        "question": " 636分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0253418280964255
    },
    {
        "question": " 1911分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.059442427426999
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.65万分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.762716782101851
    },
    {
        "question": " 157兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.6983997604832375
    },
    {
        "question": " 27万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.49541171198834943
    },
    {
        "question": " 387万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.0317406298275893
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.7万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.416788904918012
    },
    {
        "question": " 1280京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.608455931965617
    },
    {
        "question": " 401億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.666522926513748
    },
    {
        "question": " 69.5億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.2857076150777873
    },
    {
        "question": " 21.4億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.5528937562093095
    },
    {
        "question": " 396億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.597840469376705
    },
    {
        "question": " 29.2垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.966420604145616
    },
    {
        "question": " 28.7京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.521825444914939
    },
    {
        "question": " 195兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.732733454305068
    },
    {
        "question": " 1017兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.229127179963047
    },
    {
        "question": " 67.9億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.8320830247832562
    },
    {
        "question": " 1000万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.00019962689595
    },
    {
        "question": " 6893京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.339592503723099
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.2垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.272235492632634
    },
    {
        "question": " 50.1垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.14331865796214
    },
    {
        "question": " 373京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.793028407698717
    },
    {
        "question": " 347兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.540024186509724
    },
    {
        "question": " 319億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.504456427996825
    },
    {
        "question": " 448万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 3.65143040745461
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.41年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.094694887144498
    },
    {
        "question": " 786年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.837981187351204
    },
    {
        "question": " 1015万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.444048012484105
    },
    {
        "question": " 3070万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.867306751554425
    },
    {
        "question": " 38万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.738387495874015
    },
    {
        "question": " 6233日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.731214026643633
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.54億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.461472668174481
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.8万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.844733877782586
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.4時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4219878980732323
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.7時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.787133853421419
    },
    {
        "question": " 136万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.4116210583487767
    },
    {
        "question": " 1444万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.00119019715849
    },
    {
        "question": " 18.6億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.490226236762091
    },
    {
        "question": " 227分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.1335973864726565
    },
    {
        "question": " 281分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.227077469878242
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.05兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.521794550437819
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.4億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.7959144622676244
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.69兆秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.114494854837018
    },
    {
        "question": " 30.8億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.710546390621033
    },
    {
        "question": " 104万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.015015433203622
    },
    {
        "question": " 51.5秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.712158635002271
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.26兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.855086256543761
    },
    {
        "question": " 4628兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.7289329175979296
    },
    {
        "question": " 5313万msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1690477858132675
    },
    {
        "question": " 45.7億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.88158829636487
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.72万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4343272246781313
    },
    {
        "question": " 2455兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.891210196714831
    },
    {
        "question": " 22.9兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.422454032600234
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.41京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.5914140420996645
    },
    {
        "question": " 46.5京usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.889111944045819
    },
    {
        "question": " 49.5兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.695011144315609
    },
    {
        "question": " 22.7万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 2.355099837161493
    },
    {
        "question": " 576垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.261667363663722
    },
    {
        "question": " 3733垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.635576049864289
    },
    {
        "question": " 85.4京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.37503876461221
    },
    {
        "question": " 3521京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.768488381652475
    },
    {
        "question": " 844兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.926424263371425
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.7億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.195675507658422
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.13兆nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.328735909757475
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.89年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.83985353535976
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.58万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.184635167732496
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.04日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9863253161843908
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.38億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.699347464632964
    },
    {
        "question": " 139時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7617093707427414
    },
    {
        "question": " 32.9時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.295528053161653
    },
    {
        "question": " 233時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.924193594630783
    },
    {
        "question": " 845万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2060003900912397
    },
    {
        "question": " 180億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.097267681337518
    },
    {
        "question": " 45.4億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.878739049723235
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.67万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.001971771036052
    },
    {
        "question": " 26.6億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9253187509790248
    },
    {
        "question": " 1180万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.135565476570892
    },
    {
        "question": " 664億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.265872066153962
    },
    {
        "question": " 74.4万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.09344665926438
    },
    {
        "question": " 425秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.628094217415268
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.4京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.594837229838978
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.77兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.310539731308461
    },
    {
        "question": " 140億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.590402932373583
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.68億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.9758872781760135
    },
    {
        "question": " 579億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.7623639743540584
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.52万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.742130109509385
    },
    {
        "question": " 1961垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.79371543125488
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.61垓usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.48095734024191
    },
    {
        "question": " 720京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.301221518898078
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.99京usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.519848313704852
    },
    {
        "question": " 1106億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.04390014952264
    },
    {
        "question": " 197億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.2936596981376125
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.1万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 7.040170094207122
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.47垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.042075889144325
    },
    {
        "question": " 9423京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.0376962876069
    },
    {
        "question": " 3932兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.038266649907444
    },
    {
        "question": " 19.5京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.51288551936287
    },
    {
        "question": " 41.1兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.61404435465839
    },
    {
        "question": " 1959兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.292041571247882
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.75億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 5.889389839778836
    },
    {
        "question": " 258万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.973807918472879
    },
    {
        "question": " 73.2年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.585156456542366
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.19万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2943337830372568
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.2日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5324813593431497
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.28万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.264465535075727
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.68日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.821917572496198
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.33万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.18069657721769494
    },
    {
        "question": " 2235億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.969150580131545
    },
    {
        "question": " 6789万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.609943919363527
    },
    {
        "question": " 7242時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.416165299580966
    },
    {
        "question": " 78.8万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.17612097796532722
    },
    {
        "question": " 5863分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.609768838307494
    },
    {
        "question": " 334分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7457952175400617
    },
    {
        "question": " 1億分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.7781684108001
    },
    {
        "question": " 21.8分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.116238746945295
    },
    {
        "question": " 159分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.980365766883974
    },
    {
        "question": " 7163兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.35629328919018
    },
    {
        "question": " 309兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.553868565575037
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.48兆秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.317859449926749
    },
    {
        "question": " 3042万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.705063735675723
    },
    {
        "question": " 36.8万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.565545169183729
    },
    {
        "question": " 432京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.136591429923424
    },
    {
        "question": " 3924億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.657252404386495
    },
    {
        "question": " 599兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.22142464196571
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.22兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.308384895673816
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.95億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.84199575767909
    },
    {
        "question": " 54.3兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.23615139505599791
    },
    {
        "question": " 76.3京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.946226917636311
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.6兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.648381296929906
    },
    {
        "question": " 1245億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.31711164291249
    },
    {
        "question": " 131万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.11810461258084048
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.03兆usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.013422584423928
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.27usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 3.629926405249171
    },
    {
        "question": " 3028京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9824185266371614
    },
    {
        "question": " 2590垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.476879493089639
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.67京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.008301568101658
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.76京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.468556169040182
    },
    {
        "question": " 62.2京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.793626670305816
    },
    {
        "question": " 532億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.725503928131523
    },
    {
        "question": " 1678億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.224886201367847
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.59年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.922319063567309
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.2年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.708101302083639
    },
    {
        "question": " 2337日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8063160344296583
    },
    {
        "question": " 1422万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.533236256426612
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.51万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.899267379195871
    },
    {
        "question": " 1227万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.1463127219209417
    },
    {
        "question": " 341時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.153062748254795
    },
    {
        "question": " 216万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.112831327644232
    },
    {
        "question": " 19.3時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.842270578944525
    },
    {
        "question": " 235万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6504355247712779
    },
    {
        "question": " 623万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.6359454543349568
    },
    {
        "question": " 17億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.452361258516578
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.48万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.589790372809335
    },
    {
        "question": " 4418兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.14638825127513
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.38億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.592063346771115
    },
    {
        "question": " 4212億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.068142444822481
    },
    {
        "question": " 269万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.6510349697653
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.87秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.896030778595155
    },
    {
        "question": " 1187秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.07457523095507
    },
    {
        "question": " 54.9兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.240441749863574
    },
    {
        "question": " 30億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5408874990533095
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.08億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4754289849207325
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.84兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.16846997756516
    },
    {
        "question": " 29億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.462574532273262
    },
    {
        "question": " 28.7垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.959449509795603
    },
    {
        "question": " 4540兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.720587994543834
    },
    {
        "question": " 302兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.923165507025074
    },
    {
        "question": " 46.7億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.890916300247698
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.22兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.346670422974395
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.36万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.8036934360729817
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.91e+04垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.7822555440640375
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.22京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.688553887878904
    },
    {
        "question": " 13兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5568455467232103
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.99京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.823330930906009
    },
    {
        "question": " 81.4京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.910729756381336
    },
    {
        "question": " 182兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.259229728736484
    },
    {
        "question": " 5085億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.706288540238717
    },
    {
        "question": " 148万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.731340802890921
    },
    {
        "question": " 23.4年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.0896781315399915
    },
    {
        "question": " 460億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.100827626379576
    },
    {
        "question": " 8353万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.302041566590983
    },
    {
        "question": " 2274日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.515133574942623
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.39億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.981400832811726
    },
    {
        "question": " 114万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.675778658959676
    },
    {
        "question": " 194万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.066976115763493
    },
    {
        "question": " 546時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.293382540419116
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.39時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.700302134229439
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.55兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.937518277730643
    },
    {
        "question": " 692万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.681558848688473
    },
    {
        "question": " 6376分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.026411058293812
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.03万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.085178541518213
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.62万分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.987437774951845
    },
    {
        "question": " 6600万秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.3207356150662255
    },
    {
        "question": " 246億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.45527441110658
    },
    {
        "question": " 3052万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.9283280371391758
    },
    {
        "question": " 7196秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.078956373038916
    },
    {
        "question": " 37.2秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.570741145779974
    },
    {
        "question": " 415秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.618344237605493
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.8兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.492391598861814
    },
    {
        "question": " 42.4京msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.691172742531686
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.43兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.178341399100541
    },
    {
        "question": " 3億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.698277520966453
    },
    {
        "question": " 89.9万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9537672225796907
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.88msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.769101392217426
    },
    {
        "question": " 44.7兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.15116228826075995
    },
    {
        "question": " 1263京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.164948964912837
    },
    {
        "question": " 1571兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.640010051206956
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.71京usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.454113858595402
    },
    {
        "question": " 1028万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0119934845772827
    },
    {
        "question": " 295億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.47014437984105
    },
    {
        "question": " 409垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.113442003353445
    },
    {
        "question": " 154兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.25073420919742295
    },
    {
        "question": " 198垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.740701406203335
    },
    {
        "question": " 2184億nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5611639103699528
    },
    {
        "question": " 333京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.52256739236726
    },
    {
        "question": " 157億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.194701162582621
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.8万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 2.1988543330742583
    },
    {
        "question": " 4414年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.5873626569485175
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.44年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.885582351449929
    },
    {
        "question": " 48.9億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.126800280700857
    },
    {
        "question": " 7284日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.242570711621165
    },
    {
        "question": " 76.7万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.043074250703093
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.25万日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.564729049091333
    },
    {
        "question": " 503万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7591083425129783
    },
    {
        "question": " 169時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8472449405156035
    },
    {
        "question": " 21.1時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.102256705500377
    },
    {
        "question": " 180時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.810923922394762
    },
    {
        "question": " 329億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.796011737802538
    },
    {
        "question": " 1066億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.869449843667198
    },
    {
        "question": " 638万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.026391941053198
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.7万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.974757800744951
    },
    {
        "question": " 18.2億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.761538966644478
    },
    {
        "question": " 211億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.388641712838008
    },
    {
        "question": " 2287億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.803035304304027
    },
    {
        "question": " 3735万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.794183759332362
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.78京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.751756642041172
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.08億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.3814696290628372
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.94京msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.911325553782138
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.29兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.945028815890377
    },
    {
        "question": " 768億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.885088853375121
    },
    {
        "question": " 43.1万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.634270619218997
    },
    {
        "question": " 3111京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.9941433989778234
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.7兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.293247119489761
    },
    {
        "question": " 1081兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.477579261246247
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.6京usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.637273201896456
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.9億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.07497514668344
    },
    {
        "question": " 190億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.27964961384478
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.2usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 4.208690138316405
    },
    {
        "question": " 1560京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.69432831990743
    },
    {
        "question": " 3232京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.572906776986093
    },
    {
        "question": " 1616兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6522152462961444
    },
    {
        "question": " 615兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.0109733984716724
    },
    {
        "question": " 103京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.010903859754153
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.2億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.1192793250534523
    },
    {
        "question": " 19.5億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.289010947393944
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.91年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.44847371565742
    },
    {
        "question": " 6314日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2379701359781148
    },
    {
        "question": " 217万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.717552099948646
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.1日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.336011222025276
    },
    {
        "question": " 66.1日は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.756378275589693
    },
    {
        "question": " 1437万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.214868424376153
    },
    {
        "question": " 1934万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.906253511129539
    },
    {
        "question": " 544時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.513680409222913
    },
    {
        "question": " 932万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2486967756012413
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.13億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.457769800420148
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.99億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.521437986587985
    },
    {
        "question": " 241万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.159999099434941
    },
    {
        "question": " 793兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.400218934130307
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.7億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.199672549275548
    },
    {
        "question": " 19.3兆秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.72913898940094
    },
    {
        "question": " 2811億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.670681903441219
    },
    {
        "question": " 7275京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.363017562660223
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.01京msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.366282776945123
    },
    {
        "question": " 747億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.316822230827203
    },
    {
        "question": " 1241万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.315540699058951
    },
    {
        "question": " 38.2万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5816750980219414
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.52msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 3.8142405452778396
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.07垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.817057006339128
    },
    {
        "question": " 4051京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.671111208016237
    },
    {
        "question": " 82.2京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.358436526824311
    },
    {
        "question": " 152億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.404320489369296
    },
    {
        "question": " 1032兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.013568867696765
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.78万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.2499518437429058
    },
    {
        "question": " 70usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 4.845148127435342
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.02垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.8062773994016554
    },
    {
        "question": " 2371兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.438418430264553
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.76京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.121360718609877
    },
    {
        "question": " 7308億nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0856462820105583
    },
    {
        "question": " 647京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.811120679714895
    },
    {
        "question": " 820億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.913552177936017
    },
    {
        "question": " 6427nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 0.8079806031997783
    },
    {
        "question": " 240年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.3226425180342885
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.08万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.473108950859141
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.75日は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.375580211870078
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.15兆時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.675843945747133
    },
    {
        "question": " 24.7時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.012867792695537839
    },
    {
        "question": " 1287時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.887751939835663
    },
    {
        "question": " 314時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.052839359524992
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.15時間は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.616432856911576
    },
    {
        "question": " 788万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.175948570509906
    },
    {
        "question": " 676万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.6718337438185253
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.8万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4776196889925375
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.16分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.689881635413748
    },
    {
        "question": " 67.6兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.331300259434064
    },
    {
        "question": " 3936万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6585006637687245
    },
    {
        "question": " 389億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.03412393345376
    },
    {
        "question": " 1489億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.394874575736452
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.47秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.9764130475926542
    },
    {
        "question": " 1017秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.007505775777812
    },
    {
        "question": " 2199兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.843353555845927
    },
    {
        "question": " 11京msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.105148839500906
    },
    {
        "question": " 438兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.08499398941421
    },
    {
        "question": " 457万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8820453939648907
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.23億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.347724240007144
    },
    {
        "question": " 97.5msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 7.989157377233653
    },
    {
        "question": " 1587兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7018518668564253
    },
    {
        "question": " 26.9京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.493054818570007
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.7兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.199234208117735
    },
    {
        "question": " 7643億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.105091575549627
    },
    {
        "question": " 361億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.558015602832621
    },
    {
        "question": " 7126億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.8528669099386
    },
    {
        "question": " 8057京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.4073634296026722
    },
    {
        "question": " 1293兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.175058010502339
    },
    {
        "question": " 5692兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.1989898775944505
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.46京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.14930360856361
    },
    {
        "question": " 731億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8640730789981386
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.61億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 2.5580966891777446
    },
    {
        "question": " 469万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 3.670729584511725
    },
    {
        "question": " 148年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.731441932979211
    },
    {
        "question": " 57.3年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.700431089952466
    },
    {
        "question": " 6683年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.54561331182055
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.45兆日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.827683824572821
    },
    {
        "question": " 121日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.4640926439872466
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.5日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.3351313104156
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.94日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.933837712513228
    },
    {
        "question": " 68.5日は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.772330331578248
    },
    {
        "question": " 33.4億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.581717178080656
    },
    {
        "question": " 22.8万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.976921861422497
    },
    {
        "question": " 81.5時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.689204537374567
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.4時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.936591652542848
    },
    {
        "question": " 67.2時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.383671912646598
    },
    {
        "question": " 978万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2695655187199206
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.76億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.731635729014842
    },
    {
        "question": " 2786億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.66680508753177
    },
    {
        "question": " 305分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.262383837278621
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.55万分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.594464699150535
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.96分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.474010377971942
    },
    {
        "question": " 2001兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.802436116948521
    },
    {
        "question": " 1582万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.262740253365311
    },
    {
        "question": " 7419億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.314043095269636
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.76万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4683844811421674
    },
    {
        "question": " 1602秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.204743141153074
    },
    {
        "question": " 57京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.257085363560848
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.54京msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.878917405511146
    },
    {
        "question": " 71.1億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.2954262643436536
    },
    {
        "question": " 1190万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2974267297505624
    },
    {
        "question": " 469億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.671493433124792
    },
    {
        "question": " 9929msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.996924654056728
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.6京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.567045572465574
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.72京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.951280734095128
    },
    {
        "question": " 20兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.7444346950842258
    },
    {
        "question": " 130億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.336349370064105
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.99兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.844748881816226
    },
    {
        "question": " 124億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.091710573251841
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.83usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 3.261866254845054
    },
    {
        "question": " 31.1京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9938707073232045
    },
    {
        "question": " 1829兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3257566646982677
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.28京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.075105229983798
    },
    {
        "question": " 184兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.486823227604275
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.5京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.242709329205015
    },
    {
        "question": " 526兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.721076494624887
    },
    {
        "question": " 261億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.416090799093129
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.53兆日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.8404901979969
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.35万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.511548582071012
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.86万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.105818585036202
    },
    {
        "question": " 21.8億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.395659657515236
    },
    {
        "question": " 1560億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.812824537244424
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.28億時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.883974192614023
    },
    {
        "question": " 22.4万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.906661240080172
    },
    {
        "question": " 905億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.2358704715314275
    },
    {
        "question": " 71.9億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.6983801609048355
    },
    {
        "question": " 3347万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.746561679787625
    },
    {
        "question": " 8792万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.722243659622382
    },
    {
        "question": " 35.9億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.056842848617629
    },
    {
        "question": " 915億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.024972555817552
    },
    {
        "question": " 4485億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.095450740130515
    },
    {
        "question": " 102万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.232507069787293
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.3秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.238364282199985
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.3兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7122875258881374
    },
    {
        "question": " 3616兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.621675011521355
    },
    {
        "question": " 18.4兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.708317567037886
    },
    {
        "question": " 687億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.058938831065467
    },
    {
        "question": " 19.7万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2942991804762256
    },
    {
        "question": " 2509msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.399494197079331
    },
    {
        "question": " 3448兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.038804228831749
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.7京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.131258708034841
    },
    {
        "question": " 40.9億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.055071182539701
    },
    {
        "question": " 65兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.034803527694944
    },
    {
        "question": " 282億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.450254103302265
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.38兆usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.52940008645429
    },
    {
        "question": " 37.4万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 8.57276462755683
    },
    {
        "question": " 1164垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.567325084694176
    },
    {
        "question": " 3693京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.6308759593660564
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.9京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.51847834487091
    },
    {
        "question": " 7740京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.110576308163619
    },
    {
        "question": " 27.1兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.432734715856173
    },
    {
        "question": " 877億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.943155918021961
    },
    {
        "question": " 8400万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.924257207915359
    },
    {
        "question": " 995年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.94042405921246
    },
    {
        "question": " 721年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.578665179165858
    },
    {
        "question": " 79.9年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.401570469311435
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.38億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.966388085338906
    },
    {
        "question": " 48.7億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.744944988668164
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.7万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.815570844994516
    },
    {
        "question": " 4708時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.229176305585328
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.9時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.591876555785167
    },
    {
        "question": " 128億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.386867863047849
    },
    {
        "question": " 1534万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.027562659933558
    },
    {
        "question": " 4702分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8941512891699197
    },
    {
        "question": " 3535万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.326519101173073
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.13万分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.39430733941977
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.69分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.533284556414817
    },
    {
        "question": " 377兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.077437477183577
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.3億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.1883692668081824
    },
    {
        "question": " 232万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.808700839320265
    },
    {
        "question": " 39.5万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.8186353306208867
    },
    {
        "question": " 148万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.169729275670843
    },
    {
        "question": " 90.8兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.4592686719332546
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.65京msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.279917479306002
    },
    {
        "question": " 524万msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.16311681869263128
    },
    {
        "question": " 656億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.038573200391396
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.91億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.6911238698419355
    },
    {
        "question": " 393msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 8.594042005383828
    },
    {
        "question": " 1412垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.651137141802078
    },
    {
        "question": " 2521京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.465141603886075
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.91兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.3420871581679465
    },
    {
        "question": " 8229万usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.1372147345849295
    },
    {
        "question": " 20.1兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.304253912441528
    },
    {
        "question": " 5015億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.700294915913732
    },
    {
        "question": " 904万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.956261558452207
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.894e+04垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.339641012515767
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.56京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4722630606217
    },
    {
        "question": " 336兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9696628205905586
    },
    {
        "question": " 9691京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.208239453094215
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.2億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.23608856677570622
    },
    {
        "question": " 161万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 0.20737893636907478
    },
    {
        "question": " 263万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 3.420712684208901
    },
    {
        "question": " 40.1年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.165240647325428
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.99年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.321715400920775
    },
    {
        "question": " 3358万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.963809691578772
    },
    {
        "question": " 176日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.6255406329197823
    },
    {
        "question": " 66.9日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.983815145459238
    },
    {
        "question": " 1503日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.113384047415074
    },
    {
        "question": " 1202億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.137344573509043
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.7万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.648334690328129
    },
    {
        "question": " 686時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.614765329943683
    },
    {
        "question": " 117時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.624646202705488
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.23時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.90550260622878
    },
    {
        "question": " 471億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.952099445966251
    },
    {
        "question": " 3931分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.4361086985405649
    },
    {
        "question": " 237万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.5970413130618475
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.7分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.84470881115117
    },
    {
        "question": " 469億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.1727500025132107
    },
    {
        "question": " 272万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4974095080408467
    },
    {
        "question": " 965億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.428387651848627
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.22億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.939529369268486
    },
    {
        "question": " 5347秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.728095164423719
    },
    {
        "question": " 225京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.853683109467953
    },
    {
        "question": " 32.1億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5702522107338135
    },
    {
        "question": " 261兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.859550108062958
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.7億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.0480197077976285
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.9億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.075015026000364
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.59msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.414010077087547
    },
    {
        "question": " 67.4京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.329673121233956
    },
    {
        "question": " 1872億usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.3357270671502499
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.85兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.129393776353704
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.33京usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.191867228815202
    },
    {
        "question": " 82.8兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.918161045043966
    },
    {
        "question": " 6244億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.795460731122212
    },
    {
        "question": " 72万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 8.857223989437664
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.669e+05垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.170426764032992
    },
    {
        "question": " 3682京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.6295834199936134
    },
    {
        "question": " 728兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.305962004303349
    },
    {
        "question": " 48.4京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.906282790027946
    },
    {
        "question": " 1888兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.276038124436609
    },
    {
        "question": " 32.7兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.514088767875587
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.19万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 1.0738924177120135
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.61年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.4439078162019743
    },
    {
        "question": " 308年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.431501075176694
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.65兆日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.656311768296776
    },
    {
        "question": " 312日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.8749718529750132
    },
    {
        "question": " 69万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8964777546213751
    },
    {
        "question": " 93.5時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5907170354327074
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.4時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.906203358331252
    },
    {
        "question": " 188時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.830446313170304
    },
    {
        "question": " 110時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.595732091405605
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.74時間は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.993837197319117
    },
    {
        "question": " 23.4兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.6485247796157445
    },
    {
        "question": " 6116分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6281324640259112
    },
    {
        "question": " 3875億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.81012966606119
    },
    {
        "question": " 48.6万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.465081639696237
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.58分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.525164599084937
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.35億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8727009259187402
    },
    {
        "question": " 4934億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.756662167014631
    },
    {
        "question": " 126億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.5425364017028205
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.58億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.203407083593676
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.8万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.680973365431088
    },
    {
        "question": " 92.7兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.468385706320163
    },
    {
        "question": " 950億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.041310745355492
    },
    {
        "question": " 175兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.68623454561236
    },
    {
        "question": " 3920万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.815145562739527
    },
    {
        "question": " 75.3億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.876988577819799
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.34垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.1384611475307045
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.96京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.355023170263866
    },
    {
        "question": " 673億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2718185910348911
    },
    {
        "question": " 6553兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.038296692476644
    },
    {
        "question": " 531兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.725180508420891
    },
    {
        "question": " 1202万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.079849600374095
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.43usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 3.154125610532277
    },
    {
        "question": " 190京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7791893100497846
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.48垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.457578548954035
    },
    {
        "question": " 473兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1181868199723253
    },
    {
        "question": " 2081億nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5402113838164757
    },
    {
        "question": " 1540億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.187464094978726
    },
    {
        "question": " 96.5兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.984738860110385
    },
    {
        "question": " 235万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 3.370425303794673
    },
    {
        "question": " 31.2年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.056209327713562
    },
    {
        "question": " 91.3万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.902962664602951
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.16年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.786581633162217
    },
    {
        "question": " 73.1年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.3629545248484
    },
    {
        "question": " 2475万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.83119906703015
    },
    {
        "question": " 41.9日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.0026241509185647
    },
    {
        "question": " 154億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.244685017386372
    },
    {
        "question": " 96.4億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.603910686015166
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.46時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4274651256476654
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.97時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.8509271967397165
    },
    {
        "question": " 576時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.316819406864736
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.68億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.706726095865158
    },
    {
        "question": " 3268万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.3559517222823265
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.56億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.773601498250516
    },
    {
        "question": " 78.7分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.6740244655310175
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.25万分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.638294212151031
    },
    {
        "question": " 57.4兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.260054715184257
    },
    {
        "question": " 346兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.602744087353159
    },
    {
        "question": " 654億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.2589621605517625
    },
    {
        "question": " 42.3億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.847789068861477
    },
    {
        "question": " 110万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.03988616948495
    },
    {
        "question": " 75.3秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.876900283117728
    },
    {
        "question": " 7016億msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3473091592591524
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.45億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.22487171694892782
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.89億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2134734947894694
    },
    {
        "question": " 7140万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.0755710222440835
    },
    {
        "question": " 132万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.1213141610040807
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.58msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 3.87963714393714
    },
    {
        "question": " 139垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.645465883613198
    },
    {
        "question": " 45.5京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.721737470747474
    },
    {
        "question": " 917京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.406125954132072
    },
    {
        "question": " 10兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.221740619895364
    },
    {
        "question": " 30.6億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.4858600351498614
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.99億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.698316469531771
    },
    {
        "question": " 25.9usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 4.412796006221048
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.1垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.734767744886247
    },
    {
        "question": " 37.5垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.638093062304493
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.44兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.3152110791650409
    },
    {
        "question": " 22.9京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.581879160816876
    },
    {
        "question": " 214京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.329691293058929
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.5億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 2.39801279104506
    },
    {
        "question": " 3411万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.532886068029146
    },
    {
        "question": " 1036万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.577715508581102
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.34万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.46595507242072
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.22年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.514402045451847
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.57年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.051038918123265
    },
    {
        "question": " 768日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.3228638552554286
    },
    {
        "question": " 1963日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.451227068934688
    },
    {
        "question": " 470億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.729704251317605
    },
    {
        "question": " 157億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.814976944635426
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.13億時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.832717441448185
    },
    {
        "question": " 130万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.671556773063156
    },
    {
        "question": " 1029万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.291675524147402
    },
    {
        "question": " 223万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.189618777694143
    },
    {
        "question": " 3042億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.705042081701015
    },
    {
        "question": " 83.3万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.698667236622828
    },
    {
        "question": " 92.6分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.74487009601219
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.35兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.632344369486391
    },
    {
        "question": " 678万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.894866093300479
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.36億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.08288247778249
    },
    {
        "question": " 3802億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.801870472357352
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.64万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.751394537152203
    },
    {
        "question": " 52.1兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.2179379527541707
    },
    {
        "question": " 1813兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.32182114060424
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.68億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6694253882637733
    },
    {
        "question": " 456兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.880381605786464
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.46億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.976039185718573
    },
    {
        "question": " 982万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.992215274546043
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.89垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.778371444766619
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.6兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2832987889293586
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.99兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.0446630146973943
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.26兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.850843978769528
    },
    {
        "question": " 28.4億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.4533046350597454
    },
    {
        "question": " 296万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.4710404163658835
    },
    {
        "question": " 8151usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.911201475636658
    },
    {
        "question": " 579京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.263720514136277
    },
    {
        "question": " 322兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.571954718269867
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.39京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.086570088172325
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.17兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2890661889310862
    },
    {
        "question": " 259億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4135482140845967
    },
    {
        "question": " 9186兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.963106572040997
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.53兆nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.548097654681154
    },
    {
        "question": " 1996万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.862575713647075
    },
    {
        "question": " 45.5年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.378896130647882
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.39年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.02869398639947
    },
    {
        "question": " 462万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.102478094339864
    },
    {
        "question": " 333日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.9028304914360623
    },
    {
        "question": " 33.7万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.68536847233838
    },
    {
        "question": " 29.6兆時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.529016472931207
    },
    {
        "question": " 91.5万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.581296791928098
    },
    {
        "question": " 3101時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.269603199900467
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.4兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.296638295741756
    },
    {
        "question": " 1407億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.989960605679034
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.7億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.358848335063559
    },
    {
        "question": " 205分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.0901615968347205
    },
    {
        "question": " 86.1億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4359624313856445
    },
    {
        "question": " 219億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.404895329460596
    },
    {
        "question": " 61.8万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.234478319511336
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.6万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.4672584780271576
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.35万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.524698382437231
    },
    {
        "question": " 20.8秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.317492844276964
    },
    {
        "question": " 4331京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.137759611321263
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.62億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8133870029234425
    },
    {
        "question": " 391億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.036233868499993
    },
    {
        "question": " 462兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.886292001005462
    },
    {
        "question": " 8986億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.95355809965117
    },
    {
        "question": " 276垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.94262441223949
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.85京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.518881653631959
    },
    {
        "question": " 161兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.6511835724069055
    },
    {
        "question": " 452兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.876579251889119
    },
    {
        "question": " 9874兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.994504825215953
    },
    {
        "question": " 259億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.413725688806354
    },
    {
        "question": " 501usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 5.69953662313474
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.22垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.294651017259955
    },
    {
        "question": " 13京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.1759103009357226
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.6京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.689331432590813
    },
    {
        "question": " 542京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.955954608161439
    },
    {
        "question": " 260億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.414549553654505
    },
    {
        "question": " 822億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.914680722337268
    },
    {
        "question": " 37.1億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.569675828831154
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.82万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.554418529697626
    },
    {
        "question": " 80.4年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.847561536915253
    },
    {
        "question": " 397年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.319056091790504
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.2万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.524649521019443
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.23日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8892268870940876
    },
    {
        "question": " 397日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.757049728580558
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.51万日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.481988436526581
    },
    {
        "question": " 216万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.39094416119644
    },
    {
        "question": " 37億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.188351185805214
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.84時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.043677585140532
    },
    {
        "question": " 109時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.592647891940481
    },
    {
        "question": " 20.7兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.595508240654625
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.5兆分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.861829576134728
    },
    {
        "question": " 322億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.729742041383663
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.04分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.734179769324041
    },
    {
        "question": " 79.1億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.399292087282354
    },
    {
        "question": " 252万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4640640134533678
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.92兆秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.727951816523376
    },
    {
        "question": " 147万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.390394411934077
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.92秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.950138153028484
    },
    {
        "question": " 839秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.92359419999449
    },
    {
        "question": " 1174京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.570831027292806
    },
    {
        "question": " 42.8億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.695106928602368
    },
    {
        "question": " 2270万msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7998207168955296
    },
    {
        "question": " 1351億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.352527557853015
    },
    {
        "question": " 1508msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.17841050712960382
    },
    {
        "question": " 19.9万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.298561253079539
    },
    {
        "question": " 66.7msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 7.824188188312744
    },
    {
        "question": " 450垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.154851031144597
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.21兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8565160540555492
    },
    {
        "question": " 3077兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.931865456092245
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.57兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.417129950037428
    },
    {
        "question": " 5940億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.773776332304426
    },
    {
        "question": " 65.5万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 2.8159514376932346
    },
    {
        "question": " 263usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 5.420170722766663
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.839e+04垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.085449389288662
    },
    {
        "question": " 371兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6328161131566368
    },
    {
        "question": " 432京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.079311582968234
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.13兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8376286371017991
    },
    {
        "question": " 4364億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6399243358459046
    },
    {
        "question": " 809兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.90784630786618
    },
    {
        "question": " 8443nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 0.9264789219664205
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.07年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.258538713027631
    },
    {
        "question": " 18.1年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.75655657426107
    },
    {
        "question": " 2850万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.892469545024324
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.46日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5457950893407169
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.77億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.887832226961708
    },
    {
        "question": " 686万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.4563127944437975
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.97時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.155419442135101
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.99時間は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.855614752643682
    },
    {
        "question": " 4011万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8825481522405207
    },
    {
        "question": " 38.2億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.423816205764087
    },
    {
        "question": " 143万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.378679772067537
    },
    {
        "question": " 535分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.506510668186262
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.9分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.006796874444121
    },
    {
        "question": " 27.9億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9463202951839542
    },
    {
        "question": " 845兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.990450065954743
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.7万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6406983280008214
    },
    {
        "question": " 6706万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.048300519659988
    },
    {
        "question": " 40.1万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.602699250417494
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.17京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.00208977101826
    },
    {
        "question": " 39億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6544093777560753
    },
    {
        "question": " 684億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.278598287032339
    },
    {
        "question": " 2689万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6514501708522618
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.01億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.302697618059526
    },
    {
        "question": " 31.6msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.5003679680728865
    },
    {
        "question": " 958垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.482444944032478
    },
    {
        "question": " 5059京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.76758490521405
    },
    {
        "question": " 936億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4149548591192174
    },
    {
        "question": " 304億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.704365306089156
    },
    {
        "question": " 519万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7149067302354362
    },
    {
        "question": " 6187万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.791457662158562
    },
    {
        "question": " 109usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 5.038621642699736
    },
    {
        "question": " 5649垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.253152831341487
    },
    {
        "question": " 395兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6600848319475994
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.3垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.458012132764367
    },
    {
        "question": " 36兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.777583995587196
    },
    {
        "question": " 5044億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7028092421834016
    },
    {
        "question": " 5770万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.7611922182227246
    },
    {
        "question": " 8956万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.952123150757392
    },
    {
        "question": " 1977年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.8583057549595265
    },
    {
        "question": " 459年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.38247414327277
    },
    {
        "question": " 147年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.666731808157996
    },
    {
        "question": " 87.6億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.380252515404613
    },
    {
        "question": " 8399万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.304417322604447
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.1万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.275499597841451
    },
    {
        "question": " 7135日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.78988772440264
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.23日は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.026089220829478
    },
    {
        "question": " 25.9兆時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.470048276759776
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.7億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.724217584659372
    },
    {
        "question": " 253万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.180619084186452
    },
    {
        "question": " 1866億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.550212855994606
    },
    {
        "question": " 262万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.2598087703189718
    },
    {
        "question": " 672万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.049343435442566
    },
    {
        "question": " 584分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.54477370264923
    },
    {
        "question": " 833分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.6988721938124165
    },
    {
        "question": " 94兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.47431964067964
    },
    {
        "question": " 3311万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5834421308636326
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.09億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.227982263507123
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.24億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.84890997337292
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.4秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.6431180579227282
    },
    {
        "question": " 5533秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.74295334944443
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.43京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.0362152262471955
    },
    {
        "question": " 1237億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.1559823487633363
    },
    {
        "question": " 208億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.7624384425300517
    },
    {
        "question": " 3025万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.702637583041818
    },
    {
        "question": " 33万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5188117851280714
    },
    {
        "question": " 3070msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.487193164086743
    },
    {
        "question": " 4599京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.163840046118187
    },
    {
        "question": " 327兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.5780173630016234
    },
    {
        "question": " 4476兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.094559124213587
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.41京usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.754995824634996
    },
    {
        "question": " 2309兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.363493194435659
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.69兆usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.429766134751143
    },
    {
        "question": " 113垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.5549956433503445
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.37垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.438758392619153
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.44京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.090607832298014
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.79垓nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.667161260689944
    },
    {
        "question": " 75.1兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.8756521114091385
    },
    {
        "question": " 8435億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.92610465699135
    },
    {
        "question": " 35.3億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.548018752261241
    },
    {
        "question": " 8196年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.475889153509392
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.07万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.43029979325699
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.89万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.027787519770037
    },
    {
        "question": " 8163日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.292055844072587
    },
    {
        "question": " 270万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.589184317091293
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.04日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.951777924045972
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.49兆時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.70937306785073
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.82億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.880990929138662
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.03万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.085698427217116
    },
    {
        "question": " 5869時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.324887849738836
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.12時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.050047956038792
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.16億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7789691178677014
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.2億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.962986715592763
    },
    {
        "question": " 27.9万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.666994098937889
    },
    {
        "question": " 543分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.5130524156117415
    },
    {
        "question": " 323兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.010340057074922
    },
    {
        "question": " 18.8万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.3374268996316765
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.97億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.042255020757355
    },
    {
        "question": " 2098万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.543718817910176
    },
    {
        "question": " 2224京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.848280984643127
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.88億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9008891678421826
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.14億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2974796300542346
    },
    {
        "question": " 410万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8347815921711907
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.7万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.986743220779712
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.9msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.144083393193329
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.68京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7260953522615017
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.34兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.70116664848739
    },
    {
        "question": " 1246京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.539053398696597
    },
    {
        "question": " 265億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6457382844744126
    },
    {
        "question": " 362万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5587837290759545
    },
    {
        "question": " 1831億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.262717446649736
    },
    {
        "question": " 153垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.685892932800991
    },
    {
        "question": " 623兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8583031678599318
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.43京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.8297602351871705
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.7京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.6530388828574605
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.27兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.797425780650573
    },
    {
        "question": " 216億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.333886956767018
    },
    {
        "question": " 433億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.636164464998366
    },
    {
        "question": " 388年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.531019863627483
    },
    {
        "question": " 152万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.6188473113971966
    },
    {
        "question": " 2867万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.83763777634148
    },
    {
        "question": " 3663日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.722211511310379
    },
    {
        "question": " 100億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.057520586835831
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.37億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.26025636090244
    },
    {
        "question": " 20.8万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.09670033998687
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.52時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.9577915083676696
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.9時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.505651805740872
    },
    {
        "question": " 529万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0029088812731612
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.1億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.99198836521812
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.3億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.275302679834397
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.17億分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.846619376749619
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.1万分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.955987859590236
    },
    {
        "question": " 9801万秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.49247718187095835
    },
    {
        "question": " 296万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5347411305437964
    },
    {
        "question": " 554万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.1871429712896937
    },
    {
        "question": " 231万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.586165814964581
    },
    {
        "question": " 3139秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.496757991821269
    },
    {
        "question": " 8613億msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4363648967014642
    },
    {
        "question": " 8998万msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.017634865476852113
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.01京msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.447298185326137
    },
    {
        "question": " 34万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7531647312980638
    },
    {
        "question": " 3139億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.496781766662462
    },
    {
        "question": " 1msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 3.0016581223437577
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.27垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.223108798375039
    },
    {
        "question": " 7001兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.908676552365629
    },
    {
        "question": " 11兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.4843231417444755
    },
    {
        "question": " 1825兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.483222060976766
    },
    {
        "question": " 143万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.1566131274793936
    },
    {
        "question": " 883億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.945947353035948
    },
    {
        "question": " 299usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 5.476270743680832
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.058e+06垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.98663613202038
    },
    {
        "question": " 5618垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.813081257845463
    },
    {
        "question": " 167垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.667567173789124
    },
    {
        "question": " 195京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.511176690025029
    },
    {
        "question": " 270億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4318277635729948
    },
    {
        "question": " 18.8兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.274213723064795
    },
    {
        "question": " 54万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 2.732478323153801
    },
    {
        "question": " 737万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.42952121926978
    },
    {
        "question": " 48.4年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.627023400786016
    },
    {
        "question": " 1兆日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.43967912743521
    },
    {
        "question": " 8762日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.322791780752178
    },
    {
        "question": " 50日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.635891567043373
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.43億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.211768085651199
    },
    {
        "question": " 9990時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6193655843346573
    },
    {
        "question": " 348万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.319566905089442
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.01万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.562321533597015
    },
    {
        "question": " 507兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.984769920849061
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.9億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.01432080185309
    },
    {
        "question": " 144分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.38019324380882846
    },
    {
        "question": " 383万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.361206271426951
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.16億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5654722230990239
    },
    {
        "question": " 400兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.665276047006486
    },
    {
        "question": " 24.9億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.839899035827749
    },
    {
        "question": " 891秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1718352227990136
    },
    {
        "question": " 3379秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.528834267467581
    },
    {
        "question": " 373兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.073290633691294
    },
    {
        "question": " 9721億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.0512307716285
    },
    {
        "question": " 1367兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.579511626291396
    },
    {
        "question": " 565兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.974200221106914
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.23億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.348746258291883
    },
    {
        "question": " 594万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.773650260005763
    },
    {
        "question": " 2428京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.886420983338243
    },
    {
        "question": " 4兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6654208405361337
    },
    {
        "question": " 641億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2507815038727077
    },
    {
        "question": " 8160万usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.13351932309194292
    },
    {
        "question": " 40.5兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.606993639060286
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.74億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.572647994766945
    },
    {
        "question": " 390usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 5.590826829961984
    },
    {
        "question": " 88.1垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.446380534360848
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.08垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.7693254085863614
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.09垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.763163940309977
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.38京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.090020513128812
    },
    {
        "question": " 1811兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.2579363947751565
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.4億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.0185824645785586
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.1億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 5.321673494010315
    },
    {
        "question": " 6301年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.74193376898163
    },
    {
        "question": " 5201万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.153763907191175
    },
    {
        "question": " 39.5万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.754677133541572
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.85万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6428693562978149
    },
    {
        "question": " 491時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3110082952723556
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.85時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.771700581054083
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.18万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.629131780038476
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.51億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.093246346858037
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.31兆分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.959458427623101
    },
    {
        "question": " 54億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.954190506882562
    },
    {
        "question": " 8920分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.728510166856772
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.83億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.266500475384259
    },
    {
        "question": " 5685億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.818220296081488
    },
    {
        "question": " 321万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9501208688124314
    },
    {
        "question": " 10億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.222407205065958
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.08垓msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.534351206765754
    },
    {
        "question": " 26.8億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.491053651581854
    },
    {
        "question": " 2215兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.78906227950745
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.51兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.035393658205123
    },
    {
        "question": " 331億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.519864794799863
    },
    {
        "question": " 479msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 5.680524982846378
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.59msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.661785660575951
    },
    {
        "question": " 3711京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.070638867286191
    },
    {
        "question": " 4928京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.756192382199838
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.24兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.536756618457938
    },
    {
        "question": " 1003億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.223099715658566
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.84億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.584792017662049
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.3万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 2.2122673832050275
    },
    {
        "question": " 2747usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.438883942453817
    },
    {
        "question": " 763京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.38378025904323
    },
    {
        "question": " 1540垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.250889154593928
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.83京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.894902817714214
    },
    {
        "question": " 18.2兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4812651251744597
    },
    {
        "question": " 347京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.540224201967222
    },
    {
        "question": " 89.1億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.9498525180682287
    },
    {
        "question": " 36.8万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 2.5656712364710565
    },
    {
        "question": " 84.2年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.868008310417284
    },
    {
        "question": " 1091年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.758524957574958
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.02億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.445620791281377
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.65億日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.802838499181032
    },
    {
        "question": " 664万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.980499664070674
    },
    {
        "question": " 36.1兆時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.61531309551283
    },
    {
        "question": " 2002万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.921255469557787
    },
    {
        "question": " 301万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.256563600257639
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.04億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2977721628769796
    },
    {
        "question": " 151万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.019212624610393
    },
    {
        "question": " 1289億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.33194240097241
    },
    {
        "question": " 66.6分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.6018377646347877
    },
    {
        "question": " 903分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.733987645894766
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.35兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.3675253029696535
    },
    {
        "question": " 380兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.643584916018028
    },
    {
        "question": " 276億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.884594066754816
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.66億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.8898980278873445
    },
    {
        "question": " 78.5万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.894852422280925
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.3秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.3617968058507
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.83垓msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.952588180485698
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.02京msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.368806973975971
    },
    {
        "question": " 55億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.183747711245244
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.2万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.2710253508210825
    },
    {
        "question": " 50.8億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.705537470067559
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.35万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.371481472850315
    },
    {
        "question": " 8561京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.43370724855105
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.91兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8348496366248457
    },
    {
        "question": " 768億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3290555250148472
    },
    {
        "question": " 241億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.604672675550356
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.42兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.534151419714225
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.69万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.4298608659611278
    },
    {
        "question": " 174万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.240368952576844
    },
    {
        "question": " 25.6垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.910222533372517
    },
    {
        "question": " 36.1京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.6216002552413773
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.49垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.986957465180243
    },
    {
        "question": " 4180京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.842988263233224
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.2兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.121817281857494
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.1兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.0422872545911765
    },
    {
        "question": " 4486nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 0.6518661843462159
    },
    {
        "question": " 53.7万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.67246444578268
    },
    {
        "question": " 22.8億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.795642472443682
    },
    {
        "question": " 41万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.993497973631494
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.68日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.9129830698163093
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.1日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.9415612929776564
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.09日は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.975784028968183
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.5兆時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.234497582386442
    },
    {
        "question": " 969億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.605920583203037
    },
    {
        "question": " 97.5時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.7669807697865085
    },
    {
        "question": " 3143時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.053600486600494
    },
    {
        "question": " 49.4時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.250422492074751
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.3億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.4341246416867257
    },
    {
        "question": " 9204万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.805629341923005
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.1億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.267864105544518
    },
    {
        "question": " 1310分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.895282536820897
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.34万分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.415468399699154
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.14兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.556586978753527
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.06兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.089172997044075
    },
    {
        "question": " 256億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.851821877205802
    },
    {
        "question": " 1220万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.3082061497707835
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.08秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.7839427887251844
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.03兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5145047016372115
    },
    {
        "question": " 1336億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.1892937088965114
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.97兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.041967511971151
    },
    {
        "question": " 391兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.81353130047335
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.32億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.969402149486958
    },
    {
        "question": " 162万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.210677924829668
    },
    {
        "question": " 511兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2097579997046737
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.76垓usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.30933163662452
    },
    {
        "question": " 3118京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.937564563127548
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.39兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.751731168218103
    },
    {
        "question": " 2602万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4153537190916954
    },
    {
        "question": " 57.9万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 2.7626383707850852
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.5万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 8.191312534874555
    },
    {
        "question": " 2473京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.894446814476217
    },
    {
        "question": " 93.6京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.034662650997518
    },
    {
        "question": " 4013兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.0471447189279157
    },
    {
        "question": " 1289兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.33216806696359
    },
    {
        "question": " 84.7億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9277914441010471
    },
    {
        "question": " 931万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 0.9688406645986536
    },
    {
        "question": " 24.8億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.394433657030709
    },
    {
        "question": " 639年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.367836844865125
    },
    {
        "question": " 41.1万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.55663384675811
    },
    {
        "question": " 230年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.082435843559026
    },
    {
        "question": " 35.4億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.9867752518711965
    },
    {
        "question": " 372万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.950434476491032
    },
    {
        "question": " 216日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.492466993633225
    },
    {
        "question": " 22.9日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.295614732338464
    },
    {
        "question": " 218億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.395678638718528
    },
    {
        "question": " 58.8億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.389494501366814
    },
    {
        "question": " 2212兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.624209352005796
    },
    {
        "question": " 3135億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.337953626945062
    },
    {
        "question": " 1685万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.448407261496021
    },
    {
        "question": " 677万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.608959563693059
    },
    {
        "question": " 5279分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.500740010525062
    },
    {
        "question": " 140分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.924211688743625
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.75京秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.39050489703217
    },
    {
        "question": " 2639万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4850188828509747
    },
    {
        "question": " 1545億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.632577699596493
    },
    {
        "question": " 189億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.49929734423683
    },
    {
        "question": " 2399秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.380095742752746
    },
    {
        "question": " 1825京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.762465776775478
    },
    {
        "question": " 24.8京msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.458233066956955
    },
    {
        "question": " 3715万msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.013634362020327
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.28兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.944169252838753
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.8兆msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.254376961007122
    },
    {
        "question": " 1059msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.024982502673378
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.6垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.635091788331474
    },
    {
        "question": " 6397兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.869488465273982
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.73兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6824807826664454
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.68兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.787948846941623
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.59億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4135960632240447
    },
    {
        "question": " 824万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.9158870780105746
    },
    {
        "question": " 40.8万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 8.610868514476786
    },
    {
        "question": " 9423京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.4753709277810407
    },
    {
        "question": " 2370京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.4382061176694165
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.4垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.087308476425637
    },
    {
        "question": " 333京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.744579388807354
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.32兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.520653307020929
    },
    {
        "question": " 224億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.350918067699299
    },
    {
        "question": " 99.6億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.998153318448423
    },
    {
        "question": " 46.6年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.389140595575486
    },
    {
        "question": " 82.5年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.415116167835215
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.94億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.389174057021684
    },
    {
        "question": " 317万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.881314359052023
    },
    {
        "question": " 3743日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.7315295204159264
    },
    {
        "question": " 174億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.296793421380809
    },
    {
        "question": " 1139時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6764405457572706
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.28時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.136006453151873
    },
    {
        "question": " 39.7時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.155178523622968
    },
    {
        "question": " 135万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.4087111085632811
    },
    {
        "question": " 1287億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.951075713044849
    },
    {
        "question": " 700億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.067077335927907
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.43万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.932453986877844
    },
    {
        "question": " 1978分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.074296478144047
    },
    {
        "question": " 125億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.596821573783056
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.8兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.288257255571015
    },
    {
        "question": " 23.4億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.81331137003499
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.65億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.783575935358898
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.15万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.332153787303156
    },
    {
        "question": " 35.2京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.047840199955877
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.21京msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.407553069283814
    },
    {
        "question": " 2234億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.792811708921233
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.22兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.568333879750215
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.31億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.117581387163899
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.54万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.5490363785527475
    },
    {
        "question": " 49.6京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.196528862669412
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.17兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1308974137379568
    },
    {
        "question": " 4503兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.0971566767075895
    },
    {
        "question": " 312億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7160718285405183
    },
    {
        "question": " 128億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.107350737636111
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.92万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.2828891099386108
    },
    {
        "question": " 240usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 5.380014907049268
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.596e+05垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.249078385305566
    },
    {
        "question": " 304垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.546943738240747
    },
    {
        "question": " 51.6兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1560469691358366
    },
    {
        "question": " 57.7京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.982941390805096
    },
    {
        "question": " 43.8兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.641375814452723
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.68億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 2.824978482586402
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.04億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 5.017365609204742
    },
    {
        "question": " 845万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.4890230512231
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.44年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.878269282150352
    },
    {
        "question": " 70.9万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.28849417529526
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.01日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.0803890739270403
    },
    {
        "question": " 2106日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.4818501039345175
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.37日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.07223202503881
    },
    {
        "question": " 25.4日は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.340537826722995
    },
    {
        "question": " 46.9兆時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.728560397599807
    },
    {
        "question": " 50.8時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.32602934142921924
    },
    {
        "question": " 2579万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.189539914257148
    },
    {
        "question": " 4591時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.218192228273863
    },
    {
        "question": " 321兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.785398869463444
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.69万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.408940986961763
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.4万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.2801449661858353
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.24分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.127702719999476
    },
    {
        "question": " 707兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.350512043528114
    },
    {
        "question": " 5293万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7871990718813833
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.53億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.100148345943597
    },
    {
        "question": " 1444秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3812674235308664
    },
    {
        "question": " 48.1万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.682109958673232
    },
    {
        "question": " 27.4兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9382952457875335
    },
    {
        "question": " 200兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.363505683897225
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.61兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.378646021238508
    },
    {
        "question": " 75.9万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1023104903341319
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.4万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.0170321423929947
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.25万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.098627237422735
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.5京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.430746664068658
    },
    {
        "question": " 64.3京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.871907465329352
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.92兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.908526112406097
    },
    {
        "question": " 648兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.033429825524844
    },
    {
        "question": " 180万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.25628445024686863
    },
    {
        "question": " 258億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.411068903045228
    },
    {
        "question": " 363usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 5.559801604304431
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.7垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.3879056132232455
    },
    {
        "question": " 37.7京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.6403678593563327
    },
    {
        "question": " 2131兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7723377632897805
    },
    {
        "question": " 171兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.4544741205335985
    },
    {
        "question": " 355億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5501194384354045
    },
    {
        "question": " 2581万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.4117110561311386
    },
    {
        "question": " 51.1億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.708539409384854
    },
    {
        "question": " 108万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.595384821079392
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.01年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.24522943817411
    },
    {
        "question": " 134年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.62732759591724
    },
    {
        "question": " 2226億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.785238223366495
    },
    {
        "question": " 3872万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.968186194855605
    },
    {
        "question": " 579万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.92092453360095
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.18日は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.792355462809242
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.4億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.2446797222921715
    },
    {
        "question": " 75.5時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.49785686304155474
    },
    {
        "question": " 2018時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.083014990676304
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.62時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.9743876277426238
    },
    {
        "question": " 329時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.073384921340615
    },
    {
        "question": " 82.4兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.195169424558584
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.71兆分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.514396535535424
    },
    {
        "question": " 4181億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.843124645389803
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.6万分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.910946452715656
    },
    {
        "question": " 72.9億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.364166055202004
    },
    {
        "question": " 696兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.906047421085463
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.61万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0012443661013082
    },
    {
        "question": " 18.9億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.49730396967713
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.17秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.620175694303709
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.22秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.793765908728572
    },
    {
        "question": " 1490億msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6745115994420658
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.7兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.312598922668807
    },
    {
        "question": " 8952億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.3956133905610795
    },
    {
        "question": " 139億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.36572548302202
    },
    {
        "question": " 30.3億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.481871871071117
    },
    {
        "question": " 46.4msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 7.666382072971563
    },
    {
        "question": " 134京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.629733447408442
    },
    {
        "question": " 18.7京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.334347687439172
    },
    {
        "question": " 1036兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.459140350581839
    },
    {
        "question": " 5680億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.9762041860691943
    },
    {
        "question": " 385億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.585150332089017
    },
    {
        "question": " 1339億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.126635669247355
    },
    {
        "question": " 154万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.187984108406868
    },
    {
        "question": " 596垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.27633565155339
    },
    {
        "question": " 1926兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3482230641813775
    },
    {
        "question": " 180兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6984802870128402
    },
    {
        "question": " 1030京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.23469862772934
    },
    {
        "question": " 492京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.691766080538319
    },
    {
        "question": " 215万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 0.33177931377100345
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.18兆nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.337831764726475
    },
    {
        "question": " 298万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.036434679371446
    },
    {
        "question": " 55.6万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.687904920276974
    },
    {
        "question": " 84年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.645009608340484
    },
    {
        "question": " 86.8年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.437442467062889
    },
    {
        "question": " 1311億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.555292279950438
    },
    {
        "question": " 715万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.234485948627878
    },
    {
        "question": " 1018億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.065062853754647
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.5万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.8088068879367243
    },
    {
        "question": " 166万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.997300545089445
    },
    {
        "question": " 23.3万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.92310337915135
    },
    {
        "question": " 3377兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.807852342299741
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.6億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.974508864750212
    },
    {
        "question": " 45.7億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.88168699293791
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.1万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.927344127348798
    },
    {
        "question": " 188兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.776248892193923
    },
    {
        "question": " 57.5万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.823050931144752
    },
    {
        "question": " 71.1万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2953609148434473
    },
    {
        "question": " 198秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5178840009626251
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.82秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.8338586013780884
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.03秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.904907313456576
    },
    {
        "question": " 26.5京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.92433068003813
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.57億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0445732884204362
    },
    {
        "question": " 6981万msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2876144500361741
    },
    {
        "question": " 848億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.15024467044632
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.05兆msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.310731368536214
    },
    {
        "question": " 857万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.933053298265667
    },
    {
        "question": " 48垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.182187927417559
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.05兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7670655913498312
    },
    {
        "question": " 121京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.527684063420704
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.65億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.43963431535386843
    },
    {
        "question": " 1487兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.172266989899509
    },
    {
        "question": " 986億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.9937930346143125
    },
    {
        "question": " 147usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 5.167906837892979
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.62垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.166249049236837
    },
    {
        "question": " 1537垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.25005878312653
    },
    {
        "question": " 327垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.958720665265133
    },
    {
        "question": " 55京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.96218952332985
    },
    {
        "question": " 246億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3902719923543394
    },
    {
        "question": " 389億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.589988196399586
    },
    {
        "question": " 369億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.566567118976691
    },
    {
        "question": " 153年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.74647017487151
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.55年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.133667291581711
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.6万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.463083401822095
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.81億日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.961376372576563
    },
    {
        "question": " 70.9日は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.787217868214782
    },
    {
        "question": " 77.8億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.948573387442869
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.53万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.804711151787144
    },
    {
        "question": " 43.9万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.420863449132204
    },
    {
        "question": " 1240時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.649732516537672
    },
    {
        "question": " 82.7万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.19703880012109765
    },
    {
        "question": " 171万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.0739484326931796
    },
    {
        "question": " 1358億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.354892978668289
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.56万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.656485092070163
    },
    {
        "question": " 620分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.570451001800363
    },
    {
        "question": " 7151兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.355586234416947
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.82億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.513986216071957
    },
    {
        "question": " 4958億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.138965542836411
    },
    {
        "question": " 4376秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8629017837531525
    },
    {
        "question": " 1043億msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5194485939174698
    },
    {
        "question": " 1401億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.210009990540772
    },
    {
        "question": " 3409兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.976283817868143
    },
    {
        "question": " 256万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6298381714087962
    },
    {
        "question": " 4344msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6378896665111478
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.32msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 3.919914419387429
    },
    {
        "question": " 262京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.919084995788559
    },
    {
        "question": " 1291京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.17448332478378
    },
    {
        "question": " 984兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.436746454615293
    },
    {
        "question": " 40.1億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.824469325033885
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.6兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.2190623709327735
    },
    {
        "question": " 413万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.615579160898381
    },
    {
        "question": " 482usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 5.682830392679255
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.5京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6636974093911119
    },
    {
        "question": " 95.8京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.044906152872211
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.43京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.979357362809113
    },
    {
        "question": " 4553京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.880157678870031
    },
    {
        "question": " 284京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.452867575813055
    },
    {
        "question": " 32.3億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.509137097502583
    },
    {
        "question": " 45万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 2.653556056724655
    },
    {
        "question": " 21.9年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.060685412053655
    },
    {
        "question": " 1731日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6761139175942432
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.29万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.897530156142853
    },
    {
        "question": " 353日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.705878111345268
    },
    {
        "question": " 5457億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.794475581347758
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.02億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.320601965364123
    },
    {
        "question": " 380万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.357778969145903
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.06万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.579743337234435
    },
    {
        "question": " 662万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0999129686597942
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.33億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.208243193997698
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.04万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2392369228648557
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.1万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.985935151694102
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.32分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.747515290902863
    },
    {
        "question": " 394兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.096379594641268
    },
    {
        "question": " 984億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.05670034178965
    },
    {
        "question": " 1599万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.647480792066694
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.54億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.408105227520586
    },
    {
        "question": " 571秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.756905068021969
    },
    {
        "question": " 7081億msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3513090562264662
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.47京msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.713562318842175
    },
    {
        "question": " 269兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.873094075105019
    },
    {
        "question": " 251億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.621831737808995
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.56万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7449022371555012
    },
    {
        "question": " 52.2京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.219096707567989
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.93兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6574536213116975
    },
    {
        "question": " 22.8京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.801565848629174
    },
    {
        "question": " 37.4兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.795135253490198
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.2兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.342088430623774
    },
    {
        "question": " 6936usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 0.8411395364570662
    },
    {
        "question": " 18usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 4.256422693227961
    },
    {
        "question": " 102垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.508566591171472
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.66京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7320433135539934
    },
    {
        "question": " 3127京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.938784657724066
    },
    {
        "question": " 6140兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.0099920244493195
    },
    {
        "question": " 338億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5287894473350927
    },
    {
        "question": " 1429億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.155159501340662
    },
    {
        "question": " 6661nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 0.8235098035165611
    },
    {
        "question": " 26.1年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.9791645587008286
    },
    {
        "question": " 1658年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.940319167699794
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.74年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.072241080129297
    },
    {
        "question": " 501日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.1377145554325021
    },
    {
        "question": " 188日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.6542697818695102
    },
    {
        "question": " 18.5万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.424518213654345
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.36日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.3096147405638146
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.39万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.201622768710068
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.8万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.8458288142958685
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.8万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.003988415173801
    },
    {
        "question": " 222時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.9019801552938835
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.02億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2881542216422233
    },
    {
        "question": " 263億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.261554792554012
    },
    {
        "question": " 280億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.669676001727385
    },
    {
        "question": " 2240万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.128466348711102
    },
    {
        "question": " 107分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.806649987028756
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.14分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.738878952271016
    },
    {
        "question": " 31京秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.992120783497798
    },
    {
        "question": " 123兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.15363560392009
    },
    {
        "question": " 447万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.093732519507053
    },
    {
        "question": " 404秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8277578891954696
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.27兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8564643258131897
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.64億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0476295580021644
    },
    {
        "question": " 183億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.70554058480304
    },
    {
        "question": " 26.2兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.640211186339803
    },
    {
        "question": " 1776msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.2495319955548303
    },
    {
        "question": " 984msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 8.992780126416847
    },
    {
        "question": " 4913京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.192512485592098
    },
    {
        "question": " 102京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.074211796620982
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.7兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.6665633648371507
    },
    {
        "question": " 9807万usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.21340345711025277
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.38兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.377370152316213
    },
    {
        "question": " 2159万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.334268365498788
    },
    {
        "question": " 813usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 5.9102300344022645
    },
    {
        "question": " 745垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.373566382013274
    },
    {
        "question": " 1260京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.163933526992227
    },
    {
        "question": " 1972京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.738704354637123
    },
    {
        "question": " 621億nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.015242154783798867
    },
    {
        "question": " 28.3億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.4521861518329784
    },
    {
        "question": " 259兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.41318702253931
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.33兆nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.969977498978064
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.24年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.657437305302474
    },
    {
        "question": " 2028年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.02763380364471
    },
    {
        "question": " 1861日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7073915277757314
    },
    {
        "question": " 1418日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.531917030481647
    },
    {
        "question": " 98.9日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.15333293077558
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.2万日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.987375651218468
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.62日は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.35502155811688
    },
    {
        "question": " 22.8万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4150203642542625
    },
    {
        "question": " 291時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0842728982736305
    },
    {
        "question": " 29.2時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.2437121407182845
    },
    {
        "question": " 235億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.650570259781148
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.2億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.889691197215057
    },
    {
        "question": " 4748億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.898402841699848
    },
    {
        "question": " 104分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.794033234038773
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.3兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.019867538696924
    },
    {
        "question": " 550兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.803496593895723
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.66億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.328022636861131
    },
    {
        "question": " 441万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.86603151604278
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.5秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.16091839534131
    },
    {
        "question": " 77兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.387534808469886
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.86兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.520050305595151
    },
    {
        "question": " 915兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.404901698908935
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.05億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.706365449380622
    },
    {
        "question": " 82.9億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.91840647215032
    },
    {
        "question": " 523msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 5.718423307316108
    },
    {
        "question": " 77msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 7.886261754174193
    },
    {
        "question": " 53.2垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.227208523782995
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.33兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9839860864737513
    },
    {
        "question": " 37.6京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.019136607057026
    },
    {
        "question": " 33.8兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.751215807199312
    },
    {
        "question": " 4063億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.608830338818867
    },
    {
        "question": " 3390万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.530147613466408
    },
    {
        "question": " 38.2usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 4.582224280404973
    },
    {
        "question": " 32.8垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.017537486904859
    },
    {
        "question": " 3075京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.551291482758085
    },
    {
        "question": " 25.2兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8449476830113878
    },
    {
        "question": " 8051京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.127692804561107
    },
    {
        "question": " 144京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.157034754866139
    },
    {
        "question": " 131億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.117899136889668
    },
    {
        "question": " 4167万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.619825518286903
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.62万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.312388274198998
    },
    {
        "question": " 6549年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.758662736553127
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.08兆日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.471692300930739
    },
    {
        "question": " 314万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.654889897018192
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.12万日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.263076505293279
    },
    {
        "question": " 9337時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.02768458620659553
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.33万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.744159711132469
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.26時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4075973610780697
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.61万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.97291065736794
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.53時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.299327138798618
    },
    {
        "question": " 33.7兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.806986898622982
    },
    {
        "question": " 169億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.068364701522968
    },
    {
        "question": " 3214億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.728928924671248
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.84兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.395775248192535
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.4兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.222418310369838
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.91億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.439609757197436
    },
    {
        "question": " 602万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.001522572145406
    },
    {
        "question": " 3234秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.509736420498524
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.81垓msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.758355267449229
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.9京msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.237043264570952
    },
    {
        "question": " 29.1億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9070618380568956
    },
    {
        "question": " 4931万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9147713578054812
    },
    {
        "question": " 1210億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.082724799648293
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.6万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.023547185079401
    },
    {
        "question": " 70.5京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.3495390825159275
    },
    {
        "question": " 409京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.675372874473251
    },
    {
        "question": " 1006京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.44633677495723
    },
    {
        "question": " 957億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.202551951016781
    },
    {
        "question": " 8420億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.9253372555663635
    },
    {
        "question": " 3589usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 0.5550046130202191
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.18usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 3.5023697211988702
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.138e+05垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.557466884390818
    },
    {
        "question": " 1191垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.13948997194407
    },
    {
        "question": " 720京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.301072906562643
    },
    {
        "question": " 9390京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.194498656185939
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.6兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.06478632412202
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.86兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.269734834289529
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.05億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 5.020125599608981
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.74年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.183848026759373
    },
    {
        "question": " 1172年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.789443726799806
    },
    {
        "question": " 6551万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.253977815511751
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.15万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.168883671765433
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.53日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.7063536400581745
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.8億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.198118757813321
    },
    {
        "question": " 6285時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4180975090410097
    },
    {
        "question": " 163時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.9891396442529024
    },
    {
        "question": " 172時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.792172277288948
    },
    {
        "question": " 821時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.47059669327996
    },
    {
        "question": " 29.4億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.7470676222497357
    },
    {
        "question": " 5150億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.553416215669179
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.74万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7948943277510754
    },
    {
        "question": " 569分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.532925414070963
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.62万分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.19633369538799
    },
    {
        "question": " 84.8兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.429659620158535
    },
    {
        "question": " 8144億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.974362192314891
    },
    {
        "question": " 16億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.646969999272123
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.89億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.812357013126108
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.21秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.345196681853043
    },
    {
        "question": " 44兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.1441993301957916
    },
    {
        "question": " 252兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.465555781081285
    },
    {
        "question": " 27.3億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8801344101252058
    },
    {
        "question": " 77.8兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.112615767543291
    },
    {
        "question": " 126億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.0990291594114225
    },
    {
        "question": " 43.7msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.6403262346347995
    },
    {
        "question": " 2040兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8108296615813901
    },
    {
        "question": " 3811兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.644523688791446
    },
    {
        "question": " 78.6億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.3391399853182586
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.88京usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.495483872282428
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.81兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.44903708681937
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.75億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.942198349234742
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.03万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 7.3081765732907815
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.947e+05垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.097456276244282
    },
    {
        "question": " 45.5京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.72117952182946
    },
    {
        "question": " 33.1垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.963347010757337
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.06京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.708017209034793
    },
    {
        "question": " 7661億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8842575976732157
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.4兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.056353003260955
    },
    {
        "question": " 1633万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.213091373948137
    },
    {
        "question": " 29.6年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.033487854785594
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.14万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.273042963067542
    },
    {
        "question": " 88.4万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.3842556016011383
    },
    {
        "question": " 29.1日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.843910234299033
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.91日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.9979863529977253
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.14万日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.994845104404282
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.19億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.679191057416048
    },
    {
        "question": " 531時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3450369345497803
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.25万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.130434687040147
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.05万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.163925757905302
    },
    {
        "question": " 1822兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.539878642206487
    },
    {
        "question": " 1020万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.8501892343746658
    },
    {
        "question": " 5058分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9258542653447341
    },
    {
        "question": " 99.9万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.777684056017282
    },
    {
        "question": " 162億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7119271150600612
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.2億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.271737224284935
    },
    {
        "question": " 400億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.045217780531016
    },
    {
        "question": " 136万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.355670101369408
    },
    {
        "question": " 88.1秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.944945197347504
    },
    {
        "question": " 174秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.240888775525528
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.76兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.076635491308082
    },
    {
        "question": " 512兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.77253593636472
    },
    {
        "question": " 206億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.7574629510324487
    },
    {
        "question": " 6346億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.024351795362145
    },
    {
        "question": " 48.8万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.688791777524292
    },
    {
        "question": " 91.6msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.96206646631232
    },
    {
        "question": " 870msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 8.939602335466128
    },
    {
        "question": " 3065垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.987644755846821
    },
    {
        "question": " 386京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.649628033449153
    },
    {
        "question": " 2589億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8568186150442845
    },
    {
        "question": " 123億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.31105554864015
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.6億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2051495594948545
    },
    {
        "question": " 215万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.3321382477584818
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.85万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 7.686038917061573
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.454e+04垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.149984408066578
    },
    {
        "question": " 21.9垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.403807567177037
    },
    {
        "question": " 85.2垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.374152354076248
    },
    {
        "question": " 60.6兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.004143545295306
    },
    {
        "question": " 348兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.541058549478044
    },
    {
        "question": " 121万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 0.08433871579599406
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.2兆nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.080469756737342
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.57年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.3081021103072796
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.16年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.2762268193725985
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.4年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.141835697015477
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.82億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.8878525928467
    },
    {
        "question": " 1668日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.60241409348292
    },
    {
        "question": " 64.7億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.868552474579864
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.64万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8342052337236834
    },
    {
        "question": " 131時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.897074313518983
    },
    {
        "question": " 965時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.541032181327263
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.38億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8077551088483723
    },
    {
        "question": " 26.1億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.257945421904316
    },
    {
        "question": " 324億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.732737915107986
    },
    {
        "question": " 440万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.421173104865133
    },
    {
        "question": " 88兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.4456397375996115
    },
    {
        "question": " 4675億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.73324245850282
    },
    {
        "question": " 299億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.919410771570474
    },
    {
        "question": " 5475秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9602498980491423
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.86秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.895349370821789
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.79兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9472261312250738
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.2兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.569111799957971
    },
    {
        "question": " 100兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.44581502882359
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.26兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.94315414331268
    },
    {
        "question": " 1284億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.108711057570899
    },
    {
        "question": " 3327msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.522097441894562
    },
    {
        "question": " 253兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9051446805558261
    },
    {
        "question": " 370兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.632168836929414
    },
    {
        "question": " 2327億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8105486618229039
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.67億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.44480149279883086
    },
    {
        "question": " 38.3兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.583661482241437
    },
    {
        "question": " 528万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.7224371185243443
    },
    {
        "question": " 532垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.2267344057716
    },
    {
        "question": " 368兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.629815912185091
    },
    {
        "question": " 23.9兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8223865538724517
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.79兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6668829424524612
    },
    {
        "question": " 203京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.306831761719824
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.95億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 2.695017066284615
    },
    {
        "question": " 61.5億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.788808633192631
    },
    {
        "question": " 7669年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.4470668778506415
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.51万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.179116791808685
    },
    {
        "question": " 275日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.597519234842735
    },
    {
        "question": " 24.6兆時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.448882779301154
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.9億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.656725521965795
    },
    {
        "question": " 297時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.250837007361197
    },
    {
        "question": " 3717兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.849527947986852
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.31兆分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.9593434473021
    },
    {
        "question": " 260万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.637641474149205
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.15万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.276249635314071
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.94分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.373188419727711
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.83億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2667974696431916
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.7億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.1999961586982915
    },
    {
        "question": " 143万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5989368579763514
    },
    {
        "question": " 2116万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.547331373833549
    },
    {
        "question": " 894万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.951492546300356
    },
    {
        "question": " 1357秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.132446142176056
    },
    {
        "question": " 28.2京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.951746054050759
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.11兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.771856856008842
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.48京msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.985230244115435
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.2兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.230491252073598
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.56万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4082046883585975
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.16万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.06374251095059
    },
    {
        "question": " 8081msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.90744329270473
    },
    {
        "question": " 360垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.057372966043069
    },
    {
        "question": " 155兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.252530572468566
    },
    {
        "question": " 3062兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.929754807875799
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.87兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.990217648893383
    },
    {
        "question": " 1133万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0540958414017865
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.72億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.82750449599513
    },
    {
        "question": " 212万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.32565301883534
    },
    {
        "question": " 2881垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.960676608683729
    },
    {
        "question": " 4908兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7543659480005347
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.99垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.443310156120049
    },
    {
        "question": " 34.8京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.763913683949793
    },
    {
        "question": " 167京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.221984158506228
    },
    {
        "question": " 161兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.206543326662846
    },
    {
        "question": " 19億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.279022336289534
    },
    {
        "question": " 1160年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.626861790827458
    },
    {
        "question": " 868日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.3760809020667155
    },
    {
        "question": " 92.4万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.345797822432679
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.08万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.008557661002554
    },
    {
        "question": " 3422億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.591732178744031
    },
    {
        "question": " 247万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.012219545511477
    },
    {
        "question": " 44.6万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.427677786349907
    },
    {
        "question": " 162時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.765895750816883
    },
    {
        "question": " 172万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5149080969262498
    },
    {
        "question": " 28.7億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.298968769886734
    },
    {
        "question": " 387万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.809519539907923
    },
    {
        "question": " 3780分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.35565996310739
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.65分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.529939502112608
    },
    {
        "question": " 604兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.2819494538386085
    },
    {
        "question": " 169兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.291368684993566
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.24兆秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.537400548700786
    },
    {
        "question": " 237万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.59590972488011
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.1秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.046409547251571
    },
    {
        "question": " 1882秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.274659278623883
    },
    {
        "question": " 1279兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.607908657218588
    },
    {
        "question": " 18.8兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.337212851145281
    },
    {
        "question": " 464兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.110312984482277
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.8万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.47154693896117816
    },
    {
        "question": " 1588msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.20097465284257265
    },
    {
        "question": " 6645msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.82249936840856
    },
    {
        "question": " 47.3京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.176109149045086
    },
    {
        "question": " 4281兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.695046511121036
    },
    {
        "question": " 2682億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8721786883791747
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.9兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.395274280823983
    },
    {
        "question": " 511億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.708194751727187
    },
    {
        "question": " 306億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.4850813732823
    },
    {
        "question": " 3usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 3.4764751932656477
    },
    {
        "question": " 3075垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.989019661169086
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.09垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.9139833956085806
    },
    {
        "question": " 177京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.690631210288441
    },
    {
        "question": " 6901兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.060743200258279
    },
    {
        "question": " 3469兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.540171729003474
    },
    {
        "question": " 900兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.954403265073994
    },
    {
        "question": " 772億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.887544562358465
    },
    {
        "question": " 195万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.851636795639688
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.86年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.889810105710347
    },
    {
        "question": " 49.4年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.19292954759912
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.25億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.233402713829049
    },
    {
        "question": " 8748日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.322095443173506
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.04日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.173850053788616
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.51万日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.11685633412107
    },
    {
        "question": " 4496万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.710285693017034
    },
    {
        "question": " 29.8億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.094052667026881
    },
    {
        "question": " 120時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.855936346837212
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.14時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.8863211900682226
    },
    {
        "question": " 182兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.538627261714655
    },
    {
        "question": " 710万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.6930407792541176
    },
    {
        "question": " 3098分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7129282909468058
    },
    {
        "question": " 720兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.358569389659905
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.81億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.896662658523854
    },
    {
        "question": " 150万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.620310362018128
    },
    {
        "question": " 1209億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.304176591732507
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.14秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.961014334687807
    },
    {
        "question": " 70.5兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.349347179116844
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.04京msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.08125592351352
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.43京msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.829008487282437
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.73兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.460682047441605
    },
    {
        "question": " 60.1万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7785402254145195
    },
    {
        "question": " 21.3msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.3292171884561945
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.13msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.61636163890691
    },
    {
        "question": " 1199京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.580021819480386
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.91垓usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.903053882106445
    },
    {
        "question": " 50.3兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.145056013985551
    },
    {
        "question": " 1436兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.37897651942551
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.31兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.800267948456086
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.46億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.163262366981593
    },
    {
        "question": " 9306京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.4699781019755527
    },
    {
        "question": " 89.8京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.016826029720727
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.15兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.40497205421241467
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.28垓nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.328861793635395
    },
    {
        "question": " 323京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.508974951191645
    },
    {
        "question": " 240兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.37957433342121
    },
    {
        "question": " 221億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.343918566771851
    },
    {
        "question": " 1672万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.78561542173214
    },
    {
        "question": " 200年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.242460133166987
    },
    {
        "question": " 63.8万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.2427563601191722
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.63億日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.592674958320682
    },
    {
        "question": " 120日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.014746832893079
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.37日は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.803825352434457
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.3万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2414172981371518
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.76億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.562212421851552
    },
    {
        "question": " 732万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.642492898487472
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.22時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.181786556930348
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.97時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.028801664988338
    },
    {
        "question": " 105万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.30149273971175283
    },
    {
        "question": " 163万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.053158256845138
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.23億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.310026518025259
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.23分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.74327224023416
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.44億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6600483438041693
    },
    {
        "question": " 5190億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.778696387738675
    },
    {
        "question": " 6510億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.257291260589954
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.79万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.984236806823054
    },
    {
        "question": " 803兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.405742850739816
    },
    {
        "question": " 1899億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.342124776587432
    },
    {
        "question": " 4526万msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0994207594263794
    },
    {
        "question": " 26.5億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.64525546887702
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.28兆msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.106529533933221
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.99万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.999749044503465
    },
    {
        "question": " 508msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 8.705610913066664
    },
    {
        "question": " 114兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5564945276003308
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.79京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.642688762139604
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.17京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.511113833500389
    },
    {
        "question": " 76.4兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.104894039590729
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.68億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2264502952219987
    },
    {
        "question": " 4335万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.636989142966199
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.39万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 7.143148454999075
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.49京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.4303535527985136
    },
    {
        "question": " 21.1京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.3874533238679994
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.43京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.598693377551596
    },
    {
        "question": " 23.1京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.585946247030009
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.39京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.530485869620912
    },
    {
        "question": " 3330億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.522404806357903
    },
    {
        "question": " 8209億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.914265748323775
    },
    {
        "question": " 449万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.214583195707851
    },
    {
        "question": " 9776年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.71082858027426
    },
    {
        "question": " 108万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.470043555180421
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.68億日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.80777991931537
    },
    {
        "question": " 130億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.171199939296895
    },
    {
        "question": " 60.6万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.402402098951082
    },
    {
        "question": " 7345時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.422302904411798
    },
    {
        "question": " 117億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.34571946915534
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.59億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.721878482950078
    },
    {
        "question": " 234万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.59026219425459
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.61分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3356345950252457
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.1兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.286704984672812
    },
    {
        "question": " 110万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1056957226680697
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.3万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5982038639074692
    },
    {
        "question": " 91.9秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.18528134777521243
    },
    {
        "question": " 226秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.354526545711666
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.18兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5717346563685075
    },
    {
        "question": " 786億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9591107160606542
    },
    {
        "question": " 2665兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.86935802080724
    },
    {
        "question": " 29.4兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.689938621693944
    },
    {
        "question": " 18.3万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.261370333623558
    },
    {
        "question": " 606万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.782726333537305
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.2京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.6545141985234055
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.38兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4399806779643698
    },
    {
        "question": " 261京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.860647786695417
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.03兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.5294307513927565
    },
    {
        "question": " 3075万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.48784873875197
    },
    {
        "question": " 18.3億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.262040324977875
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.36京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.3680498115706232
    },
    {
        "question": " 353垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.610752828679471
    },
    {
        "question": " 9133兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.4043335858930233
    },
    {
        "question": " 130京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.335055510681681
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.38兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.923127988854811
    },
    {
        "question": " 112万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 0.04755166218198936
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.27億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 5.3554636393226005
    },
    {
        "question": " 281年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.010459288231135
    },
    {
        "question": " 2558年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.350433505340185
    },
    {
        "question": " 395年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.317144853825615
    },
    {
        "question": " 18.9億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.713178264148736
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.57日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.789580341413456
    },
    {
        "question": " 277万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.600611908837807
    },
    {
        "question": " 300日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.414182948464054
    },
    {
        "question": " 300億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.534210054320548
    },
    {
        "question": " 5208万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.336448962814814
    },
    {
        "question": " 36万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.112128714802019
    },
    {
        "question": " 291時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.019547339283282
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.54兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.259019012503883
    },
    {
        "question": " 690億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.680695415019327
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.3億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.433387128544529
    },
    {
        "question": " 19.1万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.059883538098353
    },
    {
        "question": " 24分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.158919235382054
    },
    {
        "question": " 5572兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.247199044004258
    },
    {
        "question": " 46.6億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.732014068431525
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.72億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.678734551127727
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.43億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.378362537715606
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.29秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.110705950774042
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.15垓msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.561606419185985
    },
    {
        "question": " 29.8京msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.537035932483258
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.06億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4669799243347126
    },
    {
        "question": " 120億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.30047347972153
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.27万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.104847994382696
    },
    {
        "question": " 24.8万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.394191709124879
    },
    {
        "question": " 9341msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.97040401577643
    },
    {
        "question": " 1368垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.637377304786206
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.44兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7103951262871964
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.88兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9029820205197208
    },
    {
        "question": " 2738億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.65926633253716
    },
    {
        "question": " 108億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.034797704800313
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.29万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.3606609057960861
    },
    {
        "question": " 101万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.003524401466393
    },
    {
        "question": " 2026垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.8077573773132976
    },
    {
        "question": " 504兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7663286633355204
    },
    {
        "question": " 346兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9827894594497397
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.07兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2506680855309282
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.43兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.15592211061003
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.34兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.865860683892021
    },
    {
        "question": " 184億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.265487734474412
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.38年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.939521050369016
    },
    {
        "question": " 198年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.796553110173301
    },
    {
        "question": " 88.2億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.383025087895892
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.48万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.921988143211897
    },
    {
        "question": " 82.8万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.076286994395472
    },
    {
        "question": " 180日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.1927829938030685
    },
    {
        "question": " 182万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.31755014170988
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.13万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.3296780445894014
    },
    {
        "question": " 101時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.782305251833191
    },
    {
        "question": " 3365時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.083324479958515
    },
    {
        "question": " 32.3兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.788882720249637
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.26兆分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.638013148160114
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.95万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.1737850175756033
    },
    {
        "question": " 16万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.983242966428466
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.9分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.005323906243501
    },
    {
        "question": " 5636兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.252153602129136
    },
    {
        "question": " 779兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.955255533986321
    },
    {
        "question": " 23億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.806342202779388
    },
    {
        "question": " 1972万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.516688650906629
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.72秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.673842302968579
    },
    {
        "question": " 509兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.207752575290761
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.35兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.58865102643407
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.55兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.63434211767389
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.98兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.821679171726283
    },
    {
        "question": " 1582億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.19934221044253
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.6msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 7.099681561921579
    },
    {
        "question": " 42.1京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.125370344922121
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.19兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1387314005870852
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.58京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.641565955790597
    },
    {
        "question": " 29京usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.683832945556778
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.77兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.830557936013978
    },
    {
        "question": " 1416億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.151083360352075
    },
    {
        "question": " 30.1垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.979309551633224
    },
    {
        "question": " 59.9京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.8408726607706667
    },
    {
        "question": " 42.6兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.072745594609562
    },
    {
        "question": " 171京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.455480002706265
    },
    {
        "question": " 600億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7780283353001891
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.26兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.513604938306222
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.2億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.007645063530099
    },
    {
        "question": " 19.8年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.859064732252061
    },
    {
        "question": " 849億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.366396975026575
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.44万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.537168890932401
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.08日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.19271976699984
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.93日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.221183145273862
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.54万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.24402157852532302
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.66万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.183674721160269
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.6億時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.983029571979229
    },
    {
        "question": " 326万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7920488327648367
    },
    {
        "question": " 2622万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.2603203625367865
    },
    {
        "question": " 5308万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.946810622819996
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.43分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.649390662425708
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.66兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.720765970217002
    },
    {
        "question": " 54.4兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.798898196081419
    },
    {
        "question": " 1051万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.465291456818459
    },
    {
        "question": " 40.5万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.8291899396271023
    },
    {
        "question": " 246万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.390535310284054
    },
    {
        "question": " 1689億msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7287346243267645
    },
    {
        "question": " 4419億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.708790223081321
    },
    {
        "question": " 4296兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.076734915067261
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.29兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.331912417208497
    },
    {
        "question": " 3674億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.565193365814586
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.69msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.229067027869782
    },
    {
        "question": " 23京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.863736167431883
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.83京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.515861919011361
    },
    {
        "question": " 28.8兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.903430685378896
    },
    {
        "question": " 29.4兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.689683986110338
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.8億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8921758837902334
    },
    {
        "question": " 1775億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.249244194618964
    },
    {
        "question": " 620万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.792508827106348
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.37垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.23078233369975
    },
    {
        "question": " 2491京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.459834899538207
    },
    {
        "question": " 55.6垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.188838967393153
    },
    {
        "question": " 396京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.819655659066584
    },
    {
        "question": " 79.1兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.897967875012434
    },
    {
        "question": " 365万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 0.5618944968766637
    },
    {
        "question": " 9037億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.956027280532595
    },
    {
        "question": " 23年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.859662286713395
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.51万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.091615459046552
    },
    {
        "question": " 40.3万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.985751451949664
    },
    {
        "question": " 109日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.195882932219514
    },
    {
        "question": " 5414億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.790999919958546
    },
    {
        "question": " 19.9万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.918005140707815
    },
    {
        "question": " 8885万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.726822810627096
    },
    {
        "question": " 127万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.660520265993188
    },
    {
        "question": " 23.6兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.651983851011095
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.09兆分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.879333337370793
    },
    {
        "question": " 185億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.488327994862955
    },
    {
        "question": " 670分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.604324653010295
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.89万分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.368148396196402
    },
    {
        "question": " 374兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.074294539499605
    },
    {
        "question": " 3764億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.639173421091195
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.02億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.454421202747354
    },
    {
        "question": " 818億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.13442602215906
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.19京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.576917796746626
    },
    {
        "question": " 72.2京msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.92191094488118
    },
    {
        "question": " 309億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.93315305489922
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.27兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.324628430692206
    },
    {
        "question": " 67.4万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8289449724802838
    },
    {
        "question": " 2233msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.3488335248144425
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.57msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.195673329091678
    },
    {
        "question": " 438兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1429843779130078
    },
    {
        "question": " 1926兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.348115347820495
    },
    {
        "question": " 26.4京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.865597961570192
    },
    {
        "question": " 13京usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.335191785516358
    },
    {
        "question": " 452兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.655035103880088
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.85万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.7673022033227204
    },
    {
        "question": " 554垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.245032743775743
    },
    {
        "question": " 26.8垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.491638083345247
    },
    {
        "question": " 2280京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.801576536783598
    },
    {
        "question": " 3129兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.717220098258178
    },
    {
        "question": " 44.2億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6458438499581309
    },
    {
        "question": " 7112億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.851996492459278
    },
    {
        "question": " 42.7億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.630539913306004
    },
    {
        "question": " 991年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.558274239320523
    },
    {
        "question": " 1581年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.14150286614625
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.49年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.151410292041735
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.11兆日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.48282004740116
    },
    {
        "question": " 78.5万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.274997797244669
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.26万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.257415417399237
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.97万日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.230330911516422
    },
    {
        "question": " 32.4万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5686851338600283
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.45万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.492146308745342
    },
    {
        "question": " 888時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.726390914977149
    },
    {
        "question": " 855時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.488104587146872
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.55時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.372624147374908
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.28兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.6372122133084535
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.91万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1230518745661688
    },
    {
        "question": " 189万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.4982950023549195
    },
    {
        "question": " 109分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.813860992260415
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.48京秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.670866548677248
    },
    {
        "question": " 2540万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.468289490833783
    },
    {
        "question": " 8768億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.386581016382483
    },
    {
        "question": " 29.2億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.686568811052155
    },
    {
        "question": " 91.6秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.961934857793474
    },
    {
        "question": " 521秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.716638815288409
    },
    {
        "question": " 2665兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.926869197413458
    },
    {
        "question": " 5096兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.7707573543804465
    },
    {
        "question": " 213兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.772129812887555
    },
    {
        "question": " 34.8兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.763113196687689
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.01万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6999977444591752
    },
    {
        "question": " 29.1msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.463712929045332
    },
    {
        "question": " 19.5京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.790890812158483
    },
    {
        "question": " 3兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5407277384422602
    },
    {
        "question": " 1859京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.713013680031883
    },
    {
        "question": " 43.4億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8595293935988844
    },
    {
        "question": " 115兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.059061917374951
    },
    {
        "question": " 3274usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 0.5150871399974255
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.3usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 4.052844186257198
    },
    {
        "question": " 53.8垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.232371138029901
    },
    {
        "question": " 549兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.803226225616539
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.3垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.455623999634685
    },
    {
        "question": " 7024億nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0684245004542148
    },
    {
        "question": " 23.2京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.365700824684911
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.3億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.123099403397407
    },
    {
        "question": " 527億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.721864869291906
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.07年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.267180826764827
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.71万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.376182365074932
    },
    {
        "question": " 104億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.456211222679112
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.94万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.668985252364704
    },
    {
        "question": " 244万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.545738932552489
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.18万日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.7275472292318
    },
    {
        "question": " 171億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.291603353735064
    },
    {
        "question": " 416時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.239394273475779
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.45万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.167894436874169
    },
    {
        "question": " 261時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.972742037079803
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.24億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.37115536126969
    },
    {
        "question": " 31億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.333324302807295
    },
    {
        "question": " 3605億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.778708950308362
    },
    {
        "question": " 2439万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.16530490909902
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.67万分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.204802699593715
    },
    {
        "question": " 30億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9777526093633568
    },
    {
        "question": " 122万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1501166043742173
    },
    {
        "question": " 9690億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.43004241937236
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.77万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9830372956818385
    },
    {
        "question": " 29.6万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.470733941124484
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.75秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.242932875252695
    },
    {
        "question": " 8729億msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.442166818183529
    },
    {
        "question": " 60億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8416055429413614
    },
    {
        "question": " 66兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.263251851614343
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.32兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.5869677722106434
    },
    {
        "question": " 67.2万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8271194856706705
    },
    {
        "question": " 1414垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.651668040921958
    },
    {
        "question": " 298兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.537746373659405
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.59兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8571600235710557
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.81億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9036743315307172
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.15兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.498591429753998
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.14億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.960752728027755
    },
    {
        "question": " 3596垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.057043820188074
    },
    {
        "question": " 623垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.857668381260039
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.27垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.165609788345407
    },
    {
        "question": " 445京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.870602865295618
    },
    {
        "question": " 24.7京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.392901426770324
    },
    {
        "question": " 803万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 0.904926902104094
    },
    {
        "question": " 203万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 3.306843467771279
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.5年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.738274374941655
    },
    {
        "question": " 39.4年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.316561545168733
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.12億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.931341202531967
    },
    {
        "question": " 8806万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.324994943181283
    },
    {
        "question": " 20.6億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.370972726177076
    },
    {
        "question": " 50.9億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.326175544955074
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.07時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7356903488730233
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.08時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.261790217335316
    },
    {
        "question": " 604兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.060334309100163
    },
    {
        "question": " 71.2億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.6939468841010665
    },
    {
        "question": " 20.3万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.5292953282173745
    },
    {
        "question": " 2352万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.149638502733152
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.7億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.748911293344988
    },
    {
        "question": " 619億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.855063165873775
    },
    {
        "question": " 97.9万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.434289624647902
    },
    {
        "question": " 114秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.27759571635896374
    },
    {
        "question": " 244秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.38798545045721
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.85秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.266197265493466
    },
    {
        "question": " 9475億msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4777748444249295
    },
    {
        "question": " 21.2兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.389294751977975
    },
    {
        "question": " 6838万msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.278605407713419
    },
    {
        "question": " 60億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.000093631772039
    },
    {
        "question": " 6850億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.83568073744519
    },
    {
        "question": " 135兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.630321321443339
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.9京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.238082734940619
    },
    {
        "question": " 31.4京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.9405621837253975
    },
    {
        "question": " 71.9兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.0786500203646385
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.14億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9104687712819413
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.18万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.0708822693463294
    },
    {
        "question": " 1606垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.7068933154482435
    },
    {
        "question": " 862京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.999005104681201
    },
    {
        "question": " 26.9垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.873395875425498
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.18京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.5608809589591734
    },
    {
        "question": " 623兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.794566345335128
    },
    {
        "question": " 94.7億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.976300654391043
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.85億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 5.685975462552834
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.35万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.086926429282637
    },
    {
        "question": " 180年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.753401480741344
    },
    {
        "question": " 54.2万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.171476199708696
    },
    {
        "question": " 1813日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.638571402180505
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.54日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.7067595210287485
    },
    {
        "question": " 620万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.849788615988089
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.44万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.4288953876175396
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.71時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.0105295672958947
    },
    {
        "question": " 99.7時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.555003789147744
    },
    {
        "question": " 78.7万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.1752094732569187
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.42万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4872271517210645
    },
    {
        "question": " 3804億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.802141299398393
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.34京秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.13894393053729
    },
    {
        "question": " 5647万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8153235966903924
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.7万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6107780458082155
    },
    {
        "question": " 709万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.0726954662225
    },
    {
        "question": " 594万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.774041351397694
    },
    {
        "question": " 2476兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.89485986884417
    },
    {
        "question": " 3425億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.5981460839541004
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.1億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.487991063535935
    },
    {
        "question": " 33.6万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.748546083752919
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.11億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.7862623345705835
    },
    {
        "question": " 188msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 8.273963134208968
    },
    {
        "question": " 7612京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.382671944428359
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.29京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.580103689342214
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.8兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.515076944196797
    },
    {
        "question": " 1032億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.235647193375021
    },
    {
        "question": " 2459万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3907625365111276
    },
    {
        "question": " 5749usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 0.7595952756812963
    },
    {
        "question": " 6073usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.783392326235291
    },
    {
        "question": " 4399京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.1445239992506324
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.58京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2620715487526564
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.19京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.158577783016666
    },
    {
        "question": " 1302億nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.3363552181705898
    },
    {
        "question": " 206億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3143747596414335
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.55兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.406221483375708
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.24万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 1.6275492310629835
    },
    {
        "question": " 289万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.02339374025096
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.8万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.083348426544637
    },
    {
        "question": " 21年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.821857084307846
    },
    {
        "question": " 3295日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9555762056197459
    },
    {
        "question": " 33.1日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8996428936527563
    },
    {
        "question": " 504日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.860627032079017
    },
    {
        "question": " 2953万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.527711829247153
    },
    {
        "question": " 704億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.467485774685242
    },
    {
        "question": " 386時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.364409957373148
    },
    {
        "question": " 204時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.866303004194702
    },
    {
        "question": " 32兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.785050367064415
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.44万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3786761682051873
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.8億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.393116928583602
    },
    {
        "question": " 2928億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.967824965155633
    },
    {
        "question": " 58.1万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8277421795733464
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.5万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4646545671277733
    },
    {
        "question": " 20.8万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.5391916570836566
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.55万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.816357314355908
    },
    {
        "question": " 9195秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.963533334141223
    },
    {
        "question": " 1560京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.694338868667323
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.1億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1454320540540697
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.43兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.83019036367424
    },
    {
        "question": " 74.1兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.091437562921223
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.35億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.129676649290142
    },
    {
        "question": " 791msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 5.898008669471023
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.3垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.655634952820952
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.28垓usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.694940708194682
    },
    {
        "question": " 139億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5860629584103849
    },
    {
        "question": " 2294兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.582397597789824
    },
    {
        "question": " 204万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.31032699234689987
    },
    {
        "question": " 583万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.76597129414459
    },
    {
        "question": " 6721usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.827411071896648
    },
    {
        "question": " 92.5京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4673941930093226
    },
    {
        "question": " 2000京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.3646073985003415
    },
    {
        "question": " 2678兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.87151052297262
    },
    {
        "question": " 643京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.030357038404984
    },
    {
        "question": " 200億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.300900323085984
    },
    {
        "question": " 20.2億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.3057132219967067
    },
    {
        "question": " 91.5億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.9616334235470685
    },
    {
        "question": " 24.8年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.956511272546819
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.29万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.861252034958955
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.83年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.392494484733152
    },
    {
        "question": " 109万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.4753072772941564
    },
    {
        "question": " 1817日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.639672979441127
    },
    {
        "question": " 21.4日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.489319342385073
    },
    {
        "question": " 79.1日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.834881228874213
    },
    {
        "question": " 231万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4216347112306034
    },
    {
        "question": " 35時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.16429511194221869
    },
    {
        "question": " 69.4時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.6197081674562503
    },
    {
        "question": " 6523時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.370731381554666
    },
    {
        "question": " 65.6兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.096352129762952
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.76万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5194821308201123
    },
    {
        "question": " 714億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.075798030477403
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.53万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.962915569001991
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.13万分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.394210076863045
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.4兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.307523857605345
    },
    {
        "question": " 281万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5115267775407648
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.48兆秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.614404945473828
    },
    {
        "question": " 975万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.210955298580657
    },
    {
        "question": " 592秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.772594622043073
    },
    {
        "question": " 102京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.510070111107457
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.31兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.426948866408934
    },
    {
        "question": " 4137万msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.060434652473361
    },
    {
        "question": " 295兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.692116084711687
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.71万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4330895180794945
    },
    {
        "question": " 21.5msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 7.332351737358241
    },
    {
        "question": " 2766兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9430991318466484
    },
    {
        "question": " 621京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.856418609465385
    },
    {
        "question": " 245億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.832774942109834
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.01億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.224618346368064
    },
    {
        "question": " 2813万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4491375903715553
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.55億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.6582360592787655
    },
    {
        "question": " 26.8万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 8.428908698215288
    },
    {
        "question": " 170垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.732383546306306
    },
    {
        "question": " 6028兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8436428400436133
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.05京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.400431167919448
    },
    {
        "question": " 4360兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.861319294261102
    },
    {
        "question": " 887億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.947816350858419
    },
    {
        "question": " 37.6億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.5753214855879154
    },
    {
        "question": " 4993万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.6983621823100075
    },
    {
        "question": " 806年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.84905752267463
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.38年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.644060188760915
    },
    {
        "question": " 1515日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6181890317975602
    },
    {
        "question": " 90.1日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.8912499617602165
    },
    {
        "question": " 982万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.049434754391487
    },
    {
        "question": " 7975万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.521544011838917
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.13万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.631472756244245
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.4時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.769836746578223
    },
    {
        "question": " 1398億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.424792045812268
    },
    {
        "question": " 1447億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.002121355620314
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.45億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.383525825581864
    },
    {
        "question": " 130分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.8920213945064894
    },
    {
        "question": " 1360分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.911841819929246
    },
    {
        "question": " 770兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.3878179656280825
    },
    {
        "question": " 2410億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.4454914454488454
    },
    {
        "question": " 94.6万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4196933574907167
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.52万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.2006202835357964
    },
    {
        "question": " 124万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.09204147192074
    },
    {
        "question": " 4252秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.62854395544323
    },
    {
        "question": " 367億msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.06629136443209505
    },
    {
        "question": " 470億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7359910711792157
    },
    {
        "question": " 5486億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.182947952848767
    },
    {
        "question": " 39.1万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.81412678307905
    },
    {
        "question": " 98.4万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.992859457661047
    },
    {
        "question": " 927京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.46850630018052
    },
    {
        "question": " 5647兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.815296549933191
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.18京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.51671876723869
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.06京usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.070581833537478
    },
    {
        "question": " 2035兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.308652969278322
    },
    {
        "question": " 22.6億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.354460431856285
    },
    {
        "question": " 316京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.0011978229592122
    },
    {
        "question": " 1216垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.148456107650771
    },
    {
        "question": " 36.8垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.009849514736368
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.69兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2082078900950473
    },
    {
        "question": " 172億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.23569916231562
    },
    {
        "question": " 8071億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.906945930676385
    },
    {
        "question": " 143万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 3.15476099450556
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.52万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6200727263344683
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.8日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4526183744651897
    },
    {
        "question": " 135万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.289499514850004
    },
    {
        "question": " 138万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.196170741727176
    },
    {
        "question": " 63.5億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.422735839787043
    },
    {
        "question": " 128時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.886362119384341
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.64万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.378227212713767
    },
    {
        "question": " 267万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7052535196406129
    },
    {
        "question": " 464億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.5083965144528255
    },
    {
        "question": " 306億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.707880217638518
    },
    {
        "question": " 124分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.8728487495698394
    },
    {
        "question": " 801分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.6819145178786785
    },
    {
        "question": " 17億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.732715758963853
    },
    {
        "question": " 19.2兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.347277034352174
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.4億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.602919128641131
    },
    {
        "question": " 263億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.642594053765114
    },
    {
        "question": " 29.5秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.469428307250838
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.01秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.4792167370568166
    },
    {
        "question": " 37.4兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.074019236898854
    },
    {
        "question": " 23億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4247497274002163
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.98億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.140500224724101
    },
    {
        "question": " 196万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.514725914193219
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.24兆msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.349319266973813
    },
    {
        "question": " 92.4msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 7.965462078193494
    },
    {
        "question": " 176兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7465170767688445
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.96垓usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.356817979159418
    },
    {
        "question": " 2788兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.888949892886624
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.64兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.7834800115672005
    },
    {
        "question": " 20.3億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.30784212775907
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.45億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.161529568253095
    },
    {
        "question": " 329usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 5.517052320984729
    },
    {
        "question": " 9833垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.493862947957888
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.48垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.235193573484726
    },
    {
        "question": " 103京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.456407396343219
    },
    {
        "question": " 437兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.8620651399673567
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.31兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.5194740524944224
    },
    {
        "question": " 4404億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.643857048542516
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.44万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 1.9751093201640213
    },
    {
        "question": " 2431年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.948108634994957
    },
    {
        "question": " 417年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.562128804358679
    },
    {
        "question": " 555日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.1817718705144089
    },
    {
        "question": " 4284万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.012031806414926
    },
    {
        "question": " 212万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.485380794179886
    },
    {
        "question": " 859万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.991631089217096
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.47万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7871870201326465
    },
    {
        "question": " 109時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.8164325576889735
    },
    {
        "question": " 63.4万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.35824988536081
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.33時間は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.67939692455926
    },
    {
        "question": " 45.7兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.939124924677131
    },
    {
        "question": " 3106億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.33391941707896
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.4万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.60266092093559
    },
    {
        "question": " 262分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.196532625907894
    },
    {
        "question": " 13分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.89361408560704
    },
    {
        "question": " 133兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.6240170034635355
    },
    {
        "question": " 33.7万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5910307055629815
    },
    {
        "question": " 353万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9912450842158322
    },
    {
        "question": " 29.2億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.687745354001924
    },
    {
        "question": " 3112秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.493051416238384
    },
    {
        "question": " 3493京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.044395828337839
    },
    {
        "question": " 21.5億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3956124359169542
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.08兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.350975494925071
    },
    {
        "question": " 8576億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.155146906261001
    },
    {
        "question": " 174万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.240128617375073
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.21msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.084131891737573
    },
    {
        "question": " 21.5京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.8338660018232353
    },
    {
        "question": " 144京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.220720046189559
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.55兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.101450205818148
    },
    {
        "question": " 1142億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.2793585763539657
    },
    {
        "question": " 8026億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.90447858621816
    },
    {
        "question": " 2713億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.433442985972544
    },
    {
        "question": " 313usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 5.495768763919608
    },
    {
        "question": " 41垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.114059419830328
    },
    {
        "question": " 20.8垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.38184072971513
    },
    {
        "question": " 63.7兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2480150650438282
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.26京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.575505638987922
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.5兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.021748728794053
    },
    {
        "question": " 4249億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.628303642560974
    },
    {
        "question": " 23万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 2.3609670375693614
    },
    {
        "question": " 4224日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0634562487467247
    },
    {
        "question": " 233万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.746877450669584
    },
    {
        "question": " 54.2日は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.670783278807646
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.19兆時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.13333458304195
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.85万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.205070740683993
    },
    {
        "question": " 6103万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.563727928754139
    },
    {
        "question": " 27.4時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.994384791987685
    },
    {
        "question": " 5111億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.987884236221243
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.51兆分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.49565464573038
    },
    {
        "question": " 893億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.172826856800903
    },
    {
        "question": " 50.8万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.483645547569411
    },
    {
        "question": " 562億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.250833487861696
    },
    {
        "question": " 741億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.933044752886544
    },
    {
        "question": " 4910秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.13482244229438445
    },
    {
        "question": " 11億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.261645343238779
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.05万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.311967977385438
    },
    {
        "question": " 135京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.630780200518476
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.17億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.12994476300654978
    },
    {
        "question": " 50.6兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.1478917359704655
    },
    {
        "question": " 2353億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.59345415779266
    },
    {
        "question": " 14万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.144899491472824
    },
    {
        "question": " 4463msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.649652178998742
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.14msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.853448434559889
    },
    {
        "question": " 51.6京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.213842091341417
    },
    {
        "question": " 5716京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.820578406559257
    },
    {
        "question": " 1771億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6918885391343208
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.08億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0055262768166362
    },
    {
        "question": " 183億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.261902264528654
    },
    {
        "question": " 6406万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.806584752616012
    },
    {
        "question": " 67.3usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 4.828283769894868
    },
    {
        "question": " 132垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.623236808978395
    },
    {
        "question": " 7775京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.95419474785823
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.2京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.653265788882367
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.08兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8322718209466993
    },
    {
        "question": " 13兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.114475867373909
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.87億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 2.768732033277815
    },
    {
        "question": " 461億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.664002870710717
    },
    {
        "question": " 40年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.164549688938593
    },
    {
        "question": " 1662年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.941327063184959
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.09年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.537776970599505
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.6万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.641486903752677
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.85万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.065669667830096
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.07日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.4751350117574784
    },
    {
        "question": " 5536万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.800706158469589
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.1万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.942636222138347
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.12万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.826382301818981
    },
    {
        "question": " 33時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.075366711570778
    },
    {
        "question": " 7886万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1761965488754687
    },
    {
        "question": " 7701分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7282064885621387
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.65万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6456071953816327
    },
    {
        "question": " 1657分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.997454987678783
    },
    {
        "question": " 946億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.4770477130359123
    },
    {
        "question": " 176億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.308770239677779
    },
    {
        "question": " 455億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.101950664325266
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.58億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.776142915968332
    },
    {
        "question": " 222万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.34646176035162
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.93兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3420928632547944
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.83京msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.326751440996027
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.71億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6761316139827453
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.2兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.456120327249572
    },
    {
        "question": " 9061msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9571534303387175
    },
    {
        "question": " 40.6垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.109479398050084
    },
    {
        "question": " 1505億usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.24093483439332597
    },
    {
        "question": " 642億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2509868368318444
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.9京usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.060521847048689
    },
    {
        "question": " 346億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.539101110675412
    },
    {
        "question": " 952億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.978457675578914
    },
    {
        "question": " 131usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 5.118263228239327
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.35垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.0263257759040165
    },
    {
        "question": " 57垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.819082632322597
    },
    {
        "question": " 82.4兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3598825103327505
    },
    {
        "question": " 6557京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.038531122677528
    },
    {
        "question": " 95.2兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.97849591084514
    },
    {
        "question": " 4809万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.6820276856328031
    },
    {
        "question": " 9156nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 0.9617209110399161
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.9万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.67454692372265
    },
    {
        "question": " 492年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.634341295129919
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.4年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.867928041638992
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.05万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2191909489837136
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.48万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.031446053440318
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.3万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.249313519947298
    },
    {
        "question": " 18.6兆時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.328155042937313
    },
    {
        "question": " 59時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.3907499153136962
    },
    {
        "question": " 2111時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.102651615535175
    },
    {
        "question": " 35.9万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.111864928731494
    },
    {
        "question": " 6019万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.0588455785093718
    },
    {
        "question": " 53.4億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.569269800576255
    },
    {
        "question": " 177分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.469483755777933
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.24分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8720482867396249
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.92億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.341582859084428
    },
    {
        "question": " 811万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9724348688137305
    },
    {
        "question": " 1474万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.61220046811334
    },
    {
        "question": " 36.8億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.787564307568608
    },
    {
        "question": " 77.2秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.887595224757008
    },
    {
        "question": " 4708京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.174066570891918
    },
    {
        "question": " 280兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.510303034306251
    },
    {
        "question": " 253億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.84700346661882
    },
    {
        "question": " 2767億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.663917502922737
    },
    {
        "question": " 965万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.984576839192676
    },
    {
        "question": " 297msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 5.47234815327176
    },
    {
        "question": " 3957兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.098607450134061
    },
    {
        "question": " 28.4京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.5175737754384215
    },
    {
        "question": " 73.6億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.31060788030203623
    },
    {
        "question": " 503億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9231960329174522
    },
    {
        "question": " 8127万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9099418677230218
    },
    {
        "question": " 53.7億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.7299028076939225
    },
    {
        "question": " 24.7京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8930420319226096
    },
    {
        "question": " 28.2垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.5143912152504075
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.4垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.087543390140548
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.1京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.006925533519546
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.09京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.850532958941956
    },
    {
        "question": " 93億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.968481507546957
    },
    {
        "question": " 145万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 3.1608607652658027
    },
    {
        "question": " 434年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.200295745580508
    },
    {
        "question": " 8472日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.365702466027251
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.33日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.0162304703260348
    },
    {
        "question": " 83.8億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.980646277619666
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.66億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.443334118690278
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.48時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5172595840754663
    },
    {
        "question": " 86万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.490595415841975
    },
    {
        "question": " 11億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.3201618277900833
    },
    {
        "question": " 130億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.955210171020152
    },
    {
        "question": " 306分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7082407002994329
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.49億分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.950741891787969
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.41分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.928449394670635
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.61分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.442138032458276
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.22兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.126087442468956
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.9億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.317516865605247
    },
    {
        "question": " 4193億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.066181807047244
    },
    {
        "question": " 700万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.066957428367785
    },
    {
        "question": " 75.2秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.876112088281477
    },
    {
        "question": " 8985京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.454734292540012
    },
    {
        "question": " 505億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7667645702343666
    },
    {
        "question": " 8794億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.387900137322016
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.18億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.5594334772389424
    },
    {
        "question": " 2192万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.340856104426983
    },
    {
        "question": " 52.2msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.71790493719956
    },
    {
        "question": " 151京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.679843381665676
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.32京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.58442060924996
    },
    {
        "question": " 717兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.299362772855609
    },
    {
        "question": " 6910兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.061337792166118
    },
    {
        "question": " 28.2兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.450837309569059
    },
    {
        "question": " 90.3万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 2.95583498095209
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.58usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 3.818408581250643
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.6垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.666006787607705
    },
    {
        "question": " 270京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.494420522864781
    },
    {
        "question": " 1832兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7067349302077393
    },
    {
        "question": " 166兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.441097604523322
    },
    {
        "question": " 384億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5841027029726384
    },
    {
        "question": " 11億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.0402311842573226
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.59億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 5.202550404348938
    },
    {
        "question": " 23.6万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.31591344786684
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.05万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.460131254824032
    },
    {
        "question": " 7151万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.23457623088927
    },
    {
        "question": " 19日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.214621408555617
    },
    {
        "question": " 7313億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.921568355173045
    },
    {
        "question": " 387億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.207345194689697
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.91時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.774134442151311
    },
    {
        "question": " 2178万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6174543334575409
    },
    {
        "question": " 268億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.27026897817124
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.68万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.0464176792534534
    },
    {
        "question": " 181億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.757703264361192
    },
    {
        "question": " 37.3万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6356779808911239
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.23万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4089108485915791
    },
    {
        "question": " 4270億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.8522990554704
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.68秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.670530305718512
    },
    {
        "question": " 4250京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.129572231555839
    },
    {
        "question": " 321兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.56935214689181
    },
    {
        "question": " 35.2兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.990761021109692
    },
    {
        "question": " 863億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.158032993578869
    },
    {
        "question": " 213万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.327743411180908
    },
    {
        "question": " 931万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.968985743868467
    },
    {
        "question": " 1223兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.588702365838841
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.4京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.932693426766282
    },
    {
        "question": " 70.7兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.2930542921257295
    },
    {
        "question": " 1285億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.3306084315108575
    },
    {
        "question": " 688兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.837456182951192
    },
    {
        "question": " 7061usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 0.8488739990981953
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.06usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 3.485689580629817
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.146e+06垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.832770456577993
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.23垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.154237631026018
    },
    {
        "question": " 7587京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.323776590478052
    },
    {
        "question": " 41.6兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.840554976886571
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.8兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.106614787173012
    },
    {
        "question": " 354億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.548754479012754
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.4万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 2.187165966782426
    },
    {
        "question": " 2128万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.765581212462232
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.92億日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.66451944119659
    },
    {
        "question": " 331日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.678497729267296
    },
    {
        "question": " 1671日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.159593858435812
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.11兆時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.843338861921744
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.05万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6426763496023407
    },
    {
        "question": " 8289万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.696627891065004
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.56時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.748455335202977
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.3兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.402622699018776
    },
    {
        "question": " 682億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.675303600173366
    },
    {
        "question": " 19.5万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.5111043310460555
    },
    {
        "question": " 3762分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.35361221043042
    },
    {
        "question": " 146億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6653293774328657
    },
    {
        "question": " 34.9万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.606672159045154
    },
    {
        "question": " 4567万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.103315976402566
    },
    {
        "question": " 1814秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4805531015638207
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.57万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.410626911968944
    },
    {
        "question": " 49.6秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.695821346849363
    },
    {
        "question": " 238兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.877131788648913
    },
    {
        "question": " 8864億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.011139024637343
    },
    {
        "question": " 34.6兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.982633439093159
    },
    {
        "question": " 193億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.507168375824875
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.08億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.032901857565598
    },
    {
        "question": " 3805msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.580406529553411
    },
    {
        "question": " 614msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 8.788315936077861
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.43垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.88679850855749
    },
    {
        "question": " 22.1京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.408226246820221
    },
    {
        "question": " 1812兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.70181620074234
    },
    {
        "question": " 540億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.953874578972905
    },
    {
        "question": " 2985兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.474890989674265
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.28万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.3571596289965937
    },
    {
        "question": " 30usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 4.477497174362158
    },
    {
        "question": " 194垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.788235397731136
    },
    {
        "question": " 94.8京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.040337454147382
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.52垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.624132206149715
    },
    {
        "question": " 2298億nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5831792392790747
    },
    {
        "question": " 483億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6842235333730282
    },
    {
        "question": " 256万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 0.4074825954646033
    },
    {
        "question": " 345億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.53738411132896
    },
    {
        "question": " 74.3万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.433163541021182
    },
    {
        "question": " 91.6年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.904276060722244
    },
    {
        "question": " 515年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.432302615720065
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.42万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.971834380499532
    },
    {
        "question": " 1142万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.43787025756064
    },
    {
        "question": " 47.4万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.834179857180343
    },
    {
        "question": " 8962億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.009921757515015
    },
    {
        "question": " 1697時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8495411308617449
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.61億時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.98443845734801
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.79兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.857585854480403
    },
    {
        "question": " 2357万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.214048650206439
    },
    {
        "question": " 6433万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.030234520262995
    },
    {
        "question": " 469万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.449277949637091
    },
    {
        "question": " 4700分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.450233342250218
    },
    {
        "question": " 141兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.649073823701082
    },
    {
        "question": " 185万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3297066816111835
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.73万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6818004017945445
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.7億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.359936123149181
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.04万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.847714261593607
    },
    {
        "question": " 1260秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.10032700808648
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.2兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.842643840400443
    },
    {
        "question": " 1535兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.249503829876151
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.91兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.725548878864684
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.38兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.362318839566713
    },
    {
        "question": " 2034msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.3084343996633787
    },
    {
        "question": " 312万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.493686388151767
    },
    {
        "question": " 9623兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4844926349961005
    },
    {
        "question": " 18.3兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.327094766598554
    },
    {
        "question": " 1125億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4949943671173205
    },
    {
        "question": " 1394兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.366242834521285
    },
    {
        "question": " 1058億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.024397698941707
    },
    {
        "question": " 1779億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.250221215443851
    },
    {
        "question": " 39.7垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.099597556270206
    },
    {
        "question": " 75.7垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.9426183706941735
    },
    {
        "question": " 27.4垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.881477172585736
    },
    {
        "question": " 769兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.107844719939148
    },
    {
        "question": " 177京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.248678831986162
    },
    {
        "question": " 9137兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.960807409593064
    },
    {
        "question": " 295万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 3.4697421302479823
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.31年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.531156176986415
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.7万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.166210071219073
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.05年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.742952934727976
    },
    {
        "question": " 627日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.2351269715203097
    },
    {
        "question": " 118万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.4517851095468775
    },
    {
        "question": " 13日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.0511706917707535
    },
    {
        "question": " 6億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.835641682922392
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.11万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.471806091935071
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.51万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.177802349416716
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.3億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.1985848609419487
    },
    {
        "question": " 143億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.99756886119446
    },
    {
        "question": " 1639万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.436429013245025
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.7分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8092511178216806
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.4京秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.559166177533601
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.68兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.817900672182697
    },
    {
        "question": " 64.5億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.253374092866776
    },
    {
        "question": " 202億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.527449513863182
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.22万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.346194220549348
    },
    {
        "question": " 4989京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.199215182674251
    },
    {
        "question": " 13京msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.177895645279404
    },
    {
        "question": " 871万msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.3838799108471158
    },
    {
        "question": " 31.8兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.72431756212061
    },
    {
        "question": " 8997億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.95412170772885
    },
    {
        "question": " 63.3京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.302876008025337
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.77兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6401832203122235
    },
    {
        "question": " 1717億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6784042022868928
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.34兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.859047888626017
    },
    {
        "question": " 2541万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4050480174516489
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.42万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.6451255210641103
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.67usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 3.4261594084358182
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.483e+04垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.15277390973139
    },
    {
        "question": " 46.1京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.727321821462526
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.19兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.23561492380501425
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.35垓nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.59374438269741
    },
    {
        "question": " 185兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.268300584214794
    },
    {
        "question": " 71.4億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.853639197976937
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.39兆nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.731332452639487
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.09万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.978635404415049
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.48年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.532406628074877
    },
    {
        "question": " 75.2万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.313842092765803
    },
    {
        "question": " 1004日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.160221096321237
    },
    {
        "question": " 919日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.899908936690597
    },
    {
        "question": " 9651時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.042050529511443724
    },
    {
        "question": " 438時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2611513442296807
    },
    {
        "question": " 120万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.856356210903819
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.87時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.013818462648873
    },
    {
        "question": " 1493時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.730320995636605
    },
    {
        "question": " 68.4万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.11433736280378803
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.87万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6104640951192073
    },
    {
        "question": " 103億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.235301026697691
    },
    {
        "question": " 6870万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.615096056885626
    },
    {
        "question": " 21.8京秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.840350752411084
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.13兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.11834341327589
    },
    {
        "question": " 5922億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.216148311449993
    },
    {
        "question": " 7721秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.109538041146326
    },
    {
        "question": " 23.3秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.366774906591006
    },
    {
        "question": " 40京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.103139733699494
    },
    {
        "question": " 2205兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.406974065267531
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.53億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.258456777355992
    },
    {
        "question": " 2497億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.619257945263843
    },
    {
        "question": " 3780億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.5775434655546
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.38万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.13887096643826
    },
    {
        "question": " 125msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 8.096343570937677
    },
    {
        "question": " 385京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.086670888831387
    },
    {
        "question": " 1483京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.234566156244924
    },
    {
        "question": " 338京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.973258545143358
    },
    {
        "question": " 143兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.376284728680024
    },
    {
        "question": " 203兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.307418666451802
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.49万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.1744929527214143
    },
    {
        "question": " 1910京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7822280503804455
    },
    {
        "question": " 1379垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.203023417627074
    },
    {
        "question": " 33.7京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.971497291290846
    },
    {
        "question": " 4446京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.869819146633674
    },
    {
        "question": " 84.2億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9251522708384508
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.46兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.390978201808131
    },
    {
        "question": " 341万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 3.533135268487624
    },
    {
        "question": " 215年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.895751544958601
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.82年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.170707421895281
    },
    {
        "question": " 2119万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.763776822106468
    },
    {
        "question": " 3272日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.894965118966107
    },
    {
        "question": " 115日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.99811449052717
    },
    {
        "question": " 201億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.359854592324784
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.91億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.901292959590998
    },
    {
        "question": " 1103時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.598997586865234
    },
    {
        "question": " 872万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2198838989932026
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.9億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.680508183023351
    },
    {
        "question": " 12億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.302014966259552
    },
    {
        "question": " 55億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2417286351112873
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.75億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.740144074682524
    },
    {
        "question": " 19万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7230427022787898
    },
    {
        "question": " 166秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.4430035871876714
    },
    {
        "question": " 49.2兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.1929508443195296
    },
    {
        "question": " 981億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.0553522652329157
    },
    {
        "question": " 465兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.110774368884073
    },
    {
        "question": " 21兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.54459512450897
    },
    {
        "question": " 2653万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.423792372789275
    },
    {
        "question": " 410万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.612843592939239
    },
    {
        "question": " 4223msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.625668644199752
    },
    {
        "question": " 934垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.47164003446633
    },
    {
        "question": " 1278兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.169943741392874
    },
    {
        "question": " 25.3京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.846101578337146
    },
    {
        "question": " 4171兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.84213471168746
    },
    {
        "question": " 150億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.176396059478357
    },
    {
        "question": " 90.7万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 2.9573880626964533
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.13usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 3.327377544572543
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.678e+04垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.726080814308768
    },
    {
        "question": " 1226兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.151908097810812
    },
    {
        "question": " 906京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.400781149697724
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.03兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8267654636146458
    },
    {
        "question": " 191京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.280200918560451
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.88兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.274891417304241
    },
    {
        "question": " 772億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.8878225912479
    },
    {
        "question": " 34.2万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.096729648450415
    },
    {
        "question": " 24.4年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.8864193183329
    },
    {
        "question": " 1156万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.50053483956543
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.58日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5784288970786242
    },
    {
        "question": " 269日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.588894136754022
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.87兆時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.74532782752298
    },
    {
        "question": " 142億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.771180087911274
    },
    {
        "question": " 244万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.166026121143373
    },
    {
        "question": " 5148時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.26795668870688
    },
    {
        "question": " 59.9億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.056983496858035
    },
    {
        "question": " 8205万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.755716633789826
    },
    {
        "question": " 39.2万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.8147975164457684
    },
    {
        "question": " 95.9万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.760012248308664
    },
    {
        "question": " 1167億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.568190623429124
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.36億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.4356067302918367
    },
    {
        "question": " 29.6万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9156640118719992
    },
    {
        "question": " 624秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0172226256503503
    },
    {
        "question": " 420秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.62324024731767
    },
    {
        "question": " 2095億msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.822435962782736
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.54京msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.720389646204406
    },
    {
        "question": " 687億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.280939291529479
    },
    {
        "question": " 25.5億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.628212007203006
    },
    {
        "question": " 106万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.0234236115806725
    },
    {
        "question": " 5708msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.756493499780985
    },
    {
        "question": " 1267兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.603945593627354
    },
    {
        "question": " 78.9兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.960429544904377
    },
    {
        "question": " 62.3億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.23836533864431297
    },
    {
        "question": " 9641兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.205957894940871
    },
    {
        "question": " 4044兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.606794788085656
    },
    {
        "question": " 7741usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 0.8887690901182832
    },
    {
        "question": " 7516垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.377173478016097
    },
    {
        "question": " 2296垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.424379076848764
    },
    {
        "question": " 56.7兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.197282582867929
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.62垓nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.886325964052741
    },
    {
        "question": " 31.1億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.49277219876005085
    },
    {
        "question": " 812億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.909568559637993
    },
    {
        "question": " 4258nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 0.629177578136374
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.66年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.658073157838865
    },
    {
        "question": " 19.9億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.736382685899103
    },
    {
        "question": " 320万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.885103646260133
    },
    {
        "question": " 377万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.735264805443197
    },
    {
        "question": " 7970日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.837962184422173
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.4万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.436838174585924
    },
    {
        "question": " 32.3時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.1293658655625618
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.91時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5494107827574664
    },
    {
        "question": " 7347億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.14544027204976
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.9兆分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.87956903470861
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.62億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.432101317783819
    },
    {
        "question": " 6392分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.583813378223637
    },
    {
        "question": " 422億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.126291514211866
    },
    {
        "question": " 6964億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.906355029610383
    },
    {
        "question": " 1080万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.4773047558904393
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.53億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.201021354001509
    },
    {
        "question": " 452万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.654672328324029
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.26兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8551707713359067
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.33億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.18656916127964385
    },
    {
        "question": " 4069億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.05321281925644
    },
    {
        "question": " 2338万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5907465400255147
    },
    {
        "question": " 2020億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.305269107580301
    },
    {
        "question": " 1071msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.029948109079518
    },
    {
        "question": " 2065垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.816124938190583
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.73垓usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.50041215340134
    },
    {
        "question": " 877京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.386704578189446
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.01京usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.22457537325098
    },
    {
        "question": " 1433兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.156308856194634
    },
    {
        "question": " 6191億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.791758594193134
    },
    {
        "question": " 474usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 5.675469388431058
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.301e+04垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.469737287319946
    },
    {
        "question": " 8267兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.980832247135077
    },
    {
        "question": " 440兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.0867602859455348
    },
    {
        "question": " 6184兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.0131440790349115
    },
    {
        "question": " 31.9兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.503138723181678
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.25億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 2.5122768462787324
    },
    {
        "question": " 9867億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.994167977532097
    },
    {
        "question": " 23.2年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.308080539489927
    },
    {
        "question": " 31年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.212706286045672
    },
    {
        "question": " 1年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.499791088630838
    },
    {
        "question": " 23万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.798959781473828
    },
    {
        "question": " 209万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.69981562238426
    },
    {
        "question": " 20.6万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.471870163815353
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.8日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.0764077544553805
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.49万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8695139147100761
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.6万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.720284658496099
    },
    {
        "question": " 5158時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.490622907756163
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.46兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.443897320192927
    },
    {
        "question": " 42億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.464791270122207
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.81万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9042228414707196
    },
    {
        "question": " 6494万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.590694377208099
    },
    {
        "question": " 5309万秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.22620994799916305
    },
    {
        "question": " 102億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.071093928829899
    },
    {
        "question": " 3627秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.0031949895578697873
    },
    {
        "question": " 1019万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.23013059611872
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.2秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.7161810451534683
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.2秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.047303834948578
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.19京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.575762265233866
    },
    {
        "question": " 167兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.2859408521125655
    },
    {
        "question": " 6003万msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2220600873915621
    },
    {
        "question": " 128兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.32897743171913
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.55兆msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.190277412304578
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.34万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.52426474660819
    },
    {
        "question": " 2918垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.966323114186425
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.51垓usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.804324361572865
    },
    {
        "question": " 382兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.026215076216449
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.64兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.888151730504294
    },
    {
        "question": " 63.7兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.803949082667966
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.29兆usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.36011080767678
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.13万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 7.329301456346725
    },
    {
        "question": " 21.7垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.837611965350127
    },
    {
        "question": " 4222兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6889968765189078
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.94京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.217488076809005
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.45京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.869775413877583
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.56京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.408697053013428
    },
    {
        "question": " 72.8億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.862014645924016
    },
    {
        "question": " 224億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.34988485726363
    },
    {
        "question": " 57.7年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.481978205898685
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.44年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.886061569849843
    },
    {
        "question": " 4862日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1245478614602067
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.52日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.194155136079953
    },
    {
        "question": " 69.4日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.777650782833192
    },
    {
        "question": " 226億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.412153134021109
    },
    {
        "question": " 100時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6218975590767972
    },
    {
        "question": " 3497時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.321801380840586
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.19万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.413192865107217
    },
    {
        "question": " 245時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.945294381494747
    },
    {
        "question": " 109万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.31733648506396595
    },
    {
        "question": " 6126万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.628838716089928
    },
    {
        "question": " 3967分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8203168871033304
    },
    {
        "question": " 4419万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.423434927693291
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.01兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.979055740959355
    },
    {
        "question": " 34.3兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.599004228177103
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.99万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3464121108372973
    },
    {
        "question": " 373万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.793552577636961
    },
    {
        "question": " 121秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.084116931504293
    },
    {
        "question": " 436秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.639450274088777
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.96京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.276478019096135
    },
    {
        "question": " 3434億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.5992587571309165
    },
    {
        "question": " 1323万msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5654201309386542
    },
    {
        "question": " 230兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.58290370853788
    },
    {
        "question": " 23.7万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3738560242560114
    },
    {
        "question": " 41.6msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.618837219490595
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.08msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.610623358318691
    },
    {
        "question": " 37.1兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.07070354592937922
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.95兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3533003187391146
    },
    {
        "question": " 49.4京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.137498218167353
    },
    {
        "question": " 994億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.219149641850072
    },
    {
        "question": " 1014兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.005865078145183
    },
    {
        "question": " 6522億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.81435887983059
    },
    {
        "question": " 22.8usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 4.357721717765067
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.163e+06垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.566736805092983
    },
    {
        "question": " 215兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.39615330034442064
    },
    {
        "question": " 65.5兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.259915187126136
    },
    {
        "question": " 772京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.1097336538227
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.9京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.111744837814257
    },
    {
        "question": " 638兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.804695852955643
    },
    {
        "question": " 197万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 3.293737708574361
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.86万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.248580278011331
    },
    {
        "question": " 171年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.174802542560346
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.58兆日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.635150051721055
    },
    {
        "question": " 44日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.0238625788594375
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.73日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.0464394488865505
    },
    {
        "question": " 9725億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.045369411609046
    },
    {
        "question": " 8746時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5615981805508548
    },
    {
        "question": " 5982万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.555029153453713
    },
    {
        "question": " 93.2万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.24894810922552524
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.26億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.470886013792362
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.07億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.12881689880676
    },
    {
        "question": " 7295分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.641149256871813
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.41万分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.422487201246161
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.3京秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.420022215862504
    },
    {
        "question": " 8629億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.999470413027968
    },
    {
        "question": " 313億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.939500582427833
    },
    {
        "question": " 2014秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5259933236134382
    },
    {
        "question": " 26.6秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.425472948382349
    },
    {
        "question": " 2403秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.380698433830478
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.89京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.961521568385279
    },
    {
        "question": " 906兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.020455564214098
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.07京msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.471821426066807
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.1万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.4276349351273556
    },
    {
        "question": " 41.9万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6216963090653667
    },
    {
        "question": " 207msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 5.3149959869482
    },
    {
        "question": " 2374msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.37555656750859
    },
    {
        "question": " 1187京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.575579218976002
    },
    {
        "question": " 597京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.839385918779785
    },
    {
        "question": " 114京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.501888570645981
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.32京usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.343999380038458
    },
    {
        "question": " 4090兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.611751825495853
    },
    {
        "question": " 122億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.085704349832093
    },
    {
        "question": " 3643usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.561505046059887
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.267e+05垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.604115630266632
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.23京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4111888076894794
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.2垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.494296507581412
    },
    {
        "question": " 3682兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.787947301824861
    },
    {
        "question": " 747兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.873328041878141
    },
    {
        "question": " 88.4兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.946349571489399
    },
    {
        "question": " 82億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.913950703803709
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.25年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.039252058878579
    },
    {
        "question": " 281年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.168736721959613
    },
    {
        "question": " 210万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.7592790850747635
    },
    {
        "question": " 3575万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.933452869202982
    },
    {
        "question": " 1574万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.2545102933983494
    },
    {
        "question": " 4299時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.253173050308864
    },
    {
        "question": " 6897万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.61679987961786
    },
    {
        "question": " 87.5万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.22139455793924068
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.55万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5859311214409288
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.01万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.825525141053513
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.9分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8541351762819
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.26京秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.856176654951959
    },
    {
        "question": " 324兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.57412689511913
    },
    {
        "question": " 360万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.0000508083132473
    },
    {
        "question": " 3630億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.781777342973578
    },
    {
        "question": " 747秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.873546857247888
    },
    {
        "question": " 95.3兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.480502269782737
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.42億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.2149115166023563
    },
    {
        "question": " 7181億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.299881314425266
    },
    {
        "question": " 3017億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.70148867744609
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.19万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0742130223643587
    },
    {
        "question": " 361兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0592886439858518
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.93京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.014483302364547
    },
    {
        "question": " 9621億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.426939427923948
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.7京usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.417223029460533
    },
    {
        "question": " 426万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6294525571371357
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.55億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.878083419792461
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.97万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 7.599059563630069
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.144e+04垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.559693766179345
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.77垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.506444049628264
    },
    {
        "question": " 3075京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.931593604378547
    },
    {
        "question": " 448京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.873537368141483
    },
    {
        "question": " 443兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.646802565967785
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.16億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 2.85465801151389
    },
    {
        "question": " 3318万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.520834794487925
    },
    {
        "question": " 370年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.130952175351241
    },
    {
        "question": " 4333年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.357486623838437
    },
    {
        "question": " 3009万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.916056787673748
    },
    {
        "question": " 18.4万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.644939323247085
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.77日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.8365094692801973
    },
    {
        "question": " 612万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8442393379492192
    },
    {
        "question": " 7513時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4956002080771276
    },
    {
        "question": " 857時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.489371608249557
    },
    {
        "question": " 1082時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.590493873405789
    },
    {
        "question": " 113兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.333500065686799
    },
    {
        "question": " 2392分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.22033981831123595
    },
    {
        "question": " 113万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.273202414613645
    },
    {
        "question": " 367億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.065606531743464
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.6万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.12919860575673514
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.6兆秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.42589608947642
    },
    {
        "question": " 2377秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5978495147510086
    },
    {
        "question": " 104万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.017090996185924
    },
    {
        "question": " 57.1秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.7565619060108855
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.02京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.202243324003418
    },
    {
        "question": " 1402兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.210212277703927
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.03京msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.925482304784051
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.33兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.344735688554749
    },
    {
        "question": " 34.5万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5375994484291855
    },
    {
        "question": " 70msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.845033156016253
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.64垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.061984384743991
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.7兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.231024038163941
    },
    {
        "question": " 178億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6939227209630616
    },
    {
        "question": " 361兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.779618631430032
    },
    {
        "question": " 655万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.816119606842689
    },
    {
        "question": " 9940万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.997388100358721
    },
    {
        "question": " 437usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 5.640374179348559
    },
    {
        "question": " 2163垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.836304998620614
    },
    {
        "question": " 32.7垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.577876285167296
    },
    {
        "question": " 607京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.226578436372495
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.1京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.713554746725478
    },
    {
        "question": " 810億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9084439059562741
    },
    {
        "question": " 5531兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.74282725760207
    },
    {
        "question": " 239億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.3790043828632035
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.69万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.548502931987606
    },
    {
        "question": " 40.6年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.551504069690244
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.4万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5659619616301708
    },
    {
        "question": " 802日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.284231719766966
    },
    {
        "question": " 450日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.811261393759425
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.09万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5480975324755943
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.3万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.6317474463085277
    },
    {
        "question": " 63.3時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.579432504007708
    },
    {
        "question": " 4757兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.956720634568097
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.18万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9122201930001661
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.29万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.1899435885094496
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.04分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.683367807182524
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.23分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.404736297810217
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.21分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.859477173944349
    },
    {
        "question": " 3436億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.03727501275405
    },
    {
        "question": " 390万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6546036178947798
    },
    {
        "question": " 66.2万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2643530460140493
    },
    {
        "question": " 1011万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.226518724215968
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.4万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.057283960286382
    },
    {
        "question": " 7896京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.398585055236584
    },
    {
        "question": " 151兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.243563831779904
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.48京msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.6142196176943
    },
    {
        "question": " 163兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.432950365816046
    },
    {
        "question": " 1139msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.056671094646996156
    },
    {
        "question": " 7334msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.865323621132174
    },
    {
        "question": " 61.2垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.288059117405721
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.02兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0728492609103224
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.37兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.415362428076768
    },
    {
        "question": " 45.4億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.879262885535815
    },
    {
        "question": " 2210億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.344438332430379
    },
    {
        "question": " 448万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.6516114678646794
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.8京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6724467147784574
    },
    {
        "question": " 306兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5492460367160101
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.53垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.627457686157175
    },
    {
        "question": " 55.3兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9642316597464724
    },
    {
        "question": " 3407億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.532425829168673
    },
    {
        "question": " 6112億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.786170892757925
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.91兆nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.280171372716495
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.73年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.770202156116503
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.53年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.683767776540935
    },
    {
        "question": " 44.1万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.0820432877480752
    },
    {
        "question": " 769万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.266108413824512
    },
    {
        "question": " 42.5日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.564966768782931
    },
    {
        "question": " 941万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.0309977024477917
    },
    {
        "question": " 219億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.960696703966061
    },
    {
        "question": " 19.6万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.071059633050756
    },
    {
        "question": " 1169時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.624032850662239
    },
    {
        "question": " 7126万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.132200159980452
    },
    {
        "question": " 746万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.714452661714569
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.14万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7191530316553534
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.48万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.173041391035911
    },
    {
        "question": " 62.6分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.57493981786513
    },
    {
        "question": " 8129万秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.4112371316586838
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.14億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.1220748780270737
    },
    {
        "question": " 6551秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.26001180765973797
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.2万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.563753355980757
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.96秒は何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.29218421161891
    },
    {
        "question": " 132京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.621805337583943
    },
    {
        "question": " 39.1億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.655270711632676
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.72兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.8776345045061005
    },
    {
        "question": " 165兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.439841832315794
    },
    {
        "question": " 412億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.614525924786913
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.22万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.793998192635424
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.71京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.0707002246560657
    },
    {
        "question": " 192京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.345739170392039
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.75京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.333003419534048
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.69兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.789254433666413
    },
    {
        "question": " 7676兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.885108289474205
    },
    {
        "question": " 4859万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.686581483841347
    },
    {
        "question": " 38.4万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 8.584239413406273
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.6京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6342524442982822
    },
    {
        "question": " 1624垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.274185316743761
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.2垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.450897804607525
    },
    {
        "question": " 729億nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.08469908557646622
    },
    {
        "question": " 82.5億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9164004108638957
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.47兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.650494413525511
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.69兆nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.227081990067063
    },
    {
        "question": " 159年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.763034384137209
    },
    {
        "question": " 468年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.612385467234848
    },
    {
        "question": " 125万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.533938514794924
    },
    {
        "question": " 1285万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.489223326121321
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.95日は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.934167076957634
    },
    {
        "question": " 29.7万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5307426965163695
    },
    {
        "question": " 22億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.962893516093254
    },
    {
        "question": " 1918時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.839258652590495
    },
    {
        "question": " 212万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.60549673455769
    },
    {
        "question": " 170万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.072215704830125
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.77億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.469745874995972
    },
    {
        "question": " 3312万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.298283945413075
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.87万分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.05072007283525
    },
    {
        "question": " 19.5億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7902598738274678
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.09億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.914081255556484
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.74億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.119393859338196
    },
    {
        "question": " 1158万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.285381471338539
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.91秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.279975295187092
    },
    {
        "question": " 3394秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.530695873284587
    },
    {
        "question": " 396京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.099118709801976
    },
    {
        "question": " 5949兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.837947000757045
    },
    {
        "question": " 23.5兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.8151788491249885
    },
    {
        "question": " 407万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8317599951298214
    },
    {
        "question": " 1382億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.140530220009033
    },
    {
        "question": " 413msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 5.615806534951351
    },
    {
        "question": " 121京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.583957325268484
    },
    {
        "question": " 89.8兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.0166148627021103
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.57京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.639588560440432
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.99億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6982218630747039
    },
    {
        "question": " 399兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.601218366999252
    },
    {
        "question": " 661億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.82022193637987
    },
    {
        "question": " 19usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 4.277934224677776
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.619e+06垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.919287762599511
    },
    {
        "question": " 190垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.342367808990481
    },
    {
        "question": " 714京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.2974103086481925
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.94京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.173374778407234
    },
    {
        "question": " 8742億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9415949841206634
    },
    {
        "question": " 8425億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.925588781988945
    },
    {
        "question": " 249億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.396494722730372
    },
    {
        "question": " 659万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.381383886456092
    },
    {
        "question": " 20.8万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.259884446665973
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.13兆日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.492368542418621
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.66日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3174882601290125
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.78日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.1871789945058255
    },
    {
        "question": " 901億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.012376854448892
    },
    {
        "question": " 2345億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.98997784327516
    },
    {
        "question": " 660時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.597845311144936
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.5万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.774307948131309
    },
    {
        "question": " 1832億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.542247238355246
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.41万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2232986779496025
    },
    {
        "question": " 1919万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.504812459665562
    },
    {
        "question": " 6353万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.58114138889556
    },
    {
        "question": " 3706億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.070140146282444
    },
    {
        "question": " 6512億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.8772374901280555
    },
    {
        "question": " 243万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.829601647907285
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.97億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.174503358957259
    },
    {
        "question": " 837京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.424058470862066
    },
    {
        "question": " 1522億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.2457757939924967
    },
    {
        "question": " 1952億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.734091942854195
    },
    {
        "question": " 254兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.626549539444355
    },
    {
        "question": " 128億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.106635412300997
    },
    {
        "question": " 197msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 5.293732865696608
    },
    {
        "question": " 36.9垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.068086302258939
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.16垓usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.776225963926388
    },
    {
        "question": " 1087兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.479887982093981
    },
    {
        "question": " 72.2億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.0805999222898484
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.06兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.957350980965732
    },
    {
        "question": " 2930万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.466939182232067
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.8万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 8.1705527039411
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.649e+06垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.924200045230444
    },
    {
        "question": " 1036京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.078968594293044
    },
    {
        "question": " 1384兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.584796939694458
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.55兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9659813952355665
    },
    {
        "question": " 116京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.065250563694653
    },
    {
        "question": " 55.8億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.7466514949938867
    },
    {
        "question": " 3198億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.504878531356088
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.6万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.147061126963312
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.74万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6788266469996638
    },
    {
        "question": " 22.6日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7341153601156307
    },
    {
        "question": " 448万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.80972069550512
    },
    {
        "question": " 8164日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.848408727254867
    },
    {
        "question": " 113億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.112454015069428
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.04億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.6360728132405
    },
    {
        "question": " 91.9時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.7416543758766507
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.69万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.986814631502993
    },
    {
        "question": " 62.4億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.074258361553912
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.87億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.112793941472869
    },
    {
        "question": " 1276億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.327787008226826
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.45万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.426664220125686
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.33万分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.747902101077564
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.7億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.730702187454868
    },
    {
        "question": " 354万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6125470395056918
    },
    {
        "question": " 28.7億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.902302658699465
    },
    {
        "question": " 6520万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.036127404610086
    },
    {
        "question": " 397秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.5986976526611185
    },
    {
        "question": " 27.7秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.441782806884883
    },
    {
        "question": " 185兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.7674393205257397
    },
    {
        "question": " 37京msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.63190556513339
    },
    {
        "question": " 136兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.577731614917536
    },
    {
        "question": " 32兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.726367143565616
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.5億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.097150821022397
    },
    {
        "question": " 57.5垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.260726567502573
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.2兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.568189013246758
    },
    {
        "question": " 21.6兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.7782743062585444
    },
    {
        "question": " 833億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.1424973993564564
    },
    {
        "question": " 374兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.572611297894547
    },
    {
        "question": " 43億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.633673392714742
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.2usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 4.153136687970464
    },
    {
        "question": " 68垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.3340000808822365
    },
    {
        "question": " 105京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.084879776886748
    },
    {
        "question": " 69.5垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.285944020068856
    },
    {
        "question": " 987京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.216124419140773
    },
    {
        "question": " 489億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6893505435197231
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.23兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.348518473741395
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.41万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 1.1484058914590034
    },
    {
        "question": " 42.8万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.193462447422945
    },
    {
        "question": " 31.1年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.434627256185368
    },
    {
        "question": " 76.4年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.381911567536324
    },
    {
        "question": " 941日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.41151118780451745
    },
    {
        "question": " 65日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.1933675996541
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.8日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.231942021635953
    },
    {
        "question": " 90.5日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.893187579028581
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.34兆時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.183428477207043
    },
    {
        "question": " 27.3万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.0562729473290045
    },
    {
        "question": " 1851時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.045459710803812
    },
    {
        "question": " 337兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.806736212312874
    },
    {
        "question": " 50億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.540268400034551
    },
    {
        "question": " 69.2万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.062019629898003
    },
    {
        "question": " 64.9分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.5903475153060365
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.04億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8098921130426839
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.05億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.3762372312855495
    },
    {
        "question": " 112万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4913443400522395
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.6万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.3569739906054585
    },
    {
        "question": " 18.5秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.266580505608814
    },
    {
        "question": " 218京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.839901186334
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.46億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0395191014200444
    },
    {
        "question": " 135億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.574388842491114
    },
    {
        "question": " 34.1億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.754307567139037
    },
    {
        "question": " 456億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.6593721951852425
    },
    {
        "question": " 19.2万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.28300308983001
    },
    {
        "question": " 320msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 8.505379660677502
    },
    {
        "question": " 6028兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.28136691248093
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.39垓usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.207398082196308
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.63兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.3795504603283453
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.3兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.236312367172865
    },
    {
        "question": " 814兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.910769368703797
    },
    {
        "question": " 62.8億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.797631470896018
    },
    {
        "question": " 903垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.456905870810723
    },
    {
        "question": " 36.7京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.627627813125031
    },
    {
        "question": " 250京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.841955957472996
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.54垓nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.408785787369066
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.43兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.3857374595316
    },
    {
        "question": " 318兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.502259224249288
    },
    {
        "question": " 380億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.579591288020221
    },
    {
        "question": " 44.5年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.210659333410066
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.72万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.88321717755907
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.14万年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.776058912326102
    },
    {
        "question": " 504億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.140246223422407
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.96億日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.851594064007143
    },
    {
        "question": " 27.8兆時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.500989991987364
    },
    {
        "question": " 823億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.535235603021656
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.19時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.118890708533475
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.72時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.443651502164123
    },
    {
        "question": " 1301兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.393617098060194
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.5万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.059245307368048
    },
    {
        "question": " 1720分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4574203920030249
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.37億分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.916090518929847
    },
    {
        "question": " 7301兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.364586983320951
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.14兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.122100945299871
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.2万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5214288262123634
    },
    {
        "question": " 212秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5482981796010922
    },
    {
        "question": " 26.7秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.427132621665609
    },
    {
        "question": " 36.7秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.565029865432702
    },
    {
        "question": " 70.4兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.34906844805422
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.17京msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.919168964532023
    },
    {
        "question": " 1185万msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5173373038804618
    },
    {
        "question": " 802万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1259878230421325
    },
    {
        "question": " 184万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.2642223237318846
    },
    {
        "question": " 263msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 8.420090948358247
    },
    {
        "question": " 2104兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.824137901216324
    },
    {
        "question": " 8829億usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0093919173196608
    },
    {
        "question": " 107兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.473030317992906
    },
    {
        "question": " 1156兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.284777890753025
    },
    {
        "question": " 1672億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.2233167133005
    },
    {
        "question": " 186億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.268676502823338
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.16垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.836265506208103
    },
    {
        "question": " 158兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.2626160462546512
    },
    {
        "question": " 55.1垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.1847331083875
    },
    {
        "question": " 4001京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.82402571316194
    },
    {
        "question": " 800兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.902975475875731
    },
    {
        "question": " 233億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.367845437312083
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.11兆nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.852040966700299
    },
    {
        "question": " 21万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.885138747339454
    },
    {
        "question": " 75.9万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.822988860775736
    },
    {
        "question": " 52.9年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.22253682490066
    },
    {
        "question": " 8496日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3669086881121872
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.72万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.616908666751516
    },
    {
        "question": " 144日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.317220574629711
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.93兆時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.523893615366273
    },
    {
        "question": " 33.6時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.1458375774795928
    },
    {
        "question": " 1671時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.001030133143386
    },
    {
        "question": " 233時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.923546910860077
    },
    {
        "question": " 25.9億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.6918495415843333
    },
    {
        "question": " 52.4億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.561335867859961
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.71億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.453985423257911
    },
    {
        "question": " 7573万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.657441785467707
    },
    {
        "question": " 790兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.398986289136557
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.97兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.062227797280384
    },
    {
        "question": " 204万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.753849129349566
    },
    {
        "question": " 1934万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.508332898787934
    },
    {
        "question": " 3648兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.063281390834638
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.34京msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.701460234130918
    },
    {
        "question": " 1980兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.740375554523364
    },
    {
        "question": " 54.6兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.959302766852723
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.19億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.503347251995978
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.2msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 7.152327077107143
    },
    {
        "question": " 28.5垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.95565351945963
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.4京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.25218608918386
    },
    {
        "question": " 46.6兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.111751378718232
    },
    {
        "question": " 8484兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.150430593769336
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.69億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6715264419618476
    },
    {
        "question": " 320万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.5053782001587184
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.64万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 7.421997238366936
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.334e+04垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.626210776322909
    },
    {
        "question": " 36.6京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.6272304559819912
    },
    {
        "question": " 2223京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.790612756341831
    },
    {
        "question": " 1100億nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.2632563366520191
    },
    {
        "question": " 6174億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7905780864306218
    },
    {
        "question": " 59.3億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.772812792053921
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.84億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 5.89447506569991
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.26万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.423390262158235
    },
    {
        "question": " 80万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.845687862423311
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.24年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.440340439255312
    },
    {
        "question": " 38.9年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.08913611723294
    },
    {
        "question": " 117億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.5062050000041545
    },
    {
        "question": " 350万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.924014724921044
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.47日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.8960538524950064
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.1万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.670722118986945
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.43億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.54540721957068
    },
    {
        "question": " 2302万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.140331375045307
    },
    {
        "question": " 60.9時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.340916992170788
    },
    {
        "question": " 1656万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4983404397681022
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.98万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.137480571945667
    },
    {
        "question": " 1058億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.246286028183198
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.61万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.527163555184588
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.66分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.446895648146629
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.26兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.855130450785556
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.9兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.059207255904045
    },
    {
        "question": " 542万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.1778322567365347
    },
    {
        "question": " 14万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.3672848432991085
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.69万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.986384231911796
    },
    {
        "question": " 3502秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.544332190418153
    },
    {
        "question": " 113兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.555717250378682
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.34京msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.03371809571526
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.55京msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.634470561091714
    },
    {
        "question": " 1967万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.51575023663434
    },
    {
        "question": " 2478msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.3941686248050402
    },
    {
        "question": " 3577msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.5534930406686485
    },
    {
        "question": " 87.9msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 7.943894532433115
    },
    {
        "question": " 3809兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.082049113608737
    },
    {
        "question": " 137京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.199361695626281
    },
    {
        "question": " 2109京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.76772777868922
    },
    {
        "question": " 356兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.772737479022086
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.87兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.947917690239914
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.27万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.1052776693927113
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.49usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 3.542877654158476
    },
    {
        "question": " 269京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9306258071768756
    },
    {
        "question": " 450京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.716624551079277
    },
    {
        "question": " 266垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.867959439739051
    },
    {
        "question": " 723億nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.08121802066533124
    },
    {
        "question": " 2673億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4270649943572975
    },
    {
        "question": " 1257万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.0993749164540745
    },
    {
        "question": " 122万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 3.0848818633734822
    },
    {
        "question": " 337年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.089723159292011
    },
    {
        "question": " 24.2億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.821072282380964
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.8億日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.635230479060414
    },
    {
        "question": " 2690日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.588121339001736
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.42万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5915028985280357
    },
    {
        "question": " 81.4時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5304234541661013
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.26万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.291581273586192
    },
    {
        "question": " 168億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.5049938711893045
    },
    {
        "question": " 1620億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.051204351060454
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.69億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.047393969039399
    },
    {
        "question": " 71.7分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.633507136219837
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.34兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.1391582869502415
    },
    {
        "question": " 58.6兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.831269701544889
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.1億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.446166967105163
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.45億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.870154358807118
    },
    {
        "question": " 26.8秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.428259181198808
    },
    {
        "question": " 273秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.436082788261603
    },
    {
        "question": " 560兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.249154375480427
    },
    {
        "question": " 1507兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.2416880889668755
    },
    {
        "question": " 7251億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.3041050641056975
    },
    {
        "question": " 140億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.3674201796645935
    },
    {
        "question": " 103万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.0121055354401918
    },
    {
        "question": " 357msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 8.55274875104198
    },
    {
        "question": " 7811兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.393872529909995
    },
    {
        "question": " 51.6京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.775741222181817
    },
    {
        "question": " 1063億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4702583067304875
    },
    {
        "question": " 255億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.628489221397178
    },
    {
        "question": " 2059万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3137582475342913
    },
    {
        "question": " 1267usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 0.10270207399588283
    },
    {
        "question": " 45京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1545490278484571
    },
    {
        "question": " 245京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.452131488041403
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.74京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.881855973980266
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.18兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9364027197102307
    },
    {
        "question": " 152億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.18101033239996
    },
    {
        "question": " 478万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 0.6794110248961793
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.3万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 1.5183325942525039
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.25万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.658116819512994
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.12万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.268145072550562
    },
    {
        "question": " 119万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.513712672257694
    },
    {
        "question": " 618万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.949333443772012
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.07万日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.251736448795851
    },
    {
        "question": " 845億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.984347310489331
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.42億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.153363709145022
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.39時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7506837155245556
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.1万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.562500920727382
    },
    {
        "question": " 20.6億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.5932650528098034
    },
    {
        "question": " 490億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.531766006265954
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.82億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.986684712241217
    },
    {
        "question": " 69.9分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.6225649430835913
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.42分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.930440391972848
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.14分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.8356185492467745
    },
    {
        "question": " 1220兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.58740083332826
    },
    {
        "question": " 52.4兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.782714704862562
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.41万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.087732047226606
    },
    {
        "question": " 2132億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.550724441500858
    },
    {
        "question": " 41.2万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.614518689474428
    },
    {
        "question": " 259兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.9141990157779327
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.24億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.1583770149991881
    },
    {
        "question": " 7543億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.3212506533556505
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.3兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.336729792792092
    },
    {
        "question": " 20.8万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3188452950656604
    },
    {
        "question": " 24.8msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 7.394149854547983
    },
    {
        "question": " 4680兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1714679397147396
    },
    {
        "question": " 6760京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.893450035263943
    },
    {
        "question": " 5131兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.15391450979223
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.7兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.356992374705278
    },
    {
        "question": " 432兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.635614352696027
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.97万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.6963466465742638
    },
    {
        "question": " 340usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 5.5316697819890965
    },
    {
        "question": " 772垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.388712516564339
    },
    {
        "question": " 706京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.91227500934121
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.69兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.43018779448293576
    },
    {
        "question": " 52.7兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.943562639616233
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.12京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.049154384630356
    },
    {
        "question": " 44.8兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.651621732399047
    },
    {
        "question": " 26.4億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.422014389376933
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.76年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.517491145470231
    },
    {
        "question": " 338万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.967240046439302
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.75万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.269389788496412
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.39日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.805312597512358
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.6兆時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.082810759583683
    },
    {
        "question": " 2801時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.067169272090795
    },
    {
        "question": " 7496時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.652981573117845
    },
    {
        "question": " 24.5時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.94580627308315
    },
    {
        "question": " 60.1時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.335487339006523
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.06億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.128390885653557
    },
    {
        "question": " 407万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.4511004117923747
    },
    {
        "question": " 601分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.00056883418277
    },
    {
        "question": " 2012分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.081685111049844
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.07億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8173707507842376
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.26兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.162240124504731
    },
    {
        "question": " 82億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.357526917711747
    },
    {
        "question": " 32.1万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.7278688953727435
    },
    {
        "question": " 27.5万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.43868414251011
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.77兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.179940760381942
    },
    {
        "question": " 92.1兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.027946246951004
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.94億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7307763038108548
    },
    {
        "question": " 5749億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.981473356547811
    },
    {
        "question": " 5440msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7356302086987476
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.25msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 3.5118200434597133
    },
    {
        "question": " 8230兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.416603709421387
    },
    {
        "question": " 8919億usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0137964841425173
    },
    {
        "question": " 8115兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.352965861231681
    },
    {
        "question": " 303億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.702587619326388
    },
    {
        "question": " 5113万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7086672574595518
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.21兆usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.344260119299468
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.1usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 3.785160945304651
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.984e+05垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.454663536468841
    },
    {
        "question": " 85.6京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.995819813432372
    },
    {
        "question": " 749京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.3181644375939765
    },
    {
        "question": " 5925兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.994541364751365
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.2兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.049402017077122
    },
    {
        "question": " 78.5兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.895113161195341
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.4万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 2.093261540723348
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.61年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.5004128215697845
    },
    {
        "question": " 29.2億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.902432383253396
    },
    {
        "question": " 537万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.110350803326106
    },
    {
        "question": " 5024日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.637562269494026
    },
    {
        "question": " 115日は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.996161263854633
    },
    {
        "question": " 6691万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.882958219845044
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.5万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.6796057124676143
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.66万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.446423102214612
    },
    {
        "question": " 633億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.080965563563748
    },
    {
        "question": " 1194万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.9185221710107943
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.47万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.032947852732233
    },
    {
        "question": " 42.2分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.4034512537905846
    },
    {
        "question": " 1924分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.062364590423133
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.39兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.306428661001295
    },
    {
        "question": " 1449万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2246647095165653
    },
    {
        "question": " 527万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.165665183158115
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.67億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.444900248636705
    },
    {
        "question": " 294万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.468206467129715
    },
    {
        "question": " 921京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.4653641265345
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.4京msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.078905684809182
    },
    {
        "question": " 756億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.322085277283292
    },
    {
        "question": " 98.7兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.216267639051637
    },
    {
        "question": " 137万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.1368592269595785
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.42万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.925299542713322
    },
    {
        "question": " 6767兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.331581012218178
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.07垓usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.379848903547304
    },
    {
        "question": " 1221兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.530344914186534
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.3兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.233833945453068
    },
    {
        "question": " 1668万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2222601735303473
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.46万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.16353046605147
    },
    {
        "question": " 93.6usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 4.971161034726691
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.5京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5244295100883956
    },
    {
        "question": " 3372兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.591434401697922
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.7垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.546532237466593
    },
    {
        "question": " 3421兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.75596794733315
    },
    {
        "question": " 480億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6809118196777484
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.02億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 2.480655513178065
    },
    {
        "question": " 2418億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.383385398172413
    },
    {
        "question": " 198年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.859907537665636
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.69年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.1691635670467955
    },
    {
        "question": " 277年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.940682014236284
    },
    {
        "question": " 26.4万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8596757091799585
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.6日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6009730744916713
    },
    {
        "question": " 23.4万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4264090844631805
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.21億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.413120595499102
    },
    {
        "question": " 1994万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.077883602070445
    },
    {
        "question": " 1447時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.716753493521091
    },
    {
        "question": " 34.2億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.813895397296223
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.4万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.08173362145583
    },
    {
        "question": " 193億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.508207048734626
    },
    {
        "question": " 6758万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.607968886130969
    },
    {
        "question": " 307億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9887818270361945
    },
    {
        "question": " 45.1兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.71793785552984
    },
    {
        "question": " 118万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.515515065548265
    },
    {
        "question": " 4594億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.884028817208215
    },
    {
        "question": " 567秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.753660044013845
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.65秒は何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.218315327433142
    },
    {
        "question": " 75.9京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.381680006648033
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.22京msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.149588939237152
    },
    {
        "question": " 9268億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.410676959967862
    },
    {
        "question": " 241兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.603866021465674
    },
    {
        "question": " 4924億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.692335494399364
    },
    {
        "question": " 18.4万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.265110569133409
    },
    {
        "question": " 371msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 8.569391262586784
    },
    {
        "question": " 738京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.368998637754109
    },
    {
        "question": " 103京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.075919006887457
    },
    {
        "question": " 20.8兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.7624536302404943
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.18億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7241515226578599
    },
    {
        "question": " 268億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.428780436703286
    },
    {
        "question": " 46.7億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.669574873019881
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.3usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 4.1844538854978
    },
    {
        "question": " 577京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.262471116380996
    },
    {
        "question": " 18.9京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.3399199013622227
    },
    {
        "question": " 78.3京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.33750405597009
    },
    {
        "question": " 2635億nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6426344497870096
    },
    {
        "question": " 31.9京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.503401721199323
    },
    {
        "question": " 189億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.275478095107744
    },
    {
        "question": " 60.3億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.780119772419687
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.74年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8027060757111077
    },
    {
        "question": " 10年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.722044018686582
    },
    {
        "question": " 20.7年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.814132436674335
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.26万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4042494821021396
    },
    {
        "question": " 151日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.558117090993076
    },
    {
        "question": " 26.6日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.362067169422181
    },
    {
        "question": " 605万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8390298105772374
    },
    {
        "question": " 29.3時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.087171768881944
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.38万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.50856711667916
    },
    {
        "question": " 3284時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.072705087748888
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.46時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.205203403785866
    },
    {
        "question": " 409万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8911886168472116
    },
    {
        "question": " 393億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.43597809286586
    },
    {
        "question": " 51.7億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.93562310481561
    },
    {
        "question": " 146分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.942009729223565
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.87兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.088797119043421
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.9兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.316134707388843
    },
    {
        "question": " 54.1億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.176859800858288
    },
    {
        "question": " 1660万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.44200137899877
    },
    {
        "question": " 114万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.056341272210135
    },
    {
        "question": " 62.8秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.797811068607552
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.53京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.244101943742586
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.17億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.39943371747049206
    },
    {
        "question": " 90.4兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.40002073975853
    },
    {
        "question": " 50.2兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.922174737886015
    },
    {
        "question": " 330億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.518614044402345
    },
    {
        "question": " 104垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.519534566699887
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.85京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.33159431692651
    },
    {
        "question": " 135京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.573656471953043
    },
    {
        "question": " 430億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.855037539754287
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.28億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.722694036060489
    },
    {
        "question": " 271万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.432449459319024
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.67usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 3.8850590497906854
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.504e+05垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.376501556966705
    },
    {
        "question": " 5268垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.785136923792662
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.57京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.9957884556032175
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.8京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.362162156740379
    },
    {
        "question": " 42.3億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6262437537705978
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.08兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.033063343298592
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.32兆nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.920177809878105
    },
    {
        "question": " 18.5万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.2085705745795
    },
    {
        "question": " 171年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.952603274830633
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.4年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.231539286115554
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.45万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5994251453258634
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.12億日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.99466208555283
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.3日は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.855710093804456
    },
    {
        "question": " 77.2兆時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.944866466275418
    },
    {
        "question": " 80億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.522830822438873
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.3万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.608242655951578
    },
    {
        "question": " 715億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.133937492591148
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.4万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8569358900576283
    },
    {
        "question": " 125分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.31816701925024504
    },
    {
        "question": " 2235万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.127518229205032
    },
    {
        "question": " 223分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.1270218253654525
    },
    {
        "question": " 13分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.892012218060488
    },
    {
        "question": " 1676兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.725576216660489
    },
    {
        "question": " 64.2兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.871098517388535
    },
    {
        "question": " 338億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.972391886400348
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.49億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.19889723596098
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.1兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.733705189906966
    },
    {
        "question": " 19.6京msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.355332106069664
    },
    {
        "question": " 3948万msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.040035430563624
    },
    {
        "question": " 1298億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.335145043081404
    },
    {
        "question": " 1987msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.2981138024197971
    },
    {
        "question": " 4349msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.6384052274187955
    },
    {
        "question": " 9199兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.464913228290629
    },
    {
        "question": " 182京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.32320213533315
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.9兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.5532038773136057
    },
    {
        "question": " 81.8億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1347644536296952
    },
    {
        "question": " 82.9兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.918738968091203
    },
    {
        "question": " 537万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.730356133409918
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.384e+04垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.424656079448837
    },
    {
        "question": " 651兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8770622612228551
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.29京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.411761201014576
    },
    {
        "question": " 9924億nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2185430194442881
    },
    {
        "question": " 110京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.039904944364093
    },
    {
        "question": " 835兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.921926221049008
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.25万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 1.3515596573762012
    },
    {
        "question": " 99.4年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.93990651114396
    },
    {
        "question": " 33.7万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.965335689024297
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.9日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5238823984762404
    },
    {
        "question": " 347万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.699149452472538
    },
    {
        "question": " 55.4兆時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.801250351079856
    },
    {
        "question": " 21.7万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.956256992104975
    },
    {
        "question": " 34.3時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.0921502308874755
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.7億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.3493160941252875
    },
    {
        "question": " 7266万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.702935045088076
    },
    {
        "question": " 182分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.48145937069845823
    },
    {
        "question": " 46.4分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.4450958164899106
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.66分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.60139675915852
    },
    {
        "question": " 202兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.8063674370693334
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.49億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.803252600982132
    },
    {
        "question": " 150億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.61905166476409
    },
    {
        "question": " 69.1億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.06154634688379
    },
    {
        "question": " 27.5京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.940791282774094
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.13京msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.679830643767835
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.59京msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.85725639898112
    },
    {
        "question": " 1676億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.446192107470569
    },
    {
        "question": " 8829万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.945900736412103
    },
    {
        "question": " 620msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 5.792396759783082
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.8垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.75045510022622
    },
    {
        "question": " 242京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.446865069816808
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.24京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.793117119225953
    },
    {
        "question": " 6390億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.027330011250866
    },
    {
        "question": " 101兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.004998391207906
    },
    {
        "question": " 9983usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 0.9992646580810338
    },
    {
        "question": " 86.7usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 4.938263003596118
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.34垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.025335291961783
    },
    {
        "question": " 5202垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.779677116827802
    },
    {
        "question": " 233京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.810468312408135
    },
    {
        "question": " 323兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.7306979764148873
    },
    {
        "question": " 211兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.323763276905719
    },
    {
        "question": " 230兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.361043632015653
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.04万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 1.3104140609777648
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.09万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.0521928551218735
    },
    {
        "question": " 199年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.241539832439054
    },
    {
        "question": " 58.4年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.487319572924952
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.55年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.904794054959217
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.02万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1387785693651096
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.93万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.22107015010525
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.98日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.855158515136279
    },
    {
        "question": " 2058万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.370836739655126
    },
    {
        "question": " 169億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.847146424376183
    },
    {
        "question": " 7600時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.658959898123105
    },
    {
        "question": " 70.3兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.12618822344553
    },
    {
        "question": " 2287分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.20098979649413096
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.55万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.41121673219871
    },
    {
        "question": " 605分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.559977224728652
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.12分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.487619109812173
    },
    {
        "question": " 27.3分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.214640355469493
    },
    {
        "question": " 258億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.91301939333089
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.91兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.527831001871563
    },
    {
        "question": " 4399万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.0870439964409275
    },
    {
        "question": " 476秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8998630500487093
    },
    {
        "question": " 6147億msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2898318471634618
    },
    {
        "question": " 89.5億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.015367742621547
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.15兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.505393092181122
    },
    {
        "question": " 1073億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.252264092342388
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.34兆msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.52396547342526
    },
    {
        "question": " 351万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.545896650459408
    },
    {
        "question": " 4977msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.696945394847111
    },
    {
        "question": " 404垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.107147712933926
    },
    {
        "question": " 172京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.299352680758485
    },
    {
        "question": " 2040億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7534150871952503
    },
    {
        "question": " 130兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.337003620285594
    },
    {
        "question": " 34.2億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.5343551922447736
    },
    {
        "question": " 65.5億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.8162839500948085
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.84usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 3.946521074947087
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.428e+05垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.036244376331867
    },
    {
        "question": " 126兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.16320175034309825
    },
    {
        "question": " 1557京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.636101237936131
    },
    {
        "question": " 83.8兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.145293548232261
    },
    {
        "question": " 586兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.768086942353819
    },
    {
        "question": " 53.2兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.7255821326422724
    },
    {
        "question": " 565億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.751840918095922
    },
    {
        "question": " 939年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.534890129628538
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.14年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.439969090238244
    },
    {
        "question": " 127年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.601664016016029
    },
    {
        "question": " 1908億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.718354531717353
    },
    {
        "question": " 9409万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.353748725958331
    },
    {
        "question": " 135日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.066304917439008
    },
    {
        "question": " 1409億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.206555446847773
    },
    {
        "question": " 1764億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.866175640549912
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.4時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.871787948679075
    },
    {
        "question": " 25兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.677537257317001
    },
    {
        "question": " 8124万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.751429951744772
    },
    {
        "question": " 858万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.155142856578864
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.4分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9245034997236543
    },
    {
        "question": " 1609分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.984683026264015
    },
    {
        "question": " 8868兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.448995082610928
    },
    {
        "question": " 55.6兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.80891858340908
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.05兆秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.40032642279245
    },
    {
        "question": " 192万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.504636655787536
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.32秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.1202192925059635
    },
    {
        "question": " 21.8京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.840560340693895
    },
    {
        "question": " 47.6兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.741356808288714
    },
    {
        "question": " 2477兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.837602859339263
    },
    {
        "question": " 34億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.753752655369292
    },
    {
        "question": " 217万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.336813303317425
    },
    {
        "question": " 1055msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.023411462719338
    },
    {
        "question": " 39.4垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.096520168407693
    },
    {
        "question": " 693兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.904221301888998
    },
    {
        "question": " 3634兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.004121489912487
    },
    {
        "question": " 27兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.653407073163521
    },
    {
        "question": " 36.1億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.557229121566383
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.95億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.951625153149617
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.17usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 3.5016633676144373
    },
    {
        "question": " 8615京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.436461326026711
    },
    {
        "question": " 68.3京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.897807986464602
    },
    {
        "question": " 22.2垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.789988258253315
    },
    {
        "question": " 120兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.3017876026564306
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.19兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.074981365572007
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.69億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 2.4305207673759686
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.58億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 5.660437414761713
    },
    {
        "question": " 43年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.575680742749114
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.12年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.680768717957912
    },
    {
        "question": " 10年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.499889331167848
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.37兆日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.81325117671994
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.22億日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.466935058652798
    },
    {
        "question": " 46.4日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.824845570316459
    },
    {
        "question": " 8692万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.9965959421674624
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.43億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.776240726284395
    },
    {
        "question": " 4181時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.177537162432028
    },
    {
        "question": " 1758時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.801424613471815
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.15億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6114926186839513
    },
    {
        "question": " 210万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.1642151930253117
    },
    {
        "question": " 70.2万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.068081897096945
    },
    {
        "question": " 6275分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.575754566231882
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.16万分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.396815592073771
    },
    {
        "question": " 1416兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.652290196412581
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.54兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.468567365494707
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.82万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7045095543156898
    },
    {
        "question": " 802万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.126083422221143
    },
    {
        "question": " 963秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.983714362978958
    },
    {
        "question": " 45.7京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.16120981684952
    },
    {
        "question": " 106億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.08886880680876
    },
    {
        "question": " 1935兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.730386377882725
    },
    {
        "question": " 135億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.35332698015949
    },
    {
        "question": " 8835msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9461988665949261
    },
    {
        "question": " 170万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.229950427986765
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.68京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.325701327352534
    },
    {
        "question": " 150京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.238452604512161
    },
    {
        "question": " 799兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.346186632972579
    },
    {
        "question": " 267兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.6479703358285605
    },
    {
        "question": " 310兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.490989515527037
    },
    {
        "question": " 147万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.1680285574300795
    },
    {
        "question": " 77.7京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3915614811363919
    },
    {
        "question": " 502垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.764082477248202
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.01京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.143834192277053
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.95兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9965387761444364
    },
    {
        "question": " 30億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.4767668149893822
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.68億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 2.670294273812037
    },
    {
        "question": " 9546nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 0.979824137096591
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.3年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.774016267364624
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.58億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.636910387341532
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.71日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6127998380885022
    },
    {
        "question": " 20.9万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.477932614004214
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.97億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.655749768833841
    },
    {
        "question": " 3958時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2172741422682507
    },
    {
        "question": " 78.1万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.670911323376425
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.54時間は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.743068018175526
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.2兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.903021753336628
    },
    {
        "question": " 413億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.458028285772468
    },
    {
        "question": " 41.2万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.836326754793582
    },
    {
        "question": " 134万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.905462327869359
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.37万分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.700882818024166
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.23億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0107137610013206
    },
    {
        "question": " 750億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.938375807945207
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.72兆秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.877853015490176
    },
    {
        "question": " 41.1億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.835375577674898
    },
    {
        "question": " 50.7万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.705130815173165
    },
    {
        "question": " 2013億msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8051345436105539
    },
    {
        "question": " 40.2京msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.668245261694729
    },
    {
        "question": " 209億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.7634012169801667
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.9億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.683974871287159
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.8億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.892163228777453
    },
    {
        "question": " 248兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.896214497608474
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.04兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0802354264588365
    },
    {
        "question": " 54京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.175691454277906
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.19億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5614019569352802
    },
    {
        "question": " 109兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.03711095944428
    },
    {
        "question": " 536億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.729034363681727
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.26垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.601437186345542
    },
    {
        "question": " 585垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.831005471906876
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.7京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.640004031448857
    },
    {
        "question": " 104京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.240536513815795
    },
    {
        "question": " 272億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4343027533341346
    },
    {
        "question": " 39.9兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.601161415297115
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.22兆nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.087582230682434
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.18年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.22287844967871
    },
    {
        "question": " 1718万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.672707977347334
    },
    {
        "question": " 80.7日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.2871929742554484
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.81万日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.769542060265263
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.42日は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.470274505059358
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.8億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.196803410491503
    },
    {
        "question": " 150時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7966322807897275
    },
    {
        "question": " 1598万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.98172855770887
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.65万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.773193156492278
    },
    {
        "question": " 267万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7054138055810477
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.94万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3105832560643893
    },
    {
        "question": " 6591分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.040800970900536
    },
    {
        "question": " 939万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.750628086905271
    },
    {
        "question": " 7269分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.639606147436329
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.45京秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.661322295763638
    },
    {
        "question": " 374兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.636248615398882
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.19兆秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.5197133114818
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.05億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.244716121374064
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.29秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.1093198003972375
    },
    {
        "question": " 19.8京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.798585500054748
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.76億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.893625272257792
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.71兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.200584168640946
    },
    {
        "question": " 637億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.025964839544846
    },
    {
        "question": " 1620msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.20956858414229673
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.16万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.7124188857043094
    },
    {
        "question": " 43.3兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.13781628086686148
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.78垓usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.742867804492306
    },
    {
        "question": " 497京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.140204926986469
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.24兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.940965656146371
    },
    {
        "question": " 6588万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8187499354110914
    },
    {
        "question": " 585億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.767330800071841
    },
    {
        "question": " 49.2京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1931457434342119
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.56京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4724609027962616
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.83垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.027084384091522
    },
    {
        "question": " 7274京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.083635504332342
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.2兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.119085958520121
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.6億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.025130589929157
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.96億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 5.900858177948919
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.51万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.1072667555579585
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.23年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.568635990510672
    },
    {
        "question": " 56.4億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.189231949982512
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.39億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.2003729380176535
    },
    {
        "question": " 149万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.792434226487272
    },
    {
        "question": " 202億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.585599418082142
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.9万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8373540306865066
    },
    {
        "question": " 20.9億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.54222067620147
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.43億分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.934029910774631
    },
    {
        "question": " 131兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.6184896419477095
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.9万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.13955902362263295
    },
    {
        "question": " 8311秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.3633315780690294
    },
    {
        "question": " 33.5万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.7470122639967984
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.19秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.5041736908758914
    },
    {
        "question": " 647秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.811162287422128
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.78秒は何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.89100550208007
    },
    {
        "question": " 87.6京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.443562517936112
    },
    {
        "question": " 20.3兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.371679215066148
    },
    {
        "question": " 3848万msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0288943852300358
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.6万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.28481910374862585
    },
    {
        "question": " 1154万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.062348331033611
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.21msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 3.7931434490764637
    },
    {
        "question": " 6759兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3310720313370217
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.5兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1940009502077307
    },
    {
        "question": " 104兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.459615429702014
    },
    {
        "question": " 1144兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.2801076120690436
    },
    {
        "question": " 16兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.204208454589479
    },
    {
        "question": " 73.3万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 2.8650506054871894
    },
    {
        "question": " 2022usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.305751027705277
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.56垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.909142408739197
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.6垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.266954359136703
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.63京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.864093464908318
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.76兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4675644636133511
    },
    {
        "question": " 91.6兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.962087869841326
    },
    {
        "question": " 831兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.919752531358466
    },
    {
        "question": " 1196億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.07768749153587
    },
    {
        "question": " 2667億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.863663655486125
    },
    {
        "question": " 723万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.23905199786873
    },
    {
        "question": " 76.5万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.041977628722947
    },
    {
        "question": " 1656日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.155519660207188
    },
    {
        "question": " 27.6万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4991592131503706
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.35億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.749553439151306
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.1時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.561713521807182
    },
    {
        "question": " 368万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8447982189773118
    },
    {
        "question": " 5145万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.5530409753621
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.51万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.622047501671241
    },
    {
        "question": " 2768万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.22027552067233
    },
    {
        "question": " 8321分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.69830179185653
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.67億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7237191594511672
    },
    {
        "question": " 28.2万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5135334234665601
    },
    {
        "question": " 7944秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.3437510682901135
    },
    {
        "question": " 76.1秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.10319618064293712
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.05京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.52326442162288
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.4京msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.932503750338643
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.54兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.630460148868394
    },
    {
        "question": " 4198億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.844938550736535
    },
    {
        "question": " 118万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.0702160080933263
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.04万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.018552871044454
    },
    {
        "question": " 1060京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.526670452344628
    },
    {
        "question": " 1910兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.344622142750406
    },
    {
        "question": " 394京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.039547506125848
    },
    {
        "question": " 3772億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.7983996254798944
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.5億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.0974145561023403
    },
    {
        "question": " 4534usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 0.6564644482181758
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.24万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 7.094590595890481
    },
    {
        "question": " 243京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8874320934318378
    },
    {
        "question": " 7601兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9443597913324806
    },
    {
        "question": " 149垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.61658372321347
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.45兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.760163977183018
    },
    {
        "question": " 19.4兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.288659387976929
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.5兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.176366392724645
    },
    {
        "question": " 3232億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.50951865587589
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.01年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.420414260800695
    },
    {
        "question": " 326億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.951566107516919
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.62万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.798902659430791
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.87日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.430681668834734
    },
    {
        "question": " 23.6億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.430203604535287
    },
    {
        "question": " 2287万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.9790819390662335
    },
    {
        "question": " 379時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.13540239488219
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.07億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3074614911125515
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.99万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5400683417684824
    },
    {
        "question": " 2408分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.603592317832413
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.92分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3715873517572894
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.81分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.358576803137204
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.24京秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.220544044827417
    },
    {
        "question": " 147億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.231111323363043
    },
    {
        "question": " 2219万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.789931357002556
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.9万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.2597573823304424
    },
    {
        "question": " 29万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.463075922333484
    },
    {
        "question": " 391秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.59251055077498
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.65兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.718647586168166
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.1億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.10529219660912803
    },
    {
        "question": " 3989億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.044576805749305
    },
    {
        "question": " 1518億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.403123353864666
    },
    {
        "question": " 811億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.908760040930344
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.6msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.099948297283181
    },
    {
        "question": " 2913垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.965560560574596
    },
    {
        "question": " 76.5兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9473945993692707
    },
    {
        "question": " 9712億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4310057992326217
    },
    {
        "question": " 4861億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.908556702481861
    },
    {
        "question": " 4643万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6668168345762335
    },
    {
        "question": " 1688万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.227264829923918
    },
    {
        "question": " 25.2usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 4.40157463413793
    },
    {
        "question": " 4485垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.152987110356001
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.1京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.2434368841706886
    },
    {
        "question": " 3409兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9763730742087393
    },
    {
        "question": " 109京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.259474043870936
    },
    {
        "question": " 89.5京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.95198164299878
    },
    {
        "question": " 389億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.589734407713914
    },
    {
        "question": " 9219億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.964697777293132
    },
    {
        "question": " 1633万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.775309922325091
    },
    {
        "question": " 45.9年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.160651507628584
    },
    {
        "question": " 221億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.782485141930864
    },
    {
        "question": " 33.1日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.678223470443751
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.6日は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.182174187383632
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.73兆時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.998720365475467
    },
    {
        "question": " 364時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.180534300972016
    },
    {
        "question": " 8013万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.681926343849756
    },
    {
        "question": " 1683兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.505507729463389
    },
    {
        "question": " 22億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.184844350688347
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.29億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.739299548275688
    },
    {
        "question": " 1879分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.052167716565595
    },
    {
        "question": " 94.5億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4768260222708696
    },
    {
        "question": " 680兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.89582695412837
    },
    {
        "question": " 6438秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.25244609161615417
    },
    {
        "question": " 497億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.9185066867245
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.02万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.903980585058933
    },
    {
        "question": " 1624兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.711672213050745
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.05億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.08671930895537416
    },
    {
        "question": " 1409兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.592505811435752
    },
    {
        "question": " 8742万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.1634486991347233
    },
    {
        "question": " 54.8億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.738799049909856
    },
    {
        "question": " 141msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 8.148056158396757
    },
    {
        "question": " 4517兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1560154682841794
    },
    {
        "question": " 69.3京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.9042893292514576
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.81京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.892158380764713
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.42京usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.373544251822626
    },
    {
        "question": " 41.1億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.61371010127131
    },
    {
        "question": " 162万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.2095515641585335
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.92垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.2734390654916545
    },
    {
        "question": " 1077京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.095774374452989
    },
    {
        "question": " 677兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2745931794996856
    },
    {
        "question": " 19.6兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5137052488978515
    },
    {
        "question": " 35.2京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.546548030059418
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.13兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.328765848265894
    },
    {
        "question": " 31.7億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.5011268208432424
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.34年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.0861911444536636
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.16万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.44263124697952
    },
    {
        "question": " 7194万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.29468146205031
    },
    {
        "question": " 409万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.991646872154099
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.73日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.39600799651687
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.8兆時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.28402370670635
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.31億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.13952649857601
    },
    {
        "question": " 247時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.1710513997645595
    },
    {
        "question": " 174兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.520117440709644
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.18兆分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.914176631776243
    },
    {
        "question": " 83.9分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.1453985669372082
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.59分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4399967198859853
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.46兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.666688645026129
    },
    {
        "question": " 4226万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.689409878421063
    },
    {
        "question": " 642万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.2513881463639995
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.3億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.4071451841884866
    },
    {
        "question": " 10万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.001716854246308
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.53秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.814802592126253
    },
    {
        "question": " 106京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.526099850088067
    },
    {
        "question": " 321億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5699320306887232
    },
    {
        "question": " 62億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.235986067036103
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.55兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.627615769030528
    },
    {
        "question": " 72.2万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8588199351051315
    },
    {
        "question": " 155万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.189278829033633
    },
    {
        "question": " 1416垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.65237714865885
    },
    {
        "question": " 166京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.282722325452199
    },
    {
        "question": " 41.1兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.057985055294097
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.3兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.234765344076605
    },
    {
        "question": " 995万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.997947982625198
    },
    {
        "question": " 27.4万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 2.4382911146352573
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.91usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 3.4646133690484424
    },
    {
        "question": " 3206京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.007110717572874
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.01京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5424775572728695
    },
    {
        "question": " 133兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5670656409784112
    },
    {
        "question": " 18.7兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.492778558186044
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.84京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.5846970561492055
    },
    {
        "question": " 1246兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.095398123225744
    },
    {
        "question": " 1378万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.139148970092357
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.8万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.787303036871456
    },
    {
        "question": " 9753億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.426851304283367
    },
    {
        "question": " 1804日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.636346831878548
    },
    {
        "question": " 18.1日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.416427357911901
    },
    {
        "question": " 5990日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.713910272664064
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.26万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6864566649836157
    },
    {
        "question": " 156時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8131602821322659
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.73万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.214651174159225
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.58時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.968244451243077
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.87億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5500573535986835
    },
    {
        "question": " 23.9億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.220755749174264
    },
    {
        "question": " 1009分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2257053658470807
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.83万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.543602442314355
    },
    {
        "question": " 21.8兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.839154362972234
    },
    {
        "question": " 2兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.364385229708661
    },
    {
        "question": " 591万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.215559679403751
    },
    {
        "question": " 3088秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.711473055977255
    },
    {
        "question": " 1480億msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6715542224206283
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.38京msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.931437270448258
    },
    {
        "question": " 8754兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.385909735540789
    },
    {
        "question": " 280億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.668383359312427
    },
    {
        "question": " 17億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.2312375054676945
    },
    {
        "question": " 307垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.988344999938972
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.2兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.072660304968167
    },
    {
        "question": " 405兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.0512048577305055
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.06億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.24835246190455185
    },
    {
        "question": " 3兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.477482597647541
    },
    {
        "question": " 198万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.296279522922844
    },
    {
        "question": " 91.5usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 4.961374805917604
    },
    {
        "question": " 5883京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.270820528633833
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.58京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2626983684237265
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.2垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.626218362247638
    },
    {
        "question": " 5兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9207499677158946
    },
    {
        "question": " 952億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9784748504128635
    },
    {
        "question": " 2310兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.36367695183673
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.02億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 5.846380584947093
    },
    {
        "question": " 37.1万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.131258077032703
    },
    {
        "question": " 243年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.328046760177796
    },
    {
        "question": " 153年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.683493358370042
    },
    {
        "question": " 2367億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.811812982259132
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.2万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.279889649520415
    },
    {
        "question": " 6916万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.8973726685847154
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.35億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.990671022910297
    },
    {
        "question": " 66.1時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.5985840231624766
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.2万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.737031740573144
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.31時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.673081219566493
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.86億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9658077450315345
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.99兆分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.540048236147891
    },
    {
        "question": " 794万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.121886590979178
    },
    {
        "question": " 639万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.583314873167174
    },
    {
        "question": " 3856兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.087365311604966
    },
    {
        "question": " 219億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.40304479788719
    },
    {
        "question": " 104億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.462473641236364
    },
    {
        "question": " 340秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7527400885621771
    },
    {
        "question": " 50.8秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.705901938087037
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.68秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.428493018443566
    },
    {
        "question": " 2366兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.875236052905455
    },
    {
        "question": " 7308兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.927283242288925
    },
    {
        "question": " 5036万msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1457649445359053
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.15億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.18324619935159
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.54億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.931251127537588
    },
    {
        "question": " 189万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.27598323551622
    },
    {
        "question": " 70.2京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.347716764226223
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.24兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7831118736121576
    },
    {
        "question": " 7035兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.290989072517647
    },
    {
        "question": " 8439兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.148145207574357
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.1兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.117446583253817
    },
    {
        "question": " 57.9万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 2.762674325421476
    },
    {
        "question": " 34.5万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 8.537413485571946
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.23垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.5919598023263823
    },
    {
        "question": " 89.2垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.013872458290773
    },
    {
        "question": " 121京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.524798828934121
    },
    {
        "question": " 85.6京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.154543684309384
    },
    {
        "question": " 33.4兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.523437942665231
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.26億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 2.79655235653952
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.57兆nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.87886289029761
    },
    {
        "question": " 2485万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.957547126951566
    },
    {
        "question": " 98.1万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.934023432109747
    },
    {
        "question": " 246億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.829493493645031
    },
    {
        "question": " 1546日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.569499924646349
    },
    {
        "question": " 100万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.159189504785077
    },
    {
        "question": " 696億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.900212566882765
    },
    {
        "question": " 324万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.129874500560232
    },
    {
        "question": " 93.4万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.526426505577541
    },
    {
        "question": " 174万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5198662840128632
    },
    {
        "question": " 3061万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.3274821521809095
    },
    {
        "question": " 460億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.884303243580437
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.81分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4599379284111187
    },
    {
        "question": " 36.1億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.058937109618302
    },
    {
        "question": " 225億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.416491520617156
    },
    {
        "question": " 43.4万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.0816352551896977
    },
    {
        "question": " 2363万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.595291331813027
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.34秒は何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.727851665210924
    },
    {
        "question": " 584兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.267489972568784
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.07兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.846953045544052
    },
    {
        "question": " 1299万msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.557209190790896
    },
    {
        "question": " 76.9兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.107891683084727
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.93億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.693017212350937
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.3万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.237614602223712
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.2京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.6842098071532803
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.91垓usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.527773413018494
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.88兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.2133352618804167
    },
    {
        "question": " 342億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7553015233816724
    },
    {
        "question": " 33.6兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.526913235959477
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.77兆usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.830495446113925
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.01usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 3.602756745035385
    },
    {
        "question": " 4849垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.186884359221929
    },
    {
        "question": " 116京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.128096020326542
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.72兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.014012335964458389
    },
    {
        "question": " 1695兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.451098746242607
    },
    {
        "question": " 712兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.8524414219522045
    },
    {
        "question": " 186万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 0.26888196784297436
    },
    {
        "question": " 1924万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.284272295986113
    },
    {
        "question": " 154年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.7512155797803395
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.9年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.221096670577555
    },
    {
        "question": " 2248万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.789468397077956
    },
    {
        "question": " 8771日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.323266740030221
    },
    {
        "question": " 130万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.271491289613525
    },
    {
        "question": " 5800億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.8209120125565175
    },
    {
        "question": " 19.6億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.911579821771739
    },
    {
        "question": " 6295時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.577113113399608
    },
    {
        "question": " 49.2兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.970919040155354
    },
    {
        "question": " 4099万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.454368072091768
    },
    {
        "question": " 52.8万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.9444366926313537
    },
    {
        "question": " 182分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.037278229870298
    },
    {
        "question": " 125億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.598550479724574
    },
    {
        "question": " 712兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.916233182037221
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.42億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.2513080898508
    },
    {
        "question": " 4606億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.885201643040608
    },
    {
        "question": " 43.2万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.635499885883792
    },
    {
        "question": " 2029兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.808483295106523
    },
    {
        "question": " 27京msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.494838791867785
    },
    {
        "question": " 1175億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.513830512771516
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.8万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.29327177978242247
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.49億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.977366390676906
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.25垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.221083856417807
    },
    {
        "question": " 223兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.4121891166378293
    },
    {
        "question": " 407兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.052933402790741
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.4億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.278426569241855
    },
    {
        "question": " 601億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.778822426952485
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.16億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.789276368400348
    },
    {
        "question": " 235京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.872361739615237
    },
    {
        "question": " 61.3垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.851104984684979
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.51京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.8439245309412993
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.26京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.138732029364276
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.52兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.54669490334218
    },
    {
        "question": " 1232兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.090564861159288
    },
    {
        "question": " 35.3億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.54802095419838
    },
    {
        "question": " 898万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.515455298257235
    },
    {
        "question": " 5648年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.694437401671768
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.99年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.497756580708898
    },
    {
        "question": " 71.7年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.35451161112431
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.3億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.071393318609193
    },
    {
        "question": " 832日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.300329119723286
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.58万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.569978610291806
    },
    {
        "question": " 23.8日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.312574497833846
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.16億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.847070104999088
    },
    {
        "question": " 1604万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.8251320282212005
    },
    {
        "question": " 256時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.186081878847459
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.1時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.8794966739652
    },
    {
        "question": " 715億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.1336734775867
    },
    {
        "question": " 321万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.347725118585797
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.01億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.224094898902375
    },
    {
        "question": " 106分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.8047927857440476
    },
    {
        "question": " 8687兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.44006115517836
    },
    {
        "question": " 27.9兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.508907773157052
    },
    {
        "question": " 334億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.966876202260416
    },
    {
        "question": " 2060億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.53574653175024
    },
    {
        "question": " 150万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.174656050430773
    },
    {
        "question": " 862京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.436872902201205
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.29兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.17576808438184
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.31兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.559970389669703
    },
    {
        "question": " 5496億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.961909356745984
    },
    {
        "question": " 1兆msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.000124015388021
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.36msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.866792688244323
    },
    {
        "question": " 48.9京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.190842445220864
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.59垓usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.26382492964721
    },
    {
        "question": " 87.9京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.387853630444244
    },
    {
        "question": " 5757億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.982073948353644
    },
    {
        "question": " 1158億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.063615259604083
    },
    {
        "question": " 20.3万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 2.306588965340828
    },
    {
        "question": " 521万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.71709934987739
    },
    {
        "question": " 64.7垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.312007185550977
    },
    {
        "question": " 332兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5848239872334815
    },
    {
        "question": " 80.7兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3507518072019054
    },
    {
        "question": " 38兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8021131050398598
    },
    {
        "question": " 37億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5686244462778234
    },
    {
        "question": " 1564兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.194211020322026
    },
    {
        "question": " 243万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 3.3856279054537297
    },
    {
        "question": " 317年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.063570407562979
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.25万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.803124035238802
    },
    {
        "question": " 4266年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.350695581493177
    },
    {
        "question": " 1841日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7027280346698428
    },
    {
        "question": " 427万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.010765197658198
    },
    {
        "question": " 419日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.781077265317642
    },
    {
        "question": " 230日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.29875010965417
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.98日は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.53652763680646
    },
    {
        "question": " 69.5億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.899429952066707
    },
    {
        "question": " 1210時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7026833107457606
    },
    {
        "question": " 535時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.506714518517111
    },
    {
        "question": " 455兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.937159527962695
    },
    {
        "question": " 5927万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.614484105787614
    },
    {
        "question": " 3993億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.82310762508201
    },
    {
        "question": " 134分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.9054101708250935
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.51分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.178239094204773
    },
    {
        "question": " 20.3兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.807681732469331
    },
    {
        "question": " 238万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4395902436008057
    },
    {
        "question": " 442億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.089578730482864
    },
    {
        "question": " 152秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.40450613988111006
    },
    {
        "question": " 33.8万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.528448471348938
    },
    {
        "question": " 8564秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.932663086408578
    },
    {
        "question": " 3垓msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.9784166161506
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.95兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.660259299218373
    },
    {
        "question": " 401兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.046419031084909
    },
    {
        "question": " 909万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1806343418096996
    },
    {
        "question": " 97万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9866589974286386
    },
    {
        "question": " 883万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.945841393705912
    },
    {
        "question": " 78.1msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 7.892657702662315
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.99京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.799287325918022
    },
    {
        "question": " 1111兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.109294189364974
    },
    {
        "question": " 473兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.118193109193746
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.05億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5342926125377123
    },
    {
        "question": " 504万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7020704456678417
    },
    {
        "question": " 73.1万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 2.8639260128865285
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.25usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 3.627959307309845
    },
    {
        "question": " 38.7京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0894162444790312
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.32京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7896892540924547
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.9兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.3930894041376942
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.6京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.414403771778552
    },
    {
        "question": " 28.1兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.44832062966991
    },
    {
        "question": " 45.1兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.654023701949926
    },
    {
        "question": " 698億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.843668581994959
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.17年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6321504378352123
    },
    {
        "question": " 36.3万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9979171020057005
    },
    {
        "question": " 19.5万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.449486174679123
    },
    {
        "question": " 4510日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.590710080244913
    },
    {
        "question": " 81.4兆時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.968025097691289
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.93万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.3129063621333388
    },
    {
        "question": " 10時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7783175370935065
    },
    {
        "question": " 1862時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.8261927892202525
    },
    {
        "question": " 369時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.123759325557707
    },
    {
        "question": " 304兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.7628374221034
    },
    {
        "question": " 2199億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.183912815528718
    },
    {
        "question": " 21.3億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.549730498229591
    },
    {
        "question": " 19.7万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.073545562833287
    },
    {
        "question": " 8091分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.68615327767097
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.68京秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.255406521463916
    },
    {
        "question": " 5970万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.839481668590742
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.64万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2658598074993421
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.03万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2361383035741933
    },
    {
        "question": " 5983秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.776947595338473
    },
    {
        "question": " 1060京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.52652169228296
    },
    {
        "question": " 50.4京msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.765890648337672
    },
    {
        "question": " 213兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.772549999138619
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.1億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.40021152380781
    },
    {
        "question": " 133万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.123211201105068
    },
    {
        "question": " 1799msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.255026382942599
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.9msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 7.111717883283805
    },
    {
        "question": " 2111兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8256695821075397
    },
    {
        "question": " 111兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.1092179900243453
    },
    {
        "question": " 42.1億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.06773710571298164
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.17京usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.288478799086754
    },
    {
        "question": " 384億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.58397575045137
    },
    {
        "question": " 1184億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.073336930571587
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.9万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 8.038206027943437
    },
    {
        "question": " 361垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.05859043164674
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.6京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.2572131660728108
    },
    {
        "question": " 26.2兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8622195523683818
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.77垓nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.663781658407114
    },
    {
        "question": " 2920兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.465329566243902
    },
    {
        "question": " 4793兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.680630188934899
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.2万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 2.2100385861232033
    },
    {
        "question": " 40.1万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.545708794786641
    },
    {
        "question": " 1369日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5741446959538032
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.43日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1153436999789155
    },
    {
        "question": " 5947日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.93262049684707
    },
    {
        "question": " 97.8日は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.926631456408078
    },
    {
        "question": " 193万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.341949264959624
    },
    {
        "question": " 307億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.107040165471311
    },
    {
        "question": " 5315時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.503684882267711
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.75時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.498183102417598
    },
    {
        "question": " 33億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.7976101103891113
    },
    {
        "question": " 104億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.859221562821565
    },
    {
        "question": " 271億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.655598725934667
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.55分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9675634897571292
    },
    {
        "question": " 2389分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.156436330508592
    },
    {
        "question": " 5424万秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.2355047754254802
    },
    {
        "question": " 821億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.977803123970283
    },
    {
        "question": " 110万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4835878116122387
    },
    {
        "question": " 3152秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7204166248762987
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.1秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.177725030036793
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.16京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.290549326986391
    },
    {
        "question": " 5520兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.805454568212812
    },
    {
        "question": " 47.5兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.120567485970532
    },
    {
        "question": " 1495億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.396501096416557
    },
    {
        "question": " 219万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.340182758899757
    },
    {
        "question": " 41msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.612354728252135
    },
    {
        "question": " 9280msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.967533743113018
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.3京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.5122513146969703
    },
    {
        "question": " 1011京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.06831452964333
    },
    {
        "question": " 42.2兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.068611725617818
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.52京usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.09784496527499
    },
    {
        "question": " 528億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.722744090528726
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.64億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.98426825344701
    },
    {
        "question": " 7916京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.3997128656237283
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.74京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5020315317573063
    },
    {
        "question": " 3714京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.013551933803913
    },
    {
        "question": " 9605億nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2043357600989402
    },
    {
        "question": " 299億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4752431767049823
    },
    {
        "question": " 14兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.14502985739489
    },
    {
        "question": " 2309万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.363475683083744
    },
    {
        "question": " 106万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.58661043049819
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.1万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.983949367336867
    },
    {
        "question": " 829年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.639004247438173
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.84年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.445272219773472
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.21兆日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.78196513098555
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.17万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.948940697338971
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.64日は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.151896755356672
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.13兆時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.673769234754879
    },
    {
        "question": " 226億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.973696928374874
    },
    {
        "question": " 170時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.008009789456606
    },
    {
        "question": " 493万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9719176950754227
    },
    {
        "question": " 2675分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.2690019509733266
    },
    {
        "question": " 1242分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.316140724664815
    },
    {
        "question": " 392万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.370963206438322
    },
    {
        "question": " 962億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.4844827616608045
    },
    {
        "question": " 2399億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.443561996053646
    },
    {
        "question": " 109万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.48251423536904
    },
    {
        "question": " 32億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.727365088439434
    },
    {
        "question": " 8500秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.929437885189164
    },
    {
        "question": " 6204京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.293895881468044
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.1兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.105368367404806
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.92億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9087274232108642
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.2万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.43019606337207583
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.33億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.52297207469579
    },
    {
        "question": " 510京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.208468247598519
    },
    {
        "question": " 2201兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.406040551693291
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.5兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.6869107403895383
    },
    {
        "question": " 3603兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.778475080678168
    },
    {
        "question": " 20.6億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.313246708377248
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.76万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.6777572559223541
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.543e+04垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.689650190134455
    },
    {
        "question": " 90垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.01784604450516
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.56垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.103073524286701
    },
    {
        "question": " 70.6兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.07055442109047
    },
    {
        "question": " 34.9京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.542285403877901
    },
    {
        "question": " 3461万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.5391519743009396
    },
    {
        "question": " 7362万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.867014959562721
    },
    {
        "question": " 2865年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.019404889386768
    },
    {
        "question": " 32.9万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.460217921631974
    },
    {
        "question": " 3283年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.236958443684523
    },
    {
        "question": " 1555日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6294969211235746
    },
    {
        "question": " 252日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.560450395159116
    },
    {
        "question": " 23.8万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.433772380352203
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.72万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.0550299427701866
    },
    {
        "question": " 20.9時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.0973800768313433
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.26時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.52291544471349
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.23兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.368168860925888
    },
    {
        "question": " 262万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.259705921247132
    },
    {
        "question": " 5166億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.935030504429859
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.9分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9782889499631904
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.5分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.875632183450252
    },
    {
        "question": " 1281兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.608694366965301
    },
    {
        "question": " 6573万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8812597125604977
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.23万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2381018136486288
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.3万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.460342182966648
    },
    {
        "question": " 80.2秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.904191224218335
    },
    {
        "question": " 404兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.108035662372361
    },
    {
        "question": " 1622億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.2736232245521366
    },
    {
        "question": " 374億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.016948971326021
    },
    {
        "question": " 30.9万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7119706327290654
    },
    {
        "question": " 343万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.5350589489329476
    },
    {
        "question": " 201msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 5.304167918475583
    },
    {
        "question": " 938兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4733147049702577
    },
    {
        "question": " 1097億usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.10360235314970878
    },
    {
        "question": " 120億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5234661862188772
    },
    {
        "question": " 2463兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.613241870140794
    },
    {
        "question": " 8861万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9474750772936933
    },
    {
        "question": " 2995usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 0.4764237787655523
    },
    {
        "question": " 213usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 5.328816642645608
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.125e+05垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.41101730995722
    },
    {
        "question": " 216垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.397267771225088
    },
    {
        "question": " 20.9兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7641495387191366
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.42京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.756430036270517
    },
    {
        "question": " 287兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.457235835000187
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.8兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.032284731989904
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.49億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 5.172480010977005
    },
    {
        "question": " 66.2万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.763085984865961
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.02億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.7435311890526
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.21億日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.88688719568252
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.58万日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.136329733063246
    },
    {
        "question": " 1026億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.068434840070913
    },
    {
        "question": " 3181万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.122401472998131
    },
    {
        "question": " 528時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.500416839929798
    },
    {
        "question": " 1653時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.774566789512456
    },
    {
        "question": " 131兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.397532243806253
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.45万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2310456875339626
    },
    {
        "question": " 1022億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.231215422595923
    },
    {
        "question": " 214分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.108693678142342
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.36分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.41798433491729
    },
    {
        "question": " 197兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.795969180574936
    },
    {
        "question": " 343億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.598752970963367
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.59兆秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.190776712806903
    },
    {
        "question": " 149秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.3958746927408552
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.76万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.760270740170295
    },
    {
        "question": " 40.4兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.1072016931484523
    },
    {
        "question": " 55.6億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.808247142950551
    },
    {
        "question": " 9936万msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4409302989010597
    },
    {
        "question": " 148万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3931423990019343
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.79億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.891640102106526
    },
    {
        "question": " 2502msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.398336266721327
    },
    {
        "question": " 55.4msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 7.743210398505539
    },
    {
        "question": " 68.8京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.338813519032554
    },
    {
        "question": " 1533京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.24916128584465
    },
    {
        "question": " 3387億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9735180557541032
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.92億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9941761402805938
    },
    {
        "question": " 275億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.440023365624915
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.25億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.098516836392138
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.5京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.0453533734180378
    },
    {
        "question": " 4035兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.669327898097095
    },
    {
        "question": " 782兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.337036589502741
    },
    {
        "question": " 318兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.7245298407217096
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.7兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.104842182959528
    },
    {
        "question": " 977億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.9900895224683754
    },
    {
        "question": " 49.3億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.692643399058755
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.33万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.66904051068915
    },
    {
        "question": " 2126億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.765199491864292
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.28万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.298286812957531
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.17万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.49428605339561
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.8億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.092242718802903
    },
    {
        "question": " 1197億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.6980342641966
    },
    {
        "question": " 2326万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.14479448074986
    },
    {
        "question": " 399時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.157054422242391
    },
    {
        "question": " 393時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.150209460519168
    },
    {
        "question": " 96億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.261671549923085
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.3兆分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.892899024656549
    },
    {
        "question": " 4998億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.920604263461358
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.95分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.067380816493701
    },
    {
        "question": " 117分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.847202887945556
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.9億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5769563760484595
    },
    {
        "question": " 11億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.104266528644345
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.5兆秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.621193495463828
    },
    {
        "question": " 75.1万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.097276460531002
    },
    {
        "question": " 102万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.00829978997319
    },
    {
        "question": " 122兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.588016090146283
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.1億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.242311235016621
    },
    {
        "question": " 6245兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.239225646892606
    },
    {
        "question": " 341億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.7544653387006495
    },
    {
        "question": " 3810msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5808975690686624
    },
    {
        "question": " 2439msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.387236474182009
    },
    {
        "question": " 722msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 8.858405102985076
    },
    {
        "question": " 738兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3691157104002905
    },
    {
        "question": " 5144京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.774780123019761
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.5京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.4640104538095535
    },
    {
        "question": " 21.2兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.54775731443732
    },
    {
        "question": " 786兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.895539001654418
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.1万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.3212531351357337
    },
    {
        "question": " 5783京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.2633194065401128
    },
    {
        "question": " 415京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.681309950861615
    },
    {
        "question": " 860京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.378197479110936
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.35垓nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.59214677954659
    },
    {
        "question": " 549兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.739937680658354
    },
    {
        "question": " 149億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.173268851665306
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.1万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 2.045328711922182
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.46年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.5384124777758332
    },
    {
        "question": " 950億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.415455249729495
    },
    {
        "question": " 542万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.114354449295586
    },
    {
        "question": " 279日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.60423832549923
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.75万日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.178571797519892
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.24日は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.56337588695251
    },
    {
        "question": " 1607万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.2635059018669588
    },
    {
        "question": " 221億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.963526109262146
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.98時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.252477670521981
    },
    {
        "question": " 19.4万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.844546680324358
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.51億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.155159651958913
    },
    {
        "question": " 2165億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.177065973254255
    },
    {
        "question": " 24.1億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.603537568874566
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.42億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3089259423663935
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.1万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.2694053115033457
    },
    {
        "question": " 501万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.143647309231362
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.24億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.5718758767135865
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.53秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.655833923256777
    },
    {
        "question": " 1153兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.562948091310526
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.31兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.427896679330374
    },
    {
        "question": " 750億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.318777984493605
    },
    {
        "question": " 3378億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.750470102732898
    },
    {
        "question": " 25.9万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.413194883694796
    },
    {
        "question": " 331msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 5.52025331404502
    },
    {
        "question": " 1781京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.751965160550572
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.03京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.91022090828316
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.85兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.898989014759316
    },
    {
        "question": " 260億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6368103589475256
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.94兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.595172692229911
    },
    {
        "question": " 4000万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.602030511229344
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.722e+06垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.936077257389735
    },
    {
        "question": " 531垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.78823787322505
    },
    {
        "question": " 7913兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.3420676983972406
    },
    {
        "question": " 7674兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.106861157976018
    },
    {
        "question": " 318兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.5021998103891185
    },
    {
        "question": " 20.9億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.320570732147057
    },
    {
        "question": " 583万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 3.765527300401912
    },
    {
        "question": " 74.6万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.4351667978277
    },
    {
        "question": " 1983年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.239895766777432
    },
    {
        "question": " 85.6億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.370130318695497
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.6日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.221275856212192
    },
    {
        "question": " 44.2兆時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.702436545358033
    },
    {
        "question": " 388時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2088874665772609
    },
    {
        "question": " 228時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.136888974773952
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.68万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.310310896886461
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.92億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.744705920316367
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.42億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.711799646997071
    },
    {
        "question": " 23.7万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.5966693468199464
    },
    {
        "question": " 98.9分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.773143506928135
    },
    {
        "question": " 660億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.3204296772720756
    },
    {
        "question": " 45.3兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.719338162731239
    },
    {
        "question": " 18.2億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.702657276627322
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.03万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.23375504821985
    },
    {
        "question": " 28.8万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.458737453318655
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.46京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.373811586865744
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.1京msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.107531944292724
    },
    {
        "question": " 217兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.781115187973126
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.61億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.7791324494498726
    },
    {
        "question": " 5198msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7158640185845944
    },
    {
        "question": " 96.5兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.4855363257977352
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.59京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.997321781614472
    },
    {
        "question": " 65.6兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.260359444121086
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.03京usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.233020395455114
    },
    {
        "question": " 31.7億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.5008778809516117
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.14億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.85340833774482
    },
    {
        "question": " 564万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.751098159023137
    },
    {
        "question": " 6466垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.311857706982979
    },
    {
        "question": " 4089兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6750792214379573
    },
    {
        "question": " 4119兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.0585415672881067
    },
    {
        "question": " 20.8兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.539774304559934
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.85京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.58560668491885
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.14兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.331264514238255
    },
    {
        "question": " 341億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.532741375140624
    },
    {
        "question": " 429年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.194853679340139
    },
    {
        "question": " 47.8万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.621725551596832
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.8万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5435268097046047
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.39億日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.524208841205017
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.08日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.254091466674685
    },
    {
        "question": " 78.1億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.950011054947199
    },
    {
        "question": " 612億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.406685853504314
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.42時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.752182008333104
    },
    {
        "question": " 83.5時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.477969698835947
    },
    {
        "question": " 32.8億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.795435261597179
    },
    {
        "question": " 474億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.517033115945699
    },
    {
        "question": " 45.4億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.87894289744804
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.25分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8738639345718788
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.44兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.6581412133431
    },
    {
        "question": " 142億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.2147034616247865
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.48億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.095268285068575
    },
    {
        "question": " 368億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.787253378035357
    },
    {
        "question": " 455万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.657897701830548
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.7兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5705967511467023
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.37京msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.199734834234201
    },
    {
        "question": " 1081万msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.47735514250011324
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.7万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.4181494808710029
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.11万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.61372670083886
    },
    {
        "question": " 89.4msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.951436872809717
    },
    {
        "question": " 35.6msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 7.5516596048918805
    },
    {
        "question": " 1789京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.753907604655328
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.9兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.099047463045224
    },
    {
        "question": " 29.4兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.9124919362105337
    },
    {
        "question": " 56.4億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.972833272612322
    },
    {
        "question": " 8747億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.941846558422292
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.4万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 2.0560583403568233
    },
    {
        "question": " 48.4usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 4.684400333706785
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.07垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.8173218995000644
    },
    {
        "question": " 405兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6707933199691007
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.79京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.6976579531412277
    },
    {
        "question": " 591兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.993407079526076
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.21京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.0839227294671305
    },
    {
        "question": " 5200兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.715976714321904
    },
    {
        "question": " 3253億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.512345671292904
    },
    {
        "question": " 969万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.548742760185077
    },
    {
        "question": " 86.8年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.880795620968055
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.1年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.725580559286755
    },
    {
        "question": " 35.9年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.054107719846945
    },
    {
        "question": " 742日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.3078075629081034
    },
    {
        "question": " 1042日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.397872752965968
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.2日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.168601423425034
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.75万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.49643480423963493
    },
    {
        "question": " 1785時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8714509827640058
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.36万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.749398671617932
    },
    {
        "question": " 65.6万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.372943682947922
    },
    {
        "question": " 964兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.263374205558142
    },
    {
        "question": " 782万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.7350305552106002
    },
    {
        "question": " 128万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.329457894587526
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.89分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.05372911796235
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.81万分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.226892847804383
    },
    {
        "question": " 8035万秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.40619299110860596
    },
    {
        "question": " 161兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.270976729035901
    },
    {
        "question": " 208万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7625051609615534
    },
    {
        "question": " 204万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.531196606906974
    },
    {
        "question": " 509秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.706475657162413
    },
    {
        "question": " 784億msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.3956362155851312
    },
    {
        "question": " 1315億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.182511094318542
    },
    {
        "question": " 435万msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.08257287173565997
    },
    {
        "question": " 76.7兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.106684329444978
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.04億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.015446596819278
    },
    {
        "question": " 61.3msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.7878101179050825
    },
    {
        "question": " 139兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6453760076238613
    },
    {
        "question": " 165兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.2797809453967464
    },
    {
        "question": " 50.6億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.14804167116932332
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.94億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.915611927754979
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.6億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.2450130749576003
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.33万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.122619754371792
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.54万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 7.656764108767307
    },
    {
        "question": " 6318京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.3017557947331078
    },
    {
        "question": " 33.5京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.58831675089355
    },
    {
        "question": " 565兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.195674377379999
    },
    {
        "question": " 3728京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.793291891790243
    },
    {
        "question": " 101兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.004262655192742
    },
    {
        "question": " 1967万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.293807052666247
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.8兆nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.254678885448461
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.94万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.03271781822542
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.47万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.548206641665292
    },
    {
        "question": " 7398日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.805614771205004
    },
    {
        "question": " 18.2日は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.197447233939624
    },
    {
        "question": " 179億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.309269960320927
    },
    {
        "question": " 1123万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.670295626611025
    },
    {
        "question": " 64.1万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.584827290936231
    },
    {
        "question": " 50.8時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.262083896925629
    },
    {
        "question": " 57.1万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.03634631976361824
    },
    {
        "question": " 9771億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.831566855096138
    },
    {
        "question": " 750万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.0968698065529665
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.48分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.429209927130537
    },
    {
        "question": " 48.1分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.460575910036658
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.37億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3051213758569424
    },
    {
        "question": " 191万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3446459988776271
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.89万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7211572493091434
    },
    {
        "question": " 22.4億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.572303980642367
    },
    {
        "question": " 77.3万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.88838811136585
    },
    {
        "question": " 313兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.996317855383429
    },
    {
        "question": " 31.1京msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.55631048775176
    },
    {
        "question": " 5803兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.207354575438801
    },
    {
        "question": " 268兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.650376218514095
    },
    {
        "question": " 211億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.324295082817086
    },
    {
        "question": " 90.2万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.955237224098227
    },
    {
        "question": " 6143msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.788401901094074
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.49垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.673889775682894
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.89垓usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.75262534674555
    },
    {
        "question": " 794京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.34375997385872
    },
    {
        "question": " 24.6億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6133086124194829
    },
    {
        "question": " 35.4億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.5486366700465855
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.01億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.778877867182607
    },
    {
        "question": " 41.3万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 8.61583509796091
    },
    {
        "question": " 45.7京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1615643621157334
    },
    {
        "question": " 512京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.772399130280687
    },
    {
        "question": " 27.3兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8798692592740132
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.32兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.586627056373373
    },
    {
        "question": " 168京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.225965954250814
    },
    {
        "question": " 104万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 0.015831220535301727
    },
    {
        "question": " 326億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.5127848098500305
    },
    {
        "question": " 291年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.0261729443760075
    },
    {
        "question": " 83.2万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.862465582091648
    },
    {
        "question": " 117年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.567559409507684
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.02万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4445790481829734
    },
    {
        "question": " 8325万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.300587400176312
    },
    {
        "question": " 53.4日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.886159066388793
    },
    {
        "question": " 602日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.716318969869902
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.1兆時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.139329714842447
    },
    {
        "question": " 1855万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.88806156235801
    },
    {
        "question": " 33.1万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.297844754095685
    },
    {
        "question": " 934時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.526436288355441
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.5億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.496691084091552
    },
    {
        "question": " 31.5億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.340545200683625
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.14万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.278445065379376
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.86分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3642271990594663
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.73分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.350386711059356
    },
    {
        "question": " 4387万秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.143401685116602
    },
    {
        "question": " 290万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5255907952865955
    },
    {
        "question": " 6995秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.28850927415631555
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.42億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.867636625917491
    },
    {
        "question": " 244兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.888786976844154
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.05京msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.375287921908598
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.37億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.578840565661792
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.1万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.30524407156590105
    },
    {
        "question": " 4901万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.690252932675072
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.8msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.033235929501816
    },
    {
        "question": " 25京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.89982307248522
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.85京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.3295157595738685
    },
    {
        "question": " 1889京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.720001681158424
    },
    {
        "question": " 4738億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.897480513713635
    },
    {
        "question": " 550兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.740673002697648
    },
    {
        "question": " 21.5億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.332914038915409
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.17万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 7.068657260054289
    },
    {
        "question": " 274垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.938928421934802
    },
    {
        "question": " 6197垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.855670714193437
    },
    {
        "question": " 73.2兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3083006826284405
    },
    {
        "question": " 6037億nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0026556889771965
    },
    {
        "question": " 128京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.106269391188725
    },
    {
        "question": " 3083億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.489016689048465
    },
    {
        "question": " 7545億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.877644378511388
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.5万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.920295815530377
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.72兆日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.67249910809943
    },
    {
        "question": " 252万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.781181789232008
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.01日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.94107743256361
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.41億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.439580039013769
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.84万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.386560002909411
    },
    {
        "question": " 3744時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.351506224831808
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.59時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.9697443662546483
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.6億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.835216910878613
    },
    {
        "question": " 225万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.193850709661943
    },
    {
        "question": " 66.9分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.0469910662602957
    },
    {
        "question": " 1177万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.849036804230545
    },
    {
        "question": " 3438分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.31442473408029
    },
    {
        "question": " 27.5兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.940945584557964
    },
    {
        "question": " 163万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2754339120169833
    },
    {
        "question": " 90.7億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.401457592053604
    },
    {
        "question": " 145万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.382004653803717
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.4兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.689913904410466
    },
    {
        "question": " 1947億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.3529475278800804
    },
    {
        "question": " 6586億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.262321108476362
    },
    {
        "question": " 141兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.372059078205353
    },
    {
        "question": " 376万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.5748205673240294
    },
    {
        "question": " 693msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 8.840922519632361
    },
    {
        "question": " 855京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.433230794192136
    },
    {
        "question": " 326兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.576407513923191
    },
    {
        "question": " 2477京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.83769560928109
    },
    {
        "question": " 1308億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.338608088149382
    },
    {
        "question": " 2933兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.467262787018349
    },
    {
        "question": " 23億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.36222673322562
    },
    {
        "question": " 9200垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.464992489000473
    },
    {
        "question": " 503京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.765418892042883
    },
    {
        "question": " 157京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.639162493591395
    },
    {
        "question": " 3268兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.736118049459104
    },
    {
        "question": " 287億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4583427348102218
    },
    {
        "question": " 79兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.8975231452976855
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.23億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 5.7185286847168415
    },
    {
        "question": " 161万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.76860381036399
    },
    {
        "question": " 33.9万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.473129040222721
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.51億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.313250773444156
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.03万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.393622710388208
    },
    {
        "question": " 3699日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.726486732820956
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.34日は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.305543610648881
    },
    {
        "question": " 32.7億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.571778183590011
    },
    {
        "question": " 469億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.290674905347172
    },
    {
        "question": " 62.5兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.075032320437943
    },
    {
        "question": " 127億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.944388520678814
    },
    {
        "question": " 2193分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5629510246674783
    },
    {
        "question": " 924万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.743831729063935
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.92兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.497691356975559
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.24億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.858626740110258
    },
    {
        "question": " 876万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.3861179279316667
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.88億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.497058838408799
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.2京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.652492973549114
    },
    {
        "question": " 2027兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.370373864789899
    },
    {
        "question": " 1559億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.6365797101615875
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.99億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.8227481146360063
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.5万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3982520398993437
    },
    {
        "question": " 307msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 8.4877264675903
    },
    {
        "question": " 81.4兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.41187883411193726
    },
    {
        "question": " 6548兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.879576729152088
    },
    {
        "question": " 88.5京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.39048849441605
    },
    {
        "question": " 22.6兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.575010649058862
    },
    {
        "question": " 211兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.324911244291608
    },
    {
        "question": " 2371万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.3748784109293215
    },
    {
        "question": " 4779usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.679291880362879
    },
    {
        "question": " 202京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.806837423686154
    },
    {
        "question": " 516兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.775944348109403
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.54京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.375230878596842
    },
    {
        "question": " 1009億nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.22569839119040536
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.71兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.232552833011171
    },
    {
        "question": " 985兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.993299996494981
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.5兆nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.65285328821926
    },
    {
        "question": " 1145年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.621033780045341
    },
    {
        "question": " 304億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.920686900725739
    },
    {
        "question": " 130万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.493361008889334
    },
    {
        "question": " 42.4万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.78586193206486
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.7日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.071664858995937
    },
    {
        "question": " 4217億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.682446236021088
    },
    {
        "question": " 57.5万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.379537568805276
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.31万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.190959006251884
    },
    {
        "question": " 1787兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.531364110624807
    },
    {
        "question": " 1861万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.1114749851050725
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.6万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.284527828223159
    },
    {
        "question": " 61.3分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.5655530998975946
    },
    {
        "question": " 22.8分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.136201447235688
    },
    {
        "question": " 2648億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.9240867321541084
    },
    {
        "question": " 268兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.490950845943747
    },
    {
        "question": " 28.3兆秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.895623671227531
    },
    {
        "question": " 186秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.492521500510974
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.2秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.086181549418898
    },
    {
        "question": " 25.6兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.908669339425373
    },
    {
        "question": " 1075億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.095098777283549
    },
    {
        "question": " 194億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.7305592862610295
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.19億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.5631902741176313
    },
    {
        "question": " 7552msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8780479027470256
    },
    {
        "question": " 165垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.719143954939693
    },
    {
        "question": " 8960兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.0158051336813125
    },
    {
        "question": " 194京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.732581393340922
    },
    {
        "question": " 19.1億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5039167791997443
    },
    {
        "question": " 2054万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.312510749839474
    },
    {
        "question": " 9962万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.998353119072972
    },
    {
        "question": " 4421usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.645493558877995
    },
    {
        "question": " 701垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.346632512761588
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.55京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2528780822184347
    },
    {
        "question": " 1910兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7248299368665863
    },
    {
        "question": " 1814京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.480392434767747
    },
    {
        "question": " 303兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.481946608395791
    },
    {
        "question": " 46.2億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.6650482245473337
    },
    {
        "question": " 479万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 3.6804437872383424
    },
    {
        "question": " 46.4年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.609013845901964
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.3万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5930434302235073
    },
    {
        "question": " 46.7万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.049231108418821
    },
    {
        "question": " 19.8日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.232519486641817
    },
    {
        "question": " 78.6日は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.832143755389028
    },
    {
        "question": " 3025万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.538213846234969
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.25万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.480293604165362
    },
    {
        "question": " 3543万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.32746064446636
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.76万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.80207179670975
    },
    {
        "question": " 93.6兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.25076012445328
    },
    {
        "question": " 84.8万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7701565252744587
    },
    {
        "question": " 8593万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.155986134807156
    },
    {
        "question": " 4465分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.427994311052252
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.04分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.793245472888602
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.17分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.846821585196706
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.5京秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.691062894533822
    },
    {
        "question": " 3445億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.600720875487534
    },
    {
        "question": " 115億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.503093922597251
    },
    {
        "question": " 3563秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7736715992946595
    },
    {
        "question": " 5256秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.720635491732004
    },
    {
        "question": " 30.4秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.48321069788756
    },
    {
        "question": " 2735億msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9381228893209226
    },
    {
        "question": " 130億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1787043396471417
    },
    {
        "question": " 2496億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.840993354520615
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.1兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.339940299833795
    },
    {
        "question": " 7627万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.88232882119182
    },
    {
        "question": " 1316msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.119143921195508
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.96msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.7754866531531945
    },
    {
        "question": " 4406兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1452813738636856
    },
    {
        "question": " 209京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.383519185867575
    },
    {
        "question": " 3540兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.992642473941515
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.56京usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.038561465521433
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.42兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.733708568655756
    },
    {
        "question": " 37.9億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.578306208879488
    },
    {
        "question": " 5899usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.770760281221902
    },
    {
        "question": " 6502垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.314251428228036
    },
    {
        "question": " 124垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.157131404091242
    },
    {
        "question": " 3585京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.9981401865230435
    },
    {
        "question": " 3097兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.7127910666815
    },
    {
        "question": " 3593億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.55548765069339
    },
    {
        "question": " 197兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.293768680242117
    },
    {
        "question": " 2720nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 0.43451642988053263
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.13万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.616153536614384
    },
    {
        "question": " 67.7年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.772822542346145
    },
    {
        "question": " 5827年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.486138568881833
    },
    {
        "question": " 5555億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.18236568419369
    },
    {
        "question": " 38.5日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9651633039484917
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.14日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.6551424934862053
    },
    {
        "question": " 2671億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.484194894415107
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.2億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.7707631784862405
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.09時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.464384289337313
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.3兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.491082945090283
    },
    {
        "question": " 478億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.521016199491096
    },
    {
        "question": " 1570分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.417843882912656
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.04分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.796345572638095
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.92万分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.371129215565501
    },
    {
        "question": " 823兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.416367511859655
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.4億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.304940427651619
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.18兆秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.234484251837392
    },
    {
        "question": " 38.4億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.806243293892086
    },
    {
        "question": " 2367秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.374228722744057
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.5京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.676183824278275
    },
    {
        "question": " 2794億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.509686840358208
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.8億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3356408878196646
    },
    {
        "question": " 9748億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.210779664008102
    },
    {
        "question": " 969万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.9862119078506897
    },
    {
        "question": " 65.1msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.813301642317292
    },
    {
        "question": " 29.6京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.972772336586192
    },
    {
        "question": " 517兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.7768114113037887
    },
    {
        "question": " 5055兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.14742488700964
    },
    {
        "question": " 173兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.460609056445054
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.68兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.938406967235025
    },
    {
        "question": " 8880usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 0.9484004776386734
    },
    {
        "question": " 650万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.813009784097735
    },
    {
        "question": " 1230垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.591195625520721
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.07京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9127176609945513
    },
    {
        "question": " 130垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.556466799550234
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.27垓nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.324979913109727
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.6兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.220891160196959
    },
    {
        "question": " 6711兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.826764519309014
    },
    {
        "question": " 7426nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 0.8707689348504077
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.8万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.811933934172641
    },
    {
        "question": " 23年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.304364552875879
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.33億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.074328582416073
    },
    {
        "question": " 85日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.3093807389018384
    },
    {
        "question": " 49.2日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.628351683622727
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.72兆時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.294068987570485
    },
    {
        "question": " 430時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2537366203706868
    },
    {
        "question": " 3523万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.325021840698628
    },
    {
        "question": " 152時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.737577574457033
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.58時間は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.968408412358329
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.01兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.28348374343593
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.97万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1350590865122412
    },
    {
        "question": " 3139億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.718600756369081
    },
    {
        "question": " 166万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.998913451833348
    },
    {
        "question": " 516兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.213686523575139
    },
    {
        "question": " 573兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.821393729662361
    },
    {
        "question": " 283万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.895364358478818
    },
    {
        "question": " 811億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.130844416589785
    },
    {
        "question": " 3817秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.58176930452618
    },
    {
        "question": " 95.4秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.9795704623179
    },
    {
        "question": " 50.9京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.207647590039063
    },
    {
        "question": " 5845億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.8302783582519173
    },
    {
        "question": " 5086兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.150094255582456
    },
    {
        "question": " 43.7億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.861975224878857
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.27万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.721850954237133
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.54msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 3.4043405208786814
    },
    {
        "question": " 3921兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.09456909754984
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.11垓usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.10960841894487
    },
    {
        "question": " 32京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.948198537757241
    },
    {
        "question": " 117億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2881906441583775
    },
    {
        "question": " 3689兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.566914835134696
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.51万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.1803662748596477
    },
    {
        "question": " 118垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.5722750045349825
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.9京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.2924519135694794
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.5兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.2563351667064173
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.85京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.6764702762214565
    },
    {
        "question": " 4804億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.681606817142029
    },
    {
        "question": " 134億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.127682310761466
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.64兆nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.822448415928447
    },
    {
        "question": " 35.4万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.111795744926019
    },
    {
        "question": " 6406年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.749071146634742
    },
    {
        "question": " 1401年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.867009608035874
    },
    {
        "question": " 298年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.972503583655712
    },
    {
        "question": " 1000日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.437904968421603
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.42億日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.533389428704055
    },
    {
        "question": " 50.5万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.861880686525323
    },
    {
        "question": " 1729日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.174304824048871
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.12日は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.98643660525653
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.68億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.81212371659227
    },
    {
        "question": " 342万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.153558185718444
    },
    {
        "question": " 1597時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.981578830890444
    },
    {
        "question": " 656億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.096214010604837
    },
    {
        "question": " 170億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.07308203856249
    },
    {
        "question": " 49.9億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.919820800892873
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.79分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.22420847613913
    },
    {
        "question": " 7215万秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.3594035064425394
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.4億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.11990610320249
    },
    {
        "question": " 124億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.538279975724043
    },
    {
        "question": " 1742億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.462857294916137
    },
    {
        "question": " 37.7京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.07717014633492
    },
    {
        "question": " 4910億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.7546124063573316
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.4兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.45865788773923
    },
    {
        "question": " 382万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8039746920807342
    },
    {
        "question": " 1085msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.035532021596448304
    },
    {
        "question": " 43兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.13420700380001538
    },
    {
        "question": " 440兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.707192560649344
    },
    {
        "question": " 44.2億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.08894495671416203
    },
    {
        "question": " 117兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.288938560553516
    },
    {
        "question": " 2267兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.355437462052723
    },
    {
        "question": " 734万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.865870119897462
    },
    {
        "question": " 166usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 5.221218409505912
    },
    {
        "question": " 67.9垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.333297301504082
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.56京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9959352785213844
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.06垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.758385312018509
    },
    {
        "question": " 64.8兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.0331908663020046
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.33京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.636346202349099
    },
    {
        "question": " 2388万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.3779838728093696
    },
    {
        "question": " 7020億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.846346001780136
    },
    {
        "question": " 5903年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.713599555372756
    },
    {
        "question": " 18.2億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.6985270016623355
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.1日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.588316264129756
    },
    {
        "question": " 296万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.62913104859478
    },
    {
        "question": " 20.2日は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.242234570536215
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.85億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.324117153730489
    },
    {
        "question": " 3545時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1694642918397014
    },
    {
        "question": " 488時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.4667359753578
    },
    {
        "question": " 435時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.19528283746596
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.01時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.33485718053365
    },
    {
        "question": " 971万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2664865339487685
    },
    {
        "question": " 666億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.66539212666573
    },
    {
        "question": " 487分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9097329394309006
    },
    {
        "question": " 1294万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.889991446714934
    },
    {
        "question": " 608億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.2851330238851406
    },
    {
        "question": " 8413万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9884595726394316
    },
    {
        "question": " 6299秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.24297891974987884
    },
    {
        "question": " 193億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.507295599838463
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.78万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.990477754739517
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.13秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.054685366797393
    },
    {
        "question": " 10兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5012721851411177
    },
    {
        "question": " 6272兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.86093843741819
    },
    {
        "question": " 4064億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.0526632209271956
    },
    {
        "question": " 5990億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.9992416008006755
    },
    {
        "question": " 322万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.508135384202611
    },
    {
        "question": " 61.5msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.789168224564179
    },
    {
        "question": " 1270msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.103855817589258
    },
    {
        "question": " 225垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.852887791013298
    },
    {
        "question": " 325京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.57583720583236
    },
    {
        "question": " 23.6京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.816933014444871
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.72億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6563688283375724
    },
    {
        "question": " 2637兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.421049649052861
    },
    {
        "question": " 6443万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.809066506555352
    },
    {
        "question": " 29.8usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 4.474426322076712
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.72京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.3286381525235582
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.3京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.247970491809189
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.27京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.165917738488403
    },
    {
        "question": " 36.3兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7819600849576864
    },
    {
        "question": " 21.3兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.328040449846489
    },
    {
        "question": " 29兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.462524084085649
    },
    {
        "question": " 1072億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.030151394845129
    },
    {
        "question": " 4172年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.182610938737623
    },
    {
        "question": " 29.9万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.418644697979644
    },
    {
        "question": " 19.6年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.0132672807681695
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.18年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.571411251769506
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.62万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9967832873776636
    },
    {
        "question": " 185日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.6469683076438955
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.9兆時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.2298246338049
    },
    {
        "question": " 219万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.961068927650098
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.99万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.509948759692746
    },
    {
        "question": " 135億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.410977833791753
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.38億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.76484466074638
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.83万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9057211533073413
    },
    {
        "question": " 2917万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.243031419801115
    },
    {
        "question": " 827億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.418624308401931
    },
    {
        "question": " 417億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.683896754412125
    },
    {
        "question": " 1909万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.724532535145819
    },
    {
        "question": " 166秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.44187456259599633
    },
    {
        "question": " 213秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.327713562122025
    },
    {
        "question": " 49.9秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.6983416643642935
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.76秒は何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.677765942972137
    },
    {
        "question": " 24.4兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8893462691084904
    },
    {
        "question": " 38.3兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.646432246435915
    },
    {
        "question": " 22億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7851852445979306
    },
    {
        "question": " 9462万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.1978194559774797
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.86兆msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.270415488102199
    },
    {
        "question": " 1131msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.053320022646168
    },
    {
        "question": " 1229兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5906042750710458
    },
    {
        "question": " 4843億usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7486529760980809
    },
    {
        "question": " 126兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.542536441841624
    },
    {
        "question": " 172兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.457121205771353
    },
    {
        "question": " 1034万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.014316389345593
    },
    {
        "question": " 2047usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 0.3110445050387245
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.088e+06垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.990800835696806
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.3垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.0777660508265585
    },
    {
        "question": " 910京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.402974502971125
    },
    {
        "question": " 1048兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.242297860316433
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.85兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.2678065264686262
    },
    {
        "question": " 392兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.592844165972124
    },
    {
        "question": " 415億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.618441831214988
    },
    {
        "question": " 19.2万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.22666551769466
    },
    {
        "question": " 4046年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.327646563909346
    },
    {
        "question": " 72.5年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.359082086770451
    },
    {
        "question": " 10億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.439013386568062
    },
    {
        "question": " 34.2万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.914657214332323
    },
    {
        "question": " 7322日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.022996964874158
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.99億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.057223661543238
    },
    {
        "question": " 1264万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.721449093776151
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.53億時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.964238556729553
    },
    {
        "question": " 76.5兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.163062176590948
    },
    {
        "question": " 481万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.523786002032463
    },
    {
        "question": " 4754万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.898885509261849
    },
    {
        "question": " 53.5分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.5067313423496174
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.3億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5906453299789647
    },
    {
        "question": " 2651万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.486873745238829
    },
    {
        "question": " 98.8億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.43832653198219
    },
    {
        "question": " 91.3万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.182188142587178
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.4秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.094600424544428
    },
    {
        "question": " 227京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.857670017232352
    },
    {
        "question": " 62.4京msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.85834968154142
    },
    {
        "question": " 4776万msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1227533490957664
    },
    {
        "question": " 502兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.922939056948099
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.66万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4249672124512625
    },
    {
        "question": " 1545msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.188790612064939
    },
    {
        "question": " 1017京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.5086453524614285
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.04兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5458542649933238
    },
    {
        "question": " 119兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.517754243419205
    },
    {
        "question": " 84.8億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1500554807140415
    },
    {
        "question": " 396億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.598042863728564
    },
    {
        "question": " 434万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.6379524910926184
    },
    {
        "question": " 61.1垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.2868855559967
    },
    {
        "question": " 129兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.17570892202458221
    },
    {
        "question": " 30.9兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9334920904827415
    },
    {
        "question": " 52.8京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.9444454383472065
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.12兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.326106931563496
    },
    {
        "question": " 6680万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.824779788164248
    },
    {
        "question": " 408億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.6104661890633
    },
    {
        "question": " 6057年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.344566451309685
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.21年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.566380372438591
    },
    {
        "question": " 4776年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.399752674400144
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.33年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.8654712625428145
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.2万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5232118311788887
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.16日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7136780710325905
    },
    {
        "question": " 2611日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.575197949380619
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.73万日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.824646992395584
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.8億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.820982764818772
    },
    {
        "question": " 2922万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.085506980587808
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.3万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.833068318494439
    },
    {
        "question": " 108万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.590902559086965
    },
    {
        "question": " 83.9兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.20332765261629
    },
    {
        "question": " 47.1億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.515081986360379
    },
    {
        "question": " 1823億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.482724384741946
    },
    {
        "question": " 21.3万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.10654962668475
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.6分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.87868344943998
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.7兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.172967179264284
    },
    {
        "question": " 184億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.329449169960867
    },
    {
        "question": " 41億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.056236770470294
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.6万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9696519508676067
    },
    {
        "question": " 334秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.524365594708403
    },
    {
        "question": " 2183京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.840184833839702
    },
    {
        "question": " 1460億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.2277610634635856
    },
    {
        "question": " 3477兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.984918923904484
    },
    {
        "question": " 86兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.156281567153721
    },
    {
        "question": " 252万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.4018118511197324
    },
    {
        "question": " 29.4垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.969595603413286
    },
    {
        "question": " 5455京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.800279624563338
    },
    {
        "question": " 3503億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9881795872236652
    },
    {
        "question": " 60.5億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.0035693582254943
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.15億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9616442923316146
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.2億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.236551899181645
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.7usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 3.8260250225710637
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.86垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.9575709579623375
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.06垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.0904870320036615
    },
    {
        "question": " 217兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7794386558620134
    },
    {
        "question": " 4081兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.832626356024022
    },
    {
        "question": " 173京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.23827463022819
    },
    {
        "question": " 25.1億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.3992980848413215
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.7億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.103198476516907
    },
    {
        "question": " 2017日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7424052966846362
    },
    {
        "question": " 268日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.586014242321726
    },
    {
        "question": " 4419日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.581854802397654
    },
    {
        "question": " 523万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7763705180861056
    },
    {
        "question": " 3442万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.156631831857375
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.73時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.993128124413353
    },
    {
        "question": " 169兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.508398874701792
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.37万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5718331644923966
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.46億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.032206651733012
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.42万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.3121293334988895
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.4億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.689767738421295
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.88兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.752168578230462
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.46億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.834084352122938
    },
    {
        "question": " 95.7万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.202560228168486
    },
    {
        "question": " 8871秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.947988983241634
    },
    {
        "question": " 1818秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.259486437679756
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.26京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.600905410510633
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.94京msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.658572525268873
    },
    {
        "question": " 1021億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.4526797399683105
    },
    {
        "question": " 753万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.098874470484413
    },
    {
        "question": " 51.5億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.712225898318298
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.3垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.684767015702519
    },
    {
        "question": " 3176億usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5653369204550363
    },
    {
        "question": " 525兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.164118579931229
    },
    {
        "question": " 27.1兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.65409657730317
    },
    {
        "question": " 305兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.483879481908458
    },
    {
        "question": " 2975万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.473415011486072
    },
    {
        "question": " 411万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.614151653878896
    },
    {
        "question": " 4066京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.1103081661333953
    },
    {
        "question": " 19.6京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.3561198825256566
    },
    {
        "question": " 32.4垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.95396295594982
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.03京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.233083690497919
    },
    {
        "question": " 782兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.893196841052804
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.07兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.0301203622831725
    },
    {
        "question": " 609万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 3.7844792407969208
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.35年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.532986188293491
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.65万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.160366661330906
    },
    {
        "question": " 77.1年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.385899082385427
    },
    {
        "question": " 2632万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.857902848354621
    },
    {
        "question": " 406日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.989032772577814
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.92日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.6242065709321136
    },
    {
        "question": " 74日は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.805675983024061
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.32万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8582587212968018
    },
    {
        "question": " 26.7万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.046012249663722
    },
    {
        "question": " 113時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.833070470017365
    },
    {
        "question": " 1212時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.639899602799192
    },
    {
        "question": " 140兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.42663140302114
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.66兆分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.5098189052685
    },
    {
        "question": " 1012億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.227171275273703
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.91分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.549862949385715
    },
    {
        "question": " 16分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.981514366989429
    },
    {
        "question": " 63.3兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.302260115211228
    },
    {
        "question": " 640兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.869423592778627
    },
    {
        "question": " 33.8兆秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.972783115621368
    },
    {
        "question": " 183億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.484963693981582
    },
    {
        "question": " 449秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.652011903260368
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.01垓msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.80492078297648
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.32京msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.428294908299044
    },
    {
        "question": " 5754万msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2036670690264062
    },
    {
        "question": " 22.4万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5716478842172013
    },
    {
        "question": " 884万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.9462473162245946
    },
    {
        "question": " 56.7万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.753654225186718
    },
    {
        "question": " 835msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 8.921756423817808
    },
    {
        "question": " 290兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9635269480458286
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.2兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2722211185397425
    },
    {
        "question": " 254京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.848154266970894
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.3兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.407018874502086
    },
    {
        "question": " 131万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.1161430104884631
    },
    {
        "question": " 27.9万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 2.4459827260868225
    },
    {
        "question": " 63.1usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 4.79973407927825
    },
    {
        "question": " 8828京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.4470323097921884
    },
    {
        "question": " 6318兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.864055818513387
    },
    {
        "question": " 51.3兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1538458199102497
    },
    {
        "question": " 909兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.180465166873669
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.31京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.363979587073684
    },
    {
        "question": " 29.3兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.46652576193053
    },
    {
        "question": " 3917万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.5929379748908055
    },
    {
        "question": " 822万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.477244136868002
    },
    {
        "question": " 59.1年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.49248608448165
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.42万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5913648553703719
    },
    {
        "question": " 199日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.6792666264765286
    },
    {
        "question": " 539日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.890190987204409
    },
    {
        "question": " 385万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6425238146621344
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.7万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.842458157317944
    },
    {
        "question": " 61.5時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.56721703885107
    },
    {
        "question": " 714億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.132857494455713
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.15万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1734403351581357
    },
    {
        "question": " 1092分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2601676627256375
    },
    {
        "question": " 36.4万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.339466001095617
    },
    {
        "question": " 39.2億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.0947523508742885
    },
    {
        "question": " 499億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.761579600748411
    },
    {
        "question": " 31.5億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.9421511671496745
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.81億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.904386575763097
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.1万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.206996294807947
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.46秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.165059621393517
    },
    {
        "question": " 4564京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.160538914514799
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.83兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.326610545245906
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.44兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.602421594058269
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.08万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.07215313652180977
    },
    {
        "question": " 940万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.972969799895858
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.89msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 3.689079557264081
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.3京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.712572560373718
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.15垓usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.12602283124513
    },
    {
        "question": " 30.7京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.931330671959115
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.7億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6530201960987003
    },
    {
        "question": " 5375億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.730341837816421
    },
    {
        "question": " 270億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.430578723616809
    },
    {
        "question": " 5515usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.741570773943316
    },
    {
        "question": " 25.2京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9017676246448814
    },
    {
        "question": " 1047垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.08350719730077
    },
    {
        "question": " 337垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.971640099358249
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.6兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4411078739789174
    },
    {
        "question": " 626億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.796404425512781
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.17億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 2.620185746413326
    },
    {
        "question": " 558万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 3.746261775895021
    },
    {
        "question": " 2590万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.975635740563002
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.46万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.105898097472512
    },
    {
        "question": " 2295日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7984691275913758
    },
    {
        "question": " 19.3万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.44399573927516
    },
    {
        "question": " 18.1万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3154068270158992
    },
    {
        "question": " 157億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.814346095097461
    },
    {
        "question": " 19.5時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.845714524776451
    },
    {
        "question": " 3782万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8570105695090544
    },
    {
        "question": " 2021万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.147257366395557
    },
    {
        "question": " 109分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.2596243835125478
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.28億分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.886154304582229
    },
    {
        "question": " 7431万秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.37226715144132116
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.48億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.2339146941006702
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.41兆秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.976227804328895
    },
    {
        "question": " 221秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5653813012433595
    },
    {
        "question": " 32.4万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.510019156391794
    },
    {
        "question": " 36秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.5567284984725935
    },
    {
        "question": " 60.1兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.2798959395853746
    },
    {
        "question": " 2136億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.3930443757133255
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.95兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.395439775918874
    },
    {
        "question": " 37.3万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7938518540913186
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.27万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.355687513172511
    },
    {
        "question": " 476万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.677334532612202
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.63msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.211022944806564
    },
    {
        "question": " 26.2京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.9202588169723187
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.2兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.272807738155892
    },
    {
        "question": " 72.5京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.304138411710536
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.15兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.5544596499920695
    },
    {
        "question": " 550万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7407007261807985
    },
    {
        "question": " 676億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.829978767883352
    },
    {
        "question": " 139垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.6443187261617
    },
    {
        "question": " 3285兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5799823571088623
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.62垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.862746477883336
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.59京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.423303284289006
    },
    {
        "question": " 823兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.9153895853879055
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.55億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 2.5504696977954455
    },
    {
        "question": " 2988nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 0.4753807856792891
    },
    {
        "question": " 5309年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.287287956933386
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.91年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.406166595197513
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.72年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.661029862104009
    },
    {
        "question": " 6854億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.273647925526415
    },
    {
        "question": " 38.8万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.968741154177378
    },
    {
        "question": " 112日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.206348436271502
    },
    {
        "question": " 766億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.941709249271756
    },
    {
        "question": " 29.8万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.094201269595703
    },
    {
        "question": " 7144時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.63206957902223
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.47時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.949671218670214
    },
    {
        "question": " 1236万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3713871216264983
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.8兆分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.875731402730242
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.4万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.463440802584339
    },
    {
        "question": " 412万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.39340530651937
    },
    {
        "question": " 965分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.762863476309981
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.27分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.575202177354836
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.33兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.302876626578855
    },
    {
        "question": " 102万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0739727865381887
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.64兆秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.380036307030954
    },
    {
        "question": " 26万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.636893542126909
    },
    {
        "question": " 4833秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.6841817896923015
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.98京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.403378355940928
    },
    {
        "question": " 238億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.440900909613577
    },
    {
        "question": " 25.8兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.855530111977646
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.99億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.919605162044678
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.68億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.88528459085234
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.27msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.861245620219093
    },
    {
        "question": " 247垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.89377205050565
    },
    {
        "question": " 25.6京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.472350466179221
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.25京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.409801357689554
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.78兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.983742680659057
    },
    {
        "question": " 190億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.278514744765286
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.53万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.8147589210043014
    },
    {
        "question": " 2208usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.343961876218733
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.916e+05垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.399695286673648
    },
    {
        "question": " 323京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.572948145098211
    },
    {
        "question": " 184垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.708439051617576
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.2兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.079106951459827
    },
    {
        "question": " 1157億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.0632631099029175
    },
    {
        "question": " 4110兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.613793085581758
    },
    {
        "question": " 1134nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 0.05462982037920061
    },
    {
        "question": " 394年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.15743203355068
    },
    {
        "question": " 1700年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.173019321958351
    },
    {
        "question": " 49.3年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.191885778728372
    },
    {
        "question": " 1764億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.684277081087933
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.41万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.30483295878722
    },
    {
        "question": " 112日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.206935390617387
    },
    {
        "question": " 42.2日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.561439987551037
    },
    {
        "question": " 75.3日は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.8132289868031
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.29億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.418129630942806
    },
    {
        "question": " 471億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.292473786588896
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.8万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.813094525115055
    },
    {
        "question": " 154時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.743365866740714
    },
    {
        "question": " 253億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.682471404710645
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.61兆分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.776719621149676
    },
    {
        "question": " 477分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8999227788153152
    },
    {
        "question": " 265万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.2014392446091
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.24兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.595114964804379
    },
    {
        "question": " 2872億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.52170995764158
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.17万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7803697374266572
    },
    {
        "question": " 3447万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.759285205795871
    },
    {
        "question": " 3416秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.533554943027456
    },
    {
        "question": " 242秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.384032263360627
    },
    {
        "question": " 308兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.9892672228493495
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.3京msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.117713676012897
    },
    {
        "question": " 3618兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.002118121329165
    },
    {
        "question": " 3062億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.707799881069281
    },
    {
        "question": " 194億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.287357788118042
    },
    {
        "question": " 3427msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.534971963226858
    },
    {
        "question": " 170垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.731135839779453
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.16京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.12874381466529
    },
    {
        "question": " 26.1兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.8608541198574198
    },
    {
        "question": " 9077兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.17981320281983
    },
    {
        "question": " 3628億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.5596560527277505
    },
    {
        "question": " 155億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.190464598604406
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.084e+04垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.536269643736655
    },
    {
        "question": " 16.9垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.291321024196614
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.4兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6835969640067718
    },
    {
        "question": " 1220兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.308168138301443
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.72兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.235302931582619
    },
    {
        "question": " 223万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 0.34842779359605225
    },
    {
        "question": " 70.6万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 2.848884531528303
    },
    {
        "question": " 79.3年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.461316293455953
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.68年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.3707933984600045
    },
    {
        "question": " 925億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.403981690225361
    },
    {
        "question": " 33.2万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.90081893710148
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.9日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.046772925002805
    },
    {
        "question": " 9298時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.02586021906148206
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.11億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.528985251320161
    },
    {
        "question": " 609万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.562795867587903
    },
    {
        "question": " 22.4時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.905684458930837
    },
    {
        "question": " 2261兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.633582348808297
    },
    {
        "question": " 342万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.375790171533252
    },
    {
        "question": " 140分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.36691772490837105
    },
    {
        "question": " 2240分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.128405045072906
    },
    {
        "question": " 4651分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.445660570834201
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.5兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.691808614740431
    },
    {
        "question": " 35.7億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.616100359924121
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.31万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0786174397998949
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.38億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.193979019744475
    },
    {
        "question": " 6秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.777984790290597
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.01兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5070692011107245
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.11兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.849456312883068
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.71億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.0125570346353774
    },
    {
        "question": " 8097億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.130148772038919
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.07万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0284408985277882
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.51msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.179944417323108
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.88京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7756024454949824
    },
    {
        "question": " 39.6兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6610324836966894
    },
    {
        "question": " 35.1兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.9895726999117076
    },
    {
        "question": " 46.7兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.890952471930398
    },
    {
        "question": " 65.1兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.813788517254218
    },
    {
        "question": " 45.7億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.659457761102471
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.74万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 7.57251661052187
    },
    {
        "question": " 18.5垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.767284351115104
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.18垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.135713328962963
    },
    {
        "question": " 5147兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.1552189088438185
    },
    {
        "question": " 946億nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.19772626391234116
    },
    {
        "question": " 47.9兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.680058554655937
    },
    {
        "question": " 23.4億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.3698405539959797
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.26億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 5.966428284664924
    },
    {
        "question": " 247年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.954171174261224
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.29年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.05237359911692
    },
    {
        "question": " 3342年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.244717785354865
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.69億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.666505822567257
    },
    {
        "question": " 1079万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.413317265866192
    },
    {
        "question": " 13日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.272568785005747
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.51日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.750227140470393
    },
    {
        "question": " 1279万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.1643941463539926
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.86万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.0768791368810753
    },
    {
        "question": " 188万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.052062208563292
    },
    {
        "question": " 152時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.737074081829726
    },
    {
        "question": " 1023万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2890342360010743
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.32億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.963574371943519
    },
    {
        "question": " 1163分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2874572209896207
    },
    {
        "question": " 37.8分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.355773692908064
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.11億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9940391379894575
    },
    {
        "question": " 18.6兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.333700937971635
    },
    {
        "question": " 2669万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.870069032192931
    },
    {
        "question": " 265億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.645212345515477
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.01万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.779205210043402
    },
    {
        "question": " 54.1兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.234783377402218
    },
    {
        "question": " 8973億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.016414669977485
    },
    {
        "question": " 3920万msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0369463291814496
    },
    {
        "question": " 1982万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.518869477829173
    },
    {
        "question": " 78万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8923010605137387
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.44msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 3.871645970448201
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.47msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.738291040507498
    },
    {
        "question": " 71.1兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.35331236400421684
    },
    {
        "question": " 19京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.342644286681844
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.32兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.964391447473819
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.49京usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.393656223330197
    },
    {
        "question": " 23.6億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.3733576269916163
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.9億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.279326323238074
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.03万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 7.013382846103193
    },
    {
        "question": " 24.2垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.885603006953303
    },
    {
        "question": " 17垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.293322435140636
    },
    {
        "question": " 9634兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.4275271303745605
    },
    {
        "question": " 4648兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.889072188541173
    },
    {
        "question": " 265億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4235245047082068
    },
    {
        "question": " 2822万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.4505025513693348
    },
    {
        "question": " 32.9億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.516930788184601
    },
    {
        "question": " 376年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.137654054130004
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.47年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.260741466989661
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.08億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.755357449954861
    },
    {
        "question": " 338日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.9087806431487113
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.1日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.200582962535712
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.16万日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.898454440656174
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.05日は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.956845883173259
    },
    {
        "question": " 3229万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.566578888904308
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.68万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.5051402211896656
    },
    {
        "question": " 308時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.266108685995914
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.6万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.112154260512916
    },
    {
        "question": " 18.7時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.827768523781459
    },
    {
        "question": " 5053億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.982887132138459
    },
    {
        "question": " 24万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.221352728063769
    },
    {
        "question": " 600億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.99982697916271
    },
    {
        "question": " 90.4分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.73450729873852
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.58兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.1616308000865025
    },
    {
        "question": " 1890万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3400178634605884
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.54億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.849299453650805
    },
    {
        "question": " 2354億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.59360289350123
    },
    {
        "question": " 72.3万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.858942124409735
    },
    {
        "question": " 254秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.405327916803309
    },
    {
        "question": " 778兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.391899182555045
    },
    {
        "question": " 269億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4927801479853717
    },
    {
        "question": " 8565兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.376409638810898
    },
    {
        "question": " 7225億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.080667352252784
    },
    {
        "question": " 501億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.700262399108122
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.24万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.350540291569596
    },
    {
        "question": " 8310兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.420817947764723
    },
    {
        "question": " 3865兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.650679349490241
    },
    {
        "question": " 57.6兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.204418011426333
    },
    {
        "question": " 9199万usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.18559513644134218
    },
    {
        "question": " 6681万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8248686411264592
    },
    {
        "question": " 225万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.351354063757994
    },
    {
        "question": " 549usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 5.739593234075276
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.548e+04垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.690899573533548
    },
    {
        "question": " 1462垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.228457666717643
    },
    {
        "question": " 91.7京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.40628586758449
    },
    {
        "question": " 802億nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.12614556305572955
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.41京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.733523617265367
    },
    {
        "question": " 35.2兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.546753881023951
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.82万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 1.4498146242237409
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.65万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.49924452235933
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.76年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.1874659198148025
    },
    {
        "question": " 1656年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.939604158298971
    },
    {
        "question": " 19.3万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7222710000248274
    },
    {
        "question": " 3148万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.878174006277941
    },
    {
        "question": " 347万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.699200255275855
    },
    {
        "question": " 18兆時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.312375416867093
    },
    {
        "question": " 1190時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6953911922595832
    },
    {
        "question": " 8660万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.715661284308029
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.49兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.676287225949307
    },
    {
        "question": " 74.6億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.714248914448056
    },
    {
        "question": " 5292分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9454621887484302
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.6分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.193464200443639
    },
    {
        "question": " 7305分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.641745582411023
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.08兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.1114959920016485
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.57兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.616250921708792
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.83兆秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.70575968218491
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.9億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.25850880867147
    },
    {
        "question": " 1421秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.152563634179032
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.54兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.31650304304953
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.4京msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.443205467189035
    },
    {
        "question": " 339兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.974486384440922
    },
    {
        "question": " 763億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.104580435139042
    },
    {
        "question": " 152万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.180488536996876
    },
    {
        "question": " 2946msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.469260615811187
    },
    {
        "question": " 2896垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.962982324544718
    },
    {
        "question": " 52.5京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.783752345384528
    },
    {
        "question": " 5715兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.200744108339843
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.22兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.729808003855544
    },
    {
        "question": " 635兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.80307673582015
    },
    {
        "question": " 5297万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.724023985975533
    },
    {
        "question": " 168万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.226444967914144
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.575e+04垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.43442303101501
    },
    {
        "question": " 983兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0560070481040462
    },
    {
        "question": " 18.6兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7135004756966523
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.9京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.500225749577728
    },
    {
        "question": " 60億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.778456535280051
    },
    {
        "question": " 3262兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.513516470956013
    },
    {
        "question": " 429億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.632888664224189
    },
    {
        "question": " 237年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.936635551398496
    },
    {
        "question": " 8993年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.896408148973685
    },
    {
        "question": " 24.2年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.882258129192847
    },
    {
        "question": " 7512億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.313422933120124
    },
    {
        "question": " 625日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.175970920103621
    },
    {
        "question": " 76.5万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.04197640751456
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.98億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.353505297784347
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.86億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.306818946039671
    },
    {
        "question": " 4015万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.38185398040504
    },
    {
        "question": " 2851時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.011328383176569
    },
    {
        "question": " 92.8億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.246967441798621
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.5億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.0188535716579175
    },
    {
        "question": " 60.1分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.00084751919150583
    },
    {
        "question": " 2万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.078804193449752
    },
    {
        "question": " 4098万秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.11371618724879018
    },
    {
        "question": " 298兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.537307615356351
    },
    {
        "question": " 158万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6437105739559463
    },
    {
        "question": " 1110億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.267139324545603
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.57秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.1953343422888123
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.63兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2514891889264224
    },
    {
        "question": " 2447兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.452083734346528
    },
    {
        "question": " 200億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.7437220934462747
    },
    {
        "question": " 20.2兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.526910263407693
    },
    {
        "question": " 158万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.199678672022438
    },
    {
        "question": " 1152兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.562791010490805
    },
    {
        "question": " 6637兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.885487109729693
    },
    {
        "question": " 253京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.846142498696233
    },
    {
        "question": " 6597億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.041178850657413
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.01億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6998904574670854
    },
    {
        "question": " 9016万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.955024940808553
    },
    {
        "question": " 32.6usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 4.513099222814905
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.33垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.137494135068733
    },
    {
        "question": " 945京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.038965377618384
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.19京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.300302970388088
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.11京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.181336122303774
    },
    {
        "question": " 404京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.606646377780798
    },
    {
        "question": " 3764万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.575696560766261
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.15億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 5.7888285160247035
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.18万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.065239878396855
    },
    {
        "question": " 412億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.052954786662909
    },
    {
        "question": " 294日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.8492528604434373
    },
    {
        "question": " 495日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.852721897140967
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.5兆時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.23454193133847
    },
    {
        "question": " 35.2億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.165768992733343
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.78万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.45738634378578
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.2万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.27264304609613
    },
    {
        "question": " 1613万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4868924469193623
    },
    {
        "question": " 20.1万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1441193385013433
    },
    {
        "question": " 67.9分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.0536602950931353
    },
    {
        "question": " 2993分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.254325341098799
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.86京秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.396677598271706
    },
    {
        "question": " 48.5億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.749469482924274
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.85兆秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.029168428246845
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.05万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5333840276053
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.84秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.4536949031517103
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.15秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.498073298904022
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.47兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8937557845049657
    },
    {
        "question": " 1805億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.3200815672396256
    },
    {
        "question": " 45.3億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.099643480170007
    },
    {
        "question": " 198万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5177695793449542
    },
    {
        "question": " 4961億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.695543527547079
    },
    {
        "question": " 19.6京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.793256938146503
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.9京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.206771574089625
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.5京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.604799419416239
    },
    {
        "question": " 1098億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.2624691171606814
    },
    {
        "question": " 638億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.804504816625049
    },
    {
        "question": " 299万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.476031058019954
    },
    {
        "question": " 1730垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.739226580094191
    },
    {
        "question": " 1320兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1841337682989672
    },
    {
        "question": " 618京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.23478859660073
    },
    {
        "question": " 36.4兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.783301956536147
    },
    {
        "question": " 2035兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.308618041055924
    },
    {
        "question": " 165億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.21723040047868
    },
    {
        "question": " 178億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.250822431632709
    },
    {
        "question": " 113万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.61518456461814
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.09万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.554500401014092
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.3万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9557085196895552
    },
    {
        "question": " 965万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.364543093771722
    },
    {
        "question": " 4043日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.765073654428208
    },
    {
        "question": " 551日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.677360354157084
    },
    {
        "question": " 28億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.505347064753564
    },
    {
        "question": " 52.5万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.339654095616926
    },
    {
        "question": " 3843時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.36283872549259
    },
    {
        "question": " 6549億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.0955390838653205
    },
    {
        "question": " 5800万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.605099713933826
    },
    {
        "question": " 1308億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.338568238737496
    },
    {
        "question": " 58.3分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.5437491166357873
    },
    {
        "question": " 71.6億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3561449088554043
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.04億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.5467671997586514
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.61兆秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.192488603288142
    },
    {
        "question": " 494秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9154939339008106
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.33万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.5225275929023265
    },
    {
        "question": " 2165京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.836588016865681
    },
    {
        "question": " 341億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5961490665227127
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.89億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7194479725998835
    },
    {
        "question": " 119兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.296180975537416
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.23兆msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.509139203344876
    },
    {
        "question": " 3912msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.592385299333871
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.6msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.556242950103267
    },
    {
        "question": " 77.7垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.391610241168062
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.4京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.118958929150939
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.71京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.876472356270355
    },
    {
        "question": " 45兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.87469938995123
    },
    {
        "question": " 8354兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.92191599570945
    },
    {
        "question": " 1894万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.277339664961778
    },
    {
        "question": " 401京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1047333215945727
    },
    {
        "question": " 61.5垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.852635808757274
    },
    {
        "question": " 4025京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.048514697782535
    },
    {
        "question": " 35.3兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.770114378714974
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.23兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.626050561869505
    },
    {
        "question": " 166万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 0.22028966143622708
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.31万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 1.3628026112714908
    },
    {
        "question": " 12万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.640111557311769
    },
    {
        "question": " 36.6年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.505585624102876
    },
    {
        "question": " 108億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.470966091473087
    },
    {
        "question": " 286万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.836516892513842
    },
    {
        "question": " 450日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.811395538298832
    },
    {
        "question": " 122日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.021779836914562
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.51日は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.116720410618667
    },
    {
        "question": " 50.9億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.763837682987351
    },
    {
        "question": " 36.9万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.186336810490175
    },
    {
        "question": " 87.6万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.720726568831772
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.63万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.378048052460493
    },
    {
        "question": " 574万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0384875732177423
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.5万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.031673870479663
    },
    {
        "question": " 49.4万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.9156431046339293
    },
    {
        "question": " 105万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.7978297909901055
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.11分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.101467636972387
    },
    {
        "question": " 446億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.1508397402912323
    },
    {
        "question": " 52.8兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.786196846643586
    },
    {
        "question": " 712万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.296373161129779
    },
    {
        "question": " 547万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.959974317099569
    },
    {
        "question": " 264秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.422194163549843
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.42兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.308710980031429
    },
    {
        "question": " 3053億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.5482115794812485
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.34兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.309373399202073
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.25兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.319102558591943
    },
    {
        "question": " 114万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.0587161137445964
    },
    {
        "question": " 239京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.8788908663016075
    },
    {
        "question": " 634京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.865803750778263
    },
    {
        "question": " 399京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.044532054583653
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.82億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.115104907475185
    },
    {
        "question": " 999万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9997245528507093
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.82兆usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.449778153086422
    },
    {
        "question": " 326万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.513205601324286
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.62垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.436539118800466
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.7京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.094185695703695
    },
    {
        "question": " 6970兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.286958243089596
    },
    {
        "question": " 2091兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.542206568646542
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.26京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.513136525307358
    },
    {
        "question": " 886万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 0.9476302143660609
    },
    {
        "question": " 9890nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 0.9951846107538431
    },
    {
        "question": " 82.5年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.478921924051083
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.3年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.461404941838287
    },
    {
        "question": " 1989万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.736262669656565
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.9万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.552891852188348
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.43万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.543566898794922
    },
    {
        "question": " 1673日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.15995636785513
    },
    {
        "question": " 40.7日は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.54572911205795
    },
    {
        "question": " 357万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.610086634976705
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.6億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.683040088609041
    },
    {
        "question": " 161時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.9851808734530634
    },
    {
        "question": " 28.3時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.008560712202847
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.59時間は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.758729086614249
    },
    {
        "question": " 1848億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.54600041868654
    },
    {
        "question": " 6532分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6566787356086778
    },
    {
        "question": " 110分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.2621904650458795
    },
    {
        "question": " 3422万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.312476349439478
    },
    {
        "question": " 42.4分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.405299449565515
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.45億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6625223558022153
    },
    {
        "question": " 1047万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.0834589379814195
    },
    {
        "question": " 42.6万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.073281274554227
    },
    {
        "question": " 101億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.225914051579188
    },
    {
        "question": " 90.4万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.956172997839833
    },
    {
        "question": " 185秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.266778015883466
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.11兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.460497579115728
    },
    {
        "question": " 77.7億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9540533518946845
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.81兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.701861435510387
    },
    {
        "question": " 71.9兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.078785568644477
    },
    {
        "question": " 31.9万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.503365347509565
    },
    {
        "question": " 544万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.735650074679821
    },
    {
        "question": " 70兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.3462600421161266
    },
    {
        "question": " 1890京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.340029090355213
    },
    {
        "question": " 345億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9816541617586405
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.66京usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.44255838577896
    },
    {
        "question": " 880兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.944376565439233
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.1億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.083455899678189
    },
    {
        "question": " 26.6垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.926221214065424
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.64京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.946717910317016
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.09兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.055813300481942774
    },
    {
        "question": " 354京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.770886938598478
    },
    {
        "question": " 376京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.574641313976619
    },
    {
        "question": " 4778万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.6792018923683616
    },
    {
        "question": " 2822億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.450522436362423
    },
    {
        "question": " 163万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.774487484555229
    },
    {
        "question": " 3470億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.9780320849081
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.1万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.20359988238052
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.14万日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.790186752449614
    },
    {
        "question": " 27.5日は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.37628647050786
    },
    {
        "question": " 534万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7852796647161604
    },
    {
        "question": " 59時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.3905022636825528
    },
    {
        "question": " 384万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.362625802553769
    },
    {
        "question": " 59時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.326995586984281
    },
    {
        "question": " 466万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9481882853922108
    },
    {
        "question": " 60.5億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.6232140536634425
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.64万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9729773807896596
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.17分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4919871282740127
    },
    {
        "question": " 163兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.712687902951586
    },
    {
        "question": " 1472万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.231361108199935
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.46万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9831165630256078
    },
    {
        "question": " 1038億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.23817900905522
    },
    {
        "question": " 5225秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.7181065910237105
    },
    {
        "question": " 198兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.7985790247995412
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.48兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.234883410624105
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.28億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.075211629745409
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.9兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.422610870585881
    },
    {
        "question": " 50.5億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.703111962636612
    },
    {
        "question": " 418msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 5.621635755760702
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.02msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.700841780909098
    },
    {
        "question": " 5210兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.218008202460214
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.04垓usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.082046605419677
    },
    {
        "question": " 9604兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.426135751121668
    },
    {
        "question": " 576億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9823337837279364
    },
    {
        "question": " 508万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7060911851094975
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.28兆usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.358633378141302
    },
    {
        "question": " 718万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.855917157295702
    },
    {
        "question": " 4648京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.1684927458586944
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.01垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.76333631920423
    },
    {
        "question": " 72.7兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3053002791305623
    },
    {
        "question": " 904兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.177826719109126
    },
    {
        "question": " 86.7億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.938015789308182
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.28兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.108711847197451
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.4億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 5.146058380554547
    },
    {
        "question": " 276年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.003700594857468
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.6年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.10588375275394
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.5年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.689885568039216
    },
    {
        "question": " 24.7万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.829735492972337
    },
    {
        "question": " 21.3日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.486012501953212
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.17万日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.272103589711598
    },
    {
        "question": " 12兆時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.138447552955252
    },
    {
        "question": " 2017万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.924417654090329
    },
    {
        "question": " 53.1万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.503547011442161
    },
    {
        "question": " 962時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.539544575407504
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.21億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3632360473675105
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.25兆分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.469834179581827
    },
    {
        "question": " 292億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.687416684168955
    },
    {
        "question": " 692億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.341304252668731
    },
    {
        "question": " 20.1万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.36614568608002607
    },
    {
        "question": " 5955秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.2185810957789025
    },
    {
        "question": " 28.6億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.677861250536916
    },
    {
        "question": " 9040秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.956148987189036
    },
    {
        "question": " 829兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.419619979486172
    },
    {
        "question": " 309億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.553201521632469
    },
    {
        "question": " 332億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.964702567510585
    },
    {
        "question": " 5468万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9596715891657945
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.15万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0594284156553269
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.99msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 3.7771471486680355
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.58msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.817909095729834
    },
    {
        "question": " 77.3京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.38948745908321
    },
    {
        "question": " 487兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.751223519524588
    },
    {
        "question": " 808兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.351090879101706
    },
    {
        "question": " 41.1億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8351717471188178
    },
    {
        "question": " 5455万usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7367727569114555
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.5億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.061986824416872
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.128e+04垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.116893228420052
    },
    {
        "question": " 120兆nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.14347557469674754
    },
    {
        "question": " 122垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.531294468482525
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.34兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.192200680723413
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.2兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.007810905625692
    },
    {
        "question": " 837兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.922940211449612
    },
    {
        "question": " 314億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.496653104071326
    },
    {
        "question": " 4742年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.238241632905335
    },
    {
        "question": " 201年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.245592134504781
    },
    {
        "question": " 215億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.7696339974164585
    },
    {
        "question": " 19日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.659196037288086
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.31万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.5222403523079295
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.9万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3112317821865838
    },
    {
        "question": " 2528万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.022547804709752
    },
    {
        "question": " 152時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.960021019696013
    },
    {
        "question": " 403時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.161799603739318
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.15億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.340332902802109
    },
    {
        "question": " 22.7万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1972418810884897
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.72億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.109302725130815
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.3万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.902611926285786
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.16兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.567167086917927
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.83兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.515384311615797
    },
    {
        "question": " 296億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.915457795372814
    },
    {
        "question": " 35.2億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.768945574985004
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.02垓msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.511494723947534
    },
    {
        "question": " 1265億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.1655816295940955
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.84億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4368937739293948
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.12億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.2694290999628306
    },
    {
        "question": " 1640億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.214900345384175
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.71万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.673467426061374
    },
    {
        "question": " 98msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 7.9913055321626825
    },
    {
        "question": " 27.9垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.947289405655315
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.85垓usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.32996012381482
    },
    {
        "question": " 7174億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.299485958052181
    },
    {
        "question": " 25.3兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.625294520929877
    },
    {
        "question": " 1015億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.006353034019643
    },
    {
        "question": " 2982億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.474549358250785
    },
    {
        "question": " 133垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.6249153463561115
    },
    {
        "question": " 1428垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.21830902730925
    },
    {
        "question": " 473兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.118652825250974
    },
    {
        "question": " 606億nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.004637278973798065
    },
    {
        "question": " 3126億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4950167831831127
    },
    {
        "question": " 55.3兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.742701442343995
    },
    {
        "question": " 98.7億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.994437130212999
    },
    {
        "question": " 297年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.034887372190918
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.25年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.349060902461746
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.76兆日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.878717071684736
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.12億日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.995038908425196
    },
    {
        "question": " 21.5日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.49178413283093
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.76億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.88775147060738
    },
    {
        "question": " 161億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.827504669666375
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.64億時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.991878286752343
    },
    {
        "question": " 206万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.869864558772443
    },
    {
        "question": " 677時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.38709380161678
    },
    {
        "question": " 1873万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.55195195660762
    },
    {
        "question": " 4291万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.474182852612426
    },
    {
        "question": " 1382分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3623934258758963
    },
    {
        "question": " 37.4分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.3513882067478953
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.55分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.65581754639811
    },
    {
        "question": " 42.6分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.407335532877145
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.47億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3747481510769588
    },
    {
        "question": " 507万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.768099374626182
    },
    {
        "question": " 5766秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.20456754678026878
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.83万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8052470653796635
    },
    {
        "question": " 364秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.560525832367015
    },
    {
        "question": " 883億msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.44715492449287964
    },
    {
        "question": " 46.1億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.726791976562294
    },
    {
        "question": " 396万msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.04134223763827993
    },
    {
        "question": " 77億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.108593556593685
    },
    {
        "question": " 22.5億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.352971255835547
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.63万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.419166831313074
    },
    {
        "question": " 32.7msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 7.513897610025728
    },
    {
        "question": " 57.7兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.26227038474076037
    },
    {
        "question": " 2237兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.413109058480585
    },
    {
        "question": " 783億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3377181978777686
    },
    {
        "question": " 71.9兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.0786387188433055
    },
    {
        "question": " 1342億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.127678491067378
    },
    {
        "question": " 3944万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 4.595985888151477
    },
    {
        "question": " 914京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.461955931963402
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.23京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5725393732432176
    },
    {
        "question": " 182垓nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.702583680548654
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.52京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.200484979727952
    },
    {
        "question": " 38.3億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.583374858310084
    },
    {
        "question": " 6321万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.8007552495458334
    },
    {
        "question": " 47.3万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 2.674912732016165
    },
    {
        "question": " 465年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.229958237292106
    },
    {
        "question": " 202年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.026350509793115
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.78億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.328600515525914
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.06日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1629187631957647
    },
    {
        "question": " 814万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9678871710621824
    },
    {
        "question": " 1376億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.758332375736588
    },
    {
        "question": " 31.5万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.2767687896014195
    },
    {
        "question": " 6243万分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.0747443654002073
    },
    {
        "question": " 1734億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.080769948049445
    },
    {
        "question": " 62.6万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.0181861772291105
    },
    {
        "question": " 2822万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.228668649818264
    },
    {
        "question": " 200兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.802449993500256
    },
    {
        "question": " 135兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.195088184979783
    },
    {
        "question": " 424万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.0712713848210447
    },
    {
        "question": " 1925億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.506311725890958
    },
    {
        "question": " 149秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.174568004244887
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.39兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6443547109341494
    },
    {
        "question": " 50.8兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.769444843451563
    },
    {
        "question": " 5926万msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2164436743485385
    },
    {
        "question": " 62.2兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.015541527491685
    },
    {
        "question": " 175億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.244223702330546
    },
    {
        "question": " 3205msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.505769143381638
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.5msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.9293849661571025
    },
    {
        "question": " 223兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8488981179593025
    },
    {
        "question": " 210京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.386322862992124
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.1京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.560495135495046
    },
    {
        "question": " 725兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.081936789832431
    },
    {
        "question": " 887兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.947993634787268
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.04億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.847302223442789
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.15usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 3.61797397023098
    },
    {
        "question": " 26.9垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.930867066909867
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.92垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.6571991402735655
    },
    {
        "question": " 329兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9604192309795154
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.46京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.612586716854775
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.37京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.922702216563531
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.3兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.011813431244207
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.3万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 1.9686787179888654
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.28年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.458776294310121
    },
    {
        "question": " 86.7億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.375663715415945
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.42万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.250533409778102
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.44日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.5453486788841007
    },
    {
        "question": " 4259日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.5657890483195
    },
    {
        "question": " 2197万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.399290279640933
    },
    {
        "question": " 97.3万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.607741015816584
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.49万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.4305322061068235
    },
    {
        "question": " 60.7万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.339138428700618
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.47兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.447096750842168
    },
    {
        "question": " 789万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.7386154132323246
    },
    {
        "question": " 12.6万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.323210896158326
    },
    {
        "question": " 609万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.562718724423025
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.63万分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.991012308101048
    },
    {
        "question": " 212兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.828382466420216
    },
    {
        "question": " 78兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.955444510817838
    },
    {
        "question": " 151億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.621590624773833
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.82万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4822754795444366
    },
    {
        "question": " 858秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.933468705008471
    },
    {
        "question": " 109京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.537146145762362
    },
    {
        "question": " 32.8京msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.57915661475948
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.14兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.773820364645182
    },
    {
        "question": " 728万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.083801074018752
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.58兆msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.55339277855168
    },
    {
        "question": " 161垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.707728078163505
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.65京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.7306817286206515
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.2兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.491872849410526
    },
    {
        "question": " 67.4兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.050681522243392
    },
    {
        "question": " 3339兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.523583877525502
    },
    {
        "question": " 542万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.734234235672033
    },
    {
        "question": " 44usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 4.643185960114193
    },
    {
        "question": " 773垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.389189603804156
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.07垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.378957413621967
    },
    {
        "question": " 33.1京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.963864649863257
    },
    {
        "question": " 8527兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.15262790997017
    },
    {
        "question": " 5717億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7571756024826843
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.21兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.506398987418702
    },
    {
        "question": " 2734nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 0.4367468928712015
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.5年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.753009574666233
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.61万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.877684809586082
    },
    {
        "question": " 5年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.419663073222922
    },
    {
        "question": " 221億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.781703477846799
    },
    {
        "question": " 1356万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.512448487413948
    },
    {
        "question": " 1382日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.07708207291933
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.7億時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.223367475356496
    },
    {
        "question": " 132億時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.740317729587604
    },
    {
        "question": " 64.2万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.364073437129477
    },
    {
        "question": " 36.7億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.8438278589767827
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.48万分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.580524300697207
    },
    {
        "question": " 328億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.738204490731603
    },
    {
        "question": " 58.1分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.5424824177366157
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.1京秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.505221015200663
    },
    {
        "question": " 87.4兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.004879120032616
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.55万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6352439224635731
    },
    {
        "question": " 25.8億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.63417458392605
    },
    {
        "question": " 84.3万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.925877576417701
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.8秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.16909086295108
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.17秒は何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.620385997994145
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.56兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.0530072608991445
    },
    {
        "question": " 677億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8943776060218918
    },
    {
        "question": " 482億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.126920764620695
    },
    {
        "question": " 57.8万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.98410859535356
    },
    {
        "question": " 17.2万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2360694674836745
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.68msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 3.2252145742024094
    },
    {
        "question": " 4189msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.622073985904668
    },
    {
        "question": " 1418垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.652958099366383
    },
    {
        "question": " 1047億usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.08332323006219555
    },
    {
        "question": " 209兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.763573822428704
    },
    {
        "question": " 5143兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.933067907551243
    },
    {
        "question": " 433兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.63679382518191
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.48万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.3946977171540986
    },
    {
        "question": " 47.9usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 4.680401666985727
    },
    {
        "question": " 350垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.045282881522221
    },
    {
        "question": " 2216垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.409084713399139
    },
    {
        "question": " 241京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.8263390565597994
    },
    {
        "question": " 9495京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.199362652791185
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.3億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.051213404613947855
    },
    {
        "question": " 192兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.282807839300926
    },
    {
        "question": " 3876億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.588371675350446
    },
    {
        "question": " 37.2年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.513119247305081
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.27年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.8553971433100225
    },
    {
        "question": " 30.5億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.9215177462315625
    },
    {
        "question": " 1756日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.624618078591699
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.74万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6302973818969493
    },
    {
        "question": " 37.6時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.19441586515770992
    },
    {
        "question": " 2181時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.116885705393413
    },
    {
        "question": " 1787億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.531451324010602
    },
    {
        "question": " 832億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.761690015031807
    },
    {
        "question": " 993億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.218820771282344
    },
    {
        "question": " 350分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.322547399681826
    },
    {
        "question": " 537分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.508413729377079
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.8分は何usですか？",
        "answer": 8.541537488514354
    },
    {
        "question": " 48.6兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.188041398793961
    },
    {
        "question": " 798億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.9657319589407685
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.79兆秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.889446074163258
    },
    {
        "question": " 1539億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.408957798927306
    },
    {
        "question": " 717兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.356784732740147
    },
    {
        "question": " 90.7兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.020998116345937
    },
    {
        "question": " 716万msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.2986409356123809
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.8兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.668365947223955
    },
    {
        "question": " 8629万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.935982429013299
    },
    {
        "question": " 3920msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.593310932919891
    },
    {
        "question": " 278兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9447879127319325
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.44垓usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.451732292810874
    },
    {
        "question": " 8051億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3495495218346396
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.67億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7865732228246058
    },
    {
        "question": " 6億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7778307509151667
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.03万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.8471000922048142
    },
    {
        "question": " 374万usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 9.573374158107988
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.309e+04垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.22618157098654
    },
    {
        "question": " 19.3京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.349935504939956
    },
    {
        "question": " 302兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9241711486398616
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.61垓nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.427402079153005
    },
    {
        "question": " 3515億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 2.545896633760653
    },
    {
        "question": " 508兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.706090283056072
    },
    {
        "question": " 1234万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 4.091182187521838
    },
    {
        "question": " 173年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.799785902706479
    },
    {
        "question": " 26.1年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.358966036020318
    },
    {
        "question": " 9935年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.717823184133824
    },
    {
        "question": " 394万日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.033319424122225
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.63日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.0461922657370266
    },
    {
        "question": " 2288日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.29597689907578
    },
    {
        "question": " 5198万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.7733460056384827
    },
    {
        "question": " 810時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 1.52842193416308
    },
    {
        "question": " 1197時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.8564006221824885
    },
    {
        "question": " 163億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 4.492412790095152
    },
    {
        "question": " 22.9億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.201573877639959
    },
    {
        "question": " 3219億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.729560582055202
    },
    {
        "question": " 1252万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.875873617521442
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.2分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.121132979907458
    },
    {
        "question": " 7173万秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.35688488000725105
    },
    {
        "question": " 90.9億秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.022287721886607
    },
    {
        "question": " 26.7兆秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.869488055136275
    },
    {
        "question": " 44.1万秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.866340027030909
    },
    {
        "question": " 27.7秒は何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.441894612804944
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.98垓msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.79881839807369
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.43兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.448423279826987
    },
    {
        "question": " 729兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.306158319991743
    },
    {
        "question": " 34.8万msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7631816899168686
    },
    {
        "question": " 2706万msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 4.43228162377344
    },
    {
        "question": " 140垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.648753569847639
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.6京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.195633514675229
    },
    {
        "question": " 4266億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 2.073689973959082
    },
    {
        "question": " 93.3億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.191748095342337
    },
    {
        "question": " 521兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.716586595848376
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.05億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.483902513043572
    },
    {
        "question": " 8480usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.928414059905946
    },
    {
        "question": " 1516垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.681918816368732
    },
    {
        "question": " 110垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.106027183773195
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.26兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.07285068852751819
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.4兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8650729966273305
    },
    {
        "question": " 65.4京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.815810133090228
    },
    {
        "question": " 1922兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.283722934449317
    },
    {
        "question": " 23.5億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.370642167750782
    },
    {
        "question": " 45万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.215447721120926
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.56年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.1352457766639095
    },
    {
        "question": " 153年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.906511617044466
    },
    {
        "question": " 42.4億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.065428412838688
    },
    {
        "question": " 920万日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.343869061640211
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.9万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.300455649376845
    },
    {
        "question": " 189日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.212361070359209
    },
    {
        "question": " 44.1万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.70216662409574
    },
    {
        "question": " 1934万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.906345092020015
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.03時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7890830371621935
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.2万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.634965390193193
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.67億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5012959387012526
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.18兆分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.914263216840578
    },
    {
        "question": " 4819万分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.904772008252776
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.12分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 5.4871781413858685
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.64京秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.922276086210438
    },
    {
        "question": " 2096万秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3849687643038306
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.01億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.4465298193933585
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.08億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.832471465038875
    },
    {
        "question": " 404万秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 9.60598019040599
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.49京msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.67448660535346
    },
    {
        "question": " 688兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.900835504599955
    },
    {
        "question": " 326億msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.9569764640389495
    },
    {
        "question": " 10.9億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.260664169971729
    },
    {
        "question": " 2359msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.3726477465873679
    },
    {
        "question": " 554万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.743128615034873
    },
    {
        "question": " 38.7垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 8.088580250904979
    },
    {
        "question": " 471京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.7362057169295095
    },
    {
        "question": " 1361億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5777004678540985
    },
    {
        "question": " 454億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8790380766837433
    },
    {
        "question": " 851兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.92970894130213
    },
    {
        "question": " 5019usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 0.7006038109996338
    },
    {
        "question": " 107垓nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.532581120178474
    },
    {
        "question": " 1743垓nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.304864217140352
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.43京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 4.178167240874414
    },
    {
        "question": " 593京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.994736698831738
    },
    {
        "question": " 21.5億nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 0.3316005128772792
    },
    {
        "question": " 5538万nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 1.743377603978531
    },
    {
        "question": " 650万nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 3.8128422186628965
    },
    {
        "question": " 37.4万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.135378463258782
    },
    {
        "question": " 812年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.851818026282533
    },
    {
        "question": " 108年は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.532305468853961
    },
    {
        "question": " 28.8億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.896657358966141
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.67万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.4837700994694272
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.66万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8407931839729472
    },
    {
        "question": " 5085時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 5.4844335215586355
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.28時間は何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.914716801424914
    },
    {
        "question": " 35.9億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.834493309785665
    },
    {
        "question": " 218億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.180797260779123
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.24億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 6.313725570272392
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.04万分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.088161592945792
    },
    {
        "question": " 2333兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.869045179604405
    },
    {
        "question": " 21.8兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.402369867694286
    },
    {
        "question": " 543億秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.178789386528067
    },
    {
        "question": " 170秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 0.45262951645008265
    },
    {
        "question": " 9114秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.959697948567948
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.47兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.0419287627162728
    },
    {
        "question": " 178兆msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 6.3129506919091325
    },
    {
        "question": " 3205兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.949463272689467
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.22億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.015389453422726
    },
    {
        "question": " 177億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.24712074106735
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.8万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 7.446645315141293
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.25msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 6.097425178901896
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.2垓usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.578779205774337
    },
    {
        "question": " 166兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.2830896973587054
    },
    {
        "question": " 659兆usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.262536367107594
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.19兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.725719315457083
    },
    {
        "question": " 21.2億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.326721956621992
    },
    {
        "question": " 113億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.053616025830144
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.94京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.27479396420863167
    },
    {
        "question": " 723京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.922731405518536
    },
    {
        "question": " 322兆nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9520552731196128
    },
    {
        "question": " 510兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.92955774954728
    },
    {
        "question": " 14.8京nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 8.169001035843754
    },
    {
        "question": " 9.02兆nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.955310286107751
    },
    {
        "question": " 46.7億nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 6.669185523773608
    },
    {
        "question": " 15.3万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.748010364846449
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.09万年は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 8.432972973521718
    },
    {
        "question": " 126年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 7.821728686308603
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.77兆日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.685749802445748
    },
    {
        "question": " 374日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.952859831537112
    },
    {
        "question": " 45.5日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.816504538688365
    },
    {
        "question": " 78.1日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.8293191915014155
    },
    {
        "question": " 63.3兆時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 9.858830246258545
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.95万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.3940130647063316
    },
    {
        "question": " 1438万時間は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.935990245083069
    },
    {
        "question": " 11.1兆分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.324983819157113
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.41億分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 5.4857096051616505
    },
    {
        "question": " 244分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6101222197518819
    },
    {
        "question": " 3279分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.293893777365703
    },
    {
        "question": " 13.3億秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6261031458125186
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.77兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.312119574930086
    },
    {
        "question": " 418万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.0647256795878084
    },
    {
        "question": " 861秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 1.156853852139167
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.87秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 3.2724337646953283
    },
    {
        "question": " 3256億msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0139028502012903
    },
    {
        "question": " 24.4京msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 9.45107654199011
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.15兆msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.776299049975268
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.12兆msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.131622967827255
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.55億msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.190676361681881
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.05msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 3.9060220172138527
    },
    {
        "question": " 112msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 8.049739390700791
    },
    {
        "question": " 20.3京usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 3.807674547314357
    },
    {
        "question": " 1109京usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.10837032028905
    },
    {
        "question": " 961億usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4266119306244385
    },
    {
        "question": " 4814億usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 3.904349556416735
    },
    {
        "question": " 7851億usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.894910264239974
    },
    {
        "question": " 154億usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.187246771313217
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.85usは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 3.7674053183943235
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.61京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.058845008763031004
    },
    {
        "question": " 40.4京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.6697644662615048
    },
    {
        "question": " 95.5京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 5.423892012309133
    },
    {
        "question": " 3360兆nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.748187354212173
    },
    {
        "question": " 5.64兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.750989907315324
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.87億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 2.272115616119703
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.22兆nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.085582679496321
    },
    {
        "question": " 105万年は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 8.582029680783927
    },
    {
        "question": " 339年は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 8.250556977560334
    },
    {
        "question": " 215億日は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 7.7700164844966135
    },
    {
        "question": " 101日は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.3830972863016164
    },
    {
        "question": " 159万日は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.36095913143861
    },
    {
        "question": " 915日は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 7.898124779635218
    },
    {
        "question": " 795万時間は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9577146569151824
    },
    {
        "question": " 36.2万時間は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 4.178012917531138
    },
    {
        "question": " 77.4万時間は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.444885643958683
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.05時間は何msですか？",
        "answer": 7.040903481112134
    },
    {
        "question": " 2895億分は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 5.740925121811116
    },
    {
        "question": " 5825分は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6069519773260945
    },
    {
        "question": " 1214億分は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.305958851898543
    },
    {
        "question": " 140分は何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 3.925613425989031
    },
    {
        "question": " 4229分は何msですか？",
        "answer": 8.40437237537145
    },
    {
        "question": " 71.2兆秒は何年ですか？",
        "answer": 6.353591131585584
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.31兆秒は何日ですか？",
        "answer": 7.180352095405994
    },
    {
        "question": " 1645万秒は何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 3.6598227735720434
    },
    {
        "question": " 712億秒は何分ですか？",
        "answer": 9.074074398318775
    },
    {
        "question": " 5203秒は何msですか？",
        "answer": 6.716278204393358
    },
    {
        "question": " 3.27兆msは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 2.0161941824604868
    },
    {
        "question": " 1761億msは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.309360562744833
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.39京msは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 9.58658726281267
    },
    {
        "question": " 6.42億msは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 4.029132681050519
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.35兆msは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 9.638663803211179
    },
    {
        "question": " 242万msは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.384691510362806
    },
    {
        "question": " 115msは何nsですか？",
        "answer": 8.059199286546377
    },
    {
        "question": " 91.4兆usは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 0.46221773141634115
    },
    {
        "question": " 393兆usは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 3.658275261193482
    },
    {
        "question": " 8.77京usは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.386549943690995
    },
    {
        "question": " 87.3兆usは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.162886858917033
    },
    {
        "question": " 4.57兆usは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 6.659644266077921
    },
    {
        "question": " 35.8万usは何msですか？",
        "answer": 2.5543734297566925
    },
    {
        "question": " 62.3京nsは何年ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2953332679056417
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.98京nsは何日ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3609009863178954
    },
    {
        "question": " 4471京nsは何時間ですか？",
        "answer": 7.0941010635495445
    },
    {
        "question": " 7.95京nsは何分ですか？",
        "answer": 6.1221659271772
    },
    {
        "question": " 443兆nsは何秒ですか？",
        "answer": 5.6464283834888445
    },
    {
        "question": " 2.74億nsは何msですか？",
        "answer": 2.4384491529906773
    },
    {
        "question": " 1.68兆nsは何usですか？",
        "answer": 9.224694790815064
    }
]